<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="WAREHOUSE_DISTRICT_DOMINION_EXPRESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[style.boldBrown(Dominion Express)]<br/>
		#IF(pc.isQuestFailed(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA))
			 As Natalya had you thrown out and banned from ever returning to Dominion Express, there's nothing for you to do there...
		#ELSE
			Looking at the business card given to you by Natalya, you see that the delivery company which employs her as a 'Stable Mistress' is very near to where you're currently standing, and is open to visiting members of the public between the hours of
			#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
				#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA))
					 [style.colourMinorGood([unit.time(6)]-[unit.time(22)])]. As you're a qualified filly, you're free to come and go at any time of the day, and you wonder whether you should head inside and service some of the centaur slaves...
				#ELSE
					 [style.colourMinorGood([unit.time(6)]-[unit.time(22)])]. As the warehouse out of which Dominion Express operates is currently [style.colourGood(open)], you could head inside and see if you could arrange to meet the [natalya.race] again...
				#ENDIF
			#ELSEIF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA))
				 [style.colourMinorBad([unit.time(6)]-[unit.time(22)])]. As you're a qualified filly, the opening times don't apply to you, and even though Natalya won't be present at this hour, you could still head inside and service some of the centaur slaves...
			#ELSE
				 [style.colourMinorBad([unit.time(6)]-[unit.time(22)])]. As the warehouse out of which Dominion Express operates is currently [style.colourBad(closed)], you'll have to come back during opening hours if you wanted to meet the [natalya.race] again...
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INITIAL_ENTRANCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INITIAL_ENTRANCE"><![CDATA[
	#VAR
		var collar = pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_NECK);
	#ENDVAR
	
	<p>
		[pc.Walking] up to the huge warehouse from which Dominion Express operates, you push open the front door and [pc.step] into the entrance hall. Partitioned from the main floor of the warehouse by an internal wall, this area is furnished to act as both a reception and waiting room. Several sofas and chairs are arrayed in rows on one side of this large room
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			, and sitting upon them are a couple of businessmen waiting to meet with the company's representatives.
		#ELSE
			, but due to the fact that the warehouse is currently closed to members of the public, they're completely deserted.
		#ENDIF
		 Over on the opposite side of the room, there's a very long counter running parallel to the wall, which acts as the first port of call for anyone visiting Dominion Express.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			Despite its size, however, this counter only has three employees sitting behind it, all of whom are smartly-dressed horse-girls. Noticing your entry, the nearest one breaks off from gossiping with her colleagues and turns to face you.
		#ELSE
			Due to the fact that the warehouse is closed to the public at this hour, there's only a single smartly-dressed horse-girl sitting behind the counter. Noticing your entry, she stifles a yawn and turns to face you.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA) && collar!=null && collar.getClothingType().getId().equals("innoxia_neck_filly_choker"))
			 Noticing the fact that you're wearing a filly choker, she waves you through and says, [style.speechFeminine(Go on through, filly. I'm sure there are plenty of slaves waiting for you in the stables...)]
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasQuest(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA))
			 Not wanting to be delayed, you've already got your stamped business card out, and as you show it to the receptionist, she waves you past and says,
			#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
				 [style.speechFeminine(Go on through. I'm sure Natalya is waiting to see you...)]
			#ELSE
				 [style.speechFeminine(Natalya's gone home for the day, but you can still go on through if you want...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 Beckoning you forwards, she asks in a very bored voice, [style.speechFeminine(Good [style.afternoon], [pc.sir]. How can I help you?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INITIAL_ENTRANCE_CARD_SHOWN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INITIAL_ENTRANCE_CARD_SHOWN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You [pc.walk] over to the receptionist and show her Natalya's business card, before saying that the [natalya.race] has asked for you to pay her a visit. Raising her eyebrows in surprise, the receptionist points over to the double doors which lead into the main warehouse, saying, [style.speechFeminine(You shouldn't keep Mistress Natalya waiting; go right on through.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Putting the business card away, you [pc.step] away from the counter and prepare to do as the horse-girl says...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ENTRANCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Partitioned from the main floor of the warehouse by an internal wall, this entrance hall is furnished to act as both a reception and waiting room. Several sofas and chairs are arrayed in rows on one side of this large room
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			, and sitting upon them are a couple of businessmen waiting to meet with the company's representatives.
		#ELSE
			, but due to the fact that the warehouse is currently closed to members of the public, they're completely deserted.
		#ENDIF
		 Over on the opposite side of the room, there's a very long counter running parallel to the wall, which acts as the first port of call for anyone visiting Dominion Express.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			Despite its size, however, this counter only has three employees sitting behind it, all of whom are smartly-dressed horse-girls. Having already granted you access to the main warehouse, these receptionists don't pay you any attention, and simply continue to gossip amongst themselves.
		#ELSE
			Due to the fact that the warehouse is closed to the public at this hour, there's only a single smartly-dressed horse-girl sitting behind the counter. Having already granted you access to the main warehouse, she doesn't pay you any attention, and instead continues to file her nails and stifle the occasional yawn.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CORRIDOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	#VAR
		var collar = pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_NECK);
	#ENDVAR
	
	<p>
		This wide, wooden-floored corridor cuts a direct path from one end of the warehouse to the other. While one side of this corridor is flanked by a solid wall, the other opens out onto a vast storage area, which is filled with stacks of crates, piles of furniture, and shelves stacked full of books.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			As you [pc.walk] down the corridor, you find yourself passing several centaur or centauress slaves, each of whom appears to be either delivering or picking up cargo. While most of them are carrying the goods on their backs, there's the occasional one or two whose cargo is so heavy or bulky that they're having to use a cart to pull it along.
		#ELSE
			Despite the hour of day, you find yourself passing the occasional centaur or centauress slave on your way down the corridor. Unlike in daylight hours, however, these slaves don't seem to be picking up or dropping off cargo, and instead appear to be tasked with reorganising the goods already stored here.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA) && collar!=null && collar.getClothingType().getId().equals("innoxia_neck_filly_choker"))
			 Catching sight of your filly choker, these centaurs hungrily stare at you as you pass,
			#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
				 and you realise that [style.colourPink(it's only a matter of time before one of them tries to make you service them)].
			#ELSE
				 but [style.colourBad(as you can't access your mouth, none of them will try to make you service them)].
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 Not having any business with you, these centaurs pay you no attention as you pass, allowing you to continue on your way through the warehouse without delay.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		In addition to these manual labourers, you rarely catch sight of much smaller centauresses happily trotting to and from the stables at the end of the corridor, each one wearing a choker displaying the word 'filly' in bronze or, far less commonly, silver letters. These small, busty fillies pay you absolutely no attention as they pass, as they only seem interested in the nearby slaves.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- STORAGE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STORAGE"><![CDATA[
	#VAR
		var collar = pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_NECK);
	#ENDVAR
	
	<p>
		Dominion Express is not only in the business of cargo haulage, but also operates a highly-successful storage service. The vast majority of their warehouse's floor area is set aside for this purpose, and is home to countless crates, pieces of furniture, and book-shelves.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			As you [pc.walk] through the labyrinth-like aisles formed by these stacks of stored goods, you find yourself passing the occasional centaur or centauress slave.
		#ELSE
			It's through the labyrinth-like aisles formed by these stacks of stored goods which you're currently [pc.walking], and despite the hour of day, you find yourself passing the occasional centaur or centauress slave. 
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA) && collar!=null && collar.getClothingType().getId().equals("innoxia_neck_filly_choker"))
			 Noticing the filly choker around your neck, these centaurs make lewd comments as you pass,
			#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
				 and you realise that [style.colourPink(it's only a matter of time before one of them tries to make you service them)].
			#ELSE
				 but [style.colourBad(as you can't access your mouth, none of them will try to make you service them)].
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 Not having any business with you, these centaurs pay you no attention as you pass, allowing you to continue on your way through the storage area uninterrupted.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		In addition to these manual labourers, you rarely catch sight of much smaller centauresses happily trotting around, each one wearing a choker displaying the word 'filly' in bronze or, far less commonly, silver letters. These small, busty fillies pay you absolutely no attention as they pass, as they only seem interested in the nearby slaves.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A business the size of Dominion Express inevitably generates a huge amount of paperwork, and it's in the office before you that all that tedious bureaucratic work is handled. Although the 'Administrative Staff Only' sign on the door makes it clear that you're not allowed inside, you can still take a look through the large glass windows to see a dozen or so workers filling out forms or planning deliveries.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're not permitted to enter this office, there's little for you to do except turn around and head back into the warehouse...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- FILLY_STATION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		On one side of the long corridor which runs through the warehouse, there's a small alcove, which is just about large enough to comfortably accommodate a single centaur. Stepping into this recess, you find yourself coming face-to-face with what looks to be some kind of vending machine, which is proudly displaying the words 'Filly Rewards Station'. Looking through its clear glass frontage, you see that there are a large selection of transformative potions on offer, but instead of their prices being displayed in flames, they're each marked as costing a certain number of 'filly points'.
	</p>
	<p>
		Beside this curious vending machine, you see that there's an informative poster titled 'Filly Rewards Scheme'. If you wanted to, you could spend a moment reading over the information displayed on this poster, or perhaps instead you could try interacting with the filly rewards station...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- FILLY_STATION_POSTER -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_POSTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turning your attention towards the flashy informative poster, you read:
	</p>
	<div class='container-full-width' style='text-align:center; width:75%; margin:8px 12.5%;'>
		<p>
			[style.boldPinkLight(Filly Rewards Scheme)]
			</br>
			</br>
			Welcome to the Filly Rewards Station, filly! In case you've forgotten how things work, here's a quick recap for you:
			<br/>
			- Centaur slaves earn [style.colourPinkLight(filly points)] by working hard!
			<br/>
			- They can give you these [style.colourPinkLight(filly points)] in exchange for your sexual services!
			<br/>
			- You can spend your [style.colourPinkLight(filly points)] here on all sorts of yummy transformative potions!
			<br/>
			- Simply press your filly choker up against the arcane scanner to begin!
			<br/>
			- Remember, [style.colourPinkLight(filly points)] [style.colourCrimson(are reset to zero at the start of every month)], and you [style.colourBad(lose two)] [style.colourPinkLight(filly points)] at every stroke of midnight, so make sure to service lots of centaur slaves to keep your points up!
			<br/>
			<br/>
			<i><span style='font-size:0.75em'>By signing your filly contract, you have agreed that Dominion Express cannot be held liable for any adverse effects experienced by consuming transformation potions. This points-based reward system can not be legally recognised as setting a precedent of paying fillies a salary. Dominion Express cannot be held liable for any complications arising from the use of this machine. If you would like to register a complaint, please see Mistress Natalya.</span></i>
		</p>
	</div>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA))
			Having officially qualified as one of Dominion Express's fillies, you wonder whether you should make use of this rewards station now, or perhaps you should go and earn some more filly points first...
		#ELSE
			As you're not one of Dominion Express's fillies, you doubt that you'll be able to make use of this rewards station...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- FILLY_STATION_MACHINE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_MACHINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking a closer look at the 'filly rewards station', you see that there's a small keypad which can be used to enter your selection, and above that, there's a glowing pink slit which reminds you of the light given off from a barcode scanner. Turning your attention towards the items on offer behind the machine's glass window, you notice that there's only one of each type of transformative potion on display, and unlike a vending machine, there doesn't seem to be any mechanism via which these bottles can be dispensed.
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly housing some kind of arcane instrument that's automatically detected your presence, the machine suddenly lets out a high-pitched beep, before projecting a series of coloured words into the air:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_MACHINE_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<b>[style.italicsCrimson(No filly choker detected!)]</b>
		<br/>
		[style.italicsCrimson(Please step back and make room for a qualified filly to make use of this machine!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to trigger any kind of alarm system, you step back from the machine, and as you do so, the projected arcane words thankfully disappear.
		#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA))
			 It doesn't look like you're going to be able to make use of this 'filly rewards station' without first equipping your filly choker...
		#ELSE
			 It doesn't look like you're going to be able to make use of this 'filly rewards station' without being a 'filly' yourself...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_MACHINE_ACCEPTED"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<b>[style.italicsPink(Filly detected!)]</b>
		<br/>
		[style.italicsPinkLight(Filly points:)] [style.boldPink([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0])]
		<br/>
		[style.italicsPink(Current rank:)] <i>[#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]</i>
		<br/>
		[style.italicsGood(Please present filly choker to the scanning device to begin!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Obediently doing as the machine tells you, you lean forwards and press your filly choker against the glowing pink slit. Immediately, another high-pitched beep rings out from somewhere within the device, before a scrolling menu flashes up into the air in front of your face. Looking over this menu, you see that there are several things which you can spend your filly points on:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_GENERIC_END"><![CDATA[
		 The moment that you finish entering the button combination on the mechanical keypad, a bright pink flash is emitted from out of the scanner, and right before your eyes, [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] of your filly points are drawn out of your choker and absorbed into the machine. Immediately after this, a high-pitched beep is emitted, before a previously-flat panel on the front of the machine slides aside to let a huge, silicone horse-dildo flop free.
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising what's expected of you, you lean forwards and take the dildo into your mouth, and as you start to lewdly suck on it, a hot stream of salty, cum-flavoured fluid gushes out directly down your throat. After quickly depositing all of its familiar-tasting load into your stomach, the silicone dildo retracts back into its compartment, leaving you to let out a desperate whine as you feel your body starting to transform...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_GENERIC_MENTAL_END"><![CDATA[
		 The moment that you finish entering the button combination on the mechanical keypad, a bright pink flash is emitted from out of the scanner, and right before your eyes, [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] of your filly points are drawn out of your choker and absorbed into the machine. Immediately after this, a high-pitched beep is emitted, before a previously-flat panel on the front of the machine slides aside to let a huge, silicone horse-dildo flop free.
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising what's expected of you, you lean forwards and take the dildo into your mouth, and as you start to lewdly suck on it, a hot stream of salty, cum-flavoured fluid gushes out directly down your throat. After quickly depositing all of its familiar-tasting load into your stomach, the silicone dildo retracts back into its compartment, leaving you to let out a desperate whine as you start to feel light-headed...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_BASIC_FILLY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to make sure that you've got the right sort of body, you select the option titled '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]'.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_TAUR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be hot to get mounted and rutted by the centaur slaves while having a feral horse's body, you select the option titled '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]'.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_ASS_PUSSY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have the most desirable ass out of all of Dominion Express's fillies, you select the option titled '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]'.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_THROAT_PUSSY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to be the best filly at sucking horse-cock, you select the option titled '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]'.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_ASS_LICKER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Loving the idea of being specially-transformed in order to give the best rimjobs possible, you select the option titled '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]'.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_HUNG"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have a huge cock swinging down between your legs, you select the option titled '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]'.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_SISSY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting everyone to see what a pathetic little sissy filly you are, you select the option titled '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]'.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_TOP_HEAVY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to be able to put on a show for the centaur slaves, you select the option titled '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]'.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_SUBBY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling yourself that you need to start acting more like a submissive filly slut, you select the option titled '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]'. The moment that you finish entering the button combination on the mechanical keypad, a bright pink flash is emitted from out of the scanner, and right before your eyes, [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] of your filly points are drawn out of your choker and absorbed into the machine. Immediately after this, a high-pitched beep is emitted, before a previously-flat panel at the very bottom of the machine slides aside to push a dog-bowl filled with thick, white liquid towards your feet.
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising what's expected of you, you drop down onto the floor, before leaning down to start submissively licking up the salty, cum-flavoured fluid. After quickly swallowing down the entirety of this familiar-tasting meal, the dog-bowl retracts back into its compartment, leaving you to let out a desperate whine as you start to feel light-headed...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_BIMBO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to be a ditzy bimbo who only thinks of submissively servicing horse-cock and horse-ass, you select the option titled '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]'.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_TRANSFORMATION_BIMBO_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finally, another flat panel on the front of the machine slides aside, allowing a mechanical arm to extend a bright pink lollipop towards your face. Letting out a ditzy giggle, you lean forwards and wrap your [pc.lips+] around the tasty treat, before starting to absent-mindedly suck on it.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_SILVER_COLLAR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having saved up enough points to permanently upgrade your choker, you select the 'silver choker' upgrade option. The moment that you finish entering the button combination on the mechanical keypad, a bright pink flash is emitted from out of the scanner, and right before your eyes, [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] of your filly points are drawn out of your choker and absorbed into the machine. Immediately after this, a short, high-pitched fanfare is emitted from an internal speaker, before a previously-flat panel on the front of the machine slides aside to fire a burst of silver-coloured confetti all over you.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you start brushing the glittery mess off of your body, a small mirror pokes out of the still-open panel, and you look into it to see that your filly choker has somehow been dyed silver! Smiling happily to yourself, you watch as the mirror retracts back into its compartment, before a series of arcane words are once gain projected into the air in front of your face:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<b>[style.italicsPink(Congratulations filly!)]</b>
		<br/>
		[style.italicsSilver(You are the seventh filly to receive the silver choker upgrade!)]
		<br/>
		[style.italicsGood(You may now request to sexually service Mistress Natalya once per day!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			As this text quickly fades away, you're left wondering whether you should pay your Mistress a visit straight away...
		#ELSE
			As this text quickly fades away, you're left wondering whether you should pay your Mistress a visit as soon as she arrives for work in the morning...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FILLY_STATION_REWARD_GOLD_COLLAR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having saved up enough points to permanently upgrade your choker once again, you select the 'gold choker' upgrade option. The moment that you finish entering the button combination on the mechanical keypad, a bright pink flash is emitted from out of the scanner, and right before your eyes, [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] of your filly points are drawn out of your choker and absorbed into the machine. Immediately after this, an elaborate, high-pitched fanfare is emitted from an internal speaker, before a previously-flat panel on the front of the machine slides aside to fire a burst of gold-coloured confetti all over you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like when you received your silver collar upgrade, a small mirror pokes out of the still-open panel, and you look into it to see that your filly choker has somehow been dyed gold! Smiling happily to yourself, you watch as the mirror retracts back into its compartment, before a series of arcane words are once gain projected into the air in front of your face:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<b>[style.italicsPink(Congratulations filly!)]</b>
		<br/>
		[style.italicsGold(You are the first filly to receive the gold choker upgrade!)]
		<br/>
		[style.italicsExcellent(You may now order Mistress Natalya to sexually service you once per day!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			As this text quickly fades away, you're left wondering whether you should pay your Mistress a visit and take advantage of this new perk straight away...
		#ELSE
			As this text quickly fades away, you're left wondering whether you should pay your Mistress a visit and take advantage of this new perk as soon as she arrives for work in the morning...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- STABLES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLES"><![CDATA[
	#VAR
		var collar = pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_NECK);
	#ENDVAR
	
	<p>
		At the far end of the corridor, there's a large, open archway connecting the warehouse to a sizeable annex. Looking through the archway, it's clear to see that this extension to the main building is where all of Dominion Express's centaur slaves are housed, and comprises of several long corridors lined with individual stalls, much like those found in a regular stable.
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			 As it's currently regular working hours, the vast majority of the stalls are empty, as their regular occupants are out delivering cargo all across Dominion.
		#ELSE
			 As it's currently outside of regular working hours, most of the lights in the stables are turned off, and the sound of snoring centaurs can quite clearly be heard even while standing outside in the warehouse's main corridor.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			An extremely bored-looking horse-boy is sitting behind a desk to one side of the archway, and makes a note on the papers in front of him every time a centaur comes or goes.
		#ELSE
			An extremely bored-looking horse-boy is sitting behind a desk to one side of the archway, and while his duty is clearly to make a note of which slaves are currently in the stables, there's not much for him to do at this time.
		#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLES_NO_COLLAR"><![CDATA[
		#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA))
			 As he sees you approach, he stifles a yawn and says, [style.speechMasculine(Hey, you're a filly, aren't you? Sorry, but I can't let you into the stables if you're not wearing your choker...)]
		#ELSE
			 As he sees you approach, he stifles a yawn and says, [style.speechMasculine(Sorry, [pc.sir], but visitors aren't allowed into the stables...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're not allowed into the stables, there's little else for you to do except turn around and head back into the warehouse...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLES_WRONG_BODY"><![CDATA[
		 As he sees you approach, he stifles a yawn and says, [style.speechMasculine(Hey, you're a filly, aren't you? Sorry, but I can't let you into the stables unless you meet Mistress Natalya's body requirements. You need to be a big-tittied [style.shemale] to be allowed in...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're not allowed into the stables, there's little else for you to do except turn around and head back into the warehouse...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLES_ENTER"><![CDATA[
		 As he sees you approach and catches sight of the filly choker around you neck, he waves you through and yawns, [style.speechMasculine(Go on in, filly. I'm sure there's a slave or two who could use your services.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder if you should do as the horse-boy says and enter the stables, or instead turn around and head back into the warehouse...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- STABLES_ENTERED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLES_ENTERED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
				Doing as the horse-boy says, you start to move forwards, but before you're able to pass through the archway, he glances at your companion and flatly states, [style.speechMasculine(Sorry, filly, but your friend here isn't allowed inside.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Turning towards [com.name], you tell [com.herHim] to wait here for you to return, before [pc.walking] through the archway and entering the stables. Looking into the stalls as you [pc.walk] down the corridor, you wonder if you should enter one of the occupied ones and offer to service the centaur slave within...
		#ELSE
			Doing as the horse-boy says, you continue forwards through the archway and enter the stables. Looking into the stalls as you [pc.walk] down the corridor, you wonder if you should enter one of the occupied ones and offer to service the centaur slave within...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLES_EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it's time for you to leave, you head back to the archway through which you entered the stables, and after [pc.stepping] through it, you find yourself once again back out in the warehouse's main corridor...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLE_SEX_FIND_PARTNER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to sexually service a slave and earn some filly points, you start searching the stables for [npc.a_race] who's willing to spend some time with you. Thankfully, you only have to check a couple of stalls before you find one that's occupied by a particularly pent-up [npc.race], who's currently pacing back and forth while making frustrated huffing noises. Taking note of the fact that the name '[npc.name]' is clearly displayed on the stall's half-height door, you call out over to the [npc.race] and offer to help [npc.herHim] get some release.
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly more than happy to take you up on your offer, [npc.she] throws open the door and pulls you into [npc.her] stall. Breathing heavily as [npc.she] presses [npc.her] body up against yours, [npc.she] pants, [npc.speech(I'll give you [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] filly points if you help me to cum! I haven't been serviced for over a day! Fuck, I need to cum so badly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Excited at the prospect of finally having a filly to service [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] restlessly paws at the ground, before stepping back and prancing around to point [npc.her] rear-end at you. Flicking [npc.her] tail to one side, [npc.she] presents you with [npc.her] [npc.asshole+], before looking back over [npc.her] shoulder and impatiently demanding, [npc.speech(Come on, filly, you know the drill! Kiss my ass so we can get started!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that you need to show your submission before you can get started, you dutifully kneel down behind [npc.name] and plant a big, wet kiss on [npc.her] [npc.asshole+]. Letting out an excited [npc.moan], [npc.she] turns to one side to show off [npc.her] rapidly-hardening horse-cock, and with a wild gleam in [npc.her] eyes, [npc.she] exclaims, [npc.speech(So, what'll it be, filly?! You want to suck my cock or bury your face in my ass? Or maybe you want me to mount you and rut your asshole?!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLE_SEX_FIND_PARTNER_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to pay [npc.name] another visit and earn some more filly points from [npc.herHim], you head over to [npc.her] stall and are delighted to discover that [npc.sheIs] inside. Pacing back and forth while making frustrated huffing noises, [npc.sheIs] quite clearly worked up about something, and so you call out over the door and offer to help [npc.herHim] get some release.
	</p>
	<p>
		Extremely happy to see you again and to take you up on your offer, the [npc.race] throws open the door and pulls you into [npc.her] stall. Breathing heavily as [npc.she] presses [npc.her] body up against yours, [npc.she] pants, [npc.speech(I was just thinking about you, filly! I'll give you [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] filly points if you help me to cum again! Fuck, I need to cum so badly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Excited at the prospect of having you service [npc.herHim] again, [npc.name] restlessly paws at the ground, before stepping back and prancing around to point [npc.her] rear-end at you. Flicking [npc.her] tail to one side, [npc.she] presents you with [npc.her] [npc.asshole+], before looking back over [npc.her] shoulder and impatiently demanding, [npc.speech(Come on, filly, you know the drill! Kiss my ass so we can get started!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that you need to show your submission before you can get started, you dutifully kneel down behind [npc.name] and plant a big, wet kiss on [npc.her] [npc.asshole+]. Letting out an excited [npc.moan], [npc.name] turns to one side to show off [npc.her] rapidly-hardening horse-cock, and with a wild gleam in [npc.her] eyes, [npc.she] exclaims, [npc.speech(So, what'll it be, filly?! You want to suck my cock or bury your face in my ass? Or maybe you want me to mount you and rut your asshole?!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLE_SEX_FIND_PARTNER_SADIST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to pay [npc.name] another visit and earn some more filly points from [npc.herHim], you head over to [npc.her] stall and are delighted to discover that [npc.sheIs] inside. Pacing back and forth while making frustrated huffing noises, [npc.sheIs] quite clearly worked up about something, and so you call out over the door and offer to help [npc.herHim] get some release.
	</p>
	<p>
		Immediately recognising you as the filly which [npc.she] rutted in Mistress Natalya's office, the [npc.race] throws open the door and roughly pulls you into [npc.her] stall. Breathing heavily as [npc.she] presses [npc.her] body up against yours, [npc.she] grunts, [npc.speech(You want [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] filly points, you dirty little slut? Get me to cum and they're all yours!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can respond, [npc.name] forcefully pushes you down onto your knees, before quickly turning around and stepping back to forcefully shove [npc.her] rear-end into your face. Flicking [npc.her] tail to one side, [npc.she] presents you with [npc.her] [npc.asshole+], before looking back over [npc.her] shoulder and impatiently ordering, [npc.speech(Go on, filly, you know how this works! Give my ass a nice big kiss!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that you need to show your submission before you can get started, you dutifully lean forwards and plant a big, wet kiss on [npc.namePos] puffy, ebony horse-anus. Letting out an approving grunt, the [npc.race] quickly turns to one side to show off [npc.her] rapidly-hardening ebony horse-cock, and with a wild gleam in [npc.her] eyes, [npc.she] asks, [npc.speech(What are you waiting for, filly?! Are you going to put your mouth to work, or am I going to have to mount you and rut your slutty little asshole again?!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- STABLE_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLE_SEX_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you want to service [npc.name] with your mouth, you tell [npc.herHim] that you want to suck [npc.her] [npc.cockGirth] horse-cock. More than happy to let you do this, [npc.name] eagerly pushes you down onto the floor, before stepping over the top of you and pushing the wide, flared head of her animalistic cock up against your face. As you open your mouth and lick up the bead of salty pre-cum that's leaking out of [npc.her] urethra, [npc.she] [npc.moansVerb+] and calls out, [npc.speech(Come on! Don't tease me! Take my cock down your throat already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're asked, you open wide and take [npc.namePos] cock into your mouth, causing [npc.herHim] to let out a desperate [npc.moan]. With your partner continuing to make lewd noises, you get started on giving [npc.herHim] a blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLE_SEX_ANILINGUS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to really show [npc.name] how submissive you are, you tell [npc.herHim] that you want to make [npc.herHim] cum from giving [npc.herHim] a rimjob. Flashing you a cheeky grin as [npc.she] hears you say this, [npc.name] turns around to present [npc.her] [npc.asshole+] to you once again, before turning [npc.her] head back and teasing, [npc.speech(Natalya trained you well, filly! Come on then, show me that you're a dirty little slut for horse-ass!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eager to get started, you drop down behind [npc.name], before immediately leaning forwards and burying your face in [npc.her] ass. Determined to make the [npc.race] cum receiving a rimjob alone, you begin by planting a series of passionate, wet kisses on [npc.her] animalistic horse-anus, before lewdly grinding your [pc.lips+] against [npc.her] puffy doughnut and thrusting your [pc.tongue+] into [npc.her] ass. Letting out a series of [npc.moansVerb+], your partner desperately calls out, [npc.speech(~Ooh!~ That's it filly! ~Aah!~ Fuck, you're good at this!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Encouraged by [npc.namePos] praise, you continue enthusiastically making out with [npc.her] puffy rear-entrance, confident in your ability to make [npc.her] cum without even needing to touch [npc.her] cock...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLE_SEX_MOUNTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get a real feel of [npc.namePos] [npc.cockGirth] horse-cock, you present your ass to [npc.herHim] and say that you want [npc.herHim] to mount you and pound your [pc.asshole+]. More than happy to give you what you want, [npc.she] pushes you down onto all fours, before stepping over the top of you and immediately pushing the wide, flared head of her animalistic cock up against your exposed butt. Not giving you any time in which to potentially change your mind, [npc.name] thrusts forwards and rams the wide, flared head of [npc.her] feral horse-cock into your [pc.asshole+]. Letting out [npc.a_moan+], [npc.she] calls out, [npc.speech(~Ahh!~ Yes! That's it! ~Ooh!~ Take my cock, you dirty little filly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out [pc.a_moan+] of your own, you push your [pc.hips] back and help to sink [npc.namePos] [npc.cock+] deep into your ass. Delighted by your display of enthusiasm, the [npc.race] starts pulling back and thrusting forwards, rutting your ass while continuing to make lewd noises...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_STABLE_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out one final satisfied [npc.moan], [npc.name] steps back and sinks down onto the pile of straw which serves as [npc.her] bed. Rolling over onto one side, [npc.she] presents [npc.her] softening horse-cock to you and orders, [npc.speech(Come and clean me off if you still want those points, filly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you drop down beside [npc.name] and obediently lick [npc.her] [npc.cockGirth], hot cock clean. Satisfied by your performance, [npc.she] tosses [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] small arcane beads at you and sighs, [npc.speech(Here you go, filly. Good job...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can pick them up, the enchanted beads disintegrate into arcane energy, before swirling up and being absorbed into your filly choker.
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()<=4 || game.getHourOfDay()>=22)
			 Before you can start to get up and leave, [npc.name] shuffles up on [npc.her] straw bedding and offers, [npc.speech(I've got another couple of points I can give to you, but only if you stay the night with me...)]
		#ELSE
			 Before you can start to get up and leave, [npc.name] lets out a big yawn and says, [npc.speech(I'd love to spend some more time with you, filly, but I've got a delivery to make soon, so get out of here and service some other slave...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()<4 || game.getHourOfDay()>22)
			Declining [npc.namePos] offer of staying the night with [npc.herHim], you stand up and exit [npc.her] stall, before continuing out into the stables and wondering whether you should find another slave to service...
		#ELSE
			Doing as [npc.name] says, you stand up and exit [npc.her] stall, before continuing out into the stables and wondering whether you should find another slave to service...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FAVOURITE_SLAVE_ENDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[style.italicsMinorGood(Having enjoyed your time with [npc.name], you make a note to remember where [npc.her] stall is located, so that you can visit [npc.herHim] again later...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORGET_SLAVE_ENDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[style.italicsMinorBad(Not wanting to ever have to service [npc.name] again, you decide to forget where [npc.her] stall is located...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of earning an extra couple of filly points, you accept [npc.namePos] offer of spending the night with [npc.herHim], and after [npc.sheHas] shuffled up to make room, you lie down next to [npc.herHim] on [npc.her] straw bedding. Leaning in against [npc.her] feral horse body, you snuggle into [npc.herHim] and fall asleep smelling of sex...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_NO_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		...
	</p>
	<p>
		The next morning, you're woken by the movements of [npc.name] as [npc.she] stands up and stretches. After letting out a big yawn, [npc.she] tosses a couple more arcane beads your way, before flashing you a smile and saying, [npc.speech(Thanks for spending the night, filly. I've got to get on with work now, so I'll see you another time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like the others which were given to you, these enchanted beads quickly disintegrate into pure arcane energy, before swirling up and being absorbed into your filly choker. Standing up and stretching, you thank [npc.name] for the filly points, before preparing to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		You find yourself sitting in Lilaya's laboratory, listening to her lecturing you on how the arcane works. You're finding it impossible to concentrate, however, as for some reason you're having to sit on the floor, and [npc.a_race] keeps on pushing [npc.her] [npc.cockGirth], feral horse-cock into your face. Not wanting to get in trouble with your aunt, you open your mouth to tell this troublesome [npc.race] to stop, but as you do so, [npc.she] thrusts forwards and forces the flared head of [npc.her] animalistic cock into your mouth!
	</i></p>
	<p>
		At that moment, you suddenly wake up to discover that, just like in your dream, [npc.name] has stepped over the top of you and has forcefully thrust [npc.her] throbbing horse-cock into your mouth. Hearing you let out a muffled cry, the [npc.race] happily [npc.moansVerb] down to you, [npc.speech(That's a good filly! ~Mmm!~ Take my cock deep down your throat!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_ANILINGUS"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		Although you can't remember how you got here, you find yourself back at the Enforcer Headquarters, where Candi has just finished painting your [pc.lips+] in a garish shade of bright pink. Clapping her hands in glee, she calls over a nearby [npc.race] Enforcer, before declaring that you're all ready to serve as [npc.her] new chair. Before you know what's happening, you're being pushed to the ground by this vaguely-familiar [npc.race], and without being given any time in which to react, [npc.she] turns around and sits down on your face, smothering your mouth with [npc.her] [npc.asshole+]!
	</i></p>
	<p>
		At that moment, you suddenly wake up to discover that, just like in your dream, [npc.name] has just sat down and planted [npc.her] hot, musky horse-ass down onto your face. Hearing you let out a muffled cry, the [npc.race] happily [npc.moansVerb], [npc.speech(That's a good filly! ~Mmm!~ You're going to make me cum just by giving me a rimjob!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_MOUNTED"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		For some reason, you find yourself back in Scarlett's shop, and are bowing down to the sadistic harpy as she uses one of her bird-like talons to push your head down to the ground. Letting out a triumphant laugh, she orders her [npc.race] slave to step forwards and mount you. Although [npc.sheIs] out of your sight, you hear the clopping of this [npc.race]'s hooves drawing nearer, and then suddenly [npc.sheIs] stepping over the top of you, pushing the flared head of a [npc.cockSize], feral horse-cock against your raised ass. Given the command by Scarlett, the [npc.race] thrusts forwards, pushing [npc.her] [npc.cockGirth] cock into your asshole!
	</i></p>
	<p>
		At that moment, you suddenly wake up to discover that [npc.name] has stepped over the top of you and, just like in your dream, has thrust [npc.her] [npc.cock+] into your [pc.asshole+]. Hearing you let out a surprised cry, the [npc.race] happily [npc.moansVerb], [npc.speech(That's a good filly! ~Mmm!~ There's no better start to the day than rutting some slut's ass! ~Ooh!~ Take it deep, you dirty little filly!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Responses -->
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as [npc.name] says, you stand up and exit [npc.her] stall, before continuing out into the stables and wondering whether you should find another slave to service...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_START_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With little choice but to do as you're told, you obediently get to work on sucking [npc.namePos] cock, causing [npc.herHim] to let out a series of delighted [npc.moans]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_START_ANILINGUS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With little choice but to do as you're told, you obediently get to work on kissing and licking [npc.namePos] [npc.asshole+], causing [npc.herHim] to let out a series of delighted [npc.moans]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_START_MOUNTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With little choice but to do as you're told, you obediently push your [pc.hips] back and help to sink [npc.namePos] [npc.cock+] deep into your ass, which causes [npc.herHim] to let out a series of delighted [npc.moans]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_AFTER_WAKEUP_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_AFTER_WAKEUP_SEX_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had [npc.her] fun, [npc.name] steps back and withdraws [npc.her] [npc.cock+] from your throat, causing a slimy mixture of saliva and cum to splash down all over the floor. Letting out a cheeky laugh, [npc.she] takes a quick sidestep and slaps [npc.her] softening horse-cock against your face, commanding, [npc.speech(If you want those extra couple of filly points, you'll be a good filly and clean my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you spend the next couple of minutes licking all the excess fluids off of [npc.namePos] cock, before shuffling back and telling [npc.herHim] that you've finished.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_AFTER_WAKEUP_SEX_ANILINGUS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had [npc.her] fun, [npc.name] stands up and takes [npc.her] [npc.asshole+] away from your face, leaving you panting and gasping for breath on the pile of straw bedding. Letting out a cheeky laugh, [npc.she] takes a quick sidestep and slaps [npc.her] softening horse-cock down against your face, commanding, [npc.speech(You're not finished yet, filly! If you want those extra couple of points, you'll be a good filly and clean my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Obediently doing as you're told, you lift your head up and start licking and kissing [npc.namePos] cum-coated cock. After just a couple of minutes, you've managed to clean all of the horse-jizz off of [npc.her] [npc.cockGirth] shaft, and so you shuffle back and tell [npc.herHim] that you've finished.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_AFTER_WAKEUP_SEX_MOUNTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had [npc.her] fun, [npc.name] slides [npc.her] cock out of your ass and stands up, leaving you panting and gasping for breath on the pile of straw bedding. Letting out a cheeky laugh, [npc.she] prances around to stand in front of you, before taking a quick sidestep and slapping [npc.her] softening horse-cock down against your face. As you let out a surprised gasp, [npc.she] firmly commands, [npc.speech(You're not finished yet, filly! If you want those extra couple of points, you'll be a good filly and clean my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Obediently doing as you're told, you lift your head up and start licking and kissing [npc.namePos] cum-coated cock, getting a taste of your own ass in the process. After just a couple of minutes, you've managed to clean all of the horse-jizz off of [npc.her] [npc.cockGirth] shaft, and so you shuffle back and tell [npc.herHim] that you've finished.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_AFTER_WAKEUP_SEX_FINISH"><![CDATA[
		 Letting out a satisfied huff, [npc.name] tosses a couple of arcane beads your way, before flashing you a smile and saying, [npc.speech(You're a good filly. Thanks for staying the night and providing me with some morning fun! I've got to get on with work now, so I'll see you another time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like the others which were given to you, these enchanted beads quickly disintegrate into pure arcane energy, before swirling up and being absorbed into your filly choker. Taking a moment in which to recover, you thank [npc.name] for the points, before standing up and preparing to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Responses -->
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STABLE_SEX_SLEEP_AFTER_WAKEUP_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leaving [npc.name] to get ready for a hard day's work, you exit [npc.her] stall and continue on out into the stables. Hearing sounds of other slaves waking up, you wonder whether you should head over to another nearby stall and offer your services to the occupant...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- STABLE_SHOWER -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLE_SHOWER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Over on the far side of the stables, there's a large room in which there are a series of shower cubicles, each one specially-designed so that the jets of water can clean a centaur from every angle. Deciding to make use of these shower facilities, you step into an empty cubicle and let the jets of water wash your body clean...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(natalya))
		<p>
			At the far end of the corridor, positioned next to the stables, there's a solid wooden door bearing a plaque which reads; 'Stable Mistress Natalya's Office'. Looking through the large glass windows positioned to the side of this door, you see that there's a small waiting room on the other side, in which a smartly-dressed horse-girl secretary is sitting behind a small wooden desk.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.hasQuest(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA))
				If you wanted to pay Mistress Natalya another visit, it looks as though you'll first have to enter this waiting room and deal with the secretary again...
			#ELSE
				If you wanted to pay Natalya a visit, it looks as though you'll first have to enter this waiting room and deal with this secretary...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			At the far end of the corridor, positioned next to the stables, there's a solid wooden door bearing a plaque which reads; 'Stable Mistress Natalya's Office'. Looking through the large glass windows positioned to the side of this door, you see that there's a small, totally-deserted waiting room on the other side. As Mistress Natalya isn't working at this hour, the waiting room's light are all turned off, and its door is securely locked.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.hasQuest(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA))
				If you wanted to pay Mistress Natalya another visit, you'll have to come back between the hours of [style.colourMinorBad([unit.time(6)]-[unit.time(22)])]...
			#ELSE
				If you wanted to pay Natalya a visit, you'll have to come back between the hours of [style.colourMinorBad([unit.time(6)]-[unit.time(22)])]...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_DENIED"><![CDATA[
	#VAR
		var collar = pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_NECK);
	#ENDVAR
	
	<p>
		#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_natalyaInterviewOffered))
			Deciding that you want to pay Natalya a visit, you knock on the door, which draws an immediate response from the secretary on the other side, who calls out, [style.speechFeminine(Enter!)]
		#ELSE
			Deciding that you want to pay Mistress Natalya another visit, you knock on the door, which again draws an immediate response from the secretary on the other side, who calls out, [style.speechFeminine(Enter!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning the handle and pushing the door open, you [pc.step] forwards into the small waiting room. A couple of comfortable leather sofas and a wooden coffee table are placed against the right-hand wall, while to your left, the smartly-dressed horse-girl secretary is looking at you from behind her desk.
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_natalyaBusy))
			 Recognising you from earlier, she frowns at you and flatly states, [style.speechFeminine(Mistress Natalya instructed you not to bother her again today, did she not? Come back tomorrow if you have something to discuss with her.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having been denied entry to Mistress Natalya's office, there's little else for you to do except turn around and leave...
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
			[style.italicsMinorBad(If you want to see Mistress Natalya, you'll have to come back tomorrow.)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.isPregnant())
			#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
				 Looking down at your pregnant belly, she frowns at you and flatly states, [style.speechFeminine(I am not sure if you're aware, but Mistress Natalya despises the sight of pregnancies. She will have no interest in seeing you until after you've given birth.)]
			#ELSE
				 Before you can say anything, a curious little arcane device to one side of the door lets out a high-pitched beeping noise, which causes the horse-girl to frowns at you and flatly state, [style.speechFeminine(That means you're pregnant. I am not sure if you're aware, but Mistress Natalya despises pregnancies. She will have no interest in seeing you until after you've given birth.)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Having been denied entry to Mistress Natalya's office, there's little else for you to do except turn around and leave...
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
			[style.italicsMinorBad(If you want to see Mistress Natalya, you'll have to come back after resolving your pregnancy.)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.hasIncubationLitter(ORIFICE_VAGINA))
			Before you can say anything, a curious little arcane device to one side of the door lets out a high-pitched beeping noise, which causes the horse-girl to frowns at you and flatly state, [style.speechFeminine(That means your womb's stuffed full of eggs. I am not sure if you're aware, but Mistress Natalya despises anything even remotely related to pregnancies. She will have no interest in seeing you until after you've laid your eggs.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having been denied entry to Mistress Natalya's office, there's little else for you to do except turn around and leave...
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
			[style.italicsMinorBad(If you want to see Mistress Natalya, you'll have to come back after laying the eggs which you're incubating in your womb.)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(collar==null || !collar.getClothingType().getId().equals("innoxia_neck_filly_choker"))
			 Recognising you as a qualified filly, she looks down at your neck, before frowning at you and flatly stating, [style.speechFeminine(Mistress Natalya will be furious if she sees that you're not wearing your filly choker. I can only let you into her office if you're wearing it.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having been denied entry to Mistress Natalya's office, there's little else for you to do except turn around and leave...
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
			[style.italicsMinorBad(If you want to see Mistress Natalya, you'll have to come back while wearing your filly choker.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
			 Recognising you as a qualified filly, she makes a show of looking up and down over your body, before flatly stating, [style.speechFeminine(Mistress Natalya will be furious if she sees that you're no longer a busty [pc.shemale]. I can only let you into her office if you meet her body requirements.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having been denied entry to Mistress Natalya's office, there's little else for you to do except turn around and leave...
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
			[style.italicsMinorBad(If you want to see Mistress Natalya, you'll have to come back while being [pc.a_shemale] with at least D-cup breasts.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_natalyaInterviewOffered))
			Deciding that you want to pay Natalya a visit, you knock on the door, which draws an immediate response from the secretary on the other side, who calls out, [style.speechFeminine(Enter!)]
		#ELSE
			Deciding that you want to pay Mistress Natalya another visit, you knock on the door, which again draws an immediate response from the secretary on the other side, who calls out, [style.speechFeminine(Enter!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning the handle and pushing the door open, you [pc.step] forwards into the small waiting room. A couple of comfortable leather sofas and a wooden coffee table are placed against the right-hand wall, while to your left, the smartly-dressed horse-girl secretary is looking at you from behind her desk.
		#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_natalyaInterviewOffered))
				 Raising her eyebrows, this secretary asks, [style.speechFeminine(How may I help you? Mistress Natalya isn't expecting any visitors today...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Showing the horse-girl the business card which Natalya gave to you, you explain how you were asked to come and pay her a visit. Nodding her head in approval, this secretary presses a button on the arcane intercom sitting on her desk, before leaning forwards and saying, [style.speechFeminine(Mistress Natalya? There's [pc.a_race] here to see you. [pc.SheHas] got one of your business cards...)]
		#ELSE
			 Recognising you, this secretary presses a button on the arcane intercom sitting on her desk, before leaning forwards and saying, [style.speechFeminine(Mistress Natalya? One of your fillies is here to see you.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(Show [pc.herHim] in at once!)] the voice of Natalya blares out from the speaker.
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			 Informing you that your companion will have to remain behind and wait in here, the horse-girl secretary gestures for you to head through the door on the far side of the room. Telling [com.name] to stay behind, you [pc.walk] over to the door to Natalya's office and push it open, before quickly [pc.stepping] inside and closing it after you.
		#ELSE
			 Without saying another word, the horse-girl secretary gestures for you to head through the door on the far side of the room. Doing as you're instructed, you [pc.walk] over to the door to Natalya's office and push it open, before quickly [pc.stepping] inside and closing it after you.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_INTERVIEW"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Beside its impressive size, the first thing that strikes you as you enter Natalya's office is a series of large glass windows running down the entire length of the far wall, which grant you a captivating view of the warehouse district. Looking around the office's interior, you see that the usual assortment of cabinets and potted plants are of a rather bland, modern design. The only piece of furniture which looks to have had any thought put into its selection is the impressive wooden desk on the far side of the room, behind which Dominion Express's 'Stable Mistress' is currently sitting.
	</p>
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(Come over here, filly,)] Natalya calls out, putting an end to your appraisal of her office. Seeing no reason not to do as she says, you walk over the polished wooden floor to where Natalya has just stood up from behind her desk. Once again, you can't help but notice how the lilac-skinned [natalya.race] is especially short for a taur, measuring barely more than
		#IF(game.isMetricSizes())
			 a hundred and seventy centimetres from head to hoof.
		#ELSE
			 five and a half feet from head to hoof.
		#ENDIF
		 Just like the last time you saw her, Natalya is smartly dressed in a black feminine blazer and white shirt, which are struggling to keep her large, [natalya.cupSize]-cup breasts in check. A huge black skirt is concealing her feral horse's body, while a pair of royal-purple hair sticks are keeping her silken, black hair tied up into a smart bun. Perched on the bridge of her cute feminine nose, she's wearing a pair of black, thick-rimmed glasses, behind which her grey-green eyes are flicking up and down as she looks you over.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_playerSubmittedToNatalya))
			[natalya.speech(I am pleased to see you here again, filly. I bet you've been thinking of nothing but my cock since I had you jerk me off in that alleyway,)]
		#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_playerSubmittedToNatalyaInPark))
			[natalya.speech(I am pleased to see you here again, filly. I bet you've been thinking of nothing but my cock since I had you jerk me off in that park,)]
		#ELSE
			[natalya.speech(I am pleased to see you here again, filly. I knew you'd come and see me again,)]
		#ENDIF
		 she sneers, letting an arrogant smirk settle on her face as she snaps her fingers and demands, [natalya.speech(Give me my business card back. I'll have it stamped so that those sluts behind the front desk won't hold you up next time.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as Natalya asks, you hand her business card back to her, and watch as she quickly stamps it with a red horse-shoe icon. Carelessly tossing it back to you, she reveals, [natalya.speech(The reason I wanted to see you again, filly, is that I have a feeling that you're going to make a fine addition to Dominion Express. You like the sound of sucking centaur cock all day? How about eating horse ass or getting mounted and anally rutted by some of my big strong boys and girls? Of course you do; I could tell that you're a dirty little anal slut from the moment I saw you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not giving you any time in which to react to her degrading assumption about your character, the [natalya.race] pushes her glasses up onto the bridge of her cute nose and declares, [natalya.speech(I'm sure you can't wait to show all my slaves what a filthy centaur cum-dump you are, so we'll start your interview for the official position of 'filly' right away!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you [pc.step] into Natalya's office, you find your gaze yet again being drawn to the series of large glass windows running down the entire length of the far wall, which grant you a captivating view of the warehouse district. Looking around the office's interior, you see that the usual assortment of cabinets and potted plants are of a rather bland, modern design. The only piece of furniture which looks to have had any thought put into its selection is the impressive wooden desk on the far side of the room, behind which Dominion Express's 'Stable Mistress' is currently sitting.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_WRONG_BODY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Looking up from the piles of paperwork arrayed over the desk in front of her, 
		#IF(!pc.isFeminine())
			 Mistress Natalya's face instantly scrunches up into a furious scowl as she catches sight of your masculine body, and she screams, [natalya.speech(Bad filly! How <i>dare</i> you transform yourself! You are to kneel before me, <i>right this instant</i>!)]
		#ELSEIF(pc.getBreastSize().getMeasurement()<8)
			 Mistress Natalya's face instantly scrunches up into a furious scowl as she catches sight of your reduced breast size, and she screams, [natalya.speech(Bad filly! How <i>dare</i> you transform yourself! You are to kneel before me, <i>right this instant</i>!)]
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasVagina())
			#IF(pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_VAGINA))
				 Mistress Natalya's face instantly scrunches up into a furious scowl as she catches sight of your exposed pussy, and she screams, [natalya.speech(Bad filly! How <i>dare</i> you transform yourself! You are to kneel before me, <i>right this instant</i>!)]
			#ELSE
				 Mistress Natalya's face instantly scrunches up into a suspicious glare, and she ponders, [natalya.speech(I can tell that there's something not quite right about you... Wait... You've got a filthy pussy between your [pc.legs], haven't you?! You bad filly! How <i>dare</i> you transform yourself! You are to kneel before me, <i>right this instant</i>!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_PENIS))
				 Mistress Natalya's face instantly scrunches up into a furious scowl as she sees that you no longer have a cock, and she screams, [natalya.speech(Bad filly! How <i>dare</i> you transform yourself! You are to kneel before me, <i>right this instant</i>!)]
			#ELSE
				 Mistress Natalya's face instantly scrunches up into a suspicious glare, and she ponders, [natalya.speech(I can tell that there's something not quite right about you... Wait... You've ha your penis removed, haven't you?! You bad filly! How <i>dare</i> you transform yourself! You are to kneel before me, <i>right this instant</i>!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] forwards and kneel down in front of Mistress Natalya's desk. Opening one of her drawers, the still-furious [natalya.race] grabs both her riding crop and a small bottle of transformative liquid. Quickly trotting around behind you, she swings her riding crop down and whacks you on your ass, before tossing the potion bottle down to you and snapping, [natalya.speech(Drink it all down, you bad filly!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_TRAINING_2"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Looking up from the piles of paperwork arrayed over the desk in front of her, Mistress Natalya flashes you a sly smile and orders, [natalya.speech(Come over here and kneel down beside me, filly! Today I'll have you trained to love giving rimjobs!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_TRAINING_3"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Looking up from the piles of paperwork arrayed over the desk in front of her, Mistress Natalya flashes you a sly smile and orders, [natalya.speech(Come over here and kneel down beside me, filly! Today I'll have you practice your rimjob skills on [npc.name] while I pound your ass!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_COLLAR_UPGRADED"><![CDATA[
	#VAR
		var collar = pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_NECK);
	#ENDVAR
	
	#IF(collar.getColour(0)==COLOUR_CLOTHING_GOLD)
		<p>
			Looking up from the piles of paperwork arrayed over the desk in front of her, Mistress Natalya starts to flash you one of her usual arrogant smirks, but as she catches sight of your gold filly choker, she does a double-take and asks in wide-eyed shock, [natalya.speech(W-What?! You actually managed to afford the gold upgrade?! Y-You're not supposed to be able to do that!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at your Mistress's uncharacteristic stuttering, you advance towards her and proudly show off the golden lettering on your choker. Interpreting your movement as a sign that you intend to dominate her, Mistress Natalya backs up a little and stutters, [natalya.speech(T-The contact may say something about gold fillies being able to order me to submit to them once per day, but that wasn't really intended to be serious! I mean, you're not actually going to make <i>me</i> submit to <i>you</i>, are you? You're just a submissive, anal-loving filly slut! You wouldn't dare to try and dominate me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having worked hard to earn your golden filly choker, you wonder if you should make good use of it and order Mistress Natalya to service your cock or ass. If you really wanted to, you suppose that you could also demand that she let you mount her and give her a good anal rutting...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Looking up from the piles of paperwork arrayed over the desk in front of her, Mistress Natalya immediately catches sight of your new silver filly choker, and after flashing you an amused smirk, she offers you her congratulations, [natalya.speech(Well done, filly! There aren't many other fillies who have managed to earn a silver choker! As your reward for working so hard, I'll allow you to sexually service me once per day. So, would you to suck my cock, hmm? Or maybe you'd like to eat my ass? If you really wanted me to, I suppose I could also mount you and give you a good rutting!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having worked hard to earn your silver filly choker, you wonder if you should make good use of it and ask Mistress Natalya to let you sexually service her...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_WITH_COLLAR"><![CDATA[
	#VAR
		var collar = pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_NECK);
	#ENDVAR
	
	#IF(collar.getColour(0)==COLOUR_CLOTHING_GOLD)
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_natalyaDailySexAsDom))
				Looking up from the piles of paperwork arrayed over the desk in front of her, Mistress Natalya nervously gulps as she glances down at the golden filly choker around your neck, before quickly reminding you,
				#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_natalyaDailySexAsSub))
					 [natalya.speech(T-The contract explicitly states that golden fillies only get to dominate me once a day, filly! I already submitted to you earlier, s-so you can't make me do it again today! As you've also serviced me today, there's nothing more that I can give to you!)]
				#ELSE
					 [natalya.speech(T-The contract explicitly states that golden fillies only get to dominate me once a day, filly! I already submitted to you earlier, s-so you can't make me do it again today! Perhaps you'd like me to remind you of your true place and let you service my cock or ass, hmm?!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				Looking up from the piles of paperwork arrayed over the desk in front of her, Mistress Natalya nervously gulps as she glances down at the golden filly choker around your neck, before anxiously asking, [natalya.speech(Y-You're not going to order me to submit to you, are you? You're just a submissive, anal-loving filly slut! D-Don't forget that!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(collar.getColour(0)==COLOUR_CLOTHING_SILVER)
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_natalyaDailySexAsSub))
				Looking up from the piles of paperwork arrayed over the desk in front of her, Mistress Natalya glances down at the silver filly choker around your neck, before raising her eyebrows and reminding you, [natalya.speech(You only get to service me once per day, filly! I already let you have your fun earlier, so there's nothing more for me to give to you today!)]
			#ELSE
				Looking up from the piles of paperwork arrayed over the desk in front of her, Mistress Natalya glances down at the silver filly choker around your neck, before flashing you a sly smirk and asking, [natalya.speech(What is it filly? Do you want to get a taste of my big, fat cock? Or maybe you want to eat my ass, hmm? Go on, filly, tell me what it is you want!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Looking up from the piles of paperwork arrayed over the desk in front of her, Mistress Natalya glances down at the bronze filly choker around your neck, before frowning at you and impatiently stating, [natalya.speech(There's nothing I have to give to bronze-ranked fillies! What is it that you want?!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Responses: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_DENIED_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not being able to see
		#IF(pc.hasQuest(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_NATALYA))
			 Mistress Natalya again
		#ELSE
			 Natalya
		#ENDIF
		, there's little else for you to do except turn around and exit the waiting room via the same door through which you entered. [pc.Stepping] back out into the warehouse's long corridor, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_INTERVIEW_FAIL_0"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You really don't like the sound of what Natalya is saying, and so you firmly tell her that you're not interested in being interviewed for the position of 'filly'. Clearly not used to being spoken to in such a direct manner by people who she sees as being beneath her, Natalya steps back in shock, before angrily shouting, [natalya.speech(How dare you refuse me?! Get the hell out of my office! I never want to see you here again!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_INTERVIEW_FAIL_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Frantically pressing the button on her intercom, the furious [natalya.race] starts calling for security to immediately come to her office. Getting the hint, you throw Natalya's stamped business card onto her desk, before turning your back on her and swiftly exiting her office.
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			 Telling [com.name] that the two of you are leaving, you make your way back down the warehouse's long corridor, and soon find yourselves stepping back out into Dominion's warehouse district...
		#ELSE
			 Not wanting to have to deal with whatever security Natalya has just summoned, you quickly make your way back down the warehouse's long corridor, and soon find yourself stepping back out into Dominion's warehouse district...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_TRANSFORMED_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you pull out the bottle's stopper and gulp down all the sickly-sweet liquid contained within. Almost immediately, you feel an intense heat pulsing throughout your entire body, and as you start to transform, Mistress Natalya whacks your exposed ass with her riding crop once again, before once again shouting, [natalya.speech(You bad, bad filly! At least I get the pleasure of watching you being transformed...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_FILLY_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	#VAR
		var collar = pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_NECK);
	#ENDVAR
	
	<p>
		#IF(collar.getColour(0)==COLOUR_CLOTHING_GOLD)
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_natalyaDailySexAsDom))
				#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_natalyaDailySexAsSub))
					Having already dominated and submitted to Mistress Natalya today, you're unable to have sex with her again until tomorrow. With nothing more for you to do with the [natalya.race], you tell her that you're going to return to your duties, before turning around and exiting her office.
				#ELSE
					Having already dominated Mistress Natalya today, you're unable to make her your submissive bitch again until tomorrow. Deciding that you don't want to submit to the [natalya.race], you tell her that you're going to return to your duties, before turning around and exiting her office.
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				Deciding that you don't want to have sex with the [natalya.race] right now, you tell her that you're going to return to your duties, before turning around and exiting her office.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(collar.getColour(0)==COLOUR_CLOTHING_SILVER)
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_natalyaDailySexAsSub))
				Having already submitted to Mistress Natalya today, you're unable to sexually service her again until tomorrow. With nothing more for you to do with the [natalya.race], you tell her that you're going to return to your duties, before turning around and exiting her office.
			#ELSE
				Deciding that you don't want to submit to the [natalya.race] right now, you tell her that you're going to return to your duties, before turning around and exiting her office.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Being just a bronze rank filly, and therefore unable to have sex with Mistress Natalya, there's nothing else for you to do except tell her that you're going to return to your duties, before turning around and exiting her office.
		#ENDIF
		 Passing the smartly-dressed horse-girl secretary who's still sitting behind her desk in the small waiting room, you continue on out into the warehouse's corridor and wonder where to go to next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_TRANSFORMED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_TRANSFORMED_START_TRAINING_2_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Excitedly prancing around you to take a good look at your new body, Mistress Natalya delivers one final sharp whack to your exposed ass, before declaring, [natalya.speech(That's better; now you look like a good little filly! Don't you <i>ever</i> transform yourself again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Trotting back over to sit down behind her desk, the small [natalya.race] snaps her fingers and orders, [natalya.speech(Come over here and kneel down beside me, filly! Today I'll have you trained to love giving rimjobs!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_ENTRY_TRANSFORMED_START_TRAINING_3_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Excitedly prancing around to take a good look at your new body, Mistress Natalya delivers one final sharp whack to your exposed ass, before declaring, [natalya.speech(That's better; now you look like a good little filly! Don't you <i>ever</i> transform yourself again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Trotting back over to sit down behind her desk, the small [natalya.race] snaps her fingers and orders, [natalya.speech(Come over here and kneel down beside me, filly! Today I'll have you practice your rimjob skills on [npc.name] while I pound your ass!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_1 -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_1"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself agreeing with what Natalya is saying, you thank her for the offer of an interview, to which she smirks and asks, [natalya.speech(That's right, you're a dirty little slut for centaur cock, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you open your mouth to respond, the [natalya.race] snaps, [natalya.speech(Remember to refer to me as 'Mistress' from now on, filly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, Mistress,)] you dutifully reply, [pc.speech(I'm a slut for centaur cock...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Triumphantly sneering at you, Mistress Natalya rhetorically asks, [natalya.speech(I suppose that I should explain how you are to be employed, shouldn't I? Basically, the slaves owned by Dominion Express are split into two categories; the centaur slaves who do all the manual labour, and the fillies who sexually service them in order to keep their morale high. Contrary to popular belief, it's rather expensive to keep slaves, and doubly so for centaurs who require a significant amount of daily calories and living space. Due to this, we do not take full ownership of our fillies, and instead contract them out as a type of indentured servant. If you pass this interview, you will enter into this arrangement.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Breaking off her explanation to open one of her desk's drawers and produce a black riding crop, the short [natalya.race] trots around to stand before you and state, [natalya.speech(As a filly, you will be expected to obey my every command. Let us begin by having you strip naked and kneel down before me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Impatiently pawing at the ground with one of her front hooves, Mistress Natalya points to the ground with her riding crop and snaps, [natalya.speech(Get on with it!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_FAIL_1"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You really don't want to strip naked and kneel before Natalya, and so you firmly tell her that you're not interested in continuing this interview. Clearly not used to being spoken to in such a direct manner by people who she sees as being beneath her, Natalya steps back in shock, before angrily shouting, [natalya.speech(How dare you refuse me?! Get the hell out of my office! I never want to see you here again!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_2 -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_2_STRIP_SEALED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you start stripping off your clothes, but have to tell Mistress Natalya that some of them are sealed onto you. Impatiently trotting up to you, she snaps, [natalya.speech(Who do you take me for?! A few petty enchantments won't stop me from getting what I want!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the [natalya.race] channels some of her arcane essences into your sealed clothing, removing their enchantment and letting you take them off. Not wanting to annoy your Mistress any further, you strip naked as quickly as you possibly can, before obediently kneeling down in front of her. Satisfied by your display of submission, the [natalya.race] smirks down at you and sneers, [natalya.speech(Good filly! You'll be spending a lot of your time down on your knees from now on!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_2_STRIP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you strip naked as quickly as you possibly can, before obediently kneeling down in front of Mistress Natalya. Satisfied by your display of submission, the [natalya.race] smirks down at you and sneers, [natalya.speech(Good filly! You'll be spending a lot of your time down on your knees from now on!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_2_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Remaining down on your knees, you listen to Mistress Natalya as she slowly walks around you in circles and explains, [natalya.speech(As one of Dominion Express's fillies, you will be expected to give both blowjobs and rimjobs to the centaur slaves, as well as allowing them to mount and anally fuck you. I will have you trained for these duties in three stages over the course of several days; first you shall suck my cock, then I will have you eat my ass, and finally I will mount you and fuck your slutty asshole. After each of these stages, you will repeat your performance with one of the centaur slaves.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she continues talking, you notice that Mistress Natalya's tone of voice is getting more and more excited, until eventually she comes to a halt in front of you and hungrily pants, [natalya.speech(Come on, filly! Lift my skirt and get a look at the cock you'll be sucking!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking up at the small [natalya.race], you suddenly notice that there's a steady stream of precum drooling down from beneath her skirt, which is quickly forming a small pool on the wooden floor in front of you. Seeing what it is you're looking at, Mistress Natalya exclaims, [natalya.speech(That's your fault, filly! Now hurry up and lift my skirt before I make even more of a mess!)] 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_FAIL_2"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Starting to feel uncomfortable about the situation you find yourself in, you stand up and grab your clothes, before firmly telling Natalya that you're not interested in continuing this interview. Clearly not used to being spoken to in such a direct manner by people who she sees as being beneath her, Natalya steps back in shock, before angrily shouting, [natalya.speech(How dare you refuse me?! Get the hell out of my office! I never want to see you here again!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_3 -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_3"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hurrying to do as you're told, you reach up to lift Mistress Natalya's skirt, fully revealing her black-haired horse-like body.
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_playerSubmittedToNatalya) || game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_playerSubmittedToNatalyaInPark))
			 Although you've seen it before, you still find yourself staring in awe at how huge the [natalya.race]'s [natalya.penisLengthValue] cock is, especially in proportion to her relatively small body.
		#ELSE
			 As you kneel back down beside her, you find yourself staring in awe at how huge the [natalya.race]'s [natalya.penisLengthValue] cock is, especially in proportion to her relatively small body.
		#ENDIF
		 While mostly black in colour, it's covered in light-lilac mottling, and from its flat, flared head, a musky stream of precum continues to drool down to soak the floor beneath her. Letting out an excited whinny, the small [natalya.race] turns around on the spot, presenting you with her hindquarters and showing off her rear entrance. Being puffed up into an ebony, doughnut-like ring, it looks just like a feral horse's at first glance, but as you take a closer look, you see that its surface is glistening with clear, slimy lubricant, revealing its demonic nature and making it look more like an exotic sexual orifice than a horse's asshole.
	</p>
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(Like what you see, filly?)] Mistress Natalya asks, [natalya.speech(All of the slaves and fillies here at Dominion Express are like me; we're all packing big, fat horse cocks and puffy assholes!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasVagina())
			Turning back around to look down at your groin, the [natalya.race]'s smirk quickly shifts into a scowl, and she reaches down with her riding crop to deliver a short smack to your exposed pussy. Ignoring your surprised yelp, she sneers, [natalya.speech(How disgusting! When you sign up as a filly, I'll be having that filthy hole of yours removed! Slaves with pussies end up getting pregnant, and pregnant slaves can't work! Tell me that you hate having a pussy, you bad little filly!)]
		#ELSE
			Excitedly trotting back and forth, the [natalya.race] declares, [natalya.speech(When you sign up as a filly, I'll be having you transformed into a good little busty [style.shemale] slut! You'll be forbidden from ever having a pussy, as slaves with pussies end up getting pregnant, and pregnant slaves can't work! Tell me that you hate pussies, filly!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you tell Mistress Natalya that you hate
		#IF(pc.hasVagina())
			 having a pussy,
		#ELSE
			 pussies,
		#ENDIF
		 which causes a big smirk to settle on her pretty face. Once again turning around and presenting you with her puffy asshole, the small [natalya.race] looks back over her shoulder and says, [natalya.speech(Before fillies are allowed to sexually service anyone, they must show their partner that they're a submissive, anal-loving slut. Kiss my asshole, filly, and then I'll allow you to get started on sucking my cock!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_RELUCTANT_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you're a little unsure that you'll like it, you don't want to disobey your Mistress, and so you hesitantly lean in to deliver a quick kiss on the [natalya.race]'s puffy asshole. Sensing your reluctance to do as you're told, Mistress Natalya makes an annoyed tutting noise, before suddenly stepping back and forcefully rubbing her butt into your face. Smothering your [pc.lips+] with her slimy, musky asshole, your Mistress exclaims, [natalya.speech(Come on, you dirty filly slut! Kiss it real good!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not having much choice but to do as you're told, you force yourself to passionately kiss Mistress Natalya's puffy black asshole. Satisfied that you've put some effort into it, the [natalya.race] makes another tutting noise and steps forwards, leaving you panting and gasping for breath. Turning to one side, she flashes you an evil glare, before using her riding crop to point down at her leaky cock as she orders, [natalya.speech(Get under there and suck my cock, filly! You're not going to pass this interview unless you get me to cum with your mouth!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_EAGER_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to disappoint your Mistress, you lean forwards and eagerly bury your face in her ass, before starting to passionately kiss her puffy black asshole. Letting out a delighted moan, Mistress Natalya suddenly steps back and forcefully rubs her butt into your face. Smothering your [pc.lips+] with her slimy, musky asshole, your Mistress exclaims, [natalya.speech(That's it, you dirty filly slut! Kiss it real good!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to do as you're told, you continue to passionately kiss Mistress Natalya's alluring asshole. Satisfied that you've put enough effort into it, the [natalya.race] makes another happy little moan before stepping forwards, leaving you panting and gasping for breath. Turning to one side, she flashes you an evil glare, before using her riding crop to point down at her leaky cock as she orders, [natalya.speech(Get under there and suck my cock, filly! You're not going to pass this interview unless you get me to cum with your mouth!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_BLOWJOB_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you duck down beneath the small [natalya.race]'s black-furred horse body, before leaning forwards and licking the flat, flared head of her huge horse-like cock. Letting out an impatient whinny, your Mistress steps forwards and slaps her precum-drooling cock against your face, moaning, [natalya.speech(I didn't ask for any foreplay, filly! Get my cock down your throat!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Opening wide, you do as you're told and take Mistress Natalya's cock into your mouth. With a delighted moan, the [natalya.race] steps forwards once again, thrusting her hot, [natalya.cockGirth] horse-cock down your throat. Reaching up to playfully squeeze her own breasts, she moans, [natalya.speech(That's it, filly! ~Ooh!~ Show me that you'll make a good little cock-sucker!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_FAIL_3"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The prospect of kissing Natalya's asshole is too much for you, and so you stand up and grab your clothes, before firmly telling Natalya that you're not interested in continuing this interview. Clearly not used to being spoken to in such a direct manner by people who she sees as being beneath her, Natalya steps back in shock, before angrily shouting, [natalya.speech(How dare you refuse me?! Get the hell out of my office! I never want to see you here again!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_INTERVIEW_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(~Aah!~ Good filly!)] Mistress Natalya exclaims as she steps back and slides her huge horse-cock out from your throat. Leaving you gasping for breath, the small [natalya.race] happily prances over to stand behind her desk, before snapping her fingers and ordering, [natalya.speech(Get over here and keep on licking, filly! You caused this mess, so now you get to be the one to clean me up!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing no reason not to do as you're told, you crawl after your Mistress, and once again duck your head down beneath her feral horse body. As the [natalya.race] grabs a couple of forms from out of her desk's drawer, you prepare to get started and lick her slimy cock clean...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_CONTRACT_OFFERED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_CONTRACT_OFFERED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Opening your mouth, you dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start eagerly licking up all the excess cum and saliva that's coating Mistress Natalya's softening horse-cock. Encouraged by the soft moans which she keeps on making, you spend the next several minutes cleaning the small [natalya.race]'s disproportionately-huge cock while she continues filling out the forms she retrieved from her desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		Eventually, once you've licked every last trace of sexual fluids from her flaccid, sheathed shaft, Mistress Natalya calls out, [natalya.speech(Good filly! I'm pleased to tell you that you've passed the interview! Now get around to the other side of my desk and read over your contract.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you crawl out from under your Mistress's feral horse body, before standing up and [pc.walking] around to the other side of the desk. With the small [natalya.race] peering at you over her thick-rimmed glasses, you look down at the papers which she's prepared for you.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you start to read through them, it soon becomes clear that most of the forms' content is made up of indecipherable legal jargon, leaving you with no idea of what exactly it is you'll be signing up for. Obviously having gone through this numerous times in the past, Mistress Natalya lets out an impatient sigh and offers, [natalya.speech(Would you like me to tell you what it all means?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Answering in the affirmative, you listen as the [natalya.race] explains, [natalya.speech(As I told you earlier, you'll be signing up as one of Dominion Express's non-exclusive, non-transferable, free-roaming, indentured servants. Basically, you'll be a slave, but you get to come and go as you please and work as little or as much as you want. We're not under any obligation to pay you for work done, but we do offer a points-based reward system, which you'll find out more about once you complete your filly training.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Placing the top form over to one side, Mistress Natalya points to the second one and continues, [natalya.speech(This part explains how your duties will be sexually servicing the centaur slaves, and how after you've completed your training, you'll be required to wear a special filly choker at all times. Due to the preferences of our centaur slaves, you're also required to be a busty [style.shemale].)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_CONTRACT_OFFERED_NO_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I wont need to be transformed though, will I?)] you ask, confident that your big breasts, feminine figure, and [pc.cockSize] cock are just what Natalya is looking for.
	</p>
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(From what I can see, you won't require any transforming, no. Just keep in mind that if you ever present yourself to me without being [style.a_shemale], or with tits smaller than D-cups, then I'll have to punish you and have you fixed!)] your Mistress says, before warning, [natalya.speech(Anyway, the final part of the contract is saying that you agree to let me train you as an anal-loving filly slut. Each stage of your training will follow the same format; you'll perform a sex act on me, and then I'll have you repeat that act on one of my centaur slaves. As you've already sucked my cock, we can move straight on to having you give a blowjob to one of them. Now hurry up and sign on the dotted line, so that I can start training you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at the forms in front of you, you wonder whether or not you should do as Mistress Natalya says and sign them...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_CONTRACT_OFFERED_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So you mean you're going to transform me?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasVagina())
			[natalya.speech(That is correct; I'll have your disgusting little cunt removed and turn you into a busty [style.shemale] slut! Oh, and don't even <i>think</i> of running off and getting transformed back into your current form afterwards, for you will be forbidden from servicing slaves unless you're [style.a_shemale] with tits being at least D-cups!)] your Mistress warns, before continuing,
		#ELSE
			[natalya.speech(That is correct; I'll have you turned into a busty [style.shemale] slut! Oh, and don't even <i>think</i> of running off and getting transformed back into your current form afterwards, for you will be forbidden from servicing slaves unless you're [style.a_shemale] with tits being at least D-cups!)] your Mistress warns, before continuing,
		#ENDIF
		 [natalya.speech(Anyway, the final part of the contract is saying that you agree to let me train you as an anal-loving filly slut. Each stage of your training will follow the same format; you'll perform a sex act on me, and then I'll have you repeat that act on one of the centaur slaves. As you've already sucked my cock, we can move straight onto having you give a centaur slave a blowjob. Now hurry up and sign on the dotted line.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at the forms in front of you, you wonder whether or not you should do as Mistress Natalya says and sign them...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_CONTRACT_OFFERED_REFUSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The prospect of going through further training with Natalya's centaur slaves is too much for you, and so you stand up and grab your clothes, before firmly telling Natalya that you're not going to sign up to become one of her fillies. Clearly not used to being spoken to in such a direct manner by people who she sees as being beneath her, Natalya steps back in shock, before angrily shouting, [natalya.speech(How dare you refuse me?! Get the hell out of my office! I never want to see you here again!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_CONTRACT_SIGNED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_CONTRACT_SIGNED_NO_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you sign the forms, declaring yourself willing to be trained into one of Dominion Express's fillies. Pushing her glasses up onto the bridge of her nose, Mistress Natalya allows a big grin to settle on her face as she files away your contract, before turning to face you and asking, [natalya.speech(So, filly, to complete the first stage of your training, you'll be sucking one of my centaur slaves' cocks. Would you like to service one of my big, strong boys, or would you prefer to suck a big, fat [style.shemale] cock?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_CONTRACT_SIGNED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you sign the forms, declaring yourself willing to be trained into one of Dominion Express's fillies. Pushing her glasses up onto the bridge of her nose, Mistress Natalya allows a big grin to settle on her face as she files away your contract, before turning to face you and declaring, [natalya.speech(First of all, filly, we'll get your body transformed into one that's suitable for servicing my centaur slaves.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		From out of yet another of her desk's drawers, Mistress Natalya produces a small bottle of transformative liquid. Playfully swinging it back and forth, she teases,
		#IF(pc.isAbleToHaveRaceTransformed())
			 [natalya.speech(This potion will give you the perfect little filly body, which I'm sure all of my slaves will find simply irresistible! Come over here and drink it all down, filly, so that we can get on with the real training!)]
		#ELSE
			 [natalya.speech(There's no need for me to instruct you on how to transform yourself; this potion will give you the perfect little filly body, which I'm sure all of my slaves will find simply irresistible! Come over here and drink it all down, filly, so that we can get on with the real training!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_CONTRACT_SIGNED_TRANSFORMED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] forwards and take the offered bottle, before pulling out the stopper and gulping down all the sickly-sweet liquid contained within. Almost immediately, you feel an intense heat pulsing throughout your entire body, and as you start to transform, Mistress Natalya teases, [natalya.speech(This is why I insisted on having you strip naked! I love watching new fillies being transformed...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRANSFORMED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Excitedly prancing around you to take a good look at your new body, Mistress Natalya happily exclaims, [natalya.speech(What a pretty little filly! Now, to complete the first stage of your training, you'll be sucking one of my centaur slaves' cocks. Would you like to service one of my big, strong boys, or would you prefer to suck a big, fat [style.shemale] cock?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_1 -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_1"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to service [npc.a_gender], you tell Mistress Natalya that you'd prefer to suck the cock of [npc.a_race]. Playfully biting her lip, the [npc.race] prances over to the other side of the room, giving your [pc.ass+] a quick slap as she passes you by. Opening the door to her office, she turns and commands, [natalya.speech(Stay there, filly! I shall fetch you a suitable partner!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you wait in Mistress Natalya's office while she prances off to fetch [npc.a_race] from the stables. Thankfully, you don't have to wait for long, and after just a few minutes, she returns with [npc.a_gender] [npc.race] slave in tow. Standing at [npc.heightValue] from head to hoof, and possessing a large, muscular body,
		#IF(npc.getRaceStage()==RACE_STAGE_GREATER)
			 this dark-brown-haired
		#ELSE
			 this olive-skinned, dark-brown-haired
		#ENDIF
		  [npc.race] towers above both you and Mistress Natalya.
		#IF(npc.isFeminine())
			 Thanks to the fact that she's only wearing a basic [#npc.getClothingInSlot(IS_CHEST).getName()] and a bronze slave collar around her neck,
		#ELSE
			 Thanks to the fact that he's only wearing a bronze slave collar around his neck,
		#ENDIF
		 you can see that this slave's body isn't the only thing that's huge, as [npc.sheHasFull] a massive, black horse-cock and huge pair of balls hanging down between [npc.her] hindquarters. Playfully prancing around to give this [npc.race]'s ass a slap, Mistress Natalya introduces [npc.herHim] to you by exclaiming, [natalya.speech(This here is [npc.name]! [npc.SheIs] one of my hardest workers, but as [npc.she] keeps on causing trouble in the stables, [npc.sheHas] never been promoted past the lowest rank of bronze. Isn't that right, [npc.name]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Yes, Mistress,)] the slave snorts, [npc.speech(Sorry, Mistress.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Happily prancing over to stand beside you, Mistress Natalya turns back to face [npc.name] and declares, [natalya.speech(Anyway, down to business! As you've managed to go three whole days without starting any fights, I thought I'd reward you by letting you help me train this brand new filly today!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Rubbing up against you, the small [natalya.race] suddenly grabs your [pc.boobs+], before squeezing them together and then quickly moving [natalya.her] delicate, feminine fingers down to pinch your [pc.nipples+]. Caught by surprise, you find yourself letting out a high-pitched gasp as [natalya.name] continues molesting your chest and teasing, [natalya.speech(You like this filly's hot little body, [npc.name]? Look at [pc.her] nipples getting hard from all of this excitement!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an approving grunt, the [npc.race] lustfully stares at you as Natalya makes you turn around and present your [pc.ass+] to [npc.herHim]. Tracing her fingers around the rim of your [pc.asshole+], she teases, [natalya.speech(I bet you can't wait until this little filly's finished [pc.her] training, so that you can have a go at pounding this hot little ass of [pc.hers]...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The small [natalya.race]'s teasing is having the effect she wanted, as [npc.namePos] massive horse-cock is now fully erect, and there's a significant amount of precum leaking from its flat, flared head. Playfully pouting at her slave, Mistress Natalya reveals, [natalya.speech(Unfortunately, this filly's ass isn't ready to be rutted just yet. Instead, you're here to help [pc.herHim] train [pc.her] blowjob skills. Now let [pc.herHim] show you [pc.her] submission so that [pc.she] can get started!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out yet another grunt, [npc.name] turns around on the spot and flicks [npc.her] tail to one side, presenting you with [npc.her] puffy, [npc.assholeColour] asshole. Giving your ass a quick slap, Mistress Natalya reminds you, [natalya.speech(The rule here in Dominion Express is that fillies have to kiss their partner's asshole before getting started, so that all parties are aware that the filly is a submissive anal-loving slut! So go on, filly, give [npc.namePos] asshole a big, wet kiss, then you can get started on sucking [npc.her] cock!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_1_RELUCTANT_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you're not too sure about it, you decide to do as you're told, and [pc.step] forwards to lean in and plant a quick kiss on [npc.namePos] puffy, musky back door. Not at all pleased with your lack of effort, Mistress Natalya trots forwards and grabs the back of your head, before firmly pushing your face into [npc.namePos] hindquarters. Holding her riding crop in her free hand, she swings it down to sharply whack your ass as she shouts, [natalya.speech(That's not how an anal-loving filly slut kisses horse-ass! Put some damn effort into it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your face being forced into [npc.namePos] feral horse-ass, there's little other option but to do as you're told, and you force yourself to passionately kiss the [npc.race]'s hot, ebony asshole. Loosening her grip on the back of your head, Mistress Natalya allows you pull back a little, before demanding, [natalya.speech(Tell me that you love horse-ass, you dirty filly slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to make her angry, you obediently call out, [pc.speech(I love horse-ass, Mistress!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Swinging her riding crop down to deliver another sharp slap on your ass, the small [natalya.race] teases, [natalya.speech(Is that right, filly? Show me that you're not lying!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a small whine, you lean forwards and force yourself to once again passionately kiss [npc.namePos] [npc.asshole+]. Encouraging you to keep going, Mistress Natalya continues to gently spank you with her riding crop while repeating the fact that you're nothing but a dirty, anal-loving filly. After several minutes of this, you find yourself starting to warm up to the idea of performing anilingus, but before you can really get too into it, Mistress Natalya snaps, [natalya.speech(That's enough, filly! Your real rimjob training will come later! Now drop down and lick [npc.namePos] cock!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_1_EAGER_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Eager to do as you're told, you quickly [pc.step] forwards and lean in to plant a big, wet kiss on [npc.namePos] puffy, musky back door. Clearly impressed by your enthusiastic display, Mistress Natalya trots forwards and gently taps your ass with her riding crop, exclaiming, [natalya.speech(That's my good, anal-loving filly slut! Go on, show me how much you love horse-ass!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to show your Mistress what a good filly you are, you bury your face into [npc.namePos] feral horse-ass, before starting to passionately kiss [npc.her] hot, ebony asshole. Letting out a very pleased humming noise, Mistress Natalya once again taps your ass with her riding crop, before demanding, [natalya.speech(Tell me that you love horse-ass, you dirty filly slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling back a little, you gasp for breath before obediently calling out, [pc.speech(I love horse-ass, Mistress!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Grabbing the back of your head, the small [natalya.race] excitedly pushes your face back into [npc.namePos] ass, teasing, [natalya.speech(Is that right, filly? Show me that you're not lying!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a muffled [pc.moan], you press your [pc.lips+] against [npc.namePos] [npc.asshole+] and once again start passionately kissing it. Encouraging you to keep going, Mistress Natalya continues to gently tap your ass with her riding crop while repeating the fact that you're nothing but a dirty, anal-loving filly. After several minutes of this, you find yourself starting to love the idea of performing anilingus, but before you can really get carried away, Mistress Natalya snaps, [natalya.speech(That's enough, filly! Your real rimjob training will come later! Now drop down and lick [npc.namePos] cock!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_1_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_1_SEX_SUCK_COCK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leaving [npc.namePos] [npc.asshole+] coated in a glistening sheen of your saliva, you drop down beneath [npc.her] feral horse's body and lean forwards to give [npc.her] [npc.cockSize], ebony horse-cock a long, wet lick. Calling out over the clopping sound of [npc.namePos] front hoof pawing at the ground in excitement, Mistress Natalya exclaims, [natalya.speech(That's it, filly! Lick up [npc.her] precum and get a taste of what's to come!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you shuffle around so that your face is positioned in front of [npc.namePos] throbbing cock, before leaning in and licking up the salty precum that's drooling out of [npc.her] urethra. Delighted to see that you're following her instructions, the small [natalya.race] commands, [natalya.speech(Tell me that you love horse-cock, filly! Then open wide and take [npc.her] cock into your mouth!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you pull back a little and shout out, [pc.speech(I love horse-cock, Mistress!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Remembering the second part of Mistress Natalya's command, you quickly open wide and wrap your [pc.lips+] around the wide, flared head of [npc.namePos] cock, before shuffling forwards a little and taking the first few [style.sizes] into your mouth. Letting out a mischievous laugh as she sees that you've started to suck her slave's cock, Mistress Natalya teases, [natalya.speech(Do you know why I chose [npc.name] here to be your training partner, filly? It's because [npc.she] can show you the extreme of what you're expected to be able to deal with! Go on, [npc.name], you have my permission to be as rough as you like with this filly slut! Don't hold back now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can react to Mistress Natalya's revelation, the [npc.name] lets out a deep grunt, before quickly stepping forwards and slamming [npc.her] [npc.cock+] all the way down your throat. Letting out a frantic, gargled choking noise, you do your best to relax your throat muscles and give the [npc.race] a decent blowjob, but your efforts go mostly to waste as [npc.she] starts roughly pumping [npc.her] hips and brutally fucking your face. Over the sounds of [npc.namePos] saliva-coated balls slapping against your chin, you hear Mistress Natalya arrogantly declare, [natalya.speech(This will be good training for you, filly! Please do try and keep your splutters to a bare minimum; I'm going to get some work done while you service [npc.namePos] cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		No matter how much you may want to try and obey your Mistress's request, you can't help but continue to choke and splutter on [npc.namePos] [npc.cockGirth], ebony horse-cock as [npc.she] continues to relentlessly thrust it down your throat...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_1_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_1_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had [npc.her] fun, [npc.name] steps back, sliding [npc.her] fat, feral horse-cock out from your abused throat. Coughing and gasping for breath as a stream of excess cum and saliva drools down from your [pc.lips], you look up just in time to see the uncaring [npc.race] step to one side and slap [npc.her] thick, heavy cock against your face. Letting out a deep grunt, [npc.she] snaps, [npc.speech(Clean me off, you dirty filly slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you lean forwards, and just like you did with Natalya earlier, you begin to clean [npc.namePos] softening cock with your [pc.tongue+]. Just as you get started, you hear Mistress Natalya trotting over to you from behind her desk, before suddenly feeling her riding crop lightly swatting your ass. Letting out an approving humming noise, the small [natalya.race] commends you on your performance, [natalya.speech(Well done, filly! As you can handle [npc.name] here, I'm confident that you'll be able to please all of the other slaves with your mouth. Now be a good filly and show me how much you love swallowing horse-cum!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your Mistress watching, you do as you're told and make a show of eagerly licking up and swallowing every last drop of the slimy mixture of cum and saliva that's coating [npc.namePos] cock. Once you've completely finished cleaning the [npc.race]'s hot shaft, Mistress Natalya whacks [npc.her] ass with her riding crop and commands, [natalya.speech(Run along now, [npc.name]! If you're a good [npc.girl], I'll choose you to help me finish this filly's training!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not even bothering to say anything to you, [npc.name] thrusts [npc.her] hips forwards to roughly rub [npc.her] now-sheathed cock against your face one last time, before stepping over to the door and swiftly exiting the room. Carelessly tossing a cloth down onto the floor in front of you, Mistress Natalya trots back over to her desk and calls out, [natalya.speech(Congratulations, filly; you've finished the first stage of your training! For your next session, I shall be teaching you to really love giving rimjobs, but unfortunately I have no more time for you today. Tell me that you're a good little filly who loves horse-ass and horse-cock, and then be on your way!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_1_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you turn to face Mistress Natalya and confess, [pc.speech(I'm a good filly, Mistress, and I love horse-ass and horse-cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Flashing you an arrogant smirk, the small [natalya.race] gestures towards the door and says, [natalya.speech(Good filly! You're dismissed. Return to me tomorrow so that I may continue with your training.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Quickly pulling on your clothes and heading for the door, you exit Mistress Natalya's office via the same way which you entered. Passing the smartly-dressed horse-girl secretary who's still sitting behind her desk in the small waiting room, you continue on out into the warehouse's corridor and wonder where to go to next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2 -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] around behind Mistress Natalya's desk and kneel down beside her. From this angle, you're able to see that while the [natalya.race]'s large chair is specially designed to accommodate the size and weight of her feral horse-body, it's still able to pivot around on the spot, and as you drop down onto the wooden floor beside you Mistress, she spins around to smirk down at you and declare, [natalya.speech(You're to strip naked again before I start your rimjob training, filly! So get on with it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isAnyEquippedClothingSealed())
				Doing as you're told, you start stripping off your clothes, but have to tell Mistress Natalya that some of them are sealed onto you. Letting out a frustrated sigh, she snaps, [natalya.speech(Hold still, filly! I'll sort that out for you!)] 
			</p>
			<p>
				Before you can respond, the [natalya.race] channels some of her arcane essences into your sealed clothing, removing their enchantment and letting you take them off. Not wanting to annoy your Mistress any further, you strip naked as quickly as you possibly can, before looking up at her and telling her that you're ready.
		#ELSE
				Doing as you're told, you strip naked as quickly as you possibly can, before looking up at your Mistress and telling her that you're ready.
		#ENDIF
	#IF(pc.isAbleToWearMakeup())
			 Hungrily biting her lip as she looks down at your naked body, the [natalya.race] teases, [natalya.speech(You're a pretty little filly, but if you really want to drive all of my big strong boys and girls wild, then you could do with some finishing touches...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Opening the top drawer of her desk, Mistress Natalya produces three brightly-coloured tubes of lipstick, before holding them out towards you and saying, [natalya.speech(With a liberal application of lipstick, I'm sure that you can be made to look like the sort of dirty filly slut who services horse-ass for a living. Select which one you'd like, filly; in just a minute you'll be using your lips to paint my asshole in whichever colour you choose!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking down at the tubes of lipstick, you see that you can choose from a relatively normal matte dark-blue, an attention-grabbing sparkly gold, or a spectacular glowing pink...
		</p>
	#ELSE
			 Hungrily biting her lip as she looks down at your naked body, the [natalya.race] stands up and crudely teases, [natalya.speech(You look like the sort of dirty filly slut who services horse-ass for a living! Now lift up my skirt and get ready to show me that I'm right!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_LIPSTICK_DARK_BLUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'll go with the least garish of the three lipsticks, you point at the matte dark-blue one and tell Mistress Natalya that it's your favourite of the three. Flashing you a slight smile, your Mistress places the other two down on her desk, before taking off the dark-blue lipstick's cap and ordering, [natalya.speech(Hold still, filly! I'll make you look like a dirty slut in no time!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_LIPSTICK_SPARKLY_GOLD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'll go with something a little more exciting than the boring old dark-blue option, you point at the sparkly gold lipstick and tell Mistress Natalya that it's your favourite of the three. Flashing you an amused smile, your Mistress places the other two down on her desk, before taking off the gold lipstick's cap and ordering, [natalya.speech(Hold still, filly! I'll make you look like a dirty slut in no time!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_LIPSTICK_GLOWING_PINK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'll go with the most eye-catching of the three lipsticks, you point at the glowing pink one and tell Mistress Natalya that it's your favourite of the three. Flashing you a delighted smile, your Mistress places the other two down on her desk, before taking off the pink lipstick's cap and ordering, [natalya.speech(Hold still, filly! I'll make you look like a dirty slut in no time!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_MAKEUP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_MAKEUP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you hold still as Mistress Natalya leans down and applies a liberal coating of [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] lipstick to your [pc.lips+]. Once she's done, she grabs a small hand-held mirror from out of her desk's drawer, and with a huge grin on her face, she shows you your [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] [pc.lips] and teases, [natalya.speech(You look like a dirty little slut now, filly! I bet you can't wait to put those whorish lips of yours to good use, so hurry up and pull up my skirt!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_MAKEUP_LIFT_SKIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Standing up, Mistress Natalya impatiently turns around and pushes the rear of her horse's body back towards your face. Doing what's expected of you, you pull up your Mistress's black skirt, revealing not only her [natalya.cockSize] horse-cock and heavy, dangling balls, but also her puffy, ebony asshole. While its doughnut shape is exactly like that of a feral horse's, the [natalya.race]'s asshole is quite clearly demonic in nature, as it's constantly leaking a clear, musky natural lubricant, making it look more like an inviting sexual orifice than a regular asshole.
	</p>
	<p>
		Pushing her thick-rimmed glasses up onto the bridge of her nose, Mistress Natalya looks back over her shoulder at you and commands,
		#IF(pc.isAbleToWearMakeup())
			 [natalya.speech(Go on then, my good little filly; paint my ass [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]!)]
		#ELSE
			 [natalya.speech(Go on then, my good little filly; start kissing my ass!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_MAKEUP_RELUCTANT_KISSES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not entirely sure about this, you hold back a little as you lean in to plant a quick kiss on Mistress Natalya's puffy, ebony asshole. Sensing your hesitation, the [natalya.race] takes a step back, forcefully pushing her feral hindquarters against your face and smothering your mouth with her slimy, demonic rear-entrance. As you let out a surprised, muffled gasp, your Mistress shouts, [natalya.speech(You'll have to do better than that, filly! Pretend that you're being kissed by one of my hot
		#IF(pc.getSexualOrientation().isAttractedToFeminine())
			 centauress slaves!
		#ELSE
			 centaur slaves!
		#ENDIF
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your Mistress's ass smothering your face, you have little choice but to do as she says, and, pretending that you're making out with
		#IF(pc.getSexualOrientation().isAttractedToFeminine())
			 a beautiful centauress
		#ELSE
			 a hunky centaur
		#ENDIF
		, you close your eyes and force yourself to passionately kiss her hot, puffy asshole. As you lewdly press your
		#IF(pc.isAbleToWearMakeup())
			 [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] [pc.lips]
		#ELSE
			 [pc.lips+]
		#ENDIF
		 against her ebony doughnut, the small [natalya.race] lets out an excited whinny, before moaning,
		#IF(pc.isAbleToWearMakeup())
			 [natalya.speech(That's it, filly! ~Mmm!~ Paint my ass [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]! ~Ooh!~ Tell me that you love horse-ass, you dirty little slut!)]
		#ELSE
			 [natalya.speech(That's it, filly! ~Mmm!~ Tell me that you love horse-ass, you dirty little slut!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Surprised to be finding yourself enjoying this experience more and more, you reluctantly break off from your kiss, before obediently [pc.moaning], [pc.speech(I love horse-ass, Mistress! ~Mmm!~ I love your ass!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Burying your face in her ass, you eagerly start planting kiss after kiss on the [natalya.race]'s puffy, ebony asshole. Pushing her hips back and forcefully grinding her slimy doughnut against your [pc.lips+], she bites her lip and lets out an excited, high-pitched squeal, before ordering, [natalya.speech(Get your tongue in there, filly! ~Ooh!~ You're going to make me cum from this!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_MAKEUP_EAGER_KISSES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		More than happy to do as you're told, you eagerly lean in to plant a wet, passionate kiss on Mistress Natalya's puffy, ebony asshole. With a happy little cry, the [natalya.race] responds to your move by taking a step back, forcefully pushing her feral hindquarters against your face and smothering your mouth with her slimy, demonic rear-entrance. As you let out a surprised, muffled gasp, your Mistress shouts, [natalya.speech(That's my good filly! Keep on kissing my ass, you dirty little anal-loving slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your Mistress's ass smothering your face, you have little choice but to do as she says, and you happily continue to kiss her hot, puffy asshole. As you lewdly press your
		#IF(pc.isAbleToWearMakeup())
			 [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] [pc.lips]
		#ELSE
			 [pc.lips+]
		#ENDIF
		 against her ebony doughnut, the small [natalya.race] lets out an excited whinny, before moaning,
		#IF(pc.isAbleToWearMakeup())
			 [natalya.speech(That's it, filly! ~Mmm!~ Paint my ass [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] with your [pc.lips]! ~Ooh!~ Tell me that you love horse-ass, you dirty little slut!)]
		#ELSE
			 [natalya.speech(That's it, filly! ~Mmm!~ Tell me that you love horse-ass, you dirty little slut!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to stop, you reluctantly break off from your kiss, before [pc.moaning], [pc.speech(I love horse-ass, Mistress! ~Mmm!~ I love your ass!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not being able to help yourself, you immediately bury your face in her ass, before planting kiss after kiss on the [natalya.race]'s puffy, ebony asshole. Pushing her hips back and forcefully grinding her slimy doughnut against your [pc.lips+], she bites her lip and lets out an excited, high-pitched squeal, before ordering, [natalya.speech(Get your tongue in there, filly! ~Ooh!~ You're going to make me cum from this!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_MAKEUP_ANILINGUS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_MAKEUP_ANILINGUS_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself feeling extremely aroused and desperate to continue making out with Mistress Natalya's ass, you eagerly do as you're told and immediately thrust your [pc.tongue+] into her puffy, ebony asshole.
		#IF(pc.isAbleToWearMakeup())
			 As your [pc.lips+] continue to paint your Mistress's horse-like asshole a delightful shade of [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0], the small [natalya.race] lets out a particularly lewd moan and cries out, [natalya.speech(~Aah!~ Yes! That's my good filly! ~Ooh!~ Show me that you're a dirty anal-loving filly slut! ~Aah!~ Keep going!)]
		#ELSE
			 As your [pc.lips+] press up against your Mistress's horse-like asshole, the small [natalya.race] lets out a particularly lewd moan and cries out, [natalya.speech(~Aah!~ Yes! That's my good filly! ~Ooh!~ Show me that you're a dirty anal-loving filly slut! ~Aah!~ Keep going!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you continue passionately making out with Mistress Natalya's slimy, doughnut-shaped asshole, determined to make her cum from your oral attention alone...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having emptied her huge, ebony balls all over the floor, Mistress Natalya lets out a deeply-satisfied sigh and steps forwards, leaving you kneeling down on the floor of her office panting and gasping for breath. Making good use of the hand-held mirror still sitting on her desk, Mistress Natalya looks back over her shoulder to take a look at the reflection of her puffy, saliva-coated asshole. Liking what she sees, she lets out a small laugh and comments,
		#IF(pc.isAbleToWearMakeup())
			 [natalya.speech(My ass looks good in [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1], doesn't it, filly?)]
		#ELSE
			 [natalya.speech(You've made a real slimy mess of my asshole, haven't you, filly?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking up at your Mistress's doughnut-like rear-entrance, you pant, [pc.speech(Yes, Mistress...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(With skills like yours, I'm sure that you'll be a popular filly ass-licker amongst the slaves,)] your Mistress teases, before stepping back and once again pushing her slimy asshole up against your face. Looking back over her shoulder to flash you a triumphant smirk, she commands, [natalya.speech(Clean me off, filly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Once again doing as you're told, you spend a few minutes licking the excess saliva off Mistress Natalya's ass, before moving down to clean her softening horse-cock with your mouth. Once you've obediently lapped up all of her excess sexual fluids, Mistress Natalya orders you to pull her skirt back down, before declaring, [natalya.speech(That will be all for today, filly. Your next training session will involve repeating your performance on [npc.name], while I mount you and give your ass a good rutting. After that, I'll have [npc.name] mount you, and then you'll be ready to receive your choker and become a fully qualified filly. I'm unfortunately going to be busy for the rest of today, so come back and see me again tomorrow for the last stage of your training!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_2_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With your rimjob training now complete, you quickly pull on your clothes and head for the door, exiting Mistress Natalya's office via the same way which you entered. Passing the smartly-dressed horse-girl secretary who's still sitting behind her desk in the small waiting room, you continue on out into the warehouse's corridor and wonder where to go to next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3 -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] around behind Mistress Natalya's desk and kneel down beside her. Just like the last time you were in this position, the small [natalya.race] spins around on her specially-designed chair and demands, [natalya.speech(You're to strip naked again before we can proceed with the final stage of your training, filly! So get on with it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isAnyEquippedClothingSealed())
				Doing as you're told, you start stripping off your clothes, but have to tell Mistress Natalya that some of them are sealed onto you. Letting out a frustrated sigh, she snaps, [natalya.speech(Hold still, filly! I'll sort that out for you!)] 
			</p>
			<p>
				Before you can respond, the [natalya.race] channels some of her arcane essences into your sealed clothing, removing their enchantment and letting you take them off. Not wanting to annoy your Mistress any further, you strip naked as quickly as you possibly can, before looking up at her and telling her that you're ready.
		#ELSE
				Doing as you're told, you strip naked as quickly as you possibly can, before looking up at your Mistress and telling her that you're ready.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(What a good little filly you are,)] your Mistress states, before standing up and prances over to the door. Turning to look back at you, she commands, [natalya.speech(Wait there while I go and fetch [npc.name]! Remember, you'll be eating [npc.her] ass today while I give you a good rutting!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Mistress Natalya trots out of the office, leaving you naked and kneeling on the floor beside her desk...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_SLAVE_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		No more than five minutes later, Mistress Natalya steps back into the office, with the familiar, imposing figure of [npc.name] following only a few steps behind. Using one of [npc.her] large rear hooves to kick the door closed behind [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] catches sight of your naked figure and flashes you an evil, hungry smirk. Seeing that you're still kneeling where she left you, Mistress Natalya grins as she exclaims, [natalya.speech(Good filly! Now crawl over here and show [npc.name] and I that you're ready to complete your training!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the small [natalya.race] leans back to pull up her skirt, before turning around and presenting you with her feral hindquarters. Flicking her tail to one side, she grants you an unobstructed view of her puffy, ebony asshole, which, thanks to the fact that it's glistening with natural lubricant, looks more like an inviting sexual orifice than a regular horse's asshole.
	</p>
	<p>
		Following Mistress Natalya's example, [npc.name] turns around and stands side-by side with the [natalya.race], before flicking [npc.her] tail aside in order to present you with [npc.her] feral horse-anus. Seeing these two taurs side-by-side, you're once again struck by the fact that your Mistress is especially small for a taur, and is over
		#IF(game.isMetricSizes())
			 sixty centimetres 
		#ELSE
			 two feet
		#ENDIF
		 shorter than the [npc.race] beside her. Not wanting to spend too much time making comparisons between the two of them, you start to crawl over to the pair of puffy, ebony assholes being presented to you, and as you do so, Mistress Natalya looks back over her shoulder and commands, [natalya.speech(Kiss mine first, filly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you shuffle up behind Mistress Natalya, before leaning in and planting a big, wet kiss on her slimy demonic asshole. As your [pc.lips+] make contact with her puffy doughnut, your prior training kicks in, and before you know what you're doing, you find yourself passionately tonguing her hot horse-anus. Letting out a delighted whinny, the small [natalya.race] steps forwards, before trotting around to face you and declare, [natalya.speech(You're an eager little filly, aren't you?! Now show [npc.name] what a dirty little slut you are for horse-ass!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eager to do as you're told, you move over to kneel behind [npc.name], before leaning in towards [npc.her] feral hindquarters. As you draw nearer, you see that [npc.her] asshole is very similar in appearance to Mistress Natalya's, as although it's lacking any naturally-occurring lubricant, it's every bit as puffy and dark-black as the [natalya.race]'s. Not being able to help yourself, you push your face into the [npc.race]'s ass and desperately start kissing [npc.her] hot, musky asshole.
	</p>
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(That's my good little filly slut!)] Mistress Natalya calls out from somewhere behind you, before you suddenly feel a huge weight pressing down on your back. Much to your dismay, you find your [pc.lips] being forced away from [npc.namePos] ass as you're pushed down onto the floor, and, looking back, you see that your Mistress has just mounted you. Before you can react, you feel the slimy, precum-coated head of the [natalya.race]'s huge horse-cock pressing against your exposed asshole, and she exclaims, [natalya.speech(I can see that you're a slut for horse-ass, but I need to know that you crave the feeling of being rutted by horse-cock! Tell me that you want me to pound your cute little butt, filly!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_SLAVE_ENTRY_OBEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you're not completely sure that you want it, you nevertheless do as Mistress Natalya commands and beg, [pc.speech(Please, Mistress, fuck my ass...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Picking up on the fact that you're a little reluctant to complete the final stage of your training, Mistress Natalya snaps, [natalya.speech(Don't worry, filly, I'll soon show you how good it feels to have your ass rutted! You don't need to be able to talk during this, so if you'd be so kind, [npc.name], let this little filly continue working on your butt!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_SLAVE_ENTRY_EAGERLY_OBEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Desperate to be anally rutted by your Mistress, you enthusiastically cry out, [pc.speech(Please, Mistress! Mount me and pound my ass!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Delighted to hear that you're eager to complete the final stage of your training, Mistress Natalya teases, [natalya.speech(That's my good little filly! I'm sure you're just going to love how it feels to have your ass rutted! You don't need to be able to talk during this, so if you'd be so kind, [npc.name], let this little filly continue working on your butt!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_SLAVE_ENTRY_OBEY_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Before you can react, [npc.name] drops down into a kneeing position and immediately shuffles back, forcefully pushing [npc.her] puffy, saliva-coated asshole into your face. Letting your previous training take over, you eagerly resume where you left off just a minute ago, and after planting a passionate kiss on [npc.her] ebony doughnut, you bury your face into the [npc.race]'s ass and start greedily tonguing [npc.her] puffy asshole.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you start giving [npc.name] your oral attention, you feel the flat, flared head of Mistress Natalya's huge horse-cock once again pressing down against your ass. Taking a few moments to spread a copious amount of precum all over your [pc.asshole+], the small [natalya.race] lets out a high-pitched whinny and rams her [natalya.cockGirth] horse-cock into your rear entrance. This forceful motion causes your face to be pushed forwards into [npc.namePos] musky asshole, and you find yourself letting out a muffled moan as Mistress Natalya triumphantly squeals, [natalya.speech(~Mmm!~ Your ass feels so good, filly! ~Ooh!~ You like the feeling of being a dirty little buttslut, don't you?! Go on, filly, push back and take it deeper!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_FUCKED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_FUCKED_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself loving the feeling of being anally rutted by Mistress Natalya, you do as she commands and start pushing your hips back, forcing [natalya.her] hot, feral horse-cock deep into your rear entrance. Feeling that your focus has shifted away from giving [npc.herHim] a rimjob, [npc.name] impatiently shuffles back and forcefully grinds [npc.her] puffy ebony doughnut against your [pc.lips+], grunting, [npc.speech(Get your tongue in there, you dirty filly slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you start passionately tonguing [npc.namePos] musky horse-anus, while simultaneously pushing your hips back and helping Mistress Natalya to sink her throbbing cock deep into your back door...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having well and truly emptied her huge, ebony balls into your ass, Mistress Natalya pulls back, letting a huge gush of demonic horse-cum stream out of your well-fucked asshole. Happily trotting around to watch you plant a final few wet kisses on [npc.namePos] puffy, saliva-coated asshole, she declares, [natalya.speech(Your training is almost complete, filly! All that's left is for you to have your ass rutted by [npc.name] here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking the hint, [npc.name] stands up, taking [npc.her] asshole away from your [pc.lips] and revealing a huge pool of cum beneath where [npc.she] was lying down. Glancing down at the mess that her slave has made, Mistress Natalya teases, [natalya.speech(It looks like you're all spent, [npc.name]! I wouldn't want this little filly to miss out on the feeling of having you pump [pc.her] ass full of your cum, so come over here and drink this!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaving you panting on the floor of the office, with cum still leaking out of your well-fucked asshole, [npc.name] follows Mistress Natalya over to her desk, where [npc.sheIs] given a bottle of rejuvenation potion. Quickly downing all of the liquid, [npc.name] lets out a deep grunt and states, [npc.speech(Thank you, Mistress. I'm ready to rut that filly slut now.)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(I am pleased to hear that,)] the [natalya.race] replies, before trotting over to sit behind her desk. Flashing you a smug smirk, she orders, [natalya.speech(Present your ass, filly! [npc.Name] here is going to give you a good, hard pounding!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_AFTER_SEX_ROUND_TWO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Obediently doing as you're told, you lift your ass and present yourself to [npc.name]. Letting out a deep grunt, [npc.she] quickly trots over to where you're kneeling down on the floor, before swiftly mounting you and dropping [npc.her] [npc.cockGirth], ebony horse-cock down to prod at your cum-stuffed asshole.
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing what's expected of you, you push your hips back, guiding the flat, flared head of [npc.namePos] feral horse-cock into your [pc.asshole+]. Immediately, the eager [npc.race] thrusts forwards, roughly ramming [npc.her] hot, throbbing shaft as deep as possible into your abused rear entrance. With Mistress Natalya watching you from the other side of the room, you submit to [npc.namePos] cock and enjoy the experience of getting anally rutted by such a big, strong [npc.race]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_AFTER_SEX_SECOND -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_AFTER_SEX_SECOND"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Mistress Natalya's example and having emptied [npc.her] huge, feral balls into your ass, [npc.name] steps back, letting you collapse down onto the floor and gasp for breath. Trotting over to smirk down at the stream of thick, musky horse-cum leaking from your abused asshole, Mistress Natalya happily declares, [natalya.speech(Congratulations! You've finished your training and are now a fully qualified filly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning towards [npc.name], the small [natalya.race] makes a dismissive gesture with her hand and says, [natalya.speech(I have no more need for you, [npc.name]. Get back to work!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning about on the spot, [npc.name] swiftly exits the office without even giving you so much as a goodbye, leaving you and Mistress Natalya alone together. Looking up at the [natalya.race], you see that she's holding a black choker in one hand, and she proudly lifts it up to show off the fact that there are several bold bronze letters attached to it, spelling out the word 'filly'. Stepping towards you, your Mistress orders, [natalya.speech(Show me your neck, filly, so that you can proudly wear this!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_CHOKER_EQUIPPED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_CHOKER_EQUIPPED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Lifting your head and submissively presenting your neck to Mistress Natalya, you hold still and let her strap the filly choker around your neck. The instant she straps it into place, you feel that it's been enchanted, and not only is it now sealed into place around your neck, but it's also making you feel a lot more submissive. Letting out an involuntary whine, you look up to see an amused smile settle on your Mistress's face.
	</p>
	[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(Your duty from now on is to sexually service the slaves here in Dominion Express, just as I've taught you to,)] she declares, before explaining, [natalya.speech(As you've no doubt noticed, your filly choker currently has bronze lettering. As I told you during your interview, there's a points-based reward system in place for you fillies, which allows you to rank up from bronze to silver, and then to gold. Centaur slaves are given points by working hard, which they can then give to you in exchange for having you sexually service them. Are you understanding all of this, filly?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, Mistress,)] you reply, [pc.speech(I'll be able to rank up my filly choker by earning points from sexually servicing slaves...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[natalya.speech(Good filly,)] the small [natalya.race] replies, before trotting over to her desk and retrieving a handful of small, glowing-pink beads. Holding them up for you to see, she explains, [natalya.speech(These are what will be given to you; they're specially enchanted beads which will be absorbed by your choker. For being such a good filly, I'll start you off with these ten points.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Mistress Natalya tosses the beads down on the floor in front of you, and before you can make a move to pick them up, they suddenly disintegrate into pure arcane energy, before shooting up and being absorbed by your filly choker. Flashing you an amused grin, Mistress Natalya reveals, [natalya.speech(As you've most likely already seen, there's a filly rewards station just down the corridor from my office. The arcane machines which you'll find there will be able to tell you how many points you currently have, as well as administer rewards from a special points shop. I should also mention that now your training is complete, you will no longer be allowed to sexually service me, unless you earn enough points to rank up to silver or gold.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Gesturing for you to stand up, the small [natalya.race] concludes by warning, [natalya.speech(You will lose two points at the stroke of midnight every day, meaning that you need to stay busy servicing centaur slaves to keep your points count up. All filly points are also completely reset to zero at the beginning of each month. If you need to be told how this system works again, there's a poster at the filly rewards station which you can read. Now, if you have no questions, you'd better get out there and start earning points!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_CHOKER_EQUIPPED_AMBER_SPECIAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Looking over at your pile of discarded clothing, and in particular focusing her gaze on the 'Amber's Bitch' collar which was previously fastened around your neck, your new Mistress sneers, [natalya.speech(I don't know who 'Amber' is, but you're <i>my</i> bitch now, filly! Do you understand?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a submissive whine, you tell Mistress Natalya that you're happy to be her bitch, which causes her to arrogantly smirk down at you and let out a victorious little chuckle.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_TRAINING_3_CHOKER_EQUIPPED_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Understanding everything that Mistress Natalya's said, you don't need to ask her any questions, and so you quickly pull on your clothes and head for the door. Swiftly exiting your Mistress's office, you pass the smartly-dressed horse-girl secretary who's still sitting behind her desk in the small waiting room, before continuing on out into the warehouse's corridor.
	</p>
	<p>
		With the filly choker securely fastened around your neck, you wonder whether you should head directly to the stables and start servicing the centaur slaves, or instead take some time to check out the filly rewards station which Mistress Natalya told you about...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_GIVE_BLOWJOB -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_GIVE_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get another taste of your Mistress's cock, you ask her if she'll let you give her a blowjob. Arrogantly smirking at you as she hears you say this, the small [natalya.race] responds by stepping around from behind her desk and demanding, [natalya.speech(If that's what you want, you little filly slut, then come over here and lift my skirt!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you quickly [pc.step] forwards and drop down beside Mistress Natalya, before lifting her skirt to reveal her rapidly-hardening horse-cock and naturally-lubricated, puffy asshole. Turning around to push her ass towards your face, the dominant [natalya.race] looks back over her shoulder to smirk and demand, [natalya.speech(Kiss my ass, you dirty little filly, and then you can suck my cock!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_GIVE_BLOWJOB_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again doing as you're told, you lean in to plant a big, wet kiss on your Mistress's ebony, slimy asshole. Letting out a delighted whinny as she feels your [pc.lips+] press against her ass, your Mistress impatiently paws at the ground with one of her front hooves and moans, [natalya.speech(~Ooh!~ Good filly! Now get under me and show my cock some love!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to do as your Mistress commands, you drop down beneath her feral horse's body, before leaning forwards to deliver a hot, wet lick to the flared head of her erect horse-cock. Smiling as you hear the small [natalya.race] let out yet another delighted moan, you open wide and take her cock into your mouth, before starting to give her an enthusiastic blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_GIVE_RIMJOB -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_GIVE_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get another taste of your Mistress's ass, you ask her if she'll let you give her a rimjob. Arrogantly smirking at you as she hears you say this, the small [natalya.race] responds by stepping around from behind her desk and demanding, [natalya.speech(If that's what you want, you dirty little filly, then get over here and lift my skirt!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you quickly [pc.step] forwards and drop down beside Mistress Natalya, before lifting her skirt to reveal her rapidly-hardening horse-cock and naturally-lubricated, puffy asshole. Turning around to push her ass towards your face, the dominant [natalya.race] looks back over her shoulder to smirk and say, [natalya.speech(Go on then, you little filly slut! Kiss my ass!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_GIVE_RIMJOB_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again doing as you're told, you lean in to plant a big, wet kiss on your Mistress's ebony, slimy asshole. Letting out a delighted whinny as she feels your [pc.lips+] press against her ass, your Mistress impatiently paws at the ground with one of her front hooves and moans, [natalya.speech(~Ooh!~ Good filly! Get your tongue in there, you dirty slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to do as your Mistress commands, you press your [pc.lips+] against her hot, puffy asshole, before thrusting your [pc.tongue+] into her rear entrance. The small [natalya.race] lets out yet another delighted moan in response to your oral attention, which encourages you to continue giving her a sloppy, enthusiastic rimjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_GET_MOUNTED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_GET_MOUNTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get another feel of your Mistress's cock, you ask her if she'll mount you and give you a good, hard anal rutting. Arrogantly smirking at you as she hears you say this, the small [natalya.race] responds by stepping around from behind her desk and demanding, [natalya.speech(If that's what you want, you little filly slut, then come over here and lift my skirt!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you quickly [pc.step] forwards and drop down beside Mistress Natalya, before lifting her skirt to reveal her rapidly-hardening horse-cock and naturally-lubricated, puffy asshole. Turning around to push her ass towards your face, the dominant [natalya.race] looks back over her shoulder to smirk and demand, [natalya.speech(Kiss my ass, you dirty little filly, and then I'll give you what you want!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_GET_MOUNTED_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again doing as you're told, you lean in to plant a big, wet kiss on your Mistress's ebony, slimy asshole. Letting out a delighted whinny as she feels your [pc.lips+] press against her ass, your Mistress impatiently paws at the ground with one of her front hooves and moans, [natalya.speech(~Ooh!~ Good filly! Now present yourself so that I can mount you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to do as your Mistress commands, you turn around and drop down onto all fours, presenting your [pc.asshole+] to her huge, erect horse-cock. Wasting no time at all, the [natalya.race] immediately moves forwards and mounts you, before impatiently prodding the flat, flared head of her feral cock against your [pc.asshole+]. Letting out yet a delighted whinny, Mistress Natalya quickly thrusts forwards, pushing her [natalya.cockGirth] horse-cock into your ass and starting to desperately rut you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_RECEIVE_BLOWJOB -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_RECEIVE_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to make good use of the fact that you're Dominion Express's only gold-ranked filly, you present your [pc.cock+] to Mistress Natalya and order her to give you a blowjob. Knowing that she's bound by the terms of her contract, the dominant [natalya.race] reluctantly steps around from behind her desk and sinks down onto the floor before you. Looking up at you with a scowl on her face, she snaps, [natalya.speech(I can't believe you're making me do this, you bad little filly! Don't let it go to your head; I'm still your Mistress!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_RECEIVE_BLOWJOB_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to give Mistress Natalya any more time in which to complain to you about her situation, you buck your hips forwards, forcing the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+] past her [natalya.lips+] and into her mouth. Much to your surprise and delight, the [natalya.race] reacts by leaning forwards and taking your cock deep down her throat. Clearly having accepted the fact that she's got to submit to you and service your cock, your Mistress starts expertly bobbing her head up and down, letting out a series of spluttering, gargled moans as she gives you the blowjob that you asked for...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_RECEIVE_RIMJOB -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_RECEIVE_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to make good use of the fact that you're Dominion Express's only gold-ranked filly, you present your [pc.ass+] to Mistress Natalya and order her to give you a rimjob. Knowing that she's bound by the terms of her contract, the dominant [natalya.race] reluctantly steps around from behind her desk and sinks down onto the floor behind you. With an angry scowl on her face, she snaps, [natalya.speech(I can't believe you're making me do this, you bad little filly! Don't let it go to your head; I'm still your Mistress!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_RECEIVE_RIMJOB_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to give Mistress Natalya any more time in which to complain to you about her situation, you push your hips back, forcing your [pc.ass+] into her face and smothering her [natalya.lips+] with your [pc.asshole+]. Much to your surprise and delight, the [natalya.race] reacts by planting a big, wet kiss on your [pc.asshole+], before greedily thrusting her tongue into your ass. Clearly having accepted the fact that she's got to submit to you and service your ass, your Mistress starts expertly kissing and licking your [pc.asshole+], letting out a series of wet, muffled moans as she gives you the rimjob that you asked for...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_MOUNT_HER -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_MOUNT_HER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to make good use of the fact that you're Dominion Express's only gold-ranked filly, you show off your [pc.cock+] to Mistress Natalya and order her to present her asshole to you so that you can give her a good, hard rutting. Knowing that she's bound by the terms of her contract, the dominant [natalya.race] reluctantly steps around from behind her desk, before turning her back on you and sinking down onto the floor. Pulling up her skirt to expose her puffy, naturally-lubricated asshole, she looks back over her shoulder with a scowl on her face, before snapping, [natalya.speech(I can't believe you're making me do this, you bad little filly! Don't let it go to your head; I'm still your Mistress!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_MOUNT_HER_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to give Mistress Natalya any more time in which to complain to you about her situation, you quickly mount her, before pressing the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+] against her puffy, slimy asshole and thrusting into her ass. Much to your surprise and delight, the [natalya.race] reacts by pushing back against you, letting out a horny moan as she helps to sink your [pc.cock+] deep into her rear entrance. The feeling of having your Mistress's feral, ebony asshole squeezing down around your cock sends you wild with lust, and you can't help but start to desperately rut her ass. Making a wet, slapping noise with every thrust, you join your Mistress in letting out a series of passionate moans as you fuck her on the floor of her office...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_AFTER_SEX_AS_SUB -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_AFTER_SEX_AS_SUB_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out one final high-pitched moan, Mistress Natalya steps back, withdrawing her cock from your throat and letting a mixture of cum and saliva splatter down onto the floor. Pushing her thick-rimmed glasses up onto the bridge of her nose, she smirks down at you and commands, [natalya.speech(Clean my cock off, filly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you lean back in towards the [natalya.race]'s softening horse-cock and obediently lick all of the cum and saliva off of its hot length. Once you've finished your task, your Mistress orders you to pull her skirt back down, before prancing over to sit behind her desk and exclaim, [natalya.speech(What a good filly slut you are! Now, is there anything else which you needed?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_AFTER_SEX_AS_SUB_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out one final high-pitched moan, Mistress Natalya steps forwards, taking her puffy, slimy asshole away from your mouth. Pushing her thick-rimmed glasses up onto the bridge of her nose, she looks back over her shoulder to smirk down at you and command, [natalya.speech(Clean my ass off, filly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you lean back in towards the [natalya.race]'s feral hindquarters, before starting to lick all of the excess saliva off of her feral, ebony doughnut. Once you've finished your task, your Mistress orders you to pull her skirt back down, before prancing over to sit behind her desk and exclaim, [natalya.speech(What a good filly slut you are! Now, is there anything else which you needed?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_AFTER_SEX_AS_SUB_MOUNTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out one final high-pitched moan, Mistress Natalya dismounts you and steps back, withdrawing her cock from your well-rutted asshole and letting a big dollop of thick cum splatter down onto the floor. Pushing her thick-rimmed glasses up onto the bridge of her nose, she smirks down at you and commands, [natalya.speech(Come over here and clean my cock off, filly!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you crawl over and lean in towards the [natalya.race]'s softening horse-cock, before obediently licking all of the cum off of its hot length. Once you've finished your task, your Mistress orders you to pull her skirt back down, before prancing over to sit behind her desk and exclaim, [natalya.speech(What a good little filly buttslut you are! Now, is there anything else which you needed?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_AFTER_SEX_AS_DOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_AFTER_SEX_AS_DOM_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun, you take your cock away from Mistress Natalya's mouth, before telling her that she did a good job of submissively giving you a blowjob.
		#IF(natalya.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			 Letting out a deeply-satisfied sigh, your Mistress looks up at you with a big smile on her face and admits, [natalya.speech(I enjoyed that, filly... D-Don't go getting used to this, though! I'm still your Mistress!)]
		#ELSE
			 Letting out a frustrated whine, your Mistress looks up at you and complains, [natalya.speech(You didn't even let me satisfy myself, you bad filly... I-I can't believe that you'd do this to your Mistress!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking very bashful and humiliated, the small [natalya.race] stands up and trots over to sit down behind her desk, before pushing her thick-rimmed glasses up onto the bridge of her nose and stuttering, [natalya.speech(S-So, is there anything else which you needed, filly?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_AFTER_SEX_AS_DOM_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun, you take your ass away from Mistress Natalya's mouth, before telling her that she did a good job of submissively giving you a rimjob.
		#IF(natalya.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			 Letting out a deeply-satisfied sigh, your Mistress looks up at you with a big smile on her face and admits, [natalya.speech(I enjoyed that, filly... D-Don't go getting used to this, though! I'm still your Mistress!)]
		#ELSE
			 Letting out a frustrated whine, your Mistress looks up at you and complains, [natalya.speech(You didn't even let me satisfy myself, you bad filly... I-I can't believe that you'd do this to your Mistress!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking very bashful and humiliated, the small [natalya.race] stands up and trots over to sit down behind her desk, before pushing her thick-rimmed glasses up onto the bridge of her nose and stuttering, [natalya.speech(S-So, is there anything else which you needed, filly?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_STABLE_FILLY_AFTER_SEX_AS_DOM_MOUNTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun, you take your cock away from Mistress Natalya's well-fucked asshole, before telling her that she did a good job of submissively letting you rut her ass.
		#IF(natalya.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			 Letting out a deeply-satisfied sigh, your Mistress looks up at you with a big smile on her face and admits, [natalya.speech(I enjoyed that, filly... D-Don't go getting used to this, though! I'm still your Mistress!)]
		#ELSE
			 Letting out a frustrated whine, your Mistress looks up at you and complains, [natalya.speech(You didn't even let me satisfy myself, you bad filly... I-I can't believe that you'd do this to your Mistress!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking very bashful and humiliated, the small [natalya.race] stands up and trots over to sit down behind her desk, before pushing her thick-rimmed glasses up onto the bridge of her nose and stuttering, [natalya.speech(S-So, is there anything else which you needed, filly?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
</dialogue>
