<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- WAREHOUSE_DISTRICT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WAREHOUSE_DISTRICT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While there are countless industrial buildings scattered all throughout Dominion, there's no higher concentration of them than in the place you currently find yourself travelling through. The official name for this area is proudly displayed in several places as being simply 'Dominion's Warehouse District', which, while being somewhat generic, very accurately describes it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Most of the buildings you see around you are constructed of either red brick or corrugated iron, and almost without exception they have numerous centaur-drawn carts parked outside of them.
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
				 Thanks to its strategic position right next to Dominion's canal and near to one of the main boulevards, this area is typically heaving with industrial traffic, but due to the ongoing arcane storm, all activity has come to a halt, leaving the entire area completely deserted.
			#ELSE
				 Thanks to its strategic position right next to Dominion's canal and near to one of the main boulevards, this area is absolutely heaving with industrial traffic, and you often have to step aside to let goods-filled carts rumble past.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
				 Thanks to its strategic position right next to Dominion's canal and near to one of the main boulevards, this area is typically heaving with industrial traffic, but due to the ongoing arcane storm, all activity has come to a halt, leaving the entire area completely deserted.
			#ELSE
				 Thanks to its strategic position right next to Dominion's canal and near to one of the main boulevards, a large quantity of industrial traffic is still moving through here, even despite the time of day.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WAREHOUSE_DISTRICT_NO_BUSINESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although there are plenty of businesses established in this area, they're of the kind which only provide services to other large companies. With nothing being on offer to passing members of the public, and without having a specific reason to be here, there's not much for you to do except continue on your way elsewhere...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
</dialogue>