<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- Pre-bad end stripping: -->
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_FLAMES_TOP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having willingly signed yourself into becoming her slave, you happily obey your new owner's command, and begin by giving her all [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] of your flames. Although she takes care to not show too much emotion, as well as the fact that she must already be very wealthy from this farm's profits, Evelyx goes wide-eyed as she sees how rich you were. Letting out a very happy humming noise, she greedily snatches the money from you, before securely locking it away in a safe positioned beneath her desk. Giving you a happy smile, she gloats, [evelyx.speech(I'm a very, very wealthy succubus now, thanks to you. What a good, obedient slave cow you are, to have willingly signed yourself into my possession with so much money to your name! Good slave. Yes, <i>very</i> good slave.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_FLAMES_RICH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having willingly signed yourself into becoming her slave, you happily obey your new owner's command, and begin by giving her all [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] of your flames. Although she takes care to not show too much emotion, as well as the fact that she must already be very wealthy from this farm's profits, Evelyx can't help but grin as she sees how rich you were. Letting out a happy humming noise, she greedily snatches the money from you, before securely locking it away in a safe positioned beneath her desk. Giving you an approving smirk, she gloats, [evelyx.speech(I'm a very wealthy succubus now, thanks to you. What a good, obedient slave cow you are, to have willingly signed yourself into my possession with so much money to your name! Good slave. Yes, <i>very</i> good slave.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_FLAMES_LOTS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having willingly signed yourself into becoming her slave, you happily obey your new owner's command, and begin by giving her all [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] of your flames. Although she takes care to not show too much emotion, as well as the fact that she must already be very wealthy from this farm's profits, Evelyx can't help but let a slight smile settle on her face as she sees how much money you were carrying. Letting out an approving humming noise, she greedily snatches the flames from you, before securely locking them away in a safe positioned beneath her desk. Flashing you a smirk, she gloats, [evelyx.speech(What a good, obedient slave cow you are, to have willingly signed yourself into my possession with so much money to your name. Good slave.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_FLAMES_AVERAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having willingly signed yourself into becoming her slave, you happily obey your new owner's command, and begin by giving her all [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] of your flames. As she's already very wealthy form the profits of this farm, she doesn't seem at all impressed by how much money you had on you. Letting out a brief humming noise, she greedily snatches the flames from you, before securely locking them away in a safe positioned beneath her desk. Straightening back up, she gloats, [evelyx.speech(What a good, obedient slave cow you are, to have willingly signed yourself into my possession with this money to your name. Good slave.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_FLAMES_POOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having willingly signed yourself into becoming her slave, you happily obey your new owner's command, and begin by giving her all [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] of your flames. As she's already very wealthy form the profits of this farm, she seems very disappointed by how little money you had on you. Letting out a disapproving humming noise, she nevertheless greedily snatches the flames from you, before securely locking them away in a safe positioned beneath her desk. Straightening back up, she gloats, [evelyx.speech(You're a good, obedient slave cow, to have willingly signed yourself into my possession, but I do with that you'd been a little more wealthy.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_CLOTHING_START_SEALS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With that out of the way, you move on to stripping naked, before handing over all of your clothing, weapons, and items. The seals on your clothing do nothing to prevent Evelyx from getting her hands on them, as she simply channels some of her essences into each item and quickly strips them from your body.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_CLOTHING_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With that out of the way, you move on to stripping naked, before handing over all of your clothing, weapons, and items.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_CLOTHING_TOP"><![CDATA[
		 Laying your possessions out over the office floor, your owner fails to suppress an excited giggle before declaring, [evelyx.speech(Once I've pawned all of this off in Dominion, I'll be so rich! You really are a good slave cow, to have given me all this.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_CLOTHING_RICH"><![CDATA[
		 Laying your possessions out over the office floor, your owner fails to suppress a delighted hum before declaring, [evelyx.speech(Once I've pawned all of this off in Dominion, I'll be very rich indeed. You really are a good slave cow, to have given me all this.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_CLOTHING_LOTS"><![CDATA[
		 Laying your possessions out over the office floor, your owner fails to suppress an approving hum before declaring, [evelyx.speech(I'll earn a decent amount of flames once I've pawned all of this off in Dominion. You really are a good slave cow, to have given me all this.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_CLOTHING_AVERAGE"><![CDATA[
		 Laying your possessions out over the office floor, your owner fails to suppress a disapproving tut before declaring, [evelyx.speech(It'll barely be worth the hassle to pawn all of this off in Dominion. You are a good slave cow, but I do wish that you'd have had a few more possessions to your name.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STRIP_CLOTHING_POOR"><![CDATA[
		 Laying your possessions out over the office floor, your owner fails to suppress a disgusted tut before declaring, [evelyx.speech(It's not even worth the hassle to pawn all of this rubbish off in Dominion. You are a good slave cow, but I do wish that you'd have had a few more possessions to your name. I'll have all of this junk thrown away once I'm done with you.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Bad end content: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Obediently following Evelyx, you trot along behind her as she strides out of her office and towards the locked door that sits at one end of the farm's long corridor. Unlocking this door, she leads you through it and down the short continuation of the corridor that's to be found on the other side. Coming to a halt in front of yet another wooden door, she turns to face you and commands, [evelyx.speech(Stay here for a minute, slave. I'd better not return to see that you've moved.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you wait in front of this door as your owner heads off down the corridor. Not wanting to get in trouble, you remain perfectly still for the next several minutes, until finally Evelyx returns with another blue-skinned succubus at her side. Addressing this other succubus, she commands, [evelyx.speech(Lead my slave into the barn, sister, and show her to her new home.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLAVE_BARN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hurrying to obey her sister, this other succubus hastily unlocks the door in front of you, before leading you into the barn beyond. Identical to the other three barns which you've worked in, this building constructed out of a mix of concrete and sheet metal, and is illuminated by the same kind of fluorescent lamps which are found throughout the rest of Evelyx's Dairy. Thankfully, this barn is also fitted with numerous air conditioning and heating units, which softly hum away as they work to make sure that the ambient temperature remains pleasantly warm for the slaves who are locked away in here. Underfoot, laminate wooden flooring helps to soften the overall appearance of the barn, as do the motivational posters of cow-girls which have been plastered all over the walls.
	</p>
	<p>
		Again in the exact same manner as the other barns, there are two long rows of milking stalls which run all the way down this one's considerable length. Following Evelyx's sister down the natural corridor which is formed between these stalls, you look to your left and right to see that these milking stalls are positioned so as to be facing the walls of the barn. As a result of this, the many dozens of cowtaur slaves who are being milked in here all have their exposed rear ends pointing towards you, and so you find yourself presented with dozens of feral cow-pussies.
	</p>
	<p>
		Coming to a halt beside an empty stall, the succubus asks Evelyx in a nervous tone, [style.speechFeminine(Will this stall do, sister?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(For now, yes,)] Evelyx replies, before ordering, [evelyx.speech(Get her locked in and attach those pumps. I don't want her milk going to waste.)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isPregnant())
		<p>
			Hurrying to obey, Evelyx's sister instructs you to get into position in this stall, and once you've got into the half-standing, half-prone position which its padded surfaces support, she clasps a series of steel chains around your ankles. Turning on the arcane milking machine, she then proceeds to roughly attach the pumps to your
			#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
				 breasts and [pc.udders].
			#ELSE
				 breasts.
			#ENDIF
			 As your milk starts to spurt out and be sucked down your pumps' tubes, Evelyx glances at your belly and states, [evelyx.speech(I'll have trouble auctioning you off if you're already pregnant. Sister, I had you trained to deal with pregnancies for precisely this reason. Give her as many Mother's Milks as she needs, then get her to give birth. We'll send her kids off to my bottling factory near Dominion; I could do with some more cheap labour over there, and it seems fitting that her children will end up bottling their mother's milk.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having received her instructions, Evelyx's sister forces you to drink several bottles of the pregnancy-advancing potion known as Mother's Milk, and after your stomach has grown and distended to a colossal size, she starts to channel arcane energy into your body. The intensity of this treatment is enough to make your head spin, and although you try to remain concious, you quickly feel yourself passing out... 
		</p>
		<p>
			...
		</p>
		<p>
			You regain conciousness several hours later to find that both Evelyx and her sister are nowhere to be seen. What's more, your stomach has returned to its pre-pregnancy size, and although you feel alarmed and anxious to find out what happened to your children, the slave in the stall next to yours reassures you by revealing, [style.speechFeminine(Mistress and her sister took good care of everything. I heard that Mistress's bottling factory is run by a really kind cow-girl, so you don't have to worry about your kids working there.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having been at least a little reassured by this other slave's words, you settle into your stall and enjoy the familiar, relaxing feeling of the milking machine's pumps sucking away at your teats...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Hurrying to obey, Evelyx's sister instructs you to get into position in this stall, and once you've got into the half-standing, half-prone position which its padded surfaces support, she clasps a series of steel chains around your ankles. Turning on the arcane milking machine, she then proceeds to roughly attach the pumps to your
			#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
				 breasts and [pc.udders].
			#ELSE
				 breasts.
			#ENDIF
			 As your milk starts to spurt out and be sucked down your pumps' tubes, Evelyx orders her sister, [evelyx.speech(Get a move on and contact the local herds. They need to know that I've got another slave for adoption. Oh, and if they take a fancy to you while you're there, be a good sister for me and let them fuck you. Anything to help calm them down always helps.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With a slightly nervous tone in her voice, Evelyx's sister agrees to do as she's told, before rushing out of the barn. Taking a moment to give your pussy one final glance, your owner follows in her sister's footsteps and exits the barn, leaving you to settle into your stall and enjoy the familiar, relaxing feeling of the milking machine's pumps sucking away at your teats...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLAVE_BARN_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the start of your new life so far, you find yourself letting out a series of soft, moo-like moans as you're left locked up in your stall being milked. Having something new and exciting to talk about, all of the other cowtaur slaves in the barn start to loudly gossip amongst themselves about which one of Lunette's daughters is going to adopt you. Although you try to ask them what exactly they mean by that, these slaves seem to find it amusing to keep you in the dark, and simply tell you that it's something to be looked forward to, and that you'll find out what it involves soon enough.
	</p>
	<p>
		Almost four hours later, you hear the door to this slave barn being opened once again, and you turn your head to see that both Evelyx and her sister have returned. Walking up to your stall, your owner commands her sister, [evelyx.speech(Get to it then and clean her down. I want her looking her best for her auction.)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.isIncestEnabled())
		<p>
			Moving to obey, the blue-skinned succubus, who's brought several cloths and brushes with her in expectation of having to perform this duty, moves up beside you and sets about thoroughly cleaning your body. Leaving your pussy for last, she uses a wet cloth to wipe her sister's remaining cum from out of your cunt. Seeing what it is that she's doing, Evelyx allows a slight smirk to settle on her face as she asks, [evelyx.speech(What do you think you're doing? Is your big sister's cum not good enough for you? With this sort of behaviour, and coming back from the herds without having been fucked, I start to question your loyalty... If you don't want mother to find out about your bad behaviour, then I suggest that you show a little more enthusiasm.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly wanting to avoid getting on her mother's bad side, Evelyx's younger sister drops the cloth that she was using, before leaning forwards and starting to lick what remains of the cum from your hot pussy. Forcing herself to swallow, she uses her mouth to clean out your cunt, which proves to be very much to her big sister's liking, for after spending just a moment watching this lewd scene, she pulls up her skirt to allow her massive, orange, demonic cock to rise to full erection. Stepping forwards, she roughly pulls up her sister's mini skirt and tears off her thong, before prodding the wide, flared head of her monstrous shaft against her exposed cunt. Gripping her sister's hips, she drops her posh accent as she lustfully moans, [evelyx.speech(You really thought that you'd get away with bending over and teasing me with your hot little ass? ~Mmm!~ Go on, you little slut, beg for it!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pulling back from eating you out, the younger of the two blue-skinned succubi pants, [style.speechFeminine(Oh yes, Evelyx! ~Aah!~ Please, treat me like one of your cows and fuck me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			More than happy to do as she asks, Evelyx rams her fat, demonic cock deep into her sister's pussy, and as the younger succubus continues to clean your cunt with her tongue, your owner starts roughly pounding her twat. With each of Evelyx's violent thrusts, her sister's face is pushed into your pussy, and thanks to this stimulation you very quickly find yourself staring to approach an orgasm. With her sister's tight cunt proving to be too much for her to endure, Evelyx quickly reaches her climax at the same time as you, and after letting out a desperate, passionate moan, she rams her hips forwards and empties her four, heavy balls into her sister's hot pussy. At the same moment, you feel your wet cunt start to spasm, and with a desperate squeal, you squirt all over the blue-skinned succubus's face.
		</p>
		<p>
			Experiencing her own orgasm at the same moment, the younger of the two succubi behind you moans deeply into your [pc.pussy+], and after Evelyx slides her cock out of her cunt, she collapses down onto the floor as a quivering mess. After taking a moment to smirk down at her well-fucked sister, Evelyx steps forwards and unclasps the steel chains from around your ankles. Satisfied with how clean you're looking, she orders, [evelyx.speech(Follow me, slave; it's time to have you auctioned off.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Moving to obey, the blue-skinned succubus, who's brought several cloths and brushes with her in expectation of having to perform this duty, moves up beside you and sets about thoroughly cleaning your body. Leaving your pussy for last, she uses a wet cloth to wipe her sister's remaining cum from out of your cunt. Satisfied with how clean you're looking, her older sister finally orders, [evelyx.speech(Take off her chains, sister. It's time to have this slave auctioned off.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			One again hurrying to obey, Evelyx's younger sister quickly unclasps the steel chains from around your ankles. Not wanting to delay the proceedings any further, your owner addressing you as she commands, [evelyx.speech(Follow me, slave.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUCTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.isIncestEnabled())
			Obediently following Evelyx, you leave her sister panting on the floor with cum oozing out of well-fucked cunt as you trot over to the barn's door.
		#ELSE
			Obediently following Evelyx, you trot along behind her as she strides back over to the barn's door.
		#ENDIF
		 Unlocking this door, Evelyx leads you out into the corridor beyond, and then quickly over to another wooden door that's positioned nearby. Stopping there, she turns to face you and explains, [evelyx.speech(Beyond here is the auction room. Once inside, you are to ignore the centaurs and step up onto the central platform. Stay silent and do only what I say. Do <i>not</i> show any kind of favouritism towards any of the centaurs. The last thing I want is for them to lose their temper and start fighting in here. Do you understand?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've quickly responded in the affirmative, Evelyx unlocks the door to this 'auction room' and leads you inside. Within the dimly-lit interior, you look around to see that the floor is covered in a rich, burgundy carpet, while dozens of large, taur-compatible sofas have been positioned so as to surround a raised, central platform, which unlike the rest of the dark room is brightly illuminated by means of several arcane spotlights. As you do as you were just told and trot up towards the central platform, you can't help but glance around at the numerous huge, demonic centauresses who are lounging about on the sofas.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminine(She looks like a good one! Get over here and let me get a feel of those tits!)] one of them excitedly declares.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminineStrong(Show me your cunt so I can give you a quick fuck!)] another of them demands.
	</p>
	<p>
		Remembering what Evelyx said, you ignore these comments and step up onto the central platform. Remaining stationary, you listen as Evelyx addresses this herd of Lunette's daughters, [evelyx.speech(Thank you, ladies, for coming here today. Once again, I have a slave that's available for you to adopt and treat as your own. This particular slave is a special one, as I've found out that she's a relative of Lilaya's, and as such is of Lyssieth's lineage. Please take this into account when considering your bids.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminineStrong(I'd like to give that elder bitch a good, hard fuck! That imp-breeder daughter of hers would get it too!)] one of the centauresses exclaims in response.
	</p>
	<p>
		Hearing her sister say this, one of the other centauresses lets out a deep laugh and declares, [style.speechFeminine(Once mother's had us finish with the Fields, hopefully she'll have us go after Lyssieth next! I'd love to ruin that human-loving bitch's cunt with my fat cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After that, the centauresses make several more comments about how they'd like to dominate Lyssieth and Lilaya, before agreeing among themselves that you'll make a fine substitute. Showing just the briefest of smirks as she hears how eager they are to adopt you, Evelyx cautiously waits for a gap in the conversation before declaring, [evelyx.speech(Let us start the bidding! While I will retain official ownership of this slave, by paying to adopt her you will effectively be her owner, and will be given ninety percent of all of her milk profits. As this slave is related to Lyssieth, I would value her as being worth at least five hundred thousand flames, so let's start with that.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that Evelyx is exploiting a loophole in your contract to effectively sell you on to one of these centauresses, you can't help but feel a little cheated as they eagerly agree to start the bidding at half a million flames. As you realise that Evelyx has managed to prevent her farm from being destroyed by getting Lunette's daughters to invest their flames into it, the first of them offers the starting bid, and soon they're trying to out-bid one another in their efforts to 'adopt' you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUCTION_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Remembering to do as you were told, you stay still and try not to look at any one centauress in particular as they bid against one another to adopt you. Clearly eager to get the opportunity to effectively gain ownership of a close relative of Lyssieth's, Lunette's daughters soon increase the bidding to an astronomical figure. Their willingness and ability to blow such a huge sum of money on you is soon explained, as one of them loudly comments, [style.speechFeminineStrong(I got all this money from selling a group of runaway slaves I captured the other day!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminine(It's easier to just take money from people travelling through the Fields!)] another boasts.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to be outdone by her sisters, the centauress who's currently winning the bidding brags, [owner.speech(You get the most from looting people's houses! I've got more money that I could ever possibly spend from doing that! This cow's going to be mine!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having said that, this centauress really puts her money where her mouth is, and over the course of the next several minutes, she continues to easily outbid all of her sisters. Despite Evelyx's warning to not show any kind of favouritism, as it becomes certain that she's going to be the one to adopt you, you can't help but glance across and take good look at her.
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite the fact that she's lying down on one of the sofas, you can tell from her huge figure that this centauress must be at least [owner.heightValue] tall when standing. With dark red skin, piercing yellow eyes, short black hair that's styled into a pixie cut, and a pair of long, black horns, she looks like a tauric, tomboyish version of the sort of stereotypical demon you'd seen back in your old reality.
	</p>
	<p>
		Wearing practically nothing, this centauress's massive pair of [owner.cupSize]-cup breasts are left almost completely exposed, with her big, ebony nipples only just barely being covered up by a pair of black tape crosses. A pair of huge, two-handed battle-axes are resting against the sofa by her side, which thanks to the fact that she has four arms, she's obviously able to wield simultaneously. The last part of her which really catches your eye is the fat, [owner.cockLengthValue] demonic horse-cock and pair of massive, heavy balls that she's got between her legs. Despite that fact that it's got a thick sheath into which to retract, her shaft is fully exposed thanks to the semi-hard state that it's in right now, and you gulp as you realise that she's getting turned on at the thought of winning the bidding and getting to adopt you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just as you find yourself gazing in admiration at the way her gigantic dick is coloured so as to fade from a dark red at the tip to a dull ebony at the base, this centauress looks up directly into your eyes. Clearly possessing a high level of arcane ability, she telepathically projects her thoughts into your mind, and you gulp as you hear her tease, [owner.thought(Like what you see, cow? I'll be ramming it deep into your cunt soon enough. Just be patient for a few more minutes...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Flashing you an evil smirk, this centauress makes a bid that's far higher than what her sisters can afford. After a couple of minutes of trying, and failing, to convince your soon-to-be owner to let them have a chance, all of the other centauresses back out of the bidding, leaving this dark red-skinned, four-armed mountain to be declared by Evelyx as the winner. After paying the blue-skinned succubus a truly massive amount of flames, this centauress lets out a deep, hungry grunt, before leaping up onto your platform and landing with a ground-shaking boom right by your side. Reaching forwards with her four arms, she uses two to spread your ass cheeks, before using her others to give your pussy a forceful, dominant grope.
	</p>
	<p>
		[owner.speech(This cunt's related to Lyssieth, huh?)] she growls as she continues to roughly molest your twat. Unable to prevent a horny moan from escaping your mouth, you bite your lip and whine as this centauress forcefully pushes her fingers into your [pc.pussy+] and gloats, [owner.speech(I own you now, bitch. You should feel honoured; I've led more raiding bands than I can count, and after I presented a hundred slaves to her, Lunette told me that it would only be a matter of time before she officially recognises me as one of her daughters. You understand that, you dumb cow? I'm practically a princess, and that's what you'll call me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although they overhear every word of what's being said, none of your new owner's sisters object to what she's saying, letting you know that she really must be an important daughter of Lunette's. Realising that she's expecting an answer, you quickly reply, [pc.speech(Yes, Princess. Thank you for adopting me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a deep, approving grunt, Princess continues roughly fingering your [pc.pussy+] as she asks, [owner.speech(Ready to get broken-in by my cock, slave? I'm going to be doing this to Lyssieth and her imp-fucking slut of a daughter one day, so consider yourself practice for that!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MOUNTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Before you can reply to [owner.namePos] insulting words about Lyssieth and Lilaya, she rears up and roughly mounts you right there on the raised platform before all of her sisters and Evelyx. Wasting no time with any kind of foreplay, she immediately thrusts her powerful hips forwards and slams her fat, demonic horse-cock deep into your horny cunt.
	</p>
	<p>
		[owner.speech(That's it, slave! ~Mmm!~ I own you now!)] she exclaims, and you can't help but let out a stream of erotic moans as she starts to ruthlessly slam her [owner.cock+] in and out of your [pc.pussy+] right there on the auction room's stage...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MOUNTED_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had her fun with you, [owner.name] steps back slides her huge cock out of your well-fucked pussy. Looking at her musky cum practically gushing out of your despoiled cunt, she grunts in amusement, [owner.speech(My fat cock's turned your cunt into a real filthy mess, my dirty little slave.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the show over, the rest of the Princess's sisters exit the auction room by means of a large door that heads straight out into the Fields. Calling out after them, Evelyx thanks Lunette's daughters for sparing her farm, before turning back towards Princess and saying, [evelyx.speech(I know that you've already adopted another slave, so you've been through this process before, but would you like to accompany me and witness your new slave's final housing?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[owner.speech(Yeah, and anyway, it's been quite a few hours since I was here, so it's time to give my other slave another good, hard fuck,)] Princess replies, before happily trotting on ahead of you and Evelyx. Motioning for you to fall in behind her, the blue-skinned succubus hurries to catch up with Princess, whose cum is still dripping from her softening cock to leave a trail for the two of you to follow.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BACK_HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leading you back into the slave barn, Evelyx directs you to a different stall to the one which you were locked up in previously. The reason for this turns out to be that it's directly adjacent to the one in which Princess's other slave is being kept. After you've settled into position on the stall's padded supports, the blue-skinned succubus locks a steel chain to each of your ankles to prevent you from leaving.
	</p>
	<p>
		While this is happening, Princess rears up and mounts her other cowtaur slave, before slamming her fat cock deep into her drooling cunt. As she takes a moment to watch the centauress roughly pounding her slave's feral cow-pussy, Evelyx takes this opportunity to reveal to you, [evelyx.speech(That slave was Dale's predecessor. She was a good receptionist, but she started asking too many questions about this barn. It really wouldn't do to have the the cows know about what goes on in here. Nobody would want to work for me if they knew that their eventual fate was to become a cock-sleeve for one of Lunette's daughters...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaving you with that knowledge, Evelyx exits the barn, before promptly returning with one of her sisters at her side. As the step up behind you, you see that the younger succubus has an arcane tattoo gun in her hands, and after waiting for Princess to pump what must be at least the third load of thick, musky cum into her other slave's cunt, Evelyx asks, [evelyx.speech(What would you like to call this slave? I'll have my sister here tattoo her name and number on her ass for you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Ramming her fat, demonic horse-cock deep into her slave's cunt, Princess grunts, [owner.speech(Slaves shouldn't have names. ~Mmm!~ I'll just call her 'cow' like I do with this one. ~Aah!~ Put that on her ass.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Receiving an approving nod from Evelyx, the younger succubus quickly uses the arcane tattoo gun to
		#IF(pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_ANUS)!=null)
			 erase the tattoo that you've already got, before permanently etching the text 'Cow #[#~~flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_player_number')]' in black ink on your ass.
		#ELSE
			 permanently etch the text 'Cow #[#~~flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_player_number')]' in black ink on your ass.
		#ENDIF
		 The sensation of being tattooed isn't painful, but it still stings a little, and you find yourself letting out a few whines as the succubus carries out her work. Thankfully, the whole process only takes a few minutes, and as she turns the arcane tattoo gun off, her older sister informs Princess, [evelyx.speech(Your adopted slave is ready for you to use at any time. As agreed upon, I'll have ninety percent of her milk profits ready for you at the end of each month.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Noisily orgasming and dumping yet another huge amount of cum in her other slave, Princess finally slides her cock out from her thoroughly-fucked and despoiled cunt. Her insatiable lust isn't satisfied yet, however, and now that she's reduced her other slave to a quivering, moaning mess, she steps over and rears up on her hind legs, before mounting you once again. Exchanging glances with one another, Evelyx and her sister step back and give the two of you some room, and before you know it Princess's massive, demonic horse-cock is once again slamming deep into your cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_1"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The feeling of Princess's fat, demonic horse-cock being rammed deep into your cunt becomes very familiar to you over the course of the next few weeks, as she always arrives at least once, and often multiple times every day to rut both you her other slave. Having multiple loads of thick, musky cum pumped deep into your wombs every day, it's no surprise that both of your bellies are soon swollen with Princess's children. Although her other slave is well accustomed to this preference of hers by now, you're new to discover that Princess likes the look of a heavily pregnant belly, and she leaves the two of you in this state for almost a month before finally having Evelyx's sister deliver your children.
	</p>
	<p>
		After that, the whole process repeats itself, and while she keeps the two of you on sterility pills for a while, Princess eventually decides to breed you both again, and by the time that you've delivered your second set of twins, the days have blurred together into a haze of being milked and fucked. One day, however, something different happens to break this pattern, as Princess enters the barn with both Evelyx and a newly-adopted slave in tow. This new slave is locked into the other stall beside you, and after spending a good thirty minutes roughly pounding each of your hot cunts, Princess grunts and declares, [owner.speech(Now that I've got the three cows I was looking for, I can finally have my fun transforming you all!)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.isNipplePenEnabled())
		<p>
			Producing a bottle containing some kind of transformative potion, Princess trots around in front of the ex-receptionist slave who was here before you were. Roughly pushing the neck of this bottle into her mouth, Princess forces her drink it all, and you watch in alarm as her already-massive breasts grow into absolutely huge mounds of flesh. Slapping her slave's gigantic tits, Princess produces yet another potion and forces her to drink that too, taunting as she does so, [owner.speech(I hope you're ready to have these fat tits of yours fucked!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You soon see that Princess was talking quite literally, as within moments her slave's nipples have morphed and transformed into pairs of plump lips. After pushing her fingers into each of these newly-formed lipples to make sure that there's a fuckable channel behind them, Princess rears up and mounts the first of her slave's gigantic tits. Letting out a deep moan, she forcefully slams her huge, demonic horse-cock into her slave's breast, and you watch in fascinated shock as the slave's lip-like nipple sucks and chokes on Princess's hot shaft as though it were a real mouth. This exotic new way to fuck her slave proves to be more than Princess can endure, for she quickly lets out a deep, shuddering moan and pumps a massive load of musky, demonic cum into her slave's breast.
		</p>
		<p>
			Pulling out, your owner moves on to the slave's other breast, and after mounting and roughly pounding that one, she similarly pumps it full of her hot, slimy cum. After despoiling her slave's tits in this manner, Princess looks across at you, and with an evil smirk on her face, she trots forwards and asks,
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				 [owner.speech(So, cow, what should I turn you into? I've already got a tit-fucking cow, so you'll have to have your cunt turned into my perfect cock-sleeve. Or maybe I should make you my oral pet, hmm? Oh, or maybe even a filthy buttslut! You want to take it up your ass from now on? Or should I choke you with my fat cock and feed you my cum every day? So many choices... Perhaps I'll let you help me decide...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With that, your owner moves directly over to you, and after giving your cum-stuffed cunt a rough, dominant grope, she trots forwards evilly smirks at you, before asking,
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				 [owner.speech(So, cow, what should I turn you into? I'm thinking of turning your cunt into my perfect cock-sleeve. Or maybe I should make you my oral pet, hmm? Oh, or maybe even a filthy buttslut! You want to take it up your ass from now on? Or should I choke you with my fat cock and feed you my cum every day? So many choices... Perhaps I'll let you help me decide...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_1_PUSSY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After overcoming the shock at being given the opportunity to decide your fate, you meekly suggest to Princess that you'd love to make her happy by becoming her perfect cock-sleeve. Agreeing with your choice, the centauress roughly force-feeds you several bottles of transformative potions, and as you feel your cunt start to transform and reshape itself into a new form, Princess quickly mounts you and rams her fat horse-cock deep into it. Reaching down to roughly dig her fingers into your massive breasts, she hilts her cock deep into your transforming cunt and moans, [owner.speech(~Ooh!~ Fuck! I can feel your cunt transforming around my cock! ~Mmm!~ That's it, you dirty cow slut, you're becoming nothing more than my cock-sleeve!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Keeping her cock rammed balls-deep in your quivering cunt, Princess continues to moan as both of you feel it transforming to be tentacled, ribbed, and to have extra internal muscles. After that, it rapidly transforms to be continuously drooling with girlcum, after which it puffs up and tightens to assume a cute, inexperienced appearance. Of course, that tightening doesn't last long, for as Princess feels your cunt squeezing down around her cock, she starts to roughly thrust her hips back and forth, quickly stretching you out and moulding your pussy to the perfect shape of her cock.
	</p>
	<p>
		As your transformations come to an end, Princess celebrates your cunt's new feel by pumping it full of a massive amount of hot, musky demonic-cum. After that, she declares that she's never felt a pussy as good as yours, and after declaring that you're now well and truly her personal cock-sleeve, she spends the next hour tirelessly pounding your cunt and stuffing it full of cum over and over again. Eventually, however, she remembers that she has
		#IF(game.isNipplePenEnabled())
			 another slave to transform, and leaves you to recover as she turns this last slave of hers into her
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				 anal-obsessed buttslut.
			#ELSE
				 cum-loving oral pet.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 two more slaves to transform, and leaves you to recover as she turns one into her cum-loving oral pet and the other into her anal-obsessed buttslut.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With your transformations complete, Princess leaves, only to return later that day and spend hours fucking each of you over and over again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_1_MOUTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After overcoming the shock at being given the opportunity to decide your fate, you meekly suggest to Princess that you'd love to make her happy by becoming her oral-loving pet. Agreeing with your choice, the centauress roughly force-feeds you several bottles of transformative potions, and as you feel your throat start to transform and reshape itself into a new form, Princess quickly forces your head down and rams her fat horse-cock into your mouth. Stepping forwards, she hilts her cock deep into your transforming throat and moans, [owner.speech(~Ooh!~ Fuck! I can feel you transforming around my cock! ~Mmm!~ That's it, you dirty cow slut, you're becoming nothing more than my oral pet!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Keeping her cock rammed balls-deep in your mouth, Princess continues to moan as both of you feel it transforming to be tentacled, ribbed, and to have extra internal muscles. After that, it rapidly transforms to be continuously drooling saliva, after which your lips puff up, and then finally your throat constricts and tightens. Of course, that tightening doesn't last long, for as Princess feels your oesophagus squeezing down around her cock, she starts to roughly thrust her hips back and forth, quickly stretching you out and moulding your throat to the perfect shape of her cock.
	</p>
	<p>
		As your transformations come to an end, Princess celebrates your throat's new feel by pumping your stomach full of a massive amount of hot, musky demonic-cum. After that, she declares that she's never felt a mouth-pussy as good as yours, and after declaring that you're now well and truly her personal oral pet, she spends the next hour tirelessly fucking your face and stuffing you full of cum over and over again. Eventually, however, she remembers that she has
		#IF(game.isNipplePenEnabled())
			 another slave to transform, and leaves you to recover as she turns this last slave of hers into her
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				 anal-obsessed buttslut.
			#ELSE
				 perfect cock-sleeve.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 two more slaves to transform, and leaves you to recover as she turns one into her perfect cock-sleeve and the other into her anal-obsessed buttslut.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With your transformations complete, Princess leaves, only to return later that day and spend hours fucking each of you over and over again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_1_ANUS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After overcoming the shock at being given the opportunity to decide your fate, you meekly suggest to Princess that you'd love to make her happy by becoming her dirty little buttslut. Agreeing with your choice, the centauress roughly force-feeds you several bottles of transformative potions, and as you feel your asshole start to transform and reshape itself into a new form, Princess quickly mounts you and rams her fat horse-cock deep into it. Reaching down to roughly dig her fingers into your massive breasts, she hilts her cock deep into your transforming ass and moans, [owner.speech(~Ooh!~ Fuck! I can feel your butt transforming around my cock! ~Mmm!~ That's it, you dirty cow, you're becoming nothing more than my buttslut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Keeping her cock rammed balls-deep in your quivering asshole, Princess continues to moan as both of you feel it transforming to be tentacled, ribbed, and to have extra internal muscles. After that, it rapidly transforms to be continuously drooling with natural anal lubricant, after which the rim puffs up, and then finally it tightens to assume a cute, inexperienced appearance. Of course, that tightening doesn't last long, for as Princess feels your asshole squeezing down around her cock, she starts to roughly thrust her hips back and forth, quickly stretching you out and moulding your rear entrance to the perfect shape of her cock.
	</p>
	<p>
		As your transformations come to an end, Princess celebrates the new feel of your asshole by pumping it full of a massive amount of hot, musky demonic-cum. After that, she declares that she's never felt an ass-pussy as good as yours, and after declaring that you're now well and truly her personal buttslut, she spends the next hour tirelessly pounding your ass and stuffing it full of cum over and over again. Eventually, however, she remembers that she has
		#IF(game.isNipplePenEnabled())
			 another slave to transform, and leaves you to recover as she turns this last slave of hers into her cum-loving oral pet.
		#ELSE
			 two more slaves to transform, and leaves you to recover as she turns one into her perfect cock-sleeve and the other into her cum-loving oral pet.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With your transformations complete, Princess leaves, only to return later that day and spend hours fucking each of you over and over again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_2"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Princess continues her regular visits for the next few months, making sure to thoroughly fuck your newly-transformed
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_anal))
			 asshole almost every time.
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_oral))
			 mouth almost every time.
		#ELSE
			 pussy almost every time.
		#ENDIF
		 While the other slaves in the barn are all regularly used by their owners, the three of you are by far the most thoroughly-fucked, and with your transformed appearances, you end up being the focus of much of the barn's gossip.
	</p>
	<p>
		One day, many months after becoming Evelyx's slave, Princess arrives at the barn in a particularly foul mood. While she's often angry and roughly uses the three of you to help her calm down, on this particular occasion she's in a state of rage unlike anything you've seen before.
		#IF(game.isNipplePenEnabled())
			 Although she violently pounds the ex-receptionist's lipples and stuffs her massive breasts full of her cum,
		#ELSE
			 Although she spends fifteen minutes violently pounding the ex-receptionist and stuffing her full of her cum,
		#ENDIF
		 Princess's rage only seems to get worse, and as she moves on to roughly slam her fat cock
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_anal))
			 deep into your ass,
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_oral))
			 deep down your throat,
		#ELSE
			 deep into your cunt,
		#ENDIF
		 she starts to rant and rave, [owner.speech(Take it, you fucking cow! ~Mmm!~ What did she fucking mean, saying that I wasn't '<i>wealthy enough to lead the expected life of a recognised daughter</i>'?! ~Aah!~ Fuck! Take my cock, you dumb slave! This is all your fault for not making me enough money from your milk! ~Mmm!~ I'll fucking fix that soon enough!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Obviously having been told by Lunette that she wasn't ready to be officially recognised as one of her daughters, Princess takes out her frustration and rage on the three of you, and after hate-fucking you for what seems like hours, she finally starts to calm down. With cum pouring out of each of your ruined holes, the three of you can only pant and breathlessly moan as Princess reveals her plan...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_2_FLAVOUR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[owner.speech(Flavoured milk and girlcum sells for a lot more than the regular flavours,)] Princess declares, producing several transformative potion bottles. Starting off by forcing the ex-receptionist to drink several of them, she reveals,
		#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
			[owner.speech(You'll have honey-flavoured milk from your fat tits, blueberry-flavoured udder-milk, and just in case Evelyx ever starts milking your cunt, you'll have cherry-flavoured girlcum.)]
		#ELSE
			[owner.speech(You'll have honey-flavoured milk from your fat tits, and just in case Evelyx ever starts milking your cunt, you'll have cherry-flavoured girlcum.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving on to you, Princess roughly forces you to drink yet more of the transformative potions she's brought along, before stepping back and revealing,
		#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
			 [owner.speech(As for you, you're going to have vanilla tit-milk, chocolate udder-milk, and strawberry-flavoured girlcum.)]
		#ELSE
			 [owner.speech(As for you, you're going to have vanilla milk and strawberry-flavoured girlcum.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After that, Princess moves on to her last, and newest, slave. Making her drink the rest of her potions, she grunts and says, [owner.speech(I forgot what else I brought along, so I guess you'll just be a surprise.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having transformed each of you to produce exotic-flavoured fluids, Princess's mood starts to brighten, and she declares that from now on the three of you will be making her a lot more money. With that, she rears up and mounts the slave to your left, and after giving her a long, hard fucking, she moves on to
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_anal))
			 pound your asshole
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_oral))
			 fuck your face
		#ELSE
			 pound your pussy
		#ENDIF
		 and stuff you full of yet more of her cum. Finishing off by rutting her third slave, Princess trots off and leaves the three of you well and truly exhausted...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_2_HYPER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.isNipplePenEnabled())
			[owner.speech(The two of you need tits like this cow,)] Princess states after trotting around to the front of the ex-receptionist and slapping her gigantic tits. Flashing each of you an evil smirk in turn, she continues, [owner.speech(Actually, no, they need to be bigger than this. You three are going to be making more milk than all of the other slaves in here combined.)]
		#ELSE
			[owner.speech(The three of you need tits so big that they touch the floor,)] Princess states as she trots around in front of you and slaps each of your already-huge tits in turn. With an evil smirk on her face, she continues, [owner.speech(Actually, no, they need to be bigger than that. You three are going to be making more milk than all of the other slaves in here combined.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, your owner produces a dozen transformative potion bottles, and moves between each one of you, feeding you these potions in turn. You can't help but let out a desperate, shuddering moan as
		#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
			 both your breasts and udders
		#ELSE
			 your breasts
		#ENDIF
		 expand to double in size, and then double again. Just as you think that they couldn't possibly get any larger, and with your back starting to really strain under their weight, Princess claps her hands and declares, [owner.speech(Excellent, that will serve as our starting point. I'll be back with more potions soon!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she trots out of the barn, leaving the three of you bending forwards and panting from exertion as you struggle to handle the massive increase in weight on each of your chests. After fifteen minutes of being subjected to this discomfort, Princess returns with yet more transformative potions, and as she feeds them to each of you in turn, your
		#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
			 breasts and udders
		#ELSE
			 breasts
		#ENDIF
		 expand into an absolutely colossal size. Unable to look down over the top of them, you let out a surprised gasp as you feel the underside of your gargantuan tits touch the floor. The initial shock of having your breasts expanded to this size is soon replaced by a feeling of intense relief, as with your tits being supported by the floor, the strain on your back quickly disappears. Still not satisfied, Princess continues feeding all three of you potion after potion, until eventually each of your breasts are as large as your entire bodies. It's only at this stage, when each of you are completely immobilised by the sheer size and weight of your tits, does Princess declare that you're all finished.
	</p>
	<p>
		Having completed her work, Princess's mood starts to brighten, and she declares that from now on the three of you will be making her a lot more money. With that, she rears up and mounts the slave to your left, and after giving her a long, hard fucking, she moves on to
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_anal))
			 pound your asshole
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_oral))
			 fuck your face
		#ELSE
			 pound your pussy
		#ENDIF
		 and stuff you full of yet more of her cum. Finishing off by rutting her third slave, Princess trots off and leaves the three of you well and truly exhausted...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_2_MULTI"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[owner.speech(The three of you need more tits in order to up your milk production,)] Princess states as she trots around in front of you and slaps each of your huge tits in turn. With an evil smirk on her face, she continues, [owner.speech(You three are going to be making more milk than all of the other slaves in here combined.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, your owner produces a dozen transformative potion bottles, and moves between each one of you, feeding you these potions in turn. You can't help but let out a desperate, shuddering moan you transform to have three pairs of
		#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
			 breasts and udders.
		#ELSE
			 breasts.
		#ENDIF
		 Just as you think that it's over, Princess says that she's half-way done, and she continues feeding the three of you transformative potions until you've each got
		#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
			 twelve tits and udders, each with four huge, puffy nipples on them.
		#ELSE
			 twelve tits, each with four huge, puffy nipples on them.
		#ENDIF
		 Grabbing spare pumps from the milking machines to the side of each of your stalls, Princess hooks them up to your new teats, and only after she's turned each of your chests
		#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
			 and udders
		#ENDIF
		 into a tangled mess of dozens of breast pumps does she finally declare that you're all finished.
	</p>
	<p>
		Having completed her work, Princess's mood starts to brighten, and she declares that from now on the three of you will be making her a lot more money. With that, she rears up and mounts the slave to your left, and after giving her a long, hard fucking, she moves on to
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_anal))
			 pound your asshole
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_oral))
			 fuck your face
		#ELSE
			 pound your pussy
		#ENDIF
		 and stuff you full of yet more of her cum. Finishing off by rutting her third slave, Princess trots off and leaves the three of you well and truly exhausted...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_3"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After many more months, the improvements Princess made to you and her other two slaves ends up making her very rich. Now and again during her daily visits to fuck you, she boasts about how many flames she's earning from the sale of your milk. One day, she bursts into the barn with a huge grin on her face, and after spending a good hour repeatedly blowing load after load of her hot, musky cum into each of you, she proudly declares, [owner.speech(You're now the slaves of a recognised daughter of Lunette! How does it feel, you dumb cows, to have the cum of royalty stuffed into your holes?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a series of submissive, appreciative moans, the three of you flatter your owner and beg to be given another good, hard fucking. Being in an exceptionally good mood, she happily agrees to give you what you want, and after first reducing the ex-receptionist to a quivering, cum-stuffed wreck, she moves over to you and
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_anal))
			 gives your ass a rough pounding, before emptying her balls deep inside of you multiple times.
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_oral))
			 gives your face a rough fucking, before emptying her balls deep inside of your stomach multiple times.
		#ELSE
			 gives your cunt a rough pounding, before emptying her balls deep inside of your womb multiple times.
		#ENDIF
		 After that, she moves on to her last slave, and after roughly pounding her and stuffing her full of musky, demonic-cum, she gives each of your asses a sharp slap before happily trotting out of the barn.
	</p>
	<p>
		Yet more months pass after this, until one day, through your happy haze of milking and sex, you suddenly start to wonder exactly how long you've been here. When Princess arrives later that day to give each of you your daily fucking, you ask her how long you've been her slave for. Although she's tolerated questions in the past, her ever-increasing wealth, as well as the fact that she's become a recognised daughter of Lunette, has made her exceptionally arrogant and ruthless. A dark look flashes over her face as she hears you ask her a question, and after forcefully slapping your ass you for your insolence, she snorts, [owner.speech(I've noticed that you've been giving me insolent looks recently, and now you dare to ask questions of me?! I am a recognised daughter of Lunette, and you are nothing but my cock-sleeve! I'll teach you to disrespect me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_anal))
			With that, she quickly rears up and mounts you, before angrily ramming her fat cock deep into your ass.
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_oral))
			With that, she forces you to swallow her cock, before angrily ramming it deep down your throat.
		#ELSE
			With that, she quickly rears up and mounts you, before angrily ramming her fat cock deep into your cunt.
		#ENDIF
		 Giving you the sort of brutal, rage-fuelled hate-fuck that you haven't experienced since she was denied recognition by her mother all those months ago, Princess pumps load after load of her musky, slimy cum deep inside of you. Neglecting her other two slaves, she continues to give you her full attention for the next hour, and after thoroughly abusing you in this manner, she finally steps back and grunts, [owner.speech(Simply fucking you into silence isn't enough. I know exactly what you need to make sure that you're never able to back-talk me again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Princess angrily gallops out of the barn, leaving you a quivering, broken mess, and her other two slaves whining in disappointment as they realise that they're not going to get the fucking they were hoping for. As you start to recover from this brutal fuck session, you start to wonder what Princess is going to do to you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_3_BONDAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		An hour later, and you finally find out what Princess has planned for you. Kicking open the door to the slave barn, she quickly trots over to your stall, before reaching behind her and retrieving a large package from her back. Tearing this package open, she holds up the contents and laughs, [owner.speech(How do you like the look of your new uniform, cow?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Your eyes widen as you take a look at what Princess is calling your new uniform. Being an almost-luminescent, garish shade of hot pink, the clothing in Princess's arms consists of several pieces of shiny, latex bondage gear. To begin with, and with much effort and pulling, she slides a skin-tight bodysuit over your torso, which has a pair of small holes cut out of the front to allow just your fat, puffy nipples and areolae to be left exposed. After that, she grabs hold of your latex-covered arms, before forcing them behind your back and locking them securely together into an arm-binder.
	</p>
	<p>
		[owner.speech(Feeling comfortable, cow?)] Princess teases as she traces her fingers over your latex-covered body. Not wanting to anger her any further, you let out an approving moan, after which Princess moves on to the next stage of somewhat-awkwardly forcing your quadrupedal lower body into a specially-designed feral bodysuit.
		#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
			 Just like with your breasts, there are small holes cut out of the bottom of this item of skin-tight clothing, allowing your fat teats to remain exposed.
		#ENDIF
		 This latex clothing has a special sleeve into which your tail snugly fits, and beneath that, a metal zipper allows Princess to completely seal up your pussy and asshole. With one final piece of clothing in her hands, and with your entire body apart from your head encased in skin-tight, shiny pink latex, Princess gives you a particularly evil grin and cruelly sneers, [owner.speech(Enjoy this last moment, cow. Your world's about to get a lot darker and quieter. I'll only be undoing your zippers to have you fed and fucked, and for the rest of the time the only parts of you which people will be able to see will be your fat nipples as they get sucked on by your milking machine's pumps.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Holding up the last item of latex gear to reveal that it's a completely-enclosed hood, Princess quickly forces it over your head, and within moments, your world is turned into a muffled, dark pink. You feel Princess securely zipping this hood into place so that it's joined to your bodysuit around your neck, and then with that, she's finished. Apart from a pair of small holes which allow you to breathe through your nose, the only gaps in your skin-tight latex gear are those which leave your nipples exposed and able to be sucked on by the milking machine, but as Princess reattaches your pumps into place over them, you feel like those too are now encased and sealed off from the outside world.
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite being made out of thin latex, the hood which you've been forced to wear has been enchanted in some manner so as to block out almost all of the noise from your surroundings. As such, you're only vaguely aware via a faint, muffled mumbling that Princess is saying something to you. Moments later, a sharp slap is delivered to your ass, and thanks to the thin nature of the latex, you feel the stinging blow every bit as keenly as you would have done had your ass been exposed. Although you instinctively try to let out a shocked squeal in response to this, your cry is dampened and almost completely silenced by your latex hood.
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly happy with how your new uniform has turned out, you suddenly feel Princess unzipping the latex beneath your tail, exposing your cunt and asshole to the outside world. Moments later and she's reared up and mounted you, and you let out a stream of muffled, erotic moans as she ruthlessly pounds your sopping-wet cunt, before emptying her balls deep into your womb.
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 After that, she pulls back and thrusts forwards once again, but this time she sinks her massive, demonic horse-cock into your asshole. After proceeding to spend a short while roughly pounding your butt, she unloads yet another massive quantity of hot, musky cum deep into your ass.
		#ENDIF
		 Repeating this several more times, and stuffing you absolutely full of cum, Princess finally pulls back and gets down off your back. It's at that moment that you realise that you'd always simply waited for your cum-stuffed holes to leak down onto the floor in the past, but as Princess grabs hold of your zipper, you realise that that's about to change. Sealing you up, she locks her musky cum inside your bodysuit, and you let out another silenced moan as you feel her hot cum being trapped inside your well-fucked
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 holes.
		#ELSE
			 twat.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Not finished with you just yet, Princess moves around to your front, which you only discover as you suddenly feel her undoing the zipper that seals your mouth. Before you can say anything or make any kind of noise, Princess is ramming her cum-coated shaft down your throat, and you're forced to swallow several loads of her cum before she finally withdraws her softening shaft from your abused hole. Again, before you can say anything, she quickly zips you back up, sealing your mouth and leaving you only able to make the faintest, most muffled of moans.
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		In this manner, you spend the rest of your life encased in bright-pink latex, being milked in Evelyx's slave barn. You're fucked over and over again by Princess, who never once loses her insatiable desire to sink her fat cock into your holes and stuff you full of her cum. If anything, your latex-bound form seems to have only made her desire you more, and from that moment on you're never fucked less than three times every day...
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_3_BIMBO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		An hour later, and you finally find out what Princess has planned for you. Kicking open the door to the slave barn, she quickly trots over to your stall, before lifting a tiny vial of bright-pink liquid up in front of you. Flashing you a particularly evil smirk, she laughs and reveals, [owner.speech(I had this very special little potion made for me by calling in a favour from an old and very powerful friend. I only asked for one vial, but she ended up making me two. I've long since used the first one as I'd planned; I had a very devious sister, you see, who was competing with me to be officially recognised by my mother. After slipping this potion into her food, she... Well, you'll find out what it does soon enough. I'd been wondering how best to use this other one for quite some time. Thanks to you, I can finally dispose of it in a way that doesn't seem like a waste.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Princess produces a pair of long, rubber gloves and a full-face gas mask, and after putting them on, she takes extreme care to slowly break the vial's wax seal. Positioning the vial beneath your nose, she leans back and pulls out the stopper. The heady, sickly-sweet scent which rises out of this vial immediately causes your head to spin, and you can't help but let out a deep, horny moan as you feel your cunt starting to grow especially hot and needy. Although her voice is muffled through her mask, you're still able to hear Princess clearly enough as she asks, [owner.speech(Do you want to feel good, cow? Just open your mouth and tilt your head back for me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although your head is still spinning, you find yourself able to think that you really do want to feel good, and so you unquestioningly tilt your head back and open your mouth for Princess. A moment later, and the most delicious, strawberry-flavoured liquid you've ever tasted is being poured into your mouth, and without even stopping to think about it, you greedily swallow down every last drop. Immediately, your thoughts start to slow down, and while you're still completely aware of your surroundings, you can't quite remember where you are or how you got here. The only things which you know as you look around is that the pretty lady taking off her gas mask is some kind of queen or something, and that your pussy is absolutely desperate to have her fat, demonic cock shoved deep inside of it.
	</p>
	<p>
		[owner.speech(How's that, cow? Are you feeling good yet?)] the pretty lady asks. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Tilting your head to one side as you try your hardest to understand what she's saying, you manage to comprehend that the word 'cow' is referring to you. Upon realising this, you let out a happy giggle and respond by drawling, [pc.speechNoEffects(Cow happy... Cow pussy, like, want cock... Umm... Pretty lady give big cock to cow...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		For some reason that you can't understand, a big grin breaks out across the pretty lady's face as she hears you say this. Letting out a happy moo as she reaches forwards and gropes your huge tits, you do your best to try to understand what she's talking about as she gloats, [owner.speech(That potion really fucked you up, didn't it? Well, that's to be expected of something that was created by a lilin and named 'Bimbo-Xtreme'. You've turned out just like my meddlesome sister did. You won't be asking any more foolish questions of me after this, will you, cow?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Completely and utterly lost by what the pretty lady is saying, you pout at her and whine, [pc.speechNoEffects(Cow, like, no think big words... Pretty lady cock... Cow want...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		For some incomprehensible reason, the pretty lady laughs at your words, but before you can get upset at this, she trots around behind you and rears up to quickly mount you. As her fat, demonic horse-cock prods at your horny cunt, you find yourself letting out a series of airy, bubbly giggles, which soon turn into deep, passionate moans as her hot, thick shaft slams into your needy pussy and beings to give it the hard, rough fucking that you were craving. Much to your delight, the pretty lady continues rutting and pumping load after load of hot, musky cum into your twat for a long time, and after that, she makes you an even happier cow by
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_bad_end_anal))
			 doing the same thing to your ass. Once both of your rear holes are stuffed full of cum, the nice, pretty lady allows you to take her cock down your throat, and you're made an extremely happy cow when she gives you several big, yummy loads of her delicious cum to swallow. 
		#ELSE
			 allowing you to take her cock down your throat, before giving you several big, yummy loads of her delicious cum to swallow. 
		#ENDIF
		 After that, the pretty lady makes the other cows happy, before leaving you with the nice feeling of having your nipples sucked on by this strange whirring thing...
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		In this manner, you spend the rest of your life as an air-headed bimbo, being milked in the barn. You're fucked over and over again by Princess, who never once loses her insatiable desire to sink her fat cock into your holes and stuff you full of her cum. If anything, your mind-altering transformation seems to have only made her desire you more, and from that moment on you're made a very happy cow no less than three times every day...
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NEW_LIFE_3_FERAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		An hour later, and you finally find out what Princess has planned for you. Kicking open the door to the slave barn, she quickly trots over to your stall, and she comes to a halt in front of you, you see that she's carrying a small wooden box with latch that's secured by a heavy iron padlock. Taking out a small key and unlocking this padlock, Princess says, [owner.speech(There was a time, quite a few years ago now, when temporary feral transformations were a big craze. Everyone was experimenting with turning themselves into feral animals for a few days, and sometimes even weeks or months. I could never do it myself, thanks to the fact that demons require a very special type of transformation to experience it, but apparently you get a wild, primal lust to go with it, and the sex is meant to be incredible. Unfortunately, all good things come to an end, and after an incident where a pack of ferals attacked and raped a high-ranking demon, feral transformations rapidly fell out of favour with the general population, to the point where it's quite a serious taboo to be seen in a feral form these days.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Getting the feeling like there's a point to Princess giving you this lengthy history on feral transformations, you nervously watch as she opens the wooden box that she's just unlocked. Within, sitting upon a padded, purple cushion, you see what appears to be a smooth, grey pebble. You very quickly discover that its mundane appearance hides some kind of arcane power, for as you look at it, a faint, pink shimmer suddenly sweeps across its surface. Flashing you an evil smirk as she sees you curiously looking at this item of hers, Princess explains, [owner.speech(Items capable of causing a feral transformation are particularly difficult and extremely expensive to have enchanted. As a result, almost all feral transformations are applied by spending time in contact with what came to be known as 'beast stones'. These stones could be used an unlimited number of times, but due to the difficult and finicky nature of the feral enchantment, they were typically made to be no smaller than an average-sized person. A few, however, were created by exceptionally-talented lilin to be the size of a small pebble.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising what it is that Princess intends to do to you with what is clearly one of these pebble-sized 'beast stones', you nervously gulp and flash her a worried look. Letting out a sadistic laugh, Princess teases, [owner.speech(Yes, that's the expression I was looking for! After all, once you're a feral cow, I'm not going to be able to see you make faces like that again.... And you haven't even heard the best part yet!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Carefully picking up this beast stone and holding it with a level of respect that you've never seen from Princess before, she gloats, [owner.speech(Oh, how I do enjoy showing this off, even if it is to a dumb cow like you. This little thing is likely worth more than this entire farm, and that's not only because of its exceptional rarity, but also due to what it can do thanks to its small size... Which leads me into the best part.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Trotting around behind you, Princess gives your exposed cunt a quick smack, causing you to let out a high-pitched squeal. Laughing as she roughly sticks her fingers into your drooling twat, she starts idly playing with your pussy as she reveals, [owner.speech(Every beast stone, this one included, requires at least an hour of exposure before the transformation takes place. For every hour spent touching the stone, you get a day in your feral form. At least, that's the standard behaviour which everyone is aware of. I doubt more than a hundred people know of the special transformation which all beast stones can apply, but which can only be discovered with one this size.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Delighting in taking her time to reveal what this special transformation is, which is what she was clearly referring to when she mentioned the 'best part', Princess lets out an excited moan and continues to finger your hot, wet cow-cunt for a few more moments, before excitedly sharing her secret, [owner.speech(Instead of one day of feral transformation from an hour of touching the stone, you can get one <i>year</i> of it from just one <i>minute</i> of its power. For this to happen, it needs more than to simply be touched... It needs to be <i>inside</i> of you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Princess suddenly shoves her entire hand into your cunt, and as you let out a shuddering squeal, you realise that she wasn't just idly playing with your pussy, but rubbing the beast stone up and down between your labia in anticipation of doing this. Forcing the small, pebble-like object deep into your feral cow-cunt, Princess lets go of it, before sliding her hand back out from your sopping-wet, slightly-stretched pussy. Immediately, she then quickly rears up and mounts you, before ramming her thick, demonic horse-cock into your hot twat. Thrusting forwards, she makes good use of the wide, flared head of her animalistic shaft to push and force the beast stone as deep as possible into your cunt. Letting out a wild laugh, Princess taunts, [owner.speech(Enjoy your last minute of having that upper body of yours, cow. I'll miss the money that I was making from all of that milk which your fat tits were producing, but I'm sure that we can make some improvements to your udders to make up for it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Starting to feel a deep, intense heat pulsate out from the beast stone that's lodged deep in your cunt, you find yourself unable to stop a deep, erotic moan from bursting out from between your lips. Reaching forwards over the top of you, Princess fastens a feminine wristwatch around one of your stall's supports, before adjusting it to make sure that you're able to clearly see its face. As the second hand ticks past the five o'clock mark, Princess grinds her cock into your cunt and teases, [owner.speech(When it gets to the top, it'll have been one minute. Let's enjoy these last moments of your upper body together, cow.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Princess reaches down and roughly grabs hold of your huge tits. Forcefully digging her fingers into your soft mounds of flesh, she lets out a mocking laugh as she starts groping and squeezing them. As the second hand reaches ten o'clock, she suddenly grabs hold of your head, and although the positioning is somewhat awkward for her, Princess manages to lean down and pull you into a frantic, passionate kiss. Breaking it off right at the moment that the second hand reaches twelve o'clock, she moans, [owner.speech(You might not remember who took your first kiss, but you'll always remember me as taking your last.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At that exact moment, you suddenly feel another deep, powerful wave of energy shoot out from the demon stone that's lodged deep in your pussy. Immediately, an intense tingling sensation breaks out all across your upper body, and you feel your eyes widening in shock as your arms retract into your torso and completely disappear. A moment later, and your upper body starts to sink down, compact, and transform into what rapidly becomes a thick cow's neck. Finally, your face pushes out and undergoes an alarming reshaping process, leaving you a few seconds later with an entirely feral-looking cow's face. Letting out a delighted laugh, and with her fat cock still rammed deep in your cunt, Princess holds a mirror down towards your face as she taunts, [owner.speech(Go on, cow, get a good look at yourself! Unfortunately, there's no way to get rid of that intelligent look that can be seen in a feral's eyes, but other than that, you're one-hundred percent cow!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking in the mirror, you see that Princess is right. Where once your upper body connected to your lower feral cow's body, only a very normal-looking neck and head of a cow remain. Differentiating you from a dumb animal, however, there's still the same intelligent, sapient gleam to your otherwise cow-like eyes, which you feel only adds to the humiliation of what you've become. You try to say something in response to Princess's taunts, but all that comes out is a deep, long, [pc.speechNoEffects(Moooooo!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[owner.speech(That's it, my sexy little cow, moo for me!)] Princess laughs, before pulling her hips back and thrusting her fat, throbbing cock deep into your cunt.
	</p>
	<p>
		The sensation of being fucked as a completely feral cow is unlike anything you've ever experienced before, and you find yourself overcome with the primal, animalistic lust which Princess previously mentioned as being part of the feral experience. The desperate, orgasmic moan which you try to let out escapes your feral cow's mouth as yet another heavy, prolonged, [pc.speechNoEffects(Moooooo!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[owner.speech(There's nothing better than this! ~Mmm!~ Fuck, I love fucking ferals! I should have done this to you a long time ago! ~Aah!~ Now moo for me, cow, moo!)] Princess exclaims in delight as she starts repeatedly slamming her fat cock in and out of your dripping cow-cunt. The more lewd moans which you allow to escape from your mouth as incomprehensible moos, the more turned on Princess becomes, until before you know it, her fat cock is twitching inside of you and pumping a huge load of demonic cum deep into your womb. Panting and moaning in delight, Princess leans down and taps the watch she attached to your stall earlier. As you look across to see that five minutes have passed since Princess inserted the beast stone into your pussy, she reminds you, [owner.speech(For every minute it's inside of you, the beast stone's giving you a full year of your feral form. You've already got five years to look forward to of this, and I've barely even started!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly having some kind of intense fetish for fucking ferals, Princess continues rutting your cunt and pumping you full of her cum for well over another hour. Just as she slows down and you start to think that her seemingly-insatiable lust has finally met its match, she produces some kind of potion and quickly downs it. Regaining all of her energy, the centauress takes things from the top, and after another hour of having your cunt thoroughly pounded, she finally pulls back and allows her softening cock to slide free from your cum-stuffed pussy with a lewd, wet pop. Trotting around behind you, she then suddenly shoves her hand into your slimy, musky twat, and with her flared cock no longer there to keep it lodged in position, her precious beast stone is soon recovered, cleaned off, and placed back into its secure wooden box.
	</p>
	<p>
		[owner.speech(Think you can manage almost two centuries in this form?)] Princess sneers as she taps the watch to your side. After you've let out a brief moo in response, she teases, [owner.speech(Well, if we need to give you a few more centuries, I don't think that my beast stone would mind spending some more time in your pussy.)]
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		In this manner, you spend the rest of your life as a feral cow in Evelyx's barn, with your fat, heavy udders being milked the entire time. You're fucked over and over again by Princess, who never once loses her insatiable desire to sink her fat cock into your holes and stuff you full of her cum. In fact, her fetish for fucking ferals makes her desire you more than anyone else in her life, and from that moment on she makes sure to passionately rut you no less than three times every day...
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
