<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- HOTEL_TRAVEL_TO_NEST -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HOTEL_TRAVEL_TO_NEST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Now that you're aware of the fact that there's an elevator linking 'The Golden Feather' hotel to Helena's nest up above, you head inside and make your way across the opulent foyer to where the lift is located. The harpy who's standing on duty beside the elevator doors looks you over as you approach, and after you've told her that you're an intimate acquaintance of Helena's, she respectfully curtsies and says, [style.speechFeminine(Please, [pc.sir], allow me to call the elevator for you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as the harpy says, you watch as she presses the button to call for the lift, before stepping aside and curtsying towards you once again. A few moments and a lot of mechanical whirring later, the doors automatically slide open with a ping, allowing you to step inside the elevator and press the button marked for the roof. After a short ride up,
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			 you and [com.name] soon find yourselves [pc.stepping] out into Helena's nest once again...
		#ELSE
			 you [pc.step] soon find yourself [pc.stepping] out into Helena's nest once again...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HOTEL_TRAVEL_TO_DOMINION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HOTEL_TRAVEL_TO_DOMINION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Now that you're aware of the fact that there's an elevator linking Helena's nest to 'The Golden Feather' hotel below, you head over to the small building in which it's located, before pushing open the door and [pc.stepping] inside. The harpy who's on duty behind the nearby desk looks you over as you enter, and after you've informed her that you're an intimate acquaintance of Helena's, she gestures towards the elevator doors on the other side of the room and says, [style.speechFeminine(Please, [pc.sir], go right ahead.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as the harpy says, you [pc.step] over to the doors and press the button to call for the lift. A few moments and a lot of mechanical whirring later, the doors automatically slide open with a ping, allowing you to step inside the elevator and press the button marked for the ground floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a short ride down and a brief journey across the hotel's opulent foyer,
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			 you and [com.name] [pc.step] out through the grand entrance to once again find yourselves in the streets of Dominion...
		#ELSE
			 you [pc.step] out through the grand entrance to once again find yourself in the streets of Dominion...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
</dialogue>
