<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- DATE_START -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			After telling [com.name] that [com.she] should return home, you ask Helena if she'd like to go out on a date with you this evening.
		#ELSE
			Knowing that Helena will be receptive to the idea, you ask her if she'd like to go out on a dinner date with you this evening.
		#ENDIF
		 Flashing you a delightful smile, the beautiful harpy replies,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateFirstDateComplete))
			 [helena.speech(That sounds wonderful, [pc.name]. I am sure I need not remind you, but I only dine at 'The Golden Feather', so we shall be going there.)]
		#ELSE
			 [helena.speech(That sounds wonderful, [pc.name]. I hope you haven't already made reservations anywhere, for I only dine at 'The Golden Feather' hotel, so we shall be going there.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		From the firm tone of her voice, you can tell that Helena is unwilling to negotiate on this point, and so after accepting her choice of destination, you ask her when she'll be ready to leave. With a swish of her wings, she declares, [helena.speech(I am ready to depart immediately. First, you shall accompany me to my apartment so that I can get ready for our date, and then you shall take me to the restaurant.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you prepare to leave, Helena turns to Scarlett and orders, [helena.speech(I cannot trust you to be left alone, so your work here is finished for the day. I might have need of you later, however, so you shall meet the two of us at my apartment, where I shall give you further instructions if necessary.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speech(Yes, Helena,)] Scarlett replies, before quickly exiting the store and flying off in the direction of the Harpy Nests.
	</p>
	<p>
		After informing one of her harpy employees that they're in charge until closing time, Helena turns back to face you, before smiling and saying, [helena.speech(Please lead the way, [pc.name].)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_TRAVEL_WALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Escorting the beautiful matriarch out of her shop, you [pc.walk] by her side as the two of you travel through the streets of Dominion. Having told you that her apartment is located in the Harpy Nests, Helena happily engages you in idle conversation, which helps to make your somewhat lengthy journey pass in what seems like just a few moments. Before you know it, you find yourselves walking in the shadows cast by the Harpy Nest's huge, rooftop platforms, and as you arrive in the area beneath Helena's nest, the matriarch holds up one of her white-feathered wings to point at a huge building and declare, [helena.speech(That's 'The Golden Feather' hotel. We shall be dining in its restaurant this evening, but before that, I need to head up to my apartment and get changed.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_TRAVEL_WALK_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Escorting the beautiful matriarch out of her shop, you [pc.walk] by her side as the two of you travel through the streets of Dominion. Helena happily engages you in idle conversation while you make your way towards her apartment in the Harpy Nests, which helps to make your somewhat lengthy journey pass in what seems like just a few moments. Before you know it, you once again find yourselves walking in the shadows cast by the Harpy Nest's huge, rooftop platforms, and as you arrive at 'The Golden Feather' hotel, Helena declares, [helena.speech(Let us head inside without delay; I wish to get changed as soon as possible.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_TRAVEL_FLY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Escorting the beautiful matriarch out of her shop, you suggest that the two of you should fly to her apartment so as to arrive there as quickly as possible. Liking the sound of your plan, Helena joins you in taking a short run down the street, before leaping into the air and flying up into the sky above Slaver Alley.
	</p>
	<p>
		With the regal matriarch elegantly gliding along beside you, the two of you fly off in the direction of the Harpy Nests. Thanks to your ability to fly, it only takes a few minutes before you've arrived at your destination, and, letting Helena take the lead, you follow her as she swoops down and lands in the street beneath her nest. The reason for her choice of landing site is quickly revealed, for as you land beside her, the matriarch holds up one of her white-feathered wings to point at a huge building and declare, [helena.speech(That's 'The Golden Feather' hotel. We shall be dining in its restaurant this evening, but before that, I need to head up to my apartment and get changed. There is also a rooftop entrance to the hotel up in my nest, but I do not wish to deal with my followers right now, which is why we shall be entering from ground level.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_TRAVEL_FLY_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Escorting the beautiful matriarch out of her shop, you suggest that the two of you should fly to her apartment so as to arrive there as quickly as possible. Liking the sound of your plan, Helena joins you in taking a short run down the street, before leaping into the air and flying up into the sky above Slaver Alley.
	</p>
	<p>
		With the regal matriarch elegantly gliding along beside you, the two of you fly off in the direction of the Harpy Nests. Thanks to your ability to fly, it only takes a few minutes before you've arrived at your destination, and, letting Helena take the lead, you follow her as she swoops down and lands in the street beneath her nest. With 'The Golden Feather' hotel just across the street from your landing site, Helena declares, [helena.speech(Let us head inside without delay; I wish to get changed as soon as possible.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_TRAVEL_RIDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Escorting the beautiful matriarch out of her shop, you suggest that she could ride on your back so as to arrive at her apartment as quickly as possible. Upon hearing what it is you're suggesting, Helena blushes a little and asks, [helena.speech(You would offer to let me ride upon your back? Are you not concerned that others might think you to be my slave?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling Helena that you don't care what others think, you turn to one side and present your [pc.legRace]'s body for her to sit upon. Continuing to blush a little, Helena flaps up to perch upon your back in a side-saddle position. After the surprisingly-light matriarch has told you that her apartment is located in the Harpy Nests, you set off at a canter off through the streets of Dominion.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she sometimes has to raise her voice a little to be heard over the chattering crowds of people, Helena happily engages you in idle conversation while you carry her towards her apartment, which helps to make your somewhat lengthy journey pass in what seems like just a few moments. Before you know it, you find yourself walking in the shadows cast by the Harpy Nest's huge, rooftop platforms, and as you arrive in the area beneath Helena's nest, the matriarch gets you to halt, before sliding off your back, pointing at a huge building, and declaring, [helena.speech(That's 'The Golden Feather' hotel. We shall be dining in its restaurant this evening, but before that, I need to head up to my apartment and get changed.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_TRAVEL_RIDE_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Escorting the beautiful matriarch out of her shop, you suggest that she could ride on your back so as to arrive at her apartment as quickly as possible. Upon hearing what it is you're suggesting, Helena blushes a little and asks, [helena.speech(You would offer to let me ride upon your back? Are you not concerned that others might think you to be my slave?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling Helena that you don't care what others think, you turn to one side and present your [pc.legRace]'s body for her to sit upon. Continuing to blush a little, Helena flaps up to perch upon your back in a side-saddle position. After the surprisingly-light matriarch has told you that her apartment is located in the Harpy Nests, you set off at a canter off through the streets of Dominion.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she sometimes has to raise her voice a little to be heard over the chattering crowds of people, Helena happily engages you in idle conversation while you carry her towards her apartment, which helps to make your somewhat lengthy journey pass in what seems like just a few moments. Before you know it, you find yourself walking in the shadows cast by the Harpy Nest's huge, rooftop platforms, and as you once again arrive in front of 'The Golden Feather' hotel, you stop to let Helena slip off your back and declare, [helena.speech(Let us head inside without delay; I wish to get changed as soon as possible.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_TRAVEL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_TRAVEL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As Helena starts to lead you towards the hotel's grand entrance, you realise that her apartment must also be in this building. The pretty harpy doorwoman on duty hurries to hold open the door for the two of you, and as she sees that it's none other than Helena herself who's passing her by, she bows down and squeaks, [style.speechFeminine(Good evening, ma'am!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Returning the harpy's greeting, Helena strides through the open door and enters the hotel's grand, opulent foyer, before turning to smile at you and say, [helena.speech(My apartment is on the top floor of this hotel. I shall only be a short while, so it would be best for you to wait here for my return. Oh, look, my dear Scarlett is waiting over there, so you can talk with her while you wait!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Sure enough, you see Scarlett moodily slouched down on one of the many sofas which are positioned on the far side of the foyer, and as Helena strides over to a nearby elevator and disappears from sight, you decide to head over and say hello to the black-feathered harpy. As you approach, she looks up and
		#IF(scarlett.isLikesPlayer())
			 says, [scarlett.speech(Hi, [pc.name]. It looks like both of us are having to wait for Helena's return, huh?)]
		#ELSE
			 mutters, [scarlett.speech(What the fuck do you want, [pc.name]? It's your fault that I'm having to hang around here and wait for Helena instead of finding some harpy slut to fuck...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_TRAVEL_WAIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it would be best to not risk angering Scarlett, you choose not to engage the raven-harpy in conversation and instead quietly wait upon the sofa for Helena to return. Seeming to be just as happy as you are to sit in silence, Scarlett slouches down on her seat, before lifting her bird-like legs and resting her sharp talons upon the coffee table positioned in front of her. Although you notice a couple of the members of staff pointedly glancing over at Scarlett's rude posturing, none of them dare to approach and tell her to stop, letting you know that they must already be aware of Scarlett's short temper.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_TRAVEL_SMALL_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it would be best to pass the time by engaging in conversation with Scarlett, you ask her how she is and if she visits this hotel often.
		#IF(scarlett.isLikesPlayer())
			 Although she tries to hide it, the raven-harpy is clearly happy to be getting a chance to talk with you, and after telling you that she's well, she goes on to explain, [scarlett.speech(I never used to visit this place, but since I became Helena's PA, I've been staying in one of the guest bedrooms in her apartment, so I pretty much live here now. I don't know if she's told you yet, but Helena actually owns this entire hotel, and seeing as I'm so close to her, all the hotel staff let me do pretty much anything I want in here.)]
		#ELSE
			 Although at first she tries to dismiss your questioning with a barrage of her usual foul language, she eventually relents and reluctantly tells you that she's well. Once she starts talking, she can't seem to stop, and quickly goes on to explain, [scarlett.speech(I never used to visit this fucking place, but since I became Helena's PA, I've been staying in one of the guest bedrooms in her apartment, so I pretty much live here now. I don't know if she's told you yet, but Helena actually owns this entire hotel, and seeing as I'm so close to her, all the hotel staff let me do whatever the fuck I want in here.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_RESTAURANT_ROMANTIC_SETUP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_ROMANTIC_SETUP_AGREED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting there to be a romantic atmosphere in Helena's apartment for when you escort her up there after your meal, you ask Scarlett if she could help you set something like that up. Letting out a sigh and slouching even further down on her sofa, the raven-harpy asks, [scarlett.speech(What sort of thing did you have in mind? I doubt just dimming the lights and lighting some candles is going to cut it...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Passing the trio of rose bouquets to Scarlett, you explain how you'd like her to scatter the petals leading from the entrance of Helena's apartment into her bedroom. Liking the sound of the dimmed lights and lit candles, you ask the raven-harpy if she could also do that for you. As you're one of the very few people which she actually likes, Scarlett takes the roses from you and agrees to do as you ask, [scarlett.speech(Sure, I could set all of that up for you. Hopefully it'll put Helena in a good mood over the weekend...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_ROMANTIC_SETUP_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting there to be a romantic atmosphere in Helena's apartment for when you escort her up there after your meal, you ask Scarlett if she could help you set something like that up. Flashing you a withering scowl, she starts to tell you to fuck off, before suddenly changing her mind mid-sentence and slyly offering,
		#IF(scarlett.hasPenis())
			 [scarlett.speech(Sure, I could set that up for you, but it's going to cost you. Either give a thousand flames, or get on your knees and give me a quick blowjob before Helena returns.)]
		#ELSE
			 [scarlett.speech(Sure, I could set that up for you, but it's going to cost you. Either give a thousand flames, or get on your knees and quickly eat me out before Helena returns.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Lifting the skirt of her skater dress, Scarlett grabs hold of her boyshorts and slides them off, before spreading her legs and presenting you with her
		#IF(scarlett.hasPenis())
			 rapidly-hardening cock.
		#ELSE
			 wet pussy.
		#ENDIF
		 As the sofa which she's sitting on has its back to the rest of the foyer, you realise that if you were to perform oral on her, you would be able to do so while remaining out of sight from the staff and other guests who are standing nearby. Flashing you a devious grin, Scarlett asks, [scarlett.speech(So, what's it going to be, cunt? If you want to impress Helena and get to fuck her tight little pussy, you've got to do something for me first.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_ROMANTIC_SETUP_THANKS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking her feet off the coffee table, Scarlett stands up and lets out a big yawn. Wishing you luck with your date, she hurries off to carry out her task, leaving you alone while you wait for Helena. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_ROMANTIC_SETUP_REFUSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not liking the sound of what Scarlett is saying, you flatly tell her that those conditions are not acceptable. Letting out a dismissive huff, the raven-harpy slouches down and says, [scarlett.speech(If you don't fucking like it, then don't fucking bother me about it again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your refusal clearly having put Scarlett in a foul mood, you decide that it would be best not to pay the raven-harpy any more attention, and instead quietly wait upon the sofa for Helena to return. Seeming to be just as happy as you are to sit in silence, Scarlett slouches down even further on her seat, before lifting her bird-like legs and resting her sharp talons upon the coffee table positioned in front of her. Although you notice a couple of the members of staff pointedly glancing over at Scarlett's rude posturing, none of them dare to approach and tell her to stop, letting you know that they must already be aware of Scarlett's short temper.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_ROMANTIC_SETUP_PAID"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that a thousand flames is a small price to pay in exchange for impressing Helena with a romantic gesture, you hand the money over to Scarlett. Sitting up on her sofa, the raven-harpy snatches the flames from out of your [pc.hand], before asking, [scarlett.speech(So what exactly do you fucking want me to do? I don't think just dimming the lights and lighting some candles is going to impress Helena...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Passing the trio of rose bouquets to Scarlett, you explain how you'd like her to scatter the petals leading from the entrance of Helena's apartment into her bedroom. Liking the sound of the dimmed lights and lit candles, you ask the raven-harpy if she could also do that for you. Having already received her payment, Scarlett snatches the roses from you and agrees to do as you ask, [scarlett.speech(Sure, I'll get that set up. It should put Helena in a good mood over the weekend, so it's good for me as well...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking her feet off the coffee table, Scarlett stands up and lets out a big yawn. Throwing one last sneer your way, she hurries off to carry out her task, leaving you alone to wait for Helena. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_ROMANTIC_SETUP_START_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that sucking Scarlett's cock is a small price to pay in exchange for impressing Helena with a romantic gesture, you quickly move forwards and drop your head down between her legs. Grabbing you by
		#IF(pc.hasHorns())
			 your [pc.horns]
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasHair())
			 your [pc.hair(true)]
		#ELSE
			 the back of your head
		#ENDIF
		, Scarlett pulls you down into her groin, forcing the [scarlett.cockHead+] of her dick to brush against your [pc.lips] as she teases, [scarlett.speechNoEffects(Hurry up and suck my cock, bitch! You wouldn't want Helena returning to see me balls-deep down your throat, so make sure you get to me cum as quickly as possible!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Agreeing with Scarlett's remark, you part your [pc.lips] and take her throbbing shaft into your mouth. Letting out an evil chuckle, the sadistic harpy slams your head down, forcing you to swallow her cock to the base as she teases, [scarlett.speechNoEffects(That's it, bitch! Keep going until I'm cumming down your throat!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With little choice now but to do as she says, you set about greedily sucking and slurping on Scarlett's cock...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_ROMANTIC_SETUP_START_CUNNILINGUS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that performing cunnilingus on Scarlett is a small price to pay in exchange for impressing Helena with a romantic gesture, you quickly move forwards and drop your head down between her legs. Grabbing you by
		#IF(pc.hasHorns())
			 your [pc.horns]
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasHair())
			 your [pc.hair(true)]
		#ELSE
			 the back of your head
		#ENDIF
		, Scarlett pulls you down into her groin, forcing your [pc.lips] against her [scarlett.labia+] as she teases, [scarlett.speechNoEffects(Hurry up and eat me out, bitch! You wouldn't want Helena returning to see your tongue stuffed deep in my wet cunt, so make sure you get to me climax as quickly as possible!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Agreeing with Scarlett's remark, you part your [pc.lips] and start licking her sensitive little clit. Letting out an evil chuckle, the sadistic harpy slams your head down, grinding your mouth down against her pussy as she teases, [scarlett.speechNoEffects(That's it, bitch! Keep going until I'm squirting all over your face!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With little choice now but to do as she says, you set about greedily licking and kissing Scarlett's wet cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_RESTAURANT_ROMANTIC_SETUP_AFTER_ORAL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_ROMANTIC_SETUP_AFTER_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had her fun, Scarlett pushes you back a little, before commanding,
		#IF(scarlett.hasPenis())
			 [scarlett.speechNoEffects(Clean my cock, bitch, then I'll do what you want.)]
		#ELSE
			 [scarlett.speechNoEffects(Clean my pussy, bitch, then I'll do what you want.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Having already gone this far, you see no harm in doing as Scarlett asks, and
		#IF(scarlett.hasPenis())
			 lean in to her groin to lick the excess cum and saliva off her cock.
		#ELSE
			 lean in to her groin to lick the excess fluids and saliva off her [scarlett.labia+].
		#ENDIF
		 Triumphantly chuckling to herself as you quickly finish cleaning her up, Scarlett leans back on the sofa and says, [scarlett.speech(Ok, bitch, that's enough. You can sit back down now. Oh, and you'd better wipe your face before Helena sees you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as the raven-harpy suggests, you sit back down on the sofa opposite hers, before grabbing a nearby tissue and hurriedly wiping the sexual fluids from off of your face. As you finish cleaning yourself up, Scarlett sits up on her sofa and asks, [scarlett.speech(So what exactly do you want me to do? I don't think just dimming the lights and lighting some candles is going to impress Helena...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Passing the trio of rose bouquets to Scarlett, you explain how you'd like her to scatter the petals leading from the entrance of Helena's apartment into her bedroom. Liking the sound of the dimmed lights and lit candles, you ask the raven-harpy if she could also do that for you. Having already received her 'payment' from you, Scarlett snatches the roses and agrees to do as you ask, [scarlett.speech(Sure, I'll get that set up. It should put Helena in a good mood over the weekend, so it's good for me as well...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking her feet off the coffee table, Scarlett stands up and lets out a big yawn. Throwing one last triumphant smirk your way, she hurries off to carry out her task, leaving you alone to wait for Helena. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_RESTAURANT_START -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateRomanticSetup))
			After another few minutes spent waiting on the sofa, you see the elevator doors on the other side of the foyer slide open, and from within the regal figure of Helena emerges.
		#ELSE
			After another fifteen minutes spent in Scarlett's company, you see the elevator doors on the other side of the foyer slide open, and from within the regal figure of Helena emerges.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Matching the colour of her painted nails and lipstick, she's shamelessly wearing a bright pink, plunge-neck clubbing dress, which leaves most of her breasts and stomach completely exposed. Biting her lip and beckoning you over to her with one of her white wings, she does a little spin on the spot and sluttily teases, [helena.speech(I chose to wear this as I thought it'd be the easiest to slip out of once we get up to my bedroom later... Before that, however, should we proceed to dinner?)]
		#ELSE
			 Matching the colour of her flawless feathers, she's wearing an elegant white evening gown, which, along with her diamond necklace and delicate golden tiara, accentuates her beauty to the point where the hotel's staff members are left unable to do anything but stare at her in awe. Moving to meet her as she gracefully strides across the room, you offer the harpy a sincere compliment on her appearance, which causes her blush a little and reply, [helena.speech(I'm pleased to hear that you like my choice of dress. Now, shall we proceed to dinner?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateRomanticSetup))
			After you've replied in the positive, Helena tells Scarlett that her presence will not be needed after all, and after the raven-harpy has moodily stomped off, she
		#ELSE
			Clearly not requiring Scarlett's presence, Helena makes no mention of the fact that the raven-harpy is missing, and as soon as you've replied to her previous question in the positive, she
		#ENDIF
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 leans in close to lewdly whisper to you, [helena.speech(By the way, [pc.name], I was in such a hurry that I forgot to put on any underwear... I hope you won't be distracted by that thought...)]
		#ELSE
			 steps up close beside you and pointedly says, [helena.speech(The restaurant is through the doors over there, [pc.name].)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Escorting the beautiful matriarch across the room and into the extravagantly-furnished restaurant, you're immediately approached by a smartly-dressed harpy waitress, who politely and professionally leads you over to what she describes as the best table in the restaurant. Sure enough, as you and Helena sit down opposite to one another, you find that the position of your table near to the corner of the room grants you a decent level of privacy while also not feeling as though you've been placed somewhere out of sight.
	</p>
	<p>
		After giving each of you a menu and describing the day's specials, the waitress asks what you'd like to drink. Knowing exactly what it is she wants, Helena asks for the most expensive bottle of wine on the list, before looking into your eyes and asking, [helena.speech(You'll share this bottle with me, won't you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_START_WINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to let Helena down, you tell the waitress that you'll be sharing the bottle of wine with her. Having taken your drink orders, the harpy quickly darts off to fetch the bottle of wine, leaving Helena to smugly state,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateFirstDateComplete))
			 [helena.speech(As I own this hotel, there'll be no charge for anything on the menu, so just like the last time, you won't have the opportunity to impress me by offering to pay for the meal.)]
		#ELSE
			 [helena.speech(I don't think I've mentioned it to you yet, but I actually own this entire hotel. There'll be no charge for anything on the menu, so I'm afraid that you don't have the opportunity to impress me by offering to pay for the meal.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment, the harpy waitress returns with the bottle of wine, and after opening it and pouring a small amount in Helena's glass for her to taste, she proceeds to pour each of you a full glass. Having already looked over the menu, you're able to then give the waitress your order, and after Helena has also chosen what she'd like for her meal, the waitress bows and darts off, leaving the two of you alone at last. As you take a drink from your wine glass, Helena smiles at you and strikes up a conversation...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_START_WATER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to drink any alcohol, you tell the waitress that you'd just like some water. Having taken your orders, the harpy quickly darts off to fetch your drinks, leaving Helena to pout and state,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateFirstDateComplete))
			 [helena.speech(I was hoping you'd share the wine with me, [pc.name]... Anyway, I just wanted to remind you that as I own this hotel, there'll be no charge for anything on the menu, so you won't have the opportunity to impress me by offering to pay for the meal.)]
		#ELSE
			 [helena.speech(I was hoping you'd share the wine with me, [pc.name]... Anyway, I don't think I've mentioned it to you yet, but I actually own this entire hotel. There'll be no charge for anything on the menu, so I'm afraid that you don't have the opportunity to impress me by offering to pay for the meal.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment, the harpy waitress returns with both your glass of water and Helena's chosen bottle of wine. After placing your drink down before you, she proceeds to open the bottle and pour a small amount in Helena's glass for her to taste. Expressing her approval, Helena waits for the waitress to pour her a full glass before telling her what she'd like to order for her meal. Having already looked over the menu, you're also able to give the waitress your order, and after you've done so, the harpy bows and darts off, leaving you and Helena alone at last. As you take a drink from your glass of water, Helena smiles at you and strikes up a conversation...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_START_BEER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not liking the sound of sharing a bottle of wine with Helena, you tell the waitress that you'd like a beer instead. Having taken your orders, the harpy quickly darts off to fetch your drinks, leaving Helena to pout and state,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateFirstDateComplete))
			 [helena.speech(I was hoping you'd share the wine with me, [pc.name]... Anyway, I just wanted to remind you that as I own this hotel, there'll be no charge for anything on the menu, so you won't have the opportunity to impress me by offering to pay for the meal.)]
		#ELSE
			 [helena.speech(I was hoping you'd share the wine with me, [pc.name]... Anyway, I don't think I've mentioned it to you yet, but I actually own this entire hotel. There'll be no charge for anything on the menu, so I'm afraid that you don't have the opportunity to impress me by offering to pay for the meal.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment, the harpy waitress returns with both your beer and Helena's chosen bottle of wine. After placing your drink down before you, she proceeds to open the wine bottle and pour a small amount in Helena's glass for her to taste. Expressing her approval, Helena waits for the waitress to pour her a full glass before telling her what she'd like to order for her meal. Having already looked over the menu, you're also able to give the waitress your order, and after you've done so, the harpy bows and darts off, leaving you and Helena alone at last. As you take a drink of beer, Helena smiles at you and strikes up a conversation...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_START_WHISKEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not liking the sound of sharing a bottle of wine with Helena, you tell the waitress that you'd like a glass of whiskey instead. Having taken your orders, the harpy quickly darts off to fetch your drinks, leaving Helena to pout and state,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateFirstDateComplete))
			 [helena.speech(I was hoping you'd share the wine with me, [pc.name]... Anyway, I just wanted to remind you that as I own this hotel, there'll be no charge for anything on the menu, so you won't have the opportunity to impress me by offering to pay for the meal.)]
		#ELSE
			 [helena.speech(I was hoping you'd share the wine with me, [pc.name]... Anyway, I don't think I've mentioned it to you yet, but I actually own this entire hotel. There'll be no charge for anything on the menu, so I'm afraid that you don't have the opportunity to impress me by offering to pay for the meal.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment, the harpy waitress returns with both your whiskey and Helena's chosen bottle of wine. After placing your drink down before you, she proceeds to open the wine bottle and pour a small amount in Helena's glass for her to taste. Expressing her approval, Helena waits for the waitress to pour her a full glass before telling her what she'd like to order for her meal. Having already looked over the menu, you're also able to give the waitress your order, and after you've done so, the harpy bows and darts off, leaving you and Helena alone at last. As you take a drink of whiskey, Helena smiles at you and strikes up a conversation...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Slavery: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_TALKING_SLAVES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[helena.speech(You weren't around at the time, [pc.name], or else I might have asked for your assistance in the matter, but the other day there was a group of protesters marching through Slaver Alley, shouting for slavery to be abolished,)] the matriarch reveals, the tone of her voice clearly conveying the fact that she disapproves of such protests. Taking another sip of her wine, she leans back in her chair and states, [helena.speech(That rabble kicked up such a fuss that I had to personally fly over to the Enforcer Headquarters and demand they come and break it up. Needless to say, the sergeant on duty rushed to my aid, and within the hour all of the protesters had been arrested. A few of them actually ended up getting enslaved themselves as a punishment for assaulting the Enforcers who were trying to arrest them!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly finding this fact amusing, Helena lets out a soft laugh, before asking, [helena.speech(What's your view on slavery, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_TALKING_SLAVES_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Some more protesters showed up in Slaver Alley the other day, shouting all kinds of nonsense about how slavery should be abolished,)] Helena says, before taking another sip of her wine and continuing, [helena.speech(Of course, I had the Enforcers come and arrest them, but I get the feeling that sooner or later those of them who weren't enslaved themselves will be back to start another protest. Honestly, I don't see why the Enforcers don't just enslave them all!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a weary sigh, Helena takes yet another sip of wine and asks, [helena.speech(Remind me, [pc.name], what do you think of slavery?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_SLAVES_NATURAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself approving of how Helena handled the protesters, you tell her that you believe slavery to be perfectly natural. Making the point that there are hierarchies everywhere you look in nature, you say that slaves fit into their rightful place at the very bottom of society. What's more, you argue that it's actually a blessing for most slaves to be given the chance to contribute in some way to society, for without slavery, criminals would have to be kept as prisoners at great expense to law-abiding tax payers.
	</p>
	<p>
		Delighted to hear that your views line up with hers, Helena can't help but let a big smile cross her face, and as you finish giving your opinion, she continues to expand upon the points which you've laid out. In this manner, the two of you continue your discussion on how slavery is of great benefit to society, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_SLAVES_NECESSITY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you know that Helena won't agree with what you're saying, you think it's best to give her your honest opinion on the matter of slavery. Telling her that you disapprove of it from a moral standpoint, you reluctantly concede the fact that it seems like a necessity in Dominion's society. After all, without slavery as a means of deterring and punishing criminals, the Enforcers might struggle to keep law and order in a city which already seems to have a serious problem with muggers and rapists.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although your point of view doesn't entirely line up with hers, Helena appears to be happy that you've given her your honest opinion, and after you've finished speaking, she respectfully argues that slavery is both natural and beneficial to society. In this manner, the two of you continue your discussion on slavery, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_SLAVES_WRONG"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you know that expressing your honest opinion on the matter of slavery is likely to annoy Helena, you feel as though you shouldn't lie to her just to get her to like you. With this in mind, you tell the matriarch that you think slavery is abhorrent, and you hope that one day it will be completely abolished. Considering the fact that Helena's business is completely reliant upon the slave trade, you hasten to add that you don't mean any ill-will towards her, but that you simply can't ever see a moral justification for owning other people as though they're nothing but property.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just as you expected, your answer appears to annoy Helena, and after you've finished speaking, she flaps her wings in frustration and launches into a passionate argument for how slavery is both natural and beneficial to society. Although at times your discussion threatens to heat up to the point of serious conflict, the two of you manage to keep your cool as you argue for and against slavery, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Harpy nests: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_TALKING_HARPY_NESTS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_HARPY_PACIFICATION))
			[helena.speech(So, I've heard that it was you who pacified the other matriarchs up in the Harpy Nests,)] Helena remarks, sipping her wine and smiling at you for a brief moment before continuing, [helena.speech(I've heard some people complain about the way we run things up there, but in truth it's not often that the Nests get into such a state. Besides, even if things do get a little chaotic every now and then, it's nobody's business but ours.)]
		#ELSE
			[helena.speech(You've no doubt heard about the other matriarchs kicking up a fuss in the Harpy Nests?)] Helena asks, stopping to sip her wine while she waits for your answer. After you've responded in the affirmative, she smiles at you and continues, [helena.speech(Well, I've heard some people complain about the way we run things up there, but in truth it's not often that the Nests get into such a state. Besides, even if things do get a little chaotic every now and then, it's nobody's business but ours.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning back in her chair and letting out a small sigh, the beautiful matriarch asks, [helena.speech(What's your opinion on the way the Harpy Nests are managed, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_TALKING_HARPY_NESTS_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[helena.speech(You know, a complete stranger actually had the gall to try and complain to me directly about 'the state' of the Harpy Nests the other day!)] Helena remarks, the tone of her voice conveying her disbelief at the fact that anyone would attempt to do such a thing. Taking a small sip of wine, she continues, [helena.speech(Of course, I had my followers subdue her and give her a proper punishment for her insolence, but the fact that she'd gone out of her way to stick her nose in my business really ruined my day. I must admit that after I'd had her punished, I was still so frustrated that I had the Enforcers arrest her for trying to stir up trouble in the Nests.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning back in her chair and letting out a small sigh, the beautiful matriarch asks, [helena.speech(Anyway, could you remind me of your opinion on the way the Harpy Nests are managed, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_HARPY_NESTS_HELENA_TOP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having seen first-hand the chaos that's caused when the Nests' matriarchs lose their cool, you tell Helena that things would most likely be a lot more stable under a more centralised system of control. Encouraged by the approving smile which Helena flashes you as you say this, you continue by saying that there should be a single harpy queen which all other matriarchs should swear fealty to, and that you couldn't think of a better candidate for this role than Helena herself.
	</p>
	<p>
		Allowing a very smug smile to settle on her face, Helena tells you that she's often thought of the exact same thing, but unfortunately, the other harpy matriarchs would never agree to give up their power like that. Although she doesn't seem to have high hopes of it ever becoming a reality, Helena is more than happy to continue discussing the details of a feudal harpy society with you, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_HARPY_NESTS_BALANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that the situation in the Harpy Nests isn't exactly good or bad, you tell Helena that things seem to have found a good balance up there. While there are always things that can be improved in any society, the harpy matriarchs, including her, seem to be doing a good job of keeping things under control.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she seems to be satisfied by your answer, Helena doesn't show any sign of being overly happy about what you've just said, and instead continues to press you on what areas of harpy society need improving. Focusing on the way the other matriarchs sometimes let their flocks get out of control, you continue to discuss the management of the Harpy Nests with Helena, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_HARPY_NESTS_BAD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that the management of the Harpy Nests leaves much to be desired, you tell Helena that the entire system of matriarchs ruling over flocks of subservient harpies is not one that should be allowed to stay in place for much longer. Pointing out the fact that the other nests sometimes fall into complete chaos and disarray, you suggest that harpies should abandon their hierarchical social structure and instead try to integrate more into normal Dominion society.
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly taking great offence at your direct criticism of the society which she helps to maintain, Helena lets out a frustrated huff and crosses her wing-like arms. As you try to justify your opinion to her, she flaps her wings and starts passionately arguing back in an attempt to convince you of the necessity of matriarchs in harpy society. Although at times your discussion threatens to heat up to the point of serious conflict, the two of you manage to keep your cool as you argue about the management of the Harpy Nests, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Races: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_TALKING_RACES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[helena.speech(I did some modelling work for a fashion magazine the other day, and one of the photographers actually had the audacity to say that humans are more attractive than harpies!)] Helena scoffs, before taking a sip of her wine and continuing,
		#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_HARPY)
			 [helena.speech(We harpies are quite clearly the most attractive race, and after I pointed this out to the photographer, I had him immediately fired for daring to insult me in such a crude manner. Quite rightly, after that little incident, everyone else agreed that not only harpies are the most attractive race, but that I am the most beautiful of them all.)]
		#ELSEIF(pc.getRace()==RACE_HUMAN)
			 [helena.speech(I don't mean to offend you, [pc.name], what with you being a human and all, but we harpies are quite clearly the most attractive race. After I pointed this out to the photographer, I had him immediately fired for daring to insult me in such a crude manner. Quite rightly, after that little incident, everyone else agreed that not only harpies are the most attractive race, but that I am the most beautiful of them all.)]
		#ELSE
			 [helena.speech(Harpies are quite clearly the most attractive race, and after I pointed this out to the photographer, I had him immediately fired for daring to insult me in such a crude manner. Quite rightly, after that little incident, everyone else agreed that not only harpies are the most attractive race, but that I am the most beautiful of them all.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Fluffing up her feathers in pride, the regal matriarch smiles at you and asks, [helena.speech(So, [pc.name], which race do you think is the most attractive?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_TALKING_RACES_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[helena.speech(As you've no doubt noticed, all of the staff who work in this hotel are harpies,)] Helena states, before taking a quick sip of wine and continuing, [helena.speech(I've instructed the management to never employ any other race, as I want only the most attractive of people to work here. From what I am told, some people actually pay to be transformed into a harpy before applying for a job here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a soft laugh, the regal matriarch smiles at you and asks, [helena.speech(So, [pc.name], would you agree that harpies are the most attractive race?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_RACES_HARPIES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Agreeing with Helena's point of view, you tell the proud matriarch that harpies are undoubtedly the most attractive of all races, and that she is the most beautiful of all. Encouraged by the smug smirk which quickly settles on Helena's face, you continue to praise the various physical features of harpies and say how other races simply can't compete with their universal good looks.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you bring an end to your flattery, Helena makes a show of lifting one of her flawless white wings to stroke back her head-feathers. Happily flashing you a big smile, she then launches into her own reasons for why harpies are the best of all races. Finding yourself agreeing with the vast majority of what she says, you continue to discuss the matter of harpies' beauty with Helena, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_RACES_OTHER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you want to tell her the truth, you also don't want to offend Helena, and so you make sure to choose your words carefully as you tell her that you actually find a race other than harpies to be the most beautiful. As you say this, a dark look crosses the haughty harpy's face, and you realise that despite your best efforts, she seems as though she's taking great offence at your words. Not wanting this date to come to a sudden end, you make sure to quickly follow up by saying that there are always exceptions to your preference, and that Helena is most definitely one of those. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Although her angry glare fades away as you praise her good looks, Helena still doesn't seem very happy about what you've just said, and proceeds to question you on why harpies aren't your favourite race. By continuing to compliment her good looks as you answer the matriarch's questions, you manage to defuse the situation, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_RACES_PERSONALITY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself disagreeing on a fundamental level with what Helena is saying, you explain to her how you don't find any particular race to be more attractive than another, and that to you, a person's true beauty is revealed through their personality. Admitting that looks do play at least a small part in your attraction towards someone, you emphasise the point that you could never be attracted to someone who's cruel, shallow, or manipulative, no matter how beautiful they may look.
	</p>
	<p>
		Unfortunately, this seems to be the last thing which Helena wanted to hear, and as you finish expressing your opinion, she lets out a scornful huff and crosses her wing-like arms. Clearly having taken great offence at what you've said, she furrows her eyebrows and shoots you an angry glare, before starting to scold you for not appreciating her beauty. Realising that your date is in danger of coming to an abrupt end, you passionately express to Helena that it wasn't your intention to insult her, and that you do indeed appreciate how beautiful she is. After almost twenty minutes spent explaining yourself to her, your words eventually seem to calm the angry harpy down, and after flashing you a slight smile, she says that she forgives you for insulting her.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Harpies: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_TALKING_HARPIES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Oh, look, there's a raven-harpy sitting at the table over there. She reminds you of my dear Scarlett, does she not?)] Helena observes, gesturing over to the opposite side of the restaurant. Looking across to where the matriarch is pointing, you see the pretty black-feathered harpy which she's talking about, but before you can offer a reply to her question, Helena continues, [helena.speech(Of course, she's far uglier than Scarlett, and I can tell from her face that she's a complete bitch. While my dear Scarlett's temperament also leaves much to be desired, she's at least far more attractive than that whore.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Finishing her cruel assessment of this complete stranger by taking a sip of her wine, Helena lets out a small sigh and laments, [helena.speech(If there's one thing I regret, it's enslaving and selling my dear Scarlett to you. While she often annoys me with her attitude, she is one of the most loyal members of my flock. What do you think of her, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_TALKING_HARPIES_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[helena.speech(My dear Scarlett was causing a nuisance earlier today,)] Helena sighs, [helena.speech(I left her alone for just five minutes, and in that time, she insulted a client so viciously that they ran off in tears. No matter how many times I punish her, she never changes her hostile attitude towards others...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking a small pause to have a sip of her wine, Helena flashes you a smile and says, [helena.speech(Although she causes a lot of trouble, she is still one of the most loyal members of my flock... What do you think of her, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_HARPIES_CONTROL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Helena that Scarlett's loyalty is admirable, and that while she may be rude to others, she is undoubtedly a most excellent companion for her to have. Seeing a warm smile break out on Helena's face, you continue by saying how impressive it is that she's able to subdue Scarlett with no more than a glance or a few well-chosen words.
	</p>
	<p>
		Being very receptive to your praise of her, Helena allows her smile to shift into a smug smirk, and after you've finished speaking, she encourages you to continue flattering her. Giving the haughty matriarch what she wants, you continue to express your admiration of how she's able to control not only Scarlett, but an entire nest of harpies. Silencing you with a swish of one of her large wings, the proud harpy then starts arrogantly singing her own praises, and before you know it, you've spent twenty minutes listening to how amazing she is.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_HARPIES_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to be as truthful as possible with Helena, you tell her that while Scarlett may behave while in her presence, her insufferable rudeness to almost everyone else is a real cause for concern. Seeing the matriarch's expression darken as you say this, you hasten to add that Scarlett's loyalty is something to be praised, but that her bad manners and foul language keep you from being able to describe her as a good person.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she's not happy about the way you've described her loyal companion, Helena reluctantly agrees that Scarlett's lack of manners is an issue that someday should be seriously addressed. With much to be said on the matter of Scarlett's interactions with others, you and Helena continue to discuss her behaviour, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_HARPIES_BITCH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Harbouring a deep dislike of Scarlett and the way in which she insults others, you tell Helena that the raven-harpy is unworthy of her companionship, and that the sooner she's either disciplined or sold off into slavery again, the better. Using several examples of how poorly she's treated both you and others, you describe Scarlett as being a complete bitch, with her only redeeming feature being her loyalty to Helena.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you finish speaking, Helena lets out a very annoyed huff, and after crossing her arms and glaring angrily at you, she launches into a passionate argument about how you've completely misjudged Scarlett. Realising that your entire date is in danger of coming to an abrupt end, you decide to give her the apology which she suddenly demands of you, before saying how you might have been wrong to have described Scarlett in such a negative manner. Thankfully, that seems to be enough to pacify the haughty matriarch, and after letting out one last huff, she unfolds her arms and engages you in further discussion about Scarlett's behaviour. Making sure not to say anything else that might rile her up, you continue talking with Helena in this manner, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Business: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_TALKING_BUSINESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Would you believe it, but today I discovered that a rival store in Slaver Alley has copied my idea of selling custom slaves!)] Helena exclaims, before taking a sip of her wine and continuing, [helena.speech(Of course, those amateurs pose no threat to me, and to make sure that they don't interfere with my business, I've already spread several vicious rumours about them. It'll only be a matter of time before the Enforcers step in and close their business down to investigate. I imagine that they've taken on quite a hefty amount of debt to get set up, and so when they get shut down, perhaps I'll make some inquiries and see if I can have them enslaved.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a soft laugh, Helena turns her thoughts to her own business and asks, [helena.speech(I really have done a most excellent job in making my boutique the most popular store in all of Slaver Alley, have I not?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_TALKING_BUSINESS_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[helena.speech(I think that today was the busiest my boutique has ever been,)] Helena remarks, before leaning back and relaxing in her chair. Pausing to take a small sip of wine, she continues, [helena.speech(I believe that we took around thirty orders for custom slaves, which will make me more money than other stores do in an entire month! I really am such a genius for having thought of this business idea.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Flashing you a sweet smile, the beautiful matriarch asks, [helena.speech(I really have done a most excellent job in making my boutique the most popular store in all of Slaver Alley, have I not?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_BUSINESS_FLATTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing what it is that Helena wants to hear, you tell her that she's done an outstanding job of getting her boutique set up, and that only she could have ever pulled it off so flawlessly. Seeing a big, smug smile settle on the haughty harpy's face, you continue to heap praise upon her by pointing out that while other shops in Slaver Alley have worked for years to become well-established, she managed to beat them all in just a matter of days.
	</p>
	<p>
		Happily beaming at you, Helena waits for a pause in your flattering remarks before launching into her own arrogant boasts. After declaring herself to be the greatest businesswoman Dominion has ever seen, she engages you in an intense discussion about all the other businesses she owns, including this very hotel which you're dining in tonight. While most of the conversation revolves around how amazing she is, you find Helena to be most interesting to talk to, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_BUSINESS_CREDIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While you agree that Helena has definitely had the largest role to play in the success of her business, you point out that none of it would have been possible without your help. Reminding her about all the work you did to renovate her store's frontage, you pose the question of how she'd have managed without you.
	</p>
	<p>
		While you raise a legitimate point, Helena clearly doesn't like being reminded of the fact that she relied upon outside help to get her boutique up and running. After half-heartedly thanking you for your help, she launches into a passionate argument about how she'd have been able to all the work herself if you hadn't helped her. Although you aren't quite so sure of that, you decide not to harm the harpy's pride any more than you've already done so. Steering the topic of conversation back to focusing on her successful management of her boutique, you engage Helena in a lively discussion, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RESPONSE_BUSINESS_SURPRISE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it's best to be truthful, you tell Helena that you're actually very surprised to have seen how successful her boutique has become. While you could see almost from the start that her fame was going to end up attracting a good deal of attention, you thought that it would be difficult to translate this popularity into a profitable business.
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly not the right thing to have said to her, Helena pouts as you say that her success took you by surprise, and as you finish talking, she starts angrily asking you if you really think so little of her. Realising that your date is in danger of coming to an abrupt end, you tell Helena that you didn't mean to offend her, and that if anything, the surprise success of her business is a testament to how well she's managed it. Huffing and tutting at you, the haughty harpy continues to argue that you need to give her more credit for her boutique's success, and before you know it, almost twenty minutes have passed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_RESTAURANT_PLAYER_TOPIC -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_PLAYER_TOPIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminine(Excuse me,)] a feminine voice gently calls out from behind you, interrupting the conversation which you and Helena were having. Turning to look back at the origin of the voice, you see the harpy waitress waiting to place your food down on the table. Leaning back a little to let her do so, you thank her and watch as she does a little curtsy and hurries off to let the two of you eat your food in peace.
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing just that, the two of you set about working your way through your meals, stopping every now and then to exchange remarks on how delicious your food is.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Up until now, Helena has managed to keep her newly-awoken libido in check, but as you finish eating, you suddenly feet her talons rub up against your [pc.leg] beneath the table. Taking another sip of wine and seductively biting her lip at you, she lewdly teases,
			#IF(helena.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				 [helena.speech(Have you decided on how you want me fuck you later?)]
			#ELSE
				 [helena.speech(Have you decided on how you want to fuck me later?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 Soon enough, the two of you have finished eating, and after taking another sip of her wine, Helena strikes up a conversation about how her week has been. Smiling happily at you as she talks about the sorts of customers she's had to deal with, the beautiful matriarch finishes by asking, [helena.speech(So, [pc.name], what have you been up to recently?)] 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			Giving Helena what she wants, you start flirting with her and teasing her about what sort of dirty things the two of you could do in her bedroom later this evening. Before long, you've managed to get the regal matriarch's cheeks to flush red from excitement, but just as she seems on the verge of losing control of herself, the harpy waitress returns and asks, [style.speechFeminine(Was everything to your satisfaction?)]
		#ELSE
			Happy to hear that Helena is interested in your life, you recount the tales of your adventures throughout Dominion to her. Fascinated to hear the sort of exciting things you've been getting up to, the regal matriarch is soon leaning forwards over the table and listening intently to your every word. Just as you finish telling Helena one of your many tales, the harpy waitress suddenly makes a return and asks, [style.speechFeminine(Was everything to your satisfaction?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After you and Helena have replied in the positive, the waitress swiftly clears your empty plates, before quickly returning and offering you a pair of dessert menus. Expressing her desire to order something sweet, Helena insists that you also order a dessert. Surrendering to the matriarch's demand, you choose something off of the menu which you like the sound of. Having taken your orders, the waitress curtsies again and darts off to the kitchen, leaving you with the opportunity to strike up a conversation of your choosing with Helena...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_PLAYER_TOPIC_HELENA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that she likes to talk about herself, you ask Helena what plans she has for the weekend. Clearly happy to be the focus of your conversation, Helena flashes you a big smile as she hears what it is you're asking, before leaving you to wait for a moment as she quickly finishes off the last of her wine.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(What are my plans for the weekend?)] she ponders out loud as she places the now-empty glass back down on the table,
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 before lewdly teasing,
			#IF(pc.hasPenis())
				#IF(helena.isVaginaVirgin())
					 [helena.speech(Well, other than spending this evening with your cock pounding my tight little asshole, I have plans on Saturday to do a photo shoot for a fashion magazine. On Sunday I have some business in my nest to attend to, but if you're around, you could always pay me a visit. I'm sure I could make time for you to give my horny little butt another good, hard fuck...)]
				#ELSE
					 [helena.speech(Well, other than spending this evening with your cock pounding my wet pussy, I have plans on Saturday to do a photo shoot for a fashion magazine. On Sunday I have some business in my nest to attend to, but if you're around, you could always pay me a visit. I'm sure I could make time for you to give my horny little cunt another good, hard fuck...)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				[helena.speech(Well, other than spending this evening with your face between my legs, I have plans on Saturday to do a photo shoot for a fashion magazine. On Sunday I have some business in my nest to attend to, but if you're around, you could always pay me a visit. I'm sure I could make time for you to eat out my horny little pussy again...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			before revealing, [helena.speech(Well, I have plans on Saturday to do a photo shoot for a fashion magazine. On Sunday I have some business in my nest to attend to, but if you're around, you could always pay me a visit if you'd like.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_PLAYER_TOPIC_ARCANE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to talk about spells and enchantments, you turn the topic of conversation to matters of the arcane by asking Helena what experience she has with it. Quickly finishing off her wine, the matriarch lets out a small sigh as she takes a moment to think of how to answer, before placing her now-empty glass back down on the table and leaning towards you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Although I've spent a few years studying it, I'm not really all that interested in the arcane,)] she reveals, letting you know that this choice of conversation topic was perhaps not the best.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Biting her lip and lifting one of her bird-like feet up to brush against your [pc.leg], she continues, [helena.speech(I only studied it so that I could use some spells in order to help me secure my place as a nest's matriarch. I'd much rather spend my time spreading my legs for you than spending hours poring over dusty old spell books. Speaking of which, I can't wait to get back up to my bedroom with you this evening...)]
		#ELSE
			 Flashing you a good-natured smile, she continues, [helena.speech(I only studied it so that I could use some spells in order to help me secure my place as a nest's matriarch. I'd much rather spend my time managing my businesses or doing photo shoots for fashion magazines rather than spending hours poring over dusty old spell books...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_PLAYER_TOPIC_POLITICS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to hear Helena's opinion on the state of politics in Lilith's Realm, you ask her what she thinks of Lilith and her daughters. Clearly not at all interested in the matter, the matriarch lets out a disappointed sigh, before leaving you to wait for a moment as she quickly finishes off the last of her wine.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(I honestly don't care at all about any politics outside of the Harpy Nests,)] she reveals, letting you know that this choice of conversation topic was not a good one.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Lifting one of her bird-like feet up to brush against your [pc.leg], she teases, [helena.speech(You don't want to talk about something as boring as politics, do you? How about you tell me how you want to fuck me tonight instead...)]
		#ELSE
			 Brushing one of her wings over her beautiful plume of head-feathers, she sighs and continues, [helena.speech(I'd rather we didn't talk about something as boring as politics this evening...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Although you think it's best to do as she asks, you're still interested in Helena's views on politics, and so ask her instead about how the matriarchs in the Harpy Nests organise and control their flocks. Although she lets out an exasperated sigh, Helena nevertheless gives you what you want and starts to engage you in a discussion about harpy politics.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_PLAYER_TOPIC_SEX_LIFE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Confident that Helena likes you enough by now to talk with you about her sex life, you tactfully ask her about her previous partners. Although you'd guessed that she's not too comfortable talking about such things, you're still caught a little off-guard as you see the matriarch's cheeks flush red from embarrassment as she hears what it is you're asking. With a small, nervous flap of her wings, she reveals, [helena.speech(I-I haven't ever had a 'partner' before... I've been far too busy ruling over my nest and managing my businesses to have had time to think about things like that!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Considering how beautiful and popular she is, you can't quite believe that Helena's never had a romantic interest before. Wanting to make sure that you've understood her correctly, you rephrase your question and ask if she's ever dated any of the harpies in her nest. Still furiously blushing, Helena admits, [helena.speech(If you must know, I've never been on a romantic date with anyone before you. I... I've never even kissed someone before...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment, the harpy waitress returns carrying the desserts you've ordered. Placing them down on the table in front of you, she gives each of you a big smile before darting off and leaving the two of you alone once again. With her cheeks still flushed red from embarrassment, Helena casts her gaze down and starts eating her dessert in silence. Not wanting your date to end on such an awkward note, you try to shift the topic of conversation and get Helena talking about something else, but, much to your surprise, she cuts you off by blurting out, [helena.speech(It's not as though I don't want to be kissed or anything! It's just that most people seem to be scared of asking me out, and the only ones who've done so have really not been my type at all...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having a lot more to say on the matter, Helena continues to open up to you about her non-existent sex life. Although she continues to blush and occasionally trips over her words in her embarrassment, she seems almost desperate in her haste to tell you how she's still a virgin, and that until she met you, she's never had the time nor inclination to have a romantic relationship with anyone. After lamenting upon the fact that she's the only one out of all the harpies in her inner-circle who's never had sex, she lets out a deep sigh and finally falls silent.
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you're able to strike up any further conversation with Helena, the harpy waitress returns to clear your empty dessert dishes away, before smiling at the beautiful matriarch seated opposite to you and saying, [style.speechFeminine(Thank you for dining with us tonight, Ms. [helena.surname]. All of the staff are honoured to have served the owner of this hotel, and, needless to say, the meal is on the house. I hope you have a most enjoyable evening!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the waitress skips away, leaving you and Helena alone together again. A huge weight seems to have been lifted off of the beautiful matriarch's chest, and after standing up, she warmly smiles at you and says, [helena.speech(I think I shall retire to my apartment for the remainder of the evening.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she flashes you an expectant look, you realise that Helena wants you to accompany her up to her apartment. Now that she's opened up to you about her sex life, you think that there might be an opportunity for you to take things a little further with her if you were to do as she wants and escort her upstairs...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_RESTAURANT_END -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		At that moment, the harpy waitress returns carrying the desserts you've ordered. Placing them down on the table in front of you, she gives each of you a big smile before darting off and leaving the two of you alone once again. Taking your time to enjoy the delicious desserts, you and Helena eat them at a rather leisurely pace, allowing the two of you to continue
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 flirting with one another.
		#ELSE
			 your conversation.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		About half an hour later, the harpy waitress returns to clear your empty dessert dishes away, before smiling at the beautiful matriarch seated opposite to you and saying, [style.speechFeminine(Thank you for dining here tonight with us, Ms. [helena.surname]. Needless to say, the meal is on the house. I hope you have a most enjoyable evening!)]
	</p>
	#IF(helena.isSlutty())
		<p>
			With that, the waitress skips away, leaving you and Helena alone together again. Standing up, the horny matriarch bites her lip and teases, [helena.speech(I think I shall retire to my apartment for the remainder of the evening. There's some very skimpy lingerie that I want to try on. Perhaps you'd like to accompany me upstairs and let me know if it looks any good on me?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With that, the waitress skips away, leaving you and Helena alone together again. Standing up, the beautiful matriarch warmly smiles at you and says, [helena.speech(I think I shall retire to my apartment for the remainder of the evening.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateSexLifeTalk))
				As she flashes you an expectant look, you realise that Helena wants you to accompany her up to her apartment. While you could always simply say goodbye and part ways with her here, you think that there might be an opportunity for you to take things a little further with her if you were to instead escort her upstairs...
			#ELSE
				As she flashes you an expectant look, you realise that Helena wants you to accompany her up to her apartment. While you could always simply say goodbye and part ways with her here, there might be an opportunity to give her a parting kiss if you were to instead escort her upstairs...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_END_GOODBYE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to leave as quickly as possible, you tell Helena that you're going to have to depart immediately.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Shooting you an annoyed glare, the beautiful matriarch huffs, [helena.speech(Fine! I'll just have to lie on my bed in my skimpy lingerie all by myself!)]
		#ELSE
			 Shooting you an annoyed glare, the regal matriarch sharply states, [helena.speech(Very well! I will see you at another time, [pc.name].)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly upset by the fact that you didn't offer to accompany her up to her apartment, the haughty harpy turns on the spot and storms off, leaving you standing there all alone beside the table you've just had dinner at. Ignoring the glances that a couple of the restaurant's customers shoot your way, you head towards the exit, and after making your way across the hotel's foyer, you [pc.step] out into the streets of Dominion. Without a backwards glance, you set off on your way towards whatever was more important than accompanying the most beautiful harpy in all of Dominion up to her apartment...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_RESTAURANT_END_HOME -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_END_HOME_ROMANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that Scarlett will have set up the romantic scene by now, you eagerly offer to accompany Helena up to her apartment.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Flashing you a dirty look, the harpy leans in against you and sensually replies, [helena.speech(I'm hoping that you'll accompany me all the way into my bedroom...)]
		#ELSE
			 Throwing a warm smile your way, the harpy steps up beside you and offers you her wing as she replies, [helena.speech(Thank you, [pc.name]. Please, lead the way.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking hold of her wing-like arm, you escort Helena out of the restaurant, across the foyer, and into the elevator.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			#IF(helena.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				 As the doors slide close behind you, the horny matriarch dominantly presses you back against the wall, and after planting a passionate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], she draws back and moans, [helena.speech(I'm going to fuck you so hard tonight...)]
			#ELSE
				 As the doors slide close behind you, the horny matriarch submissively rubs herself up against you, and after planting a passionate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], she draws back and moans, [helena.speech(I want you to fuck me so hard tonight...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 As the doors slide close behind you, the regal matriarch moves to gently press herself against you, before contentedly sighing, [helena.speech(Thank you for the wonderful evening, [pc.name]...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Just a moment later, you and Helena find yourselves stepping out of the elevator and walking down the wide, well-lit corridor towards her apartment. Arriving at the front door, you see that Scarlett's left it slightly ajar, allowing you to push it open and lead Helena inside. As you enter, the two of you see that the lights inside are dimmed, with the interior of the apartment being primarily illuminated by several lit candles which have been placed upon some of the hallway's side tables. On the floor, you see that Scarlett has scattered rose petals leading from the entrance hall to the door of Helena's bedroom, while to finish off the romantic atmosphere, a quiet, gentle melody is being played from out of the apartment's arcane speaker system.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			Unable to contain her excitement, Helena throws herself at you and starts planting a series of sloppy, passionate kisses upon your [pc.lips+]. After a few moments of making out with you in the doorway, Helena suddenly draws back, before breathlessly panting,
			#IF(helena.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				 [helena.speech(Come on, [pc.name]! I'm taking you to my bedroom!)]
			#ELSE
				 [helena.speech(Come on, [pc.name]! Take me to my bedroom!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Letting out a surprised gasp, Helena turns towards you with a bashful look on her face. Blushing deeply, she presses herself against you and plants a sloppy, passionate kiss upon your [pc.lips+]. After a few moments of making out with you in the doorway, Helena suddenly draws back, before breathlessly panting, [helena.speech(Come on, [pc.name]! Show me to my bedroom!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_END_HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that she'll be upset if you were to simply say goodbye to her here, you offer to accompany Helena up to her apartment.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Flashing you a dirty look, the harpy leans in against you and sensually replies, [helena.speech(I'm hoping that you'll accompany me all the way into my bedroom...)]
		#ELSE
			 Throwing a warm smile your way, the harpy steps up beside you and offers you her wing as she replies, [helena.speech(Thank you, [pc.name]. Please, lead the way.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking hold of her wing-like arm, you escort Helena out of the restaurant, across the foyer, and into the elevator.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			#IF(helena.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				 As the doors slide close behind you, the horny matriarch dominantly presses you back against the wall, and after planting a passionate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], she draws back and moans, [helena.speech(I'm going to fuck you so hard tonight...)]
			#ELSE
				 As the doors slide close behind you, the horny matriarch submissively rubs herself up against you, and after planting a passionate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], she draws back and moans, [helena.speech(I want you to fuck me so hard tonight...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 As the doors slide close behind you, the regal matriarch moves to gently press herself against you, before contentedly sighing, [helena.speech(Thank you for the wonderful evening, [pc.name]...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Just a moment later, you and Helena find yourselves stepping out of the elevator and walking down the wide, well-lit corridor towards her apartment. Arriving at the front door, the regal matriarch presses the doorbell, and after just a few seconds, a harpy maid opens it and respectfully curtsies to the two of you.
		#IF(helena.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
			 Before you have the chance to say or do anything, Helena dominantly grabs hold of you and pulls you inside, before eagerly moaning, [helena.speech(I'm taking you straight to my bedroom!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF(helena.isSlutty())
				 Stepping through the open doorway, Helena turns to face you and asks, [helena.speech(You're coming inside to give me a good, hard fuck, aren't you, [pc.name]?)]
			#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateSexLifeTalk))
				 Stepping through the open doorway, Helena turns to face you and asks, [helena.speech(Would you like to come inside for some coffee, [pc.name]?)]
			#ELSE
				 Stepping through the open doorway, Helena turns to face you and says, [helena.speech(I really did have a wonderful time tonight, [pc.name]. If you'd like, we could do this again next Friday?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_ROMANTIC_SCENE_BEDROOM"><![CDATA[
	#IF(helena.isSlutty())
		#IF(helena.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
			<p>
				Letting Helena take charge, you allow her to pull you along behind her as she leads you down the hall and into her bedroom. After seeing that the rose petals leading up onto her bed, she turns and plants one last dominant, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], before pushing you down onto the mattress and then stepping over to the door of her walk-in wardrobe. Flashing you a hungry grin, she commands, [helena.speech(Be a good [pc.girl] and wait there for me, [pc.name].)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Doing as you're told, you wait on the bed for Helena to return. Thankfully, it doesn't take her long to get changed, and after just a couple of minutes she steps back out into the room. Holding up her huge, white-feathered wings to cover her body, she grins as she slowly paces towards you, before suddenly sweeping her arms down to reveal that she's wearing nothing but a cupless bra and crotchless thong. With her [helena.breasts+] and [helena.pussy+] on display, she asks, [helena.speech(So, how would you like me to fuck you, [pc.name]?)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Doing as Helena asks, you pull her along beside you as you lead her down the hall and into her bedroom. Upon seeing that the rose petals leading up onto her bed, the beautiful matriarch turns and plants one last desperate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], before gently guiding you over to sit on the mattress and then stepping over to the door of her walk-in wardrobe. Submissively batting her eyelids at you, she teases, [helena.speech(Please give me a minute to get myself ready for you, [pc.name].)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Deciding to do as she asks, you wait on the bed for Helena to return. Thankfully, it doesn't take her long to get changed, and after just a couple of minutes she steps back out into the room. Holding up her huge, white-feathered wings to cover her body, she seductively bites her lip as she slowly paces towards you, before suddenly sweeping her arms down to reveal that she's wearing nothing but a cupless bra and crotchless thong. With her [helena.breasts+] and [helena.pussy+] on display, she bashfully asks, [helena.speech(So, how would you like to fuck me, [pc.name]?)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Doing as Helena asks, you lead her along beside you as you head down the hall and into her bedroom. Upon seeing that the rose petals lead up onto her bed, the beautiful matriarch turns and plants one last desperate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], before gently guiding you over to sit on the mattress and then stepping over to the door of her walk-in wardrobe. Flashing you a loving smile, she shyly asks, [helena.speech(Could you please give me a minute to slip into something more comfortable?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as she asks, you wait on the bed for Helena to return. Thankfully, it doesn't take her long to get changed, and after just a couple of minutes she steps back out into the room. Holding up her huge, white-feathered wings to cover her body, she seductively bites her lip as she slowly paces towards you, before suddenly sweeping her arms down to reveal that she's wearing nothing but a matching lacy white bra and thong. Standing before you in this skimpy lingerie, she runs her feathered hands down between her bird-like legs and bashfully asks, [helena.speech(Please, [pc.name], could you perform oral on me again?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_HELENA_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting Helena take charge, you allow her to pull you along behind her as she leads you down the hall and into her bedroom. Closing the door behind you, she turns and plants one last dominant, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], before pushing you down onto her bed and then stepping over to the door of her walk-in wardrobe. Flashing you a hungry grin, she commands, [helena.speech(Be a good [pc.girl] and wait there for me, [pc.name].)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you wait on the bed for Helena to return. Thankfully, it doesn't take her long to get changed, and after just a couple of minutes she steps back out into the room. Holding up her huge, white-feathered wings to cover her body, she grins as she slowly paces towards you, before suddenly sweeping her arms down to reveal that she's wearing nothing but a cupless bra and crotchless thong. With her [helena.breasts+] and [helena.pussy+] on display, she asks, [helena.speech(So, how would you like me to fuck you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_END_HOME_GOODBYE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to leave as quickly as possible, you tell Helena that you're going to have to depart immediately.
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateSexLifeTalk))
			 Shooting you a disappointed glare, the beautiful matriarch sighs, [helena.speech(Fine... Maybe you'll have time to come inside next Friday...)]
		#ELSE
			 Flashing you a warm smile, the beautiful matriarch says, [helena.speech(Thank you again for the wonderful evening, [pc.name]. I hope to see you again soon!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Helena closes the door to her apartment, leaving you standing there all alone in the corridor. Turning around and heading back to the elevator, you ride it down to the ground floor, before making your way across the hotel's foyer and [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion.
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateSexLifeTalk))
			 Without a backwards glance, you set off on your way towards whatever was more important than accompanying the most beautiful harpy in all of Dominion up to her apartment...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_END_HOME_GOODBYE_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateSexLifeTalk))
			Wanting to leave as quickly as possible, you tell Helena that you're going to have to depart immediately. Knowing that she's likely to feel let down by this, you [pc.step] forwards and plant a loving kiss on her cheek as a way of apologising for your hasty exit. While there's definitely a look of disappointment in her eyes, the beautiful matriarch can't help but smile as you kiss her, and she sighs, [helena.speech(Very well, [pc.name], if you really must be leaving right away, I suppose I shouldn't keep you...)]
		#ELSE
			Wanting to give Helena something else to remember the evening by, you [pc.step] forwards and plant a loving kiss on her cheek. Blushing deeply in response to your bold move, the beautiful matriarch can't help but smile as she bashfully exclaims, [helena.speech(Oh, [pc.name]! Before you leave, I must say thank you so much for the wonderful evening. I hope that we can do this again next Friday!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Helena flashes you one last smile and then closes the door to her apartment, leaving you standing there all alone in the corridor. Turning around and heading back to the elevator, you ride it down to the ground floor, before making your way across the hotel's foyer and [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_RESTAURANT_END_HOME_BEDROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As she's so eager to have sex with you again, you decide to take Helena directly to her bedroom. Stepping into her apartment, you take hold of her waist and pull her along beside you as you lead her down the hall and into her bedroom. After you've closed the door behind you, the beautiful matriarch leans in to plant one last desperate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], before gently guiding you over to sit on the mattress and then stepping over to the door of her walk-in wardrobe. Submissively batting her eyelids at you, she teases, [helena.speech(Please give me a minute to get myself ready for you, [pc.name].)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding to do as she asks, you wait on the bed for Helena to return. Thankfully, it doesn't take her long to get changed, and after just a couple of minutes she steps back out into the room. Holding up her huge, white-feathered wings to cover her body, she seductively bites her lip as she slowly paces towards you, before suddenly sweeping her arms down to reveal that she's wearing nothing but a cupless bra and crotchless thong. With her [helena.breasts+] and [helena.pussy+] on display, she bashfully asks, [helena.speech(So, how would you like to fuck me, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_APARTMENT_START -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			Accepting Helena's invitation to come inside, you tell her that you'd like to have some coffee before moving on to the sorts of lewd things she's been asking for all evening. Frustrated at not immediately getting what she wants, the beautiful harpy huffs, [helena.speech(Fine, we can have some coffee, but you'd better give me a good, hard fuck once we're done!)]
		#ELSE
			Accepting Helena's invitation to come inside, you tell her that you'd love to have some coffee with her. Flashing you a warm smile, the beautiful harpy excitedly exclaims, [helena.speech(Excellent! Please, come in!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaDateApartmentSeen))
		<p>
			Once again finding yourself stepping inside Helena's apartment, you see the usual three harpy maids waiting patiently for instructions from their matriarch. Turning to the nearest of these maids, Helena says, [helena.speech([pc.Name] and I intend to have coffee in the lounge. Please prepare it for us.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Hurrying to obey, two of the harpy maids dash off down the hallway and disappear from sight. The final maid stays behind and remains quiet as Helena turns to you and says, [helena.speech(Please follow me, [pc.name]. The lounge is right this way.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as Helena says, you follow her into her impressive lounge and end up sitting down next to her on one of the many designed sofas which are scattered about the place. Before the two of you can strike up a conversation, the two harpy maids return to place a pot of coffee and two delicate cups down on the table in front of you. After they've respectfully curtsied and left, you and Helena soon lose interest in the hot beverage as 
			#IF(helena.isSlutty())
				 she starts desperately flirting with you and begging for you to take her into her bedroom and fuck her...
			#ELSEIF(!helena.getFetishDesire(FETISH_ORAL_RECEIVING).isPositive())
				 you start talking first about her apartment, and then about how she's always wanted to experience what it's like to kiss someone...
			#ELSE
				 you start talking first about her apartment, and then about how it might be fun to take things into her bedroom...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Stepping inside Helena's apartment, you find yourself amazed at not only how huge and lavishly decorated the hallway before you is, but also at the fact that there are no less than three harpy maids waiting patiently for instructions from their matriarch. Turning to the nearest of these maids, Helena says, [helena.speech([pc.Name] and I intend to have coffee in the lounge. Please prepare it for us.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Hurrying to obey, two of the harpy maids dash off down the hallway and disappear from sight. The final maid stays behind and remains quiet as Helena turns to you and says, [helena.speech(Please follow me, [pc.name]. The lounge is right this way.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as Helena says, you follow her down the leftmost branch in the corridor before you, before taking a sharp turn and entering what Helena modestly refers to as her lounge. Putting most other penthouse apartments to shame, the room which you find yourself entering is quite simply breathtaking. Large glass panels and sliding doors make up the entire length of the left-hand wall, which not only provide an outstanding view of the rooftops and streets below, but which also grant access to a private balcony, complete with outdoor hot-tub. The actual lounge itself is huge, and is furnished with numerous designer sofas and coffee tables. It's to one of these sofas which Helena leads you, and after she's had you sit down next to her, she asks, [helena.speech(So, do you like my apartment?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After you've responded in the affirmative, the harpy maids make a sudden return. Placing a pot of coffee and two delicate cups down on the table in front of you, they curtsy and hurry off back to the kitchen. Finding yourselves alone with one another, you and Helena soon lose interest in the hot beverage as you start talking first about her apartment, and then about how she's always wanted to experience what it's like to kiss someone...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_START_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having finished your coffee, you feel as though there's no reason for you to hang around in here any longer, and so you tell Helena that you're going to have to leave. Knowing that she's likely to feel let down by this, you move forwards and plant a loving kiss on her cheek as a way of apologising for your hasty exit.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Although she smiles as you kiss her, she's definitely very disappointed by your decision to leave, and whines, [helena.speech(You didn't even want to stay for a quick fuck? You'd better visit me in my nest over the weekend and make it up to me...)]
		#ELSE
			 While there's definitely a look of disappointment in her eyes, the beautiful matriarch can't help but smile as you kiss her, and she sighs, [helena.speech(Very well, [pc.name], if you really must be leaving right away, I suppose I shouldn't keep you...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Helena calls over one of her maids to escort you out of her apartment, and after you've said one final goodbye to the beautiful matriarch, you find yourself being led back to the front door and ushered outside. Not wanting to waste nay more time, you quickly head back to the elevator and ride it down to the ground floor, before making your way across the hotel's foyer and [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_START_BEDROOM"><![CDATA[
	#IF(helena.isSlutty())
		<p>
			Liking the sound of what Helena is suggesting, you lean in to plant a kiss on her [helena.lips+], before drawing back a little and suggesting that the two of you take things to her bedroom. More than happy to do as you say, the horny harpy leaps up off the sofa, before excitedly leading you down the hall and into her bedroom. After you've closed the door behind you, the beautiful matriarch leans in to plant a desperate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], before gently guiding you over to sit on the mattress and then stepping over to the door of her walk-in wardrobe. Submissively batting her eyelids at you, she teases, [helena.speech(Please give me a minute to get myself ready for you, [pc.name].)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Deciding to do as she asks, you wait on the bed for Helena to return. Thankfully, it doesn't take her long to get changed, and after just a couple of minutes she steps back out into the room. Holding up her huge, white-feathered wings to cover her body, she seductively bites her lip as she slowly paces towards you, before suddenly sweeping her arms down to reveal that she's wearing nothing but a cupless bra and crotchless thong. With her [helena.breasts+] and [helena.pussy+] on display, she bashfully asks, [helena.speech(So, how would you like to fuck me, [pc.name]?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Liking the sound of what Helena is suggesting, you lean in to plant a kiss on her [helena.lips+], before drawing back a little and suggesting that the two of you take things to her bedroom. More than happy to do as you say, the horny harpy leaps up off the sofa, before excitedly leading you down the hall and into her bedroom. After you've closed the door behind you, the beautiful matriarch turns and plants one last desperate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], before gently guiding you over to sit on the mattress and then stepping over to the door of her walk-in wardrobe. Flashing you a loving smile, she shyly asks, [helena.speech(Could you please give me a minute to slip into something more comfortable?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as she asks, you wait on the bed for Helena to return. Thankfully, it doesn't take her long to get changed, and after just a couple of minutes she steps back out into the room. Holding up her huge, white-feathered wings to cover her body, she seductively bites her lip as she slowly paces towards you, before suddenly sweeping her arms down to reveal that she's wearing nothing but a matching lacy white bra and thong. Standing before you in this skimpy lingerie, she runs her feathered hands down between her bird-like legs and bashfully asks, [helena.speech(So, [pc.name], what would you like to do now?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_APARTMENT_COFFEE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_COFFEE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting the coffee to go to waste, you pick up the pot and pour both Helena and yourself another cup of the hot beverage before leaning back on the sofa to enjoy it.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Pouting at you as she sees that you're more interested in the coffee than her demands for sex, the beautiful matriarch whines, [helena.speech(Come on, [pc.name]... Can't we just go to my bedroom and fuck already?)]
		#ELSE
			 Taking a sip of the hot beverage, the beautiful matriarch smiles at you and says, [helena.speech(I hope this blend is to your satisfaction, [pc.name]...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to rush things, you take your time in drinking your cup of coffee while continuing to engage Helena in conversation. Despite your leisurely drinking speed, the two of you soon find yourselves with empty cups, and after placing hers down on the coffee table, Helena
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 bites her lip and teases, [helena.speech(Now it's time for a good, hard fuck. Right, [pc.name]?)]
		#ELSEIF(!helena.getFetishDesire(FETISH_ORAL_RECEIVING).isPositive())
			 once again brings the topic of conversation back to the fact that she's never kissed anyone before. Shuffling a little closer to you, she sighs, [helena.speech(You know, [pc.name], I really want to know how it feels to be kissed by someone...)]
		#ELSE
			 bats her eyelids at you and suggests, [helena.speech(Perhaps we could spend the rest of the evening in my bedroom...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_APARTMENT_KISS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_KISS_FIRST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From all of the hints that she's been dropping, as well as the way she's shuffling closer and closer towards you on the sofa, you can tell that Helena is desperate for you to kiss her. More than happy to give her what she so clearly wants, you move a little closer and slowly lean in towards her. Seeing that you're making a move on her, the beautiful harpy gently tilts her head to one side and lets out an excited little sigh. Quickly closing the gap between the two of you, you feel Helena's hot breath on your [pc.lips] as lean forwards and pull her into a deep kiss.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(~Mmm!~)] Helena sighs, before parting her [helena.lips+] and taking your [pc.tongue+] into her mouth. Getting more and more excited with each passing moment, the beautiful matriarch suddenly wraps her huge wing-like arms around you, and with a desperate moan, she presses herself against you and starts sloppily sliding her own [helena.tongue] over yours.
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 Clearly enjoying this new experience, Helena starts heavily panting as she continues to respond to your kiss in an extremely passionate manner.
		#ELSE
			 Clearly enjoying this new experience, Helena starts heavily panting as she slides into your lap and continues to respond to your kiss in an extremely passionate manner.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			Despite any movement you try to make, the horny harpy refuses to let you go, and before you know it, you've spent almost half an hour in the matriarch's enthusiastic embrace.
		#ELSE
			Despite any movement you try to make, the horny harpy refuses to move off of your lap, and before you know it, you've spent almost half an hour in the matriarch's enthusiastic embrace.
		#ENDIF
		 Just as you're starting to wonder how long she's going to want to continue making out with you like this, Helena suddenly pulls back, allowing you to see that her face has flushed red from a mixture of passion and embarrassment. Wiping the excess saliva off of her glistening lips, she stands up and stutters, [helena.speech(O-Oh my goodness... That was far better than I'd imagined... I-I think I need some time in which to calm down...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can say anything, she turns around and runs off in the direction of her bedroom. Before she disappears from your sight, she turns to shout, [helena.speech(T-Thank you for the wonderful evening, [pc.name]! I-I'll see you again soon!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you try to process what just happened, one of the harpy maids approaches and says, [style.speechFeminine(It would appear as though Ms. [helena.surname] wishes to retire for the evening. Please allow me to show you out.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to spend some time making out with Helena on the sofa, you move up next to her and pull her into a deep, passionate kiss. Letting out a happy moan, the beautiful matriarch wraps her arm-like wings around you as she enthusiastically returns your kiss.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			Just like the first time you kissed her, Helena very quickly seems to lose control of herself, and starts heavily panting and moaning as she sloppily kisses you.
		#ELSE
			Just like the first time you kissed her, Helena very quickly seems to lose control of herself, and starts heavily panting and moaning as she slides into your lap and sloppily kisses you.
		#ENDIF
		 In this manner, the two of you continue making out with one another for a good five minutes or so, until eventually Helena pulls back and gasps, [helena.speech(Come on, [pc.name], let's go to my bedroom!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_KISS_FIRST_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With Helena having made a swift and sudden exit, there's very little left for you to do except let the harpy maid lead you to the front door. As you follow her back through the hallway, you find yourself wondering if Helena will be willing to go a little further with you after you next date.
	</p>
	<p>
		Still thinking about Helena's reaction to sharing her first kiss with you, you exit her apartment and quickly ride the elevator back down to the ground floor. Making your way across the hotel's foyer, you once again find yourself [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_KISS_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you've enjoyed your time this evening, you feel as though it's time for you to depart, and so you tell Helena that you're unfortunately going to have to go.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Clearly being very disappointed by your decision to suddenly leave, she whines, [helena.speech(You didn't even want to stay for a quick fuck? You'd better visit me in my nest over the weekend and make it up to me!)]
		#ELSE
			 Clearly being very disappointed by your decision to suddenly leave, she sighs, [helena.speech(Very well, [pc.name], if you really must be leaving right away, I suppose I shouldn't keep you...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Helena calls over one of her maids to escort you out of her apartment, and after you've said one final goodbye to the beautiful matriarch, you find yourself being led back to the front door and ushered outside. Not wanting to waste nay more time, you quickly head back to the elevator and ride it down to the ground floor, before making your way across the hotel's foyer and [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_KISS_BEDROOM"><![CDATA[
	#IF(helena.isSlutty())
		<p>
			Thinking that it would now be best to take things into the bedroom, you plant a final, passionate kiss on Helena's [helena.lips+], before drawing back a little and suggesting that the two of you go and have some fun on her bed. More than happy to do as you say, the horny harpy leaps up off the sofa, before excitedly leading you down the hall and into her bedroom. After you've closed the door behind you, the beautiful matriarch leans in to plant a desperate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], before gently guiding you over to sit on the mattress and then stepping over to the door of her walk-in wardrobe. Submissively batting her eyelids at you, she teases, [helena.speech(Please give me a minute to get myself ready for you, [pc.name].)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Deciding to do as she asks, you wait on the bed for Helena to return. Thankfully, it doesn't take her long to get changed, and after just a couple of minutes she steps back out into the room. Holding up her huge, white-feathered wings to cover her body, she seductively bites her lip as she slowly paces towards you, before suddenly sweeping her arms down to reveal that she's wearing nothing but a cupless bra and crotchless thong. With her [helena.breasts+] and [helena.pussy+] on display, she bashfully asks, [helena.speech(So, how would you like to fuck me, [pc.name]?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Thinking that it would now be best to take things into the bedroom, you plant a final, passionate kiss on Helena's [helena.lips+], before drawing back a little and suggesting that the two of you go and have some fun on her bed. More than happy to do as you say, the horny harpy leaps up off the sofa, before excitedly leading you down the hall and into her bedroom. After you've closed the door behind you, the beautiful matriarch turns and plants one last desperate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], before gently guiding you over to sit on the mattress and then stepping over to the door of her walk-in wardrobe. Flashing you a loving smile, she shyly asks, [helena.speech(Could you please give me a minute to slip into something more comfortable?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as she asks, you wait on the bed for Helena to return. Thankfully, it doesn't take her long to get changed, and after just a couple of minutes she steps back out into the room. Holding up her huge, white-feathered wings to cover her body, she seductively bites her lip as she slowly paces towards you, before suddenly sweeping her arms down to reveal that she's wearing nothing but a matching lacy white bra and thong. Standing before you in this skimpy lingerie, she runs her feathered hands down between her bird-like legs and bashfully asks, [helena.speech(So, [pc.name], what would you like to do now?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM -->
	
	<!-- Pre-virginity taking cunnilingus -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_ROMANCE_PERFORM_CUNNILINGUS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be a good idea to get her well lubricated and ready to lose her virginity, you tell Helena that you're more than happy to perform oral on her. Flashing you a seductive smile as she hears you agree to her request, Helena hooks her feathered thumbs into the band of her lacy white thong, and after swiftly sliding them down her legs and discarding them on the floor, she lies back on her bed and moans, [helena.speech(Come on then, [pc.name]! I want to feel your tongue in my pussy again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The sight of the beautiful matriarch presenting her
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 bird-like cloaca to you
		#ELSE
			 pussy to you
		#ENDIF
		 is too much for you resist, and you immediately drop your head down between her legs to plant a kiss on her [helena.labia+]. Letting out an exited moan, Helena spreads her legs a little wider, which is all the encouragement you need to slide your [pc.tongue] into her virgin cunt and begin to enthusiastically eat her out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Kissing breasts -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_FINGERING_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			As this is her first real sexual experience, you know that Helena is definitely not going to be willing to go too far with you just yet. With this in mind, you tell the beautiful harpy to let you know if she wants you to stop at any point, before [pc.stepping] up to her and pulling her into a deep, passionate kiss. Encouraged by her happy moans, you reach around behind her back and unfasten her bra, before lifting your [pc.hands] up to start groping and playing with her [helena.breasts+].
		#ELSE
			As this is her first real sexual experience, you know that Helena is definitely not going to be willing to go too far with you just yet. With this in mind, you tell the beautiful harpy to let you know if she wants you to stop at any point, before [pc.stepping] up to her and pulling her into a deep, passionate kiss. Continuing to make out with her, you take hold of her hips and slowly guide her back over to her bed, before sitting down on the edge and pulling her down to sit in your lap. Encouraged by her happy moans, you reach around behind her back and unfasten her bra, before lifting your [pc.hands] up to start groping and playing with her [helena.breasts+].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Yes...)] Helena sighs, before guiding one of your [pc.hands] down between her legs and encouraging you to start stroking her pussy. Pleased to discover that she's willing to go this far with you, you slide your [pc.fingers+] up and down over Helena's lacy white thong, gently pressing the thin fabric down against her labia and causing her to let out a deep, muffled moan into your mouth.
	</p>
	<p>
		Thinking that now would be a good moment to take things just a little further, you break off your kiss and move your head down to start paying some oral attention to her [helena.breasts+]. As you take one of her [helena.nipples+] into your mouth, Helena suddenly hooks her feathered thumbs into the band of her lacy white thong, and after swiftly sliding them down her legs and discarding them on the floor, she pushes your [pc.hand] between her legs and pleads, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes! Come on, [pc.name]! ~Mmm!~ Give me a little more...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she asks, you continue running your [pc.fingers] up and down over her [helena.labia+] for a few more moments, before gently sliding them into her pussy and starting to finger her. Letting out an excited squeal, the horny harpy pants, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ That's it! Keep on doing it like that!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_FINGERING_EXPERIENCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			Not wanting to take things too far with her tonight, you [pc.step] up to Helena and pull her into a deep, passionate kiss.
		#ELSE
			Not wanting to take things too far with her tonight, you [pc.step] up to Helena and pull her into a deep, passionate kiss. Continuing to make out with her, you take hold of her hips and slowly guide her back over to her bed, before sitting down on the edge and pulling her down to sit in your lap.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Encouraged by her happy moans, you lift your [pc.hands] up to start groping and playing with her exposed [helena.breasts].
		#ELSE
			 Encouraged by her happy moans, you reach around behind her back and unfasten her bra, before lifting your [pc.hands] up to start groping and playing with her [helena.breasts+].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			[helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Yes...)] Helena sighs, before guiding your [pc.hand] down between her legs and pleading, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Come on, [pc.name]! ~Mmm!~ Give me a little more...)]
		#ELSE
			[helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Yes...)] Helena sighs, before hooking her feathered thumbs into the band of her lacy white thong and swiftly sliding them down her legs to discard them on the floor. Pushing your [pc.hand] between her legs, she pleads, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Come on, [pc.name]! ~Mmm!~ Give me a little more...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she asks, you run your [pc.fingers] up and down over her [helena.labia+] for a few moments, before gently sliding them into her pussy and starting to finger her. Letting out an excited squeal, the horny harpy pants, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ That's it! Keep on doing it like that!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Paizuri -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_PAIZURI_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting Helena to put her big, [helena.cupSize]-cup breasts to good use, you tell her that you want her to push them together so that you can fuck them. Sitting down on the edge of her bed, you expose your [pc.cock+] to the beautiful matriarch and gesture for her to come and kneel down before you.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 With an excited gleam in her eyes, she happily drops down to her knees in front you, before taking off her cupless bra and letting her naked breasts bounce completely free. Looking up at you, she pushes her pillowy mounds together and lewdly teases, [helena.speechNoEffects(Come on then, stick your cock in here and let me take care of you!)] 
		#ELSE
			 Blushing at the thought of doing something so lewd, she hesitantly drops down to her knees in front you, before taking off her lacy white bra and letting her naked breasts bounce completely free. Looking up at you, she clumsily pushes her pillowy mounds together and asks, [helena.speechNoEffects(A-Am I doing this right?)] 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			Doing as the horny harpy says, you push your throbbing cock up between her breasts, causing her to let out an excited squeal. While she shows great enthusiasm, Helena clearly isn't very competent at performing a titjob, and accidentally lets your hard shaft slip out from between her breasts as she tries to use them to jerk you off.
		#ELSE
			Reassuring her that she's doing fine, you push your throbbing cock up between Helena's breasts, causing her to let out an excited squeal. Unfortunately, she's clearly not very competent at performing titjobs, and accidentally lets your hard shaft slip out from between her breasts as she awkwardly tries to use them to jerk you off.
		#ENDIF
		 Encouraging her to try again, you sit back and relax as the gorgeous matriarch shifts position and attempts to perform paizuri on you for a second time. While still a little clumsy at first, she soon figures out how best to do it, and within a few minutes you find yourself happily [pc.moaning] as Helena's tits slide up and down around your [pc.cock+]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_PAIZURI_EXPERIENCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting Helena to put her big, [helena.cupSize]-cup breasts to good use, you tell her that you want her to push them together so that you can fuck them again. Sitting down on the edge of her bed, you expose your [pc.cock+] to the beautiful matriarch and gesture for her to come and kneel down before you. Flashing you an amused smirk, she happily drops down to her knees in front you, before taking off her bra and letting her naked breasts bounce completely free. Looking up at you, she pushes her pillowy mounds together and lewdly teases, [helena.speechNoEffects(Come on then, stick your cock in here and let me take care of you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as the horny harpy says, you push your throbbing cock up between her breasts, causing her to let out an excited squeal. Having previously figured out the best way to perform paizuri, Helena expertly wraps her pillowy mounds around your hard shaft, before sliding them up and down as she uses them to jerk you off...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Cunnilingus -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_PERFORM_CUNNILINGUS_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to give Helena yet another new experience, you suggest to her that you could perform oral on her. Blushing as she hears you say this, the gorgeous matriarch nervously replies, [helena.speechNoEffects(Well, I suppose that'd be ok...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Continuing to fiercely blush, Helena slips her feathered thumbs into the band of her lacy white thong, before pulling it down and discarding it on the floor. With an animated flap of her wing-like arms, she hops up to kneel on the bed beside you and asks how she should position herself. Planting a loving kiss on her [helena.lips+], you help to guide her down so that she's lying on her back. Reassuring her that she'll enjoy this, you drop your head down towards her groin, before taking hold of her legs and gently pushing them apart.
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 With Helena's bird-like cloaca now just [style.sizes] away from your face, you lean in and plant a wet kiss on it, which causes her to cry out, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ D-Do that again!)]
		#ELSE
			 With Helena's virgin pussy now just [style.sizes] away from your face, you lean in and plant a wet kiss on her [helena.labia+], which causes her to cry out, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ D-Do that again!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Happily doing as the beautiful matriarch asks, you plant a series of increasingly-passionate kisses on
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 the exterior of her cloaca,
		#ELSE
			 her soft folds,
		#ENDIF
		 before burying your face between her legs and enthusiastically licking and sucking on her sensitive little clit. This sudden stimulation causes Helena to let out a sharp squeal, and before you know what's happening, she's reaching down between her legs to firmly push the back of your head down into her groin. As you slide your [pc.tongue+] into her wet pussy, she passionately moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Oh yes! I didn't know it would feel this good! ~Ooh!~ Keep going!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		From her excessive writhing, panting, and squealing, you realise that you must have awoken a new fetish inside of the previously-pure matriarch, and you can't help but smirk into her pussy as you continue to eat her out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_PERFORM_CUNNILINGUS_EXPERIENCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get another taste of Helena's pussy, you tell her that you could perform oral on her again. Grinning as she hears you say this, the gorgeous matriarch
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 flaps her wing-like arms and hops up to kneel on the bed beside you.
		#ELSE
			 slips her feathered thumbs into the band of her lacy white thong, before pulling it down and discarding it on the floor. With her pussy now exposed, Helena flaps her wing-like arms and hops up to kneel on the bed beside you.
		#ENDIF
		 Leaning in to plant a quick, sloppy kiss on your [pc.lips], the horny matriarch lies back on her bed and spreads her legs for you, before teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(Come on then, [pc.name]! I want to feel your tongue in my pussy again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Happily doing as the beautiful matriarch asks, you drop your head down to her groin, and after planting a series of increasingly-passionate kisses on
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 the exterior of her cloaca,
		#ELSE
			 her soft folds,
		#ENDIF
		 you bury your face between her legs and start enthusiastically licking and sucking on her sensitive little clit. This sudden stimulation causes Helena to let out a sharp squeal, and before you know what's happening, she's reaching down between her legs to firmly push the back of your head down into her groin. As you slide your [pc.tongue+] into her wet pussy, she passionately moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Oh yes! That feels so good! ~Ooh!~ Keep going!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Receiving cunnilingus -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_RECEIVE_CUNNILINGUS_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having previously performed oral on Helena, you tell her that you'd like her to return the favour this time.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Flashing you a cheeky grin as she hears you say this, the horny matriarch readily agrees to do as you ask by teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(You know, I <i>have</i> always wondered what your pussy would taste like, [pc.name]...)]
		#ELSE
			 Seeing the nervous look in the matriarch's eyes as you say this, you reassure her by telling her that you're sure she'll enjoy it. Nervously rubbing her feathered hands, Helena accepts to do as you ask by saying, [helena.speechNoEffects(Well, I suppose I could always give it a go...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Happy to hear that she's willing to eat you out, you stand up and turn around to present the rear of your feral [pc.legRace] to Helena.
			#IF(pc.hasTail())
				 Looking back over your shoulder and swishing your tail to one side,
			#ELSE
				 Looking back over your shoulder and flashing her an encouraging smile,
			#ENDIF
			 you step back to bring your animalistic cunt closer to the beautiful harpy.
			#IF(helena.isSlutty())
				 Not being put off by the fact that her first experience of performing cunnilingus is going to be on what is essentially a feral [pc.pussyRace]'s pussy, Helena drops down onto her knees behind you and instantly leans forwards to plant a passionate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.labia+].
			#ELSE
				 Visibly gulping at the prospect of having her first experience of performing cunnilingus being on what is essentially a feral [pc.pussyRace]'s pussy, Helena drops down onto her knees behind you and hesitantly leans forwards to plant a quick kiss on your [pc.labia+].
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(helena.isSlutty())
				Feeling the gorgeous harpy's [helena.lips+] make contact with your pussy causes you to let out an excited [pc.moan], which spurs her on to plant yet another big, wet kiss on your [pc.labia+]. Clearly liking this new experience, Helena then reaches up to take hold of your hind legs, before shuffling forwards and starting to desperately make out with your animalistic pussy. Once again, you seem to have awakened a new fetish within the once-pure matriarch, and before you know what's happening, she's passionately thrusting her tongue into your [pc.pussy+] as she eats you out...
			#ELSE
				Feeling the gorgeous harpy's [helena.lips+] make contact with your pussy causes you to let out an excited [pc.moan], which spurs her on to plant yet another small kiss on your [pc.labia+]. Clearly liking this new experience, Helena suddenly reaches up to take hold of your hind legs, before shuffling forwards and delivering a passionate, sloppy kiss to your animalistic pussy. Once again, you seem to have awakened a new fetish within the once-pure matriarch, and before you know what's happening, she's passionately thrusting her tongue into your [pc.pussy+] as she eats you out...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Happy to hear that she's willing to eat you out, you lie back on her bed and #IF(pc.hasLegs())spread your legs to #ENDIFpresent your [pc.pussy+] to Helena.
			#IF(helena.isSlutty())
				 Clearly eager to be sharing her first experience of performing cunnilingus with you, Helena immediately jumps up onto the bed, before dropping her beautiful face down #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your legs#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and leaning forwards to plant a passionate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.labia+].
			#ELSE
				 Visibly gulping at the prospect of performing cunnilingus for the first time, Helena slowly clambers up onto the bed, before haltingly dropping her beautiful face down IF(pc.hasLegs())between your legs#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and leaning forwards to plant a quick kiss on your [pc.labia+].
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(helena.isSlutty())
				Feeling the gorgeous harpy's [helena.lips+] make contact with your pussy causes you to let out an excited [pc.moan], which spurs her on to plant yet another big, wet kiss on your [pc.labia+]. Clearly liking this new experience, Helena firmly presses her [helena.lips+] down against your saliva-coated cunt before desperately starting to make out with your pussy. Once again, you seem to have awakened a new fetish within the once-pure matriarch, and before you know what's happening, she's passionately thrusting her tongue into your [pc.pussy+] as she eats you out...
			#ELSE
				Feeling the gorgeous harpy's [helena.lips+] make contact with your pussy causes you to let out an excited [pc.moan], which spurs her on to plant yet another small kiss on your [pc.labia+]. Clearly liking this new experience, Helena suddenly presses her [helena.lips+] down against your saliva-coated cunt before delivering a series of passionate, sloppy kisses to your pussy. Once again, you seem to have awakened a new fetish within the once-pure matriarch, and before you know what's happening, she's passionately thrusting her tongue into your [pc.pussy+] as she eats you out...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_RECEIVE_CUNNILINGUS_EXPERIENCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have Helena perform oral on you again, you ask her if she'd like to eat you out. Flashing you a seductive smirk as she hears you say this, the horny matriarch eagerly accepts your proposition by teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(You know, I have been wanting to get another taste of your pussy, [pc.name]...)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Happy to hear that she's willing to eat you out, you stand up and turn around to present the rear of your feral [pc.legRace]'s body to Helena.
			#IF(pc.hasTail())
				 Looking back over your shoulder and swishing your tail to one side,
			#ELSE
				 Looking back over your shoulder and flashing her an encouraging smile,
			#ENDIF
			 you step back to bring your animalistic cunt closer to the beautiful harpy. Not being put off by the fact that what she's being presented with is essentially a feral [pc.pussyRace]'s pussy, Helena drops down onto her knees behind you and instantly leans forwards to plant a passionate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.labia+].
		</p>
		<p>
			Feeling the gorgeous harpy's [helena.lips+] make contact with your pussy causes you to let out an excited [pc.moan], which spurs her on to plant yet another big, wet kiss on your [pc.labia+]. Clearly enjoying herself, Helena then reaches up to take hold of your hind legs, before shuffling forwards and pressing her [helena.lips+] against your saliva-coated cunt. Not being able to help yourself, you let out a series of [pc.moans+] as Helena passionately thrusts her tongue into your [pc.pussy+] and starts to eat you out...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Happy to hear that she's willing to eat you out, you lie back on her bed and #IF(pc.hasLegs())spread your legs to #ENDIFpresent your [pc.pussy+] to Helena. Clearly eager to be performing cunnilingus on you again, Helena immediately jumps up onto the bed, before dropping her beautiful face down #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your legs#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and leaning forwards to plant a passionate, sloppy kiss on your [pc.labia+].
		</p>
		<p>
			Feeling the gorgeous harpy's [helena.lips+] make contact with your pussy causes you to let out an excited [pc.moan], which spurs her on to plant yet another big, wet kiss on your [pc.labia+]. Clearly enjoying herself, Helena firmly presses her [helena.lips+] down against your saliva-coated cunt before desperately passionately thrusting her tongue into your [pc.pussy+] and starting to eat you out...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Receiving blowjob -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_RECEIVE_BLOWJOB_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having previously performed oral on Helena, you tell her that you'd like her to return the favour and give you a blowjob.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 Flashing you a cheeky grin as she hears you say this, the horny matriarch readily agrees to do as you ask by teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(You know, I <i>have</i> always wondered what your cock would taste like, [pc.name]...)]
		#ELSE
			 Seeing the nervous look in the matriarch's eyes as you say this, you reassure her by telling her that you're sure she'll enjoy it. Nervously rubbing her feathered hands, Helena accepts to do as you ask by saying, [helena.speechNoEffects(Well, I suppose I could always give it a go...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Happy to hear that she's willing to suck your cock, you stand up and turn to one side to present your feral [pc.legRace]'s body to Helena.
			#IF(helena.isSlutty())
				 Not being put off by the fact that her first experience of giving a blowjob is going to be on what is essentially a feral [pc.cockRace]'s cock, Helena drops down onto her knees beside you, before shuffling forwards beneath your animalistic lower body. Letting out an excited moan, she instantly leans forwards to plant a passionate, sloppy kiss on the [pc.cockHead+] of your erect shaft.
			#ELSE
				 Visibly gulping at the prospect of having her first experience of giving a blowjob being on what is essentially a feral [pc.cockRace]'s cock, Helena slowly sinks down onto her knees beside you, before hesitantly shuffling forwards beneath your animalistic lower body. Letting out a deep sigh, she takes her time in leaning forwards to plant a quick kiss on the [pc.cockHead+] of your erect shaft.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Happy to hear that she's willing to suck your cock, you sit down on the edge of her bed and present your rapidly-hardening cock to Helena.
			#IF(helena.isSlutty())
				 Clearly eager to be sharing her first experience of performing a blowjob with you, Helena immediately sinks down to her knees in front of you, before dropping her beautiful face down #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your legs#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and leaning forwards to plant a passionate, sloppy kiss on the [pc.cockHead+] of your erect shaft.
			#ELSE
				 Visibly gulping at the prospect of performing a blowjob for the first time, Helena slowly sinks down to her knees in front of you, before hesitantly shuffling forwards and dropping her beautiful face down #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your legs#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF. Letting out a deep sigh, she takes her time in leaning forwards to plant a quick kiss on the [pc.cockHead+] of your erect shaft.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			Feeling the gorgeous harpy's [helena.lips+] make contact with your cock causes you to let out an excited [pc.moan], which spurs her on to deliver a long, slow lick up the entire length of your throbbing shaft.
		#ELSE
			Feeling the gorgeous harpy's [helena.lips+] make contact with your cock causes you to let out an excited [pc.moan], which spurs her on to deliver a long, slow lick up the entire length of your throbbing shaft.
		#ENDIF
		 Clearly liking this new experience, Helena then reaches up to deliver a few loving strokes to your [pc.cockGirth] dick, before leaning forwards and wrapping her [helena.lips+] around the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock. Once again, you seem to have awakened a new fetish within the once-pure matriarch, and before you know what's happening, she's passionately taking your hot, throbbing shaft into her mouth and giving you an enthusiastic blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_RECEIVE_BLOWJOB_EXPERIENCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have Helena suck your cock again, you tell her that you'd like her to give you a blowjob. Flashing you a cheeky grin as she hears you say this, the horny matriarch readily agrees to do as you ask by teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(I wouldn't mind getting another taste of your cock, [pc.name]...)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Happy to hear that she's willing to suck your cock, you stand up and turn to one side to present your feral [pc.legRace]'s body to Helena. Not being put off by the fact that she's going to be sucking what is essentially a feral [pc.cockRace]'s cock, Helena drops down onto her knees beside you, before shuffling forwards beneath your animalistic lower body. Letting out an excited moan, she instantly leans forwards to plant a passionate, sloppy kiss on the [pc.cockHead+] of your erect shaft.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Happy to hear that she's willing to suck your cock, you sit down on the edge of her bed and present your rapidly-hardening cock to Helena. Clearly eager to give you a blowjob, Helena immediately sinks down to her knees in front of you, before dropping her beautiful face down #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your legs#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and leaning forwards to plant a passionate, sloppy kiss on the [pc.cockHead+] of your erect shaft.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Feeling the gorgeous harpy's [helena.lips+] make contact with your cock causes you to let out an excited [pc.moan], which spurs her on to deliver a series of long, hungry licks up the length of your throbbing shaft. Pulling back a little, Helena then reaches up to deliver a few loving strokes to your [pc.cockGirth] dick, before leaning forwards and wrapping her [helena.lips+] around the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock. Letting out [pc.a_moan+], you place one [pc.hand] on the back of the gorgeous matriarch's head as she passionately takes your hot, throbbing shaft into her mouth and starts giving you an enthusiastic blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Sixty-nine -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_SIXTY_NINE_PENIS_HELENA_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be fun for you and Helena to simultaneously perform oral on one another, you suggest to her that you could have some fun in the sixty-nine position. Clearly liking the sound of what it is you're saying, Helena flashes you a delighted grin, before dominantly pushing you back down onto her bed and swiftly sitting on your face. Dropping her big white tail-feathers down over your eyes, Helena lets out a hungry little moan, before planting her cunt down over your mouth and demanding, [helena.speechNoEffects(If you want me to suck your cock, then you're going to have to earn it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With Helena dominantly grinding her wet pussy down against your [pc.lips], you really have little choice but to do as she asks. Kissing and licking her [helena.labia+], you greedily slide your [pc.tongue+] into her [helena.pussy+] and start desperately eating her out. A delighted moan drifts down from up above you, and after letting her legs completely give way and smothering your face with her cunt, the beautiful matriarch leans down to plant a sloppy kiss on the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock. Continuing to eat out the dominant harpy, you can't help but to happily moan into her pussy as you feel her then wrap her [helena.lips+] around your [pc.cock+] and start give you an enthusiastic blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_SIXTY_NINE_HELENA_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be fun for you and Helena to simultaneously perform oral on one another, you suggest to her that you could have some fun in the sixty-nine position. Clearly liking the sound of what it is you're saying, Helena flashes you a delighted grin, before dominantly pushing you back down onto her bed and swiftly sitting on your face. Dropping her big white tail-feathers down over your eyes, Helena lets out a hungry little moan, before planting her cunt down over your mouth and demanding, [helena.speechNoEffects(If you want me to eat you out, then you're going to have to earn it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With Helena dominantly grinding her wet pussy down against your [pc.lips], you really have little choice but to do as she asks. Kissing and licking her [helena.labia+], you greedily slide your [pc.tongue+] into her [helena.pussy+] and start desperately eating her out. A delighted moan drifts down from up above you, and after letting her legs completely give way and smothering your face with her cunt, the beautiful matriarch leans down to plant a sloppy kiss on your [pc.labia+]. Continuing to eat out the dominant harpy, you can't help but to happily moan into her groin as you feel her then press her [helena.lips+] against your [pc.pussy+] and start to enthusiastically eat you out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_SIXTY_NINE_PENIS_HELENA_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be fun for you and Helena to simultaneously perform oral on one another, you suggest to her that you could have some fun in the sixty-nine position. Clearly liking the sound of what it is you're saying, Helena seductively bites her lip before
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 stepping over towards you and lying back on her bed.
		#ELSE
			 stripping off her lacy white thong and lying back on her bed.
		#ENDIF
		 Clearly wanting you to be on top, Helena lets out a hungry little moan, before batting her eyelids at you and teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(Come on then, [pc.name]! Give me a taste of your cock already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to give the horny harpy what she wants, you quickly straddle her face and lower your [pc.cock+] down towards her waiting lips. Craning her head forwards, Helena impatiently plants a sloppy kiss on the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock, before greedily taking your throbbing shaft down her throat.
	</p>
	<p>
		Eager to return the favour, you bend down over the beautiful matriarch's body and bring your head down between her legs. Wasting no time, you start kissing and licking her [helena.labia+], before greedily sliding your [pc.tongue+] into her [helena.pussy+] and starting to desperately eat her out. A delighted, gargled moan bursts out from Helena's cock-filled mouth, and as she continues to suck and slurp on your [pc.cock+], you alternate between kissing her sensitive little clit and greedily thrusting your [pc.tongue+] into her sopping wet cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_SIXTY_NINE_HELENA_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be fun for you and Helena to simultaneously perform oral on one another, you suggest to her that you could have some fun in the sixty-nine position. Clearly liking the sound of what it is you're saying, Helena seductively bites her lip before
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 stepping over towards you and lying back on her bed.
		#ELSE
			 stripping off her lacy white thong and lying back on her bed.
		#ENDIF
		 Clearly wanting you to be on top, Helena lets out a hungry little moan, before batting her eyelids at you and teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(Come on then, [pc.name]! Give me a taste of your pussy already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to give the horny harpy what she wants, you quickly straddle her face and lower your [pc.pussy+] down towards her waiting lips. Craning her head forwards, Helena impatiently plants a sloppy kiss on your [pc.labia+], before greedily sliding her [helena.tongue+] into your hot cunt.
	</p>
	<p>
		Eager to return the favour, you bend down over the beautiful matriarch's body and bring your head down between her legs. Wasting no time, you start kissing and licking her [helena.labia+], before greedily sliding your [pc.tongue+] into her [helena.pussy+] and starting to desperately eat her out. A delighted, muffled moan bursts out from Helena's mouth, and with your heads between one another's legs, the two of you take great pleasure in orally servicing one another's sopping wet cunts...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Scissoring -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_SCISSORING_DOM_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to do something new with Helena, you suggest to her that the two of you could scissor with one another. Liking the sound of what you're suggesting, the horny harpy leaps up to join you on the bed, before dominantly pushing you down onto your back and quickly gaining access to your pussy. Reaching down to trace her feathered fingers over your [pc.labia+], she suddenly grabs one of your [pc.legs] and pulls it up, before clumsily shuffling forwards and bumping her [helena.pussy+] against yours. Letting out an excited squeal, she demands, [helena.speechNoEffects(Come on, [pc.name], get those hips moving!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you start gyrating your [pc.hips+], letting out [pc.a_moan+] of your own as you grind and bump your [pc.pussy+] against the gorgeous matriarch's hot cunt. As this is her first time doing this, Helena's movements don't quite compliment your own, and she starts awkwardly shuffling about as she tries to find a comfortable position. Thankfully, she soon manages to get into a proper stance, and as the two of you start to press and rub your clits and pussies together, she moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Oh, yes! ~Ooh!~ Keep moving like that, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_SCISSORING_DOM_EXPERIENCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to scissor with Helena again, you suggest to her that the two of you could have some fun rubbing your cunts together. Liking the sound of what you're suggesting, the horny harpy leaps up to join you on the bed, before dominantly pushing you down onto your back and quickly gaining access to your pussy. Reaching down to trace her feathered fingers over your [pc.labia+], she suddenly grabs one of your [pc.legs] and pulls it up, before moving forwards and grinding her [helena.pussy+] against yours. Letting out an excited squeal, she demands, [helena.speechNoEffects(Come on, [pc.name], get those hips moving!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you start gyrating your [pc.hips+], letting out [pc.a_moan+] of your own as you rub and bump your [pc.pussy+] against the gorgeous matriarch's hot cunt. Having already gained experience with you in this position, Helena confidently grinds her clit up and down over your [pc.pussy+], moaning, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Oh, yes! ~Ooh!~ Keep moving like that, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_SCISSORING_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to do something new with Helena, you suggest to her that the two of you could scissor with one another. Nervously blushing as she hears what it is you're suggesting, the horny harpy nevertheless agrees to do as you ask, and climbs up onto the bed beside you.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 As her pussy is already exposed, you reach down to give Helena's [helena.labia+] a quick stroke, before gently pushing her down onto her back and positioning your own pussy up against hers.
		#ELSE
			 Helping her to slide off her lacy white thong, you reach down to give Helena's [helena.labia+] a quick stroke, before gently pushing her down onto her back and positioning your own pussy up against hers.
		#ENDIF
		 Starting to get into it, the beautiful matriarch clumsily shuffles forwards and bumps her [helena.pussy+] against yours. Biting her lip and starting to gyrate her hips, she breathlessly pants, [helena.speechNoEffects(T-This feel good... A-Am I doing it right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reassuring her that she's doing fine, you similarly start gyrating your [pc.hips+] in time with hers, letting out [pc.a_moan+] as you start to grind and bump your [pc.pussy+] against the gorgeous harpy's hot cunt. As this is her first time doing this, Helena's movements don't quite compliment your own, and she starts awkwardly shuffling about as she tries to find a comfortable position. Thankfully, she soon manages to get into a proper stance, and as the two of you start to press and rub your clits and pussies together, she desperately moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Oh, yes! ~Ooh!~ Keep moving like that, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_SCISSORING_EXPERIENCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to scissor with Helena again, you suggest to her that the two of you could have some fun rubbing your cunts together. Liking the sound of what you're suggesting, the horny harpy eagerly agrees to do as you ask, and climbs up onto the bed beside you.
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			 As her pussy is already exposed, you reach down to give Helena's [helena.labia+] a quick stroke, before gently pushing her down onto her back and positioning your own pussy up against hers.
		#ELSE
			 Helping her to slide off her lacy white thong, you reach down to give Helena's [helena.labia+] a quick stroke, before gently pushing her down onto her back and positioning your own pussy up against hers.
		#ENDIF
		 Impatient to get started, the beautiful matriarch impatiently shuffles forwards to bump her [helena.pussy+] against yours. Biting her lip and starting to gyrate her hips, she breathlessly pants, [helena.speechNoEffects(Come on, [pc.name], get those hips moving!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you start gyrating your [pc.hips+], letting out [pc.a_moan+] of your own as you rub and bump your [pc.pussy+] against the gorgeous matriarch's hot cunt. Having already gained experience with you in this position, Helena confidently grinds her clit up and down over your [pc.pussy+], moaning, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Oh, yes! ~Ooh!~ Keep moving like that, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Sex -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_COWGIRL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get straight down to business, you tell Helena that you want to fuck her pussy again. As she hears you say this, the gorgeous harpy bites her lip and runs her feathered hands down between her legs, before spreading her [helena.labia+] and teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(You want to sink your big, hard cock into my horny little pussy, do you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After she's heard you eagerly reply in the affirmative, Helena points to her bed and orders, [helena.speechNoEffects(Get down on your back and present me with your cock! I'm going to be the one in charge tonight!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that this will be the only way in which the dominant harpy will allow you to penetrate her pussy, you do as you're told and lie back on her bed, presenting your hard cock for her to slide down onto. Grinning at your show of obedience, Helena flaps her wings and flutters up onto the bed, before throwing one of her bird-like legs over your stomach and lowering herself down to tease her [helena.labia+] against the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock. Flashing you a delighted grin, she takes things one step further by teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ You want to feel my horny cunt squeezing down around your cock? Then beg for it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Finding yourself at the mercy of Helena's dominant demand, you do as she orders and beg for her to slip your cock into her pussy. Flashing you one last cheeky smirk, the gorgeous matriarch reaches down between her legs, before guiding your throbbing shaft up to her cunt and lowering herself down on it. Filling her [helena.pussy+] with your [pc.cock+], Helena gasps, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ Fuck! Yes, fuck me, [pc.name]! ~Ooh~ Fuck me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Using what little room to manoeuvre you have available, you give Helena what she wants by bucking your hips up and driving your cock into her hot cunt. Moaning and panting, the beautiful matriarch starts bouncing up and down on top on your cock, giving you exactly what it is that you wanted...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_MISSIONARY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get straight down to business, you tell Helena that you want to fuck her pussy again. As she hears you say this, the gorgeous harpy bites her lip and runs her feathered hands down between her legs, before spreading her [helena.labia+] and teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(So what are you waiting for? I want to feel your big, hard cock inside of my horny little pussy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing that she's quite clearly desperate for it, you push Helena down onto her bed, before spreading her legs and positioning yourself between them. Encouraged by the excited moan which the gorgeous harpy lets out, you point your throbbing cock at the entrance to her [helena.pussy+], before starting to tease the [pc.cockHead+] up and down between her [helena.labia+]. Not being able to endure this, Helena desperately squeals, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ Stop doing that! Just fuck me already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding to give her what she wants, you thrust forwards, pushing your [pc.cock+] into the horny matriarch's [helena.pussy+] and causing her to let out [helena.a_moan+]. Pulling back a little, you thrust forwards again, letting out [pc.a_moan] of your own as you feel her hot cunt gripping down around your throbbing shaft. Encouraged by the lewd noises which she keeps on making, you fall into a steady rhythm of pounding Helena's pussy in the missionary position...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_DOGGY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get straight down to business, you tell Helena that you want her to get down on all fours so that you can fuck her pussy from behind. As she hears you say this, the gorgeous harpy bites her lip and runs her feathered hands down between her legs, before spreading her [helena.labia+] and teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(You want to fuck my horny little pussy again? That sounds good to me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Helena jumps up onto her bed, before dropping down on all fours and presenting herself to you. Lifting her tail-feathers and looking back over her shoulder, the gorgeous harpy lets out an excited squeal as she sees
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 you stepping over the top of her and preparing to mount her like an animal.
		#ELSE
			 you dropping down onto your knees behind her and preparing to fuck her like an animal.
		#ENDIF
		 Not wanting to waste another moment, you press your throbbing cock up against the entrance to Helena's [helena.pussy+], before starting to tease the [pc.cockHead+] up and down between her [helena.labia+]. Not being able to endure this, Helena pushes back against you and desperately squeals, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ Stop doing that! Just fuck me already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding to give her what she wants, you thrust forwards, pushing your [pc.cock+] into the horny matriarch's [helena.pussy+] and causing her to let out [helena.a_moan+]. Pulling back a little, you thrust forwards again, letting out [pc.a_moan] of your own as you feel her hot cunt gripping down around your throbbing shaft. Encouraged by the lewd noises which she keeps on making, you fall into a steady rhythm of pounding Helena's pussy in the doggy-style position...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_MATING_PRESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get straight down to business, you tell Helena that you're not only going to fuck her pussy, but that you're going finish inside of her and knock her up. Not giving her any time in which to react to your plans, you grab the blushing harpy and dominantly throw her down onto her bed, before pushing her legs up and apart in such a manner so that her hot pussy is raised up and presented for you to start pounding it.
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 Quickly stepping over the top of her, you lower your [pc.legRace]'s body down so that the [pc.cockHead+] of your feral cock is pushing against the matriarch's [helena.labia+], ready to be slammed inside at any moment.
		#ELSE
			 Quickly squatting down over the top of Helena in order to pin her down on her bed, you position yourself so that the [pc.cockHead+] of your throbbing cock is pushing against the matriarch's [helena.labia+], ready to be slammed inside at any moment.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(!helena.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isPositive())
		<p>
			Finally finding a moment in which to react, Helena gasps, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ D-Did you just say that you want to knock me up?!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Knowing that actions speak louder than words, you drop your hips down and thrust your [pc.cock+] into the matriarch's hot little cunt. Being penetrated in such a dominant manner causes Helena to let out an exceptionally high-pitched squeal, and as you keep your throbbing shaft buried inside of her for a moment, a switch seems to flip inside of her head, and she passionately screams, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ Oh, fuck! D-Do it, [pc.name]! ~Aah!~ Pound my hot little pussy and fill me with your seed! Breed me!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Finally finding a moment in which to react, Helena lewdly gasps, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ Yes! Come on, [pc.name], pound my hot little pussy and fill me with your seed! Breed me!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Happy to hear that Helena is just as excited about this as you are, you draw back a little before slamming down into her horny cunt once again. Moaning and squealing beneath you, the soon-to-be pregnant harpy continues begging for you to pound her horny pussy, which is a request that you're more than happy to grant...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Virginity talk -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_VIRGINITY_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling as though Helena might be willing to lose her virginity, you ask her if she'd be willing to have full penetrative sex with you. Letting out a deep sigh, the beautiful matriarch crosses her wing-like arms and firmly replies, [helena.speech(Sorry, [pc.name], but I don't feel as though the time's right for me to go that far with you. Perhaps I'll be willing to lose my virginity one day, but I'm really not feeling it tonight.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		While her answer is most definitely a 'no' for tonight, you get the feeling that Helena would be willing to lose her virginity to you, if you could only get her into a more romantic mood beforehand. Interpreting the thoughtful look on your face as one of disappointment, Helena steps forwards and offers,
		#IF(helena.hasFetish(FETISH_ORAL_GIVING))
			#IF(pc.hasPenis())
				 [helena.speech(If you'd like, I could always give you a blowjob instead...)]
			#ELSE
				 [helena.speech(If you'd like, I could always eat you out instead...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 [helena.speech(If you'd like, you could always eat me out again instead...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
	<i>
		The next time you start a date with Helena, you will have the opportunity to ask Scarlett to set up a romantic scene to help convince Helena to lose her virginity to you.
		<br/>
		[style.italicsMinorGood(You will require at least <b>three 'Rose Bouquets'</b> in your inventory to do this!)]
	</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Anilingus (on Helena) -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_ANILINGUS_DOM_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling as though the time is right to offer something a little more adventurous to Helena, you propose that she allow you to give her a rimjob. Visibly recoiling in shock as she hears what it is you're suggesting, the beautiful harpy asks in disbelief, [helena.speechNoEffects(Y-You want to do what?! You mean you actually want to... I mean... But that's the wrong hole!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Repeating your request to the nervous harpy, you tell her that you'll make sure that she'll enjoy it. Shaking her head in disbelief at what she's agreeing to, Helena dominantly commands, [helena.speechNoEffects(Well, if I'm going to let you do this, then I'm going to be the one in charge! Lie down on your back so that I can sit on your face and go at my own pace!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Ecstatic to hear that she's actually agreeing to let you perform anilingus on her, you quickly lie down on Helena's bed and get ready for her to sit on your face. With a flap of her wing-like arms, the beautiful matriarch leaps up to join you on the bed, and after letting out a deep sigh, she lowers herself down over your face until her
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 bird-like cloaca is hovering just [style.sizes] away from your mouth.
		#ELSE
			 [helena.asshole+] is hovering just [style.sizes] away from your mouth.
		#ENDIF
		 Placing one last condition on her agreement to do this, the hesitant harpy says, [helena.speechNoEffects(If I don't like it, I'm immediately putting a stop to this. Oh, and don't <i>ever</i> ask me to do this to you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply to this,
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 Helena drops down and firmly plants her bird-like cloaca over your [pc.lips]. Knowing that you're not interested in her pussy, she shifts about a little until her asshole is positioned directly over your mouth, before calling out,
		#ELSE
			 Helena reaches back to spread her perfectly-smooth ass cheeks, before suddenly dropping down and firmly pressing her asshole against your [pc.lips]. Dropping her tail-feathers down over your eyes, she calls out,
		#ENDIF
		 [helena.speechNoEffects(Go on then! Get started and show me that this can feel good...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eagerly obeying, you start planting a series of passionate kisses on Helena's [helena.asshole], before starting to trace the tip of your [pc.tongue+] around her rear entrance. Letting out a surprisingly-erotic moan, the harpy breathlessly pants, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ K-Keep going, [pc.name]! That actually does feel pretty good...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Showing Helena what you can really do, you plant one last big, wet kiss on her [helena.asshole+], before pushing your [pc.tongue+] inside and starting to enthusiastically perform anilingus on her. Just as you hoped she would, the gorgeous matriarch turns out to love the feeling of having her asshole orally pleasured, and as she desperately grinds her [helena.asshole+] down against your [pc.lips+], she lewdly moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes, [pc.name], keep on doing it just like that! ~Ooh!~ Don't stop, I want more!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_ANILINGUS_DOM_EXPERIENCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get a taste of Helena's ass, you suggest to her that she let you give her a rimjob again. Flashing you an amused smirk as she hears what it is you're suggesting, the beautiful harpy teases, [helena.speechNoEffects(So, you want me to sit on your face again? Very well; lie down on my bed!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Happy to hear that she's willing to let you perform anilingus on her, you quickly lie down on Helena's bed and get ready for her to sit on your face. With a flap of her wing-like arms, the beautiful matriarch leaps up to join you on the bed, and after letting out an excited moan, she lowers herself down over your face until her
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 bird-like cloaca is hovering just [style.sizes] away from your mouth.
		#ELSE
			 [helena.asshole+] is hovering just [style.sizes] away from your mouth.
		#ENDIF
		 Before you can say anything or make a move of your own,
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 Helena drops down and firmly plants her bird-like cloaca over your [pc.lips]. Knowing that you're not interested in her pussy, she shifts about a little until her asshole is positioned directly over your mouth, before calling out,
		#ELSE
			 Helena reaches back to spread her perfectly-smooth ass cheeks, before suddenly dropping down and firmly pressing her asshole against your [pc.lips]. Dropping her tail-feathers down over your eyes, she calls out,
		#ENDIF
		 [helena.speechNoEffects(Go on, [pc.name]! Worship my ass!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eagerly obeying, you start planting a series of passionate kisses on Helena's [helena.asshole], before starting to trace the tip of your [pc.tongue+] around her rear entrance. Letting out a deeply erotic moan, the harpy breathlessly pants, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ That's it! Give me more!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Showing Helena what you can really do, you plant one last big, wet kiss on her [helena.asshole+], before pushing your [pc.tongue+] inside and starting to enthusiastically perform anilingus on her. Just like the last time you did this to her, the gorgeous matriarch turns soon starts desperately grinding her [helena.asshole+] down against your [pc.lips+], before lewdly moaning, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes, [pc.name], keep on doing it just like that! ~Ooh!~ Don't stop, I want more!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_ANILINGUS_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling as though the time is right to offer something a little more adventurous to Helena, you propose that she allow you to give her a rimjob. Visibly recoiling in shock as she hears what it is you're suggesting, the beautiful harpy asks in disbelief, [helena.speechNoEffects(Y-You want to do what?! You mean you actually want to... I mean... But that's the wrong hole!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Repeating your request to the nervous harpy, you tell her that you'll make sure that she'll enjoy it. Shaking her head in disbelief at what she's agreeing to, Helena hesitantly offers, [helena.speechNoEffects(Well, I suppose we could try it... I'm really not too sure about this, though...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Ecstatic to hear that she's actually agreeing to let you perform anilingus on her, you tell Helena that it would be best for her to get down on all fours and present her ass to you. With a flap of her wing-like arms, the beautiful matriarch leaps up to join you on the bed, and after letting out a deep sigh, she does as you suggest and drops down onto all fours, before raising her tail-feathers and presenting you with her
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 bird-like cloaca.
		#ELSE
			 [helena.asshole+].
		#ENDIF
		 Placing one last condition on her agreement to do this, the hesitant harpy looks back over her shoulder and says, [helena.speechNoEffects(I-If I don't like it, I'm immediately putting a stop to this! Oh, and don't <i>ever</i> ask me to do this to you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to give the nervous matriarch any time in which to change her mind,
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 you drop down behind her and quickly press your [pc.lips] against her bird-like cloaca. Knowing that you're not interested in her pussy, Helena shifts about a little until her asshole is pointing directly towards your mouth, before calling out,
		#ELSE
			 you take hold of her perfectly-smooth ass cheeks and spread them apart, before dropping down behind her and quickly pressing your [pc.lips] against her [helena.asshole+]. Feeling your mouth make contact with her butt, Helena calls out,
		#ENDIF
		 [helena.speechNoEffects(G-Go on then! Show me that this can feel good...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eagerly obeying, you start planting a series of passionate kisses on Helena's [helena.asshole], before starting to trace the tip of your [pc.tongue+] around her rear entrance. Letting out a surprisingly-erotic moan, the harpy breathlessly pants, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ K-Keep going, [pc.name]! That actually does feel pretty good...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Showing Helena what you can really do, you plant one last big, wet kiss on her [helena.asshole+], before pushing your [pc.tongue+] inside and starting to enthusiastically perform anilingus on her. Just as you hoped she would, the gorgeous matriarch turns out to love the feeling of having her asshole orally pleasured, and as she desperately grinds her [helena.asshole+] back against your [pc.lips+], she lewdly moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes, [pc.name], keep on doing it just like that! ~Ooh!~ Don't stop, I want more!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_ANILINGUS_EXPERIENCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get a taste of Helena's ass, you suggest to her that she let you give her a rimjob again. Flashing you an amused smirk as she hears what it is you're suggesting, the beautiful harpy teases, [helena.speechNoEffects(Oh, you want another taste of my butt, do you? Very well, come and worship my ass!)]
	</p>
		Before you can say anything, the beautiful matriarch quickly leaps up to join you on the bed, and after letting out an excited moan, she drops down onto all fours, before raising her tail-feathers and presenting you with her
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 bird-like cloaca.
		#ELSE
			 [helena.asshole+].
		#ENDIF
		 Looking back over her shoulder, the horny harpy calls out, [helena.speechNoEffects(Come on then, [pc.name]! Get that tongue of yours into my asshole!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to do as she demands,
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 you drop down behind Helena and quickly press your [pc.lips] against her bird-like cloaca. Knowing that you're not interested in her pussy, the gorgeous matriarch shifts about a little until her asshole is pointing directly towards your mouth, before calling out,
		#ELSE
			 you take hold of Helena's perfectly-smooth ass cheeks and spread them apart, before dropping down behind her and quickly pressing your [pc.lips] against her [helena.asshole+]. Feeling your mouth make contact with her butt, the gorgeous matriarch calls out,
		#ENDIF
		 [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Yes, that's it, [pc.name]! Now get started!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eagerly obeying, you plant a series of passionate kisses on Helena's [helena.asshole], before starting to trace the tip of your [pc.tongue+] around her rear entrance. Letting out a deeply erotic moan, the harpy breathlessly pants, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ That's it! Give me more!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Showing Helena what you can really do, you plant one last big, wet kiss on her [helena.asshole+], before pushing your [pc.tongue+] inside and starting to enthusiastically perform anilingus on her. Just like the last time you did this to her, the gorgeous matriarch turns soon starts desperately grinding her [helena.asshole+] back against your [pc.lips+], before lewdly moaning, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes, [pc.name], keep on doing it just like that! ~Ooh!~ Don't stop, I want more!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Anal -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_ANAL_VIRGINITY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having already introduced Helena to the pleasures of receiving anilingus, you feel as though she'll now be willing to entertain the idea of letting you fuck her virgin ass.
		#IF(helena.isVaginaVirgin())
			 Telling her that losing her anal virginity isn't the same as losing her 'real' virginity, you ask the beautiful matriarch if she'd like to know what anal sex feels like. Frowning at you as you say this, Helena takes a moment to think about what you've just said, before cautiously asking, [helena.speechNoEffects(It's not going to hurt or anything, is it?)]
		#ELSE
			 Telling her that losing her anal virginity is no big deal now that she's also lost her 'real' virginity, you ask the beautiful matriarch if she'd like to know what anal sex feels like. Flashing you a dirty look as she hears you say this, Helena says, [helena.speechNoEffects(Sure, I wouldn't mind finding out what it feels like to have your cock buried deep in my butt. It's not going to hurt, is it?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've reassured Helena that you'll take it slow and make sure that it's not a painful experience for her, you can't help but smile as you hear her reply, [helena.speechNoEffects(Ok, you can fuck my ass, but you're going to get me lubed up first.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(helena.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
			#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
				Spreading her legs a little and assuming a dominant pose, the horny harpy reaches down between her legs and gives her bird-like cloaca a playful stroke. Snapping her feathered fingers and pointing at her groin, she orders you to kneel before her and give her a rimjob in order to get her nice and wet. Happy to do as she says, you drop down in front of the dominant harpy and quickly start kissing and licking her rear entrance.
			#ELSE
				Turning around and spreading her legs a little, the horny harpy lifts her tail-feathers, before reaching back and grabbing hold of her ass cheeks. Pulling them apart in order to present her virgin asshole, she orders you to kneel behind her and give her a rimjob in order to get her nice and wet. Happy to do as she says, you drop down behind the dominant harpy and quickly start kissing and licking her rear entrance.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			With a quick flap of her wings, the horny harpy gracefully leaps up onto her bed, before dropping down onto all fours and shuffling around to present her 
			#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
				 bird-like cloaca to you. Looking back over her shoulder and lifting her tail-feathers, she tells you that before she's willing to take your cock in her asshole, you're going to have to give her a rimjob in order to get her nice and wet. Happy to do as she says, you drop down behind the blushing harpy and quickly start kissing and licking her rear entrance.
			#ELSE
				 [helena.ass+] to you. Looking back over her shoulder and lifting her tail-feathers, she tells you that before she's willing to take your cock in her butt, you're going to have to give her a rimjob in order to get her nice and wet. Happy to do as she says, you drop down behind the blushing harpy and quickly start kissing and licking her rear entrance.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(helena.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
		<p>
			Soon enough, Helena's virgin asshole is sopping wet from all of your saliva, and upon feeling that she's now well-lubed and ready to take your cock, she steps away and turns towards you to command, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Ok, [pc.name], that's enough! Now get down on your back so I can ride you!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Knowing that the dominant harpy won't accept any other position, you do as you're told and lie back on her bed, presenting your hard cock for her to penetrate herself on. Grinning at your show of obedience, Helena flaps her wings and flutters up onto the bed, before throwing one of her bird-like legs over your stomach and lowering herself down to tease her
			#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
				 saliva-coated bird-like cloaca
			#ELSE
				 saliva-coated asshole
			#ENDIF
			 against the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock. As she feels your cock prod at her slimy rear-entrance, the horny harpy lets out an excited moan and teases, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ You want to be the first person to ever penetrate my asshole, do you? Then beg for it!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Finding yourself at the mercy of Helena's dominant demand, you do as she orders and beg for her to slip your cock into her rear entrance. Flashing you one last cheeky smirk, the gorgeous matriarch reaches down between her legs, before guiding your throbbing shaft up to her
			#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
				 cloaca
			#ELSE
				 asshole
			#ENDIF
			 and slowly lowering herself down on it. Letting out a series of increasingly-loud gasps as she fills her [helena.asshole+] with your [pc.cock+], Helena whines, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ Fuck! Yes, [pc.name], take my anal virginity! ~Ooh~ Fuck me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Using what little room to manoeuvre you have available, you give Helena what she wants by bucking your hips up and driving your cock into her virgin asshole. Moaning and panting, the beautiful matriarch fully sinks down onto your throbbing shaft, before starting to ride you and squeal, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes! ~Ooh!~ Fuck my ass, [pc.name]!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Soon enough, Helena's virgin asshole is sopping wet from all of your saliva, and upon feeling that she's now well-lubed and ready to take your cock, she looks back over her shoulder and calls out, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Ok, [pc.name], that's enough! Y-You can use your cock now, but just go slow, ok?!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Not wanting to waste another moment, you quickly reposition yourself behind Helena, before pointing your throbbing cock at her
			#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
				 cloaca
			#ELSE
				 [helena.ass+]
			#ENDIF
			 and then starting to tease the [pc.cockHead+] of your shaft up and down over her saliva-coated rear entrance. Quickly losing herself to her overwhelming lust, Helena suddenly pushes back against you and desperately squeals, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ No more teasing! Just take my anal virginity already!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Deciding to give her what she wants, you slowly push forwards, sliding your [pc.cock+] into the horny matriarch's [helena.asshole+] and causing her to let out a desperate, shocked gasp. Pulling back a little, you thrust forwards again, letting out [pc.a_moan] of your own as you feel her virgin asshole gripping down around your throbbing shaft. Encouraged by the lewd noises which she keeps on making, you fall into a steady rhythm of pounding Helena's asshole, causing her to cry out, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes! ~Ooh!~ Fuck my ass, [pc.name]!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_COWGIRL_ANAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get straight down to business, you tell Helena that you want to fuck her ass again. As she hears you say this, the gorgeous harpy bites her lip and
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 runs her feathered hands down between her legs, before spreading her bird-like cloaca and teasing,
		#ELSE
			 turns around to show off her [helena.ass+], before looking back over her shoulder and teasing,
		#ENDIF
		 [helena.speechNoEffects(You want to sink your big, hard cock into my hot little asshole, do you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After she's heard you eagerly reply in the affirmative, Helena points to her bed and orders, [helena.speechNoEffects(Get down on your back then! First, I'll have you give me a rimjob to get me nice and wet, then I'll let you fuck my butt!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that this will be the only way in which the dominant harpy will allow you to penetrate her asshole, you do as you're told and lie back on her bed, presenting your hard cock for her to slide down onto. Grinning at your show of obedience, Helena flaps her wings and flutters up onto the bed, before quickly sitting down on your face and forcing you to perform anilingus on her.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a short while of having you kiss and lick her rear entrance, the horny matriarch stands up and repositions herself over your groin, before lowering herself down to tease her saliva-coated asshole against the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock. Flashing you a delighted grin, she takes things one step further by teasing, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ You want to feel my asshole squeezing down around your cock, do you? Then beg for it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Finding yourself at the mercy of Helena's dominant demand, you do as she orders and beg for her to slip your cock into her asshole. Flashing you one last cheeky smirk, the gorgeous matriarch reaches down between her legs, before guiding your throbbing shaft up to her butt and lowering herself down onto it. Filling her [helena.asshole+] with your [pc.cock+], Helena gasps, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ Fuck! Yes, fuck me, [pc.name]! ~Ooh~ Fuck my ass!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Using what little room to manoeuvre you have available, you give Helena what she wants by bucking your hips up and driving your cock into her slutty asshole. Moaning and panting, the beautiful matriarch starts bouncing up and down on top on your cock, giving you exactly what it is that you wanted...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_DOGGY_ANAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get straight down to business, you tell Helena that you want her to get down on all fours so that you can fuck her asshole from behind. As she hears you say this, the gorgeous harpy bites her lip and
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 runs her feathered hands down between her legs, before spreading her bird-like cloaca and teasing,
		#ELSE
			 turns around to show off her [helena.ass+], before looking back over her shoulder and teasing,
		#ENDIF
		 [helena.speechNoEffects(You want to fuck my horny little butt again? That sounds good to me, but first you've got to get me lubed up...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Helena jumps up onto her bed, before dropping down on all fours and presenting herself to you. Lifting her tail-feathers and looking back over her shoulder, the gorgeous harpy lets out an excited squeal as she sees you drop down behind her and move forwards to plant a big, wet kiss on her exposed asshole. Continuing to kiss, lick, and tongue the horny matriarch's butt for a few more moments, you eventually hear her call out, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ Ok, [pc.name]! That's enough, you can fuck me now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to do as she says, you draw back from Helena's asshole, before
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 stepping over the top of her and preparing to mount her like an animal.
		#ELSE
			 repositioning yourself behind her and preparing to fuck her like an animal.
		#ENDIF
		 Not wanting to waste another moment, you press your throbbing cock up against the beautiful matriarch's
		#IF(helena.getGenitalArrangement()==GENITALS_CLOACA)
			 cloaca,
		#ELSE
			 ass,
		#ENDIF
		 before starting to tease the [pc.cockHead+] of your shaft up and down over her saliva-coated rear entrance. Quickly losing herself to her overwhelming lust, Helena suddenly pushes back against you and desperately squeals, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ No more teasing! Just fuck my ass already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding to give her what she wants, you push forwards, sliding your [pc.cock+] into the horny matriarch's [helena.asshole+] and causing her to let out a desperate, high-pitched squeal. Pulling back a little, you thrust forwards again, letting out [pc.a_moan] of your own as you feel her asshole gripping down around your throbbing shaft. Encouraged by the lewd noises which she keeps on making, you fall into a steady rhythm of pounding Helena's asshole, causing her to cry out, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes! ~Ooh!~ Fuck my ass, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Talonjob -->
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_TALONJOB"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!helena.getFetishDesire(FETISH_FOOT_GIVING).isPositive())
		<p>
			The sight of Helena's bare, bird-like legs and feet is too much for you to resist, and you find yourself asking her if she'd be willing to use them to give you a footjob. Raising her eyebrows in surprise as she hears what it is you're asking, the gorgeous matriarch pointedly looks down at her large, sharp talons, and after giving them a flex, she asks, [helena.speechNoEffects(Are you sure that'd be a good idea?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reassuring her that it will be fine, you kneel down next to Helena's bed and motion for her to come and sit down on the edge of her mattress. Doing as you ask, the matriarch hesitantly sits down on the edge of her bed, before lifting her bird-like feet towards you and asking you what exactly you want her to do with them. Reaching forwards to take hold of her perfectly-manicured talons, you can't help but smile as you run your [pc.hands] over her feet and feel how surprisingly soft the scaly, bird-like skin which covers her legs is. Instructing her to half-clench her talons together in order to form a loose cylinder, you expose your hard cock and push it up into the makeshift orifice.
		</p>
		<p>
			Blushing and fidgeting about a little on her bed, Helena does her best to gently grip your [pc.cock+] and start to give you a potentially-dangerous talonjob. Letting out soft little moans as she concentrates on giving you a pleasurable experience, she says, [helena.speech(I never thought anyone would be interested in fucking a harpy's feet...)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			Delighted to discover that she's surprisingly proficient at using her feet in this manner, you soon find yourself [pc.moaning+] at the wonderful feeling of Helena's talons sliding up and down around your [pc.cock+]. Clearly enjoying herself, the beautiful matriarch is soon letting out a series of soft moans herself, and you can't help but grin as you realise that she's easily going to be able to bring you to orgasm with just her feet...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			The sight of Helena's bare, bird-like legs and feet is too much for you to resist, and you find yourself asking her if she'd be willing to use them to give you a footjob again. Flashing you a soft smile as she hears what it is you're asking, the gorgeous matriarch pointedly flexes her large, sharp talons, before striding over to sit on the edge of her bed and saying, [helena.speechNoEffects(Come on then, [pc.name]. Get your cock out for me.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			More than happy to obey, you drop down before Helena and present her with your rapidly-hardening cock. Seeing the beautiful matriarch give you a consenting nod, you reach forwards to take hold of her perfectly-manicured talons, and once again you find yourself smiling as you run your [pc.hands] over her feet to feel how surprisingly soft the scaly, bird-like skin which covers her legs is. Having her half-clench her talons together in order to form a loose cylinder, you push your [pc.cock+] up into the makeshift orifice.
		</p>
		<p>
			Having already gained experience in doing this with you, Helena expertly grips your [pc.cock+] in her bird-like feet and starts to give you a potentially-dangerous talonjob. Letting out soft little moans as she concentrates on giving you a pleasurable experience, she says, [helena.speech(I never expected you to like my feet this much...)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			Thanks to Helena's high level of proficiency at using her feet in this manner, you soon find yourself [pc.moaning+] at the wonderful feeling of her talons sliding up and down around your [pc.cock+]. Clearly enjoying herself, the beautiful matriarch is soon letting out a series of soft moans herself, and you can't help but grin as you realise that she's easily going to be able to bring you to orgasm with just her feet...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_ROMANCE_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_ROMANCE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Collapsing back down onto her bed and panting for breath, Helena sighs, [helena.speech(That was amazing... Give me a moment, [pc.name]...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she asks, you pull your head away from the beautiful matriarch's pussy, leaving it glistening in a slimy layer of saliva and girlcum. Taking this opportunity to catch your own breath, you watch as Helena's perfect breasts rise and fall under her laboured breathing, and as you lie there, you can't help but think about how stunningly-beautiful this harpy is.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenis())
			After a few minutes, Helena's heavy panting has eased off, and as she turns to seductively bite her lip at you, you can't help but notice that she's tentatively spreading her legs a little further, as though she's inviting you to take the final step and claim her virginity...
		#ELSE
			After a few minutes, Helena's heavy panting has eased off, and as she turns to seductively bite her lip at you, you can't help but notice that she's tentatively spreading her legs a little further, as though she's inviting you forwards for another round of sex...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_ROMANCE_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenis())
			Deciding that you shouldn't take Helena's virginity tonight, you ignore her provocative movement and simply lie down on the bed next to her.
		#ELSE
			Deciding that you don't want to go any further with Helena tonight, you ignore her provocative movement and simply lie down on the bed next to her.
		#ENDIF
		  Rolling over onto her side, she places one of her wing-like arms over you and contentedly sighs, [helena.speech(I'm so glad I met you, [pc.name]...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've returned the beautiful matriarch's sentiments, the two of you spend a good twenty minutes simply lying next to one another. Clearly feeling a little dirty due to her pussy still being coated in a slimy mixture of saliva and girlcum, Helena eventually sits up and says that she's going to take a shower and get ready for bed. Taking this opportunity to announce your intention to leave for the night, you lean forwards to plant a loving kiss on the matriarch's cheek, before standing up and starting to get your things in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although there's an unmistakable look of disappointment on Helena's face, she doesn't seem annoyed by your decision to leave, and in an understanding tone, she says, [helena.speech(Thank you for the wonderful evening, [pc.name]. I hope that we can do this again next week. Oh, and please do visit me up in my nest any time you want!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Assuring her that you'll do just that, you say one last goodbye to the gorgeous harpy, before leaving her to take her shower and letting one of the harpy maids escort you to the front door. Eager to be on your way, you quickly exit Helena's apartment, and after riding the elevator back down to the ground floor, you make your way across the hotel's foyer and soon find yourself [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_ROMANCE_SEX_VIRGINITY_HELENA_DOM"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Feeling as though the time has come to take Helena's virginity, you respond to her provocative movement by leaning down to plant another big, wet kiss on her [helena.pussy+]. From the deeply-aroused moan which the beautiful harpy lets out, you can immediately tell that she's desperate for more attention, and so with this final positive signal, you look up and ask her if she's ready to lose her virginity to you. Nervously blushing, she takes a worried look at your lower [pc.legRace]'s body and says, [helena.speechNoEffects(So my first time will be with a feral [pc.legRace]'s cock? I mean, seeing as it's you, I guess I could agree to that, but it still seems a little extreme...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reassuring Helena by telling her that you'll let her go at her own pace, you awkwardly roll over onto your back and present your [pc.cock+] for her to ride. Gaining more confidence with each passing second, the gorgeous matriarch begins by throwing one of her bird-like legs over your stomach, before lowering herself down and straddling you in the cowgirl position. Moving her hips back, she brushes her ass against your feral cock, before sliding her slimy, saliva-coated labia up and down over your throbbing shaft. Really starting to get into the flow of things, Helena starts to show a real dominant streak as she looks down into your eyes and demands, [helena.speechNoEffects(Tell me that you want me, [pc.name]! Go on, I want to hear you begging for my virgin cunt!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as Helena says, you beg for her to penetrate herself on your cock and give up her precious virginity to you. Satisfied with your display of submission, the beautiful harpy continues teasing you for a few moments more, before very slowly dropping down and letting the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+] push its way past her [helena.labia+]. Pausing before you fully penetrate her, Helena bites her lip and moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ So, [pc.name], are you ready to take my virginity?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly replying in the affirmative, you let out a desperate [pc.moan] as Helena very slowly drops her hips all the way down, forcing your [pc.cock+] [style.size]-by-[style.size] into her virginal cunt. Although she's very well lubricated from the combination of your saliva and her girlcum, the tearing of her hymen still causes Helena to let out a frantic wail as she spears herself on your feral cock. Thankfully, this almost immediately turns into a desperate moan, and with her tight, wet pussy still filled with your cock, the gorgeous matriarch calls out, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes! Fuck! ~Ooh!~ That feels so good, [pc.name]! Fuck, I want more!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a series of high-pitched squeals, the horny, dominant matriarch starts rhythmically bouncing up and down in your lap, forcing your [pc.cock+] in and out of her broken-in cunt...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling as though the time has come to take Helena's virginity, you respond to her provocative movement by leaning down to plant another big, wet kiss on her [helena.pussy+]. From the deeply-aroused moan which the beautiful harpy lets out, you can immediately tell that she's desperate for more attention, and so with this final positive signal, you look up and ask her if she's ready to lose her virginity to you. Nervously blushing, she covers the lower half of her face with one of her big white wings and says, [helena.speechNoEffects(I-I think I'm ready for that, yes... Just please be gentle...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reassuring Helena by telling her that you'll let her go at her own pace, you lie down on your back and present your [pc.cock+] for her to ride. Gaining more confidence with each passing second, the gorgeous matriarch begins by throwing one of her bird-like legs over your stomach, before lowering herself down and straddling you in the cowgirl position. Moving her hips back, she brushes her ass against your hard cock, before sliding her slimy, saliva-coated labia up and down over your throbbing shaft. Really starting to get into the flow of things, Helena starts to show a real dominant streak as she looks down into your eyes and demands, [helena.speechNoEffects(Tell me that you want me, [pc.name]! Go on, I want to hear you begging for my virgin cunt!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as Helena says, you beg for her to penetrate herself on your cock and give up her precious virginity to you. Satisfied with your display of submission, the beautiful harpy continues teasing you for a few moments more, before very slowly dropping down and letting the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+] push its way past her [helena.labia+]. Pausing before you fully penetrate her, Helena bites her lip and moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ So, [pc.name], are you ready to take my virginity?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly replying in the affirmative, you let out a desperate [pc.moan] as Helena very slowly drops her hips all the way down, forcing your [pc.cock+] [style.size]-by-[style.size] into her virginal cunt. Although she's very well lubricated from the combination of your saliva and her girlcum, the tearing of her hymen still causes Helena to let out a frantic wail as she spears herself on your [pc.cock+]. Thankfully, this almost immediately turns into a desperate moan, and with her tight, wet pussy still filled with your cock, the gorgeous matriarch calls out, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes! Fuck! ~Ooh!~ That feels so good, [pc.name]! Fuck, I want more!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a series of high-pitched squeals, the horny, dominant matriarch starts rhythmically bouncing up and down in your lap, forcing your [pc.cock+] in and out of her broken-in cunt...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_ROMANCE_SEX_VIRGINITY_HELENA_SUB"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Feeling as though the time has come to take Helena's virginity, you respond to her provocative movement by leaning down to plant another big, wet kiss on her [helena.pussy+]. From the deeply-aroused moan which the beautiful harpy lets out, you can immediately tell that she's desperate for more attention, and so with this final positive signal, you look up and ask her if she's ready to lose her virginity to you. Nervously blushing, she takes a worried look at your lower [pc.legRace]'s body and says, [helena.speechNoEffects(So my first time will be with a feral [pc.legRace]'s cock? I mean, seeing as it's you, I guess I could agree to that, but it still seems a little extreme...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reassuring Helena that you'll be as gentle as possible, you get her to roll over and push herself up onto all fours, effectively presenting herself to you so that you can mount her like an animal. Leaning down to plant one last kiss on her virgin pussy, you stand up and step over the top of the beautiful matriarch, before lowering your hips and moving forwards until you feel your erect cock prodding at her naked rear end. Letting out a surprised gasp as she feels your feral cock bump into her, Helena nervously says, [helena.speechNoEffects(J-Just please be gentle, [pc.name]!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Shifting your hips down a little, you can't help but let out an excited [pc.moan] as you feel the [pc.cockHead+] of your bestial cock rubbing against Helena's slimy, saliva-coated labia. Not wanting this experience to be in any way bad for the beautiful matriarch, you very slowly start to push forwards and spread her [helena.labia+] around your [pc.cock+]. Giving her some time in which to get accustomed to this feeling, you stop at simply pushing the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock in and out of her pussy few times, before asking Helena if she's ready to fully take it. Bracing herself on her bed, she moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes, [pc.name]! ~Ooh!~ Just do it slowly...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as she asks, you very slowly push all the way forwards, and [style.size]-by-[style.size], you drive your cock all the way into her pussy. Although she's very well lubricated from the combination of your saliva and her girlcum, the tearing of her hymen still causes Helena to let out a frantic wail. Thankfully, this almost immediately turns into a desperate moan, and you can't help but let out a sigh of relief as you hear the gorgeous matriarch call out, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes! Fuck! ~Ooh!~ Fuck me, [pc.name]! I want more!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out [pc.a_moan+] of your own, you do just that, and in time with her high-pitched squeals, you start to rhythmically pump your [pc.cock+] in and out of the beautiful matriarch's broken-in cunt...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling as though the time has come to take Helena's virginity, you respond to her provocative movement by leaning down to plant another big, wet kiss on her [helena.pussy+]. From the deeply-aroused moan which the beautiful harpy lets out, you can immediately tell that she's desperate for more attention, and so with this final positive signal, you look up and ask her if she's ready to lose her virginity to you. Nervously blushing, she covers the lower half of her face with one of her big white wings and says, [helena.speechNoEffects(I-I think I'm ready for that, yes... Just please be gentle...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reassuring Helena that you'll be as gentle as possible, you lean down to plant one last kiss on her virgin pussy, before rising to your knees and shuffling forwards between her legs. Reaching down to take a hold of her slender waist, you slowly push your hips forwards and prod your erect cock against her saliva-coated labia. Letting out a nervous gasp as she looks down to see your [pc.cockGirth] shaft pressing against the entrance to her unspoiled pussy, Helena nervously reminds you, [helena.speechNoEffects(J-Just please be gentle, [pc.name]!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Shifting your hips up and down, you can't help but let out an excited [pc.moan] as you slide the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock up and down over Helena's slimy, saliva-coated labia. Not wanting this experience to be in any way bad for the beautiful matriarch, you very slowly start to push forwards and spread her [helena.labia+] around your [pc.cock+]. Giving her some time in which to get accustomed to this feeling, you stop at simply pushing the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock in and out of her pussy few times, before asking Helena if she's ready to fully take it. Looking up and flashing you a gentle smile, she moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes, [pc.name]! ~Ooh!~ Just do it slowly...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as she asks, you very slowly push all the way forwards, and [style.size]-by-[style.size], you drive your cock all the way into her pussy. Although she's very well lubricated from the combination of your saliva and her girlcum, the tearing of her hymen still causes Helena to let out a frantic wail. Thankfully, this almost immediately turns into a desperate moan, and you can't help but let out a sigh of relief as the gorgeous matriarch desperately gazes up into your eyes and calls out, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes! Fuck! ~Ooh!~ Fuck me, [pc.name]! I want more!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out [pc.a_moan+] of your own, you do just that, and in time with her high-pitched squeals, you start to rhythmically pump your [pc.cock+] in and out of the beautiful matriarch's broken-in cunt...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_ROMANCE_SEX_VIRGINITY_HELENA_SUB_SADIST"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Feeling as though the time has come to take Helena's virginity, you respond to her provocative movement by leaning down to plant another big, wet kiss on her [helena.pussy+]. From the deeply-aroused moan which the beautiful harpy lets out, you can immediately tell that she's desperate for more attention, and so with this final positive signal, you look up and ask her if she's ready to lose her virginity to you. Nervously blushing, she takes a worried look at your lower [pc.legRace]'s body and says, [helena.speechNoEffects(So my first time will be with a feral [pc.legRace]'s cock? I mean, seeing as it's you, I guess I could agree to that, but it still seems a little extreme...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reassuring Helena that you'll be as gentle as possible, you get her to roll over and push herself up onto all fours, effectively presenting herself to you so that you can mount her like an animal. Leaning down to plant one last kiss on her virgin pussy, you stand up and step over the top of the beautiful matriarch, before lowering your hips and moving forwards until you feel your erect cock prodding at her naked rear end. Letting out a surprised gasp as she feels your feral cock bump into her, Helena nervously says, [helena.speechNoEffects(J-Just please be gentle, [pc.name]!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Shifting your hips down a little, you can't help but let out an excited [pc.moan] as you feel the [pc.cockHead+] of your bestial cock rubbing against Helena's slimy, saliva-coated labia. While you don't want to give her cause to dislike you, your sadistic nature tells you that you need to make sure that the beautiful matriarch remembers this moment, and so despite your repeated assurances that you'd be gentle with her, you can't help but sadistically slam forwards the instant you feel that you're in a position to penetrate her. Tearing through her hymen and spearing her on your feral cock, you find yourself with a big grin on your face as you hear Helena let out a painful scream. Telling her that the pain is normal and that it'll be over in a moment, you immediately start to roughly rut her, causing her to let out several more frantic wails as you relentlessly pound her tight cunt.
		</p>
		<p>
			Soon enough, you hear her frenzied cries turn into desperate moans, and, knowing that she's most definitely still finding your rough penetration to be painful, you evilly grin to yourself as you realise that you've turned this once-pure matriarch into your masochistic, slutty cock-sleeve. Burying your [pc.cock+] as deep as possible in her hot little pussy, you ask Helena if she's enjoying this experience. Pushing her hips back against you, she desperately moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes, [pc.name]! ~Mmm!~ Pound my dirty little cunt and rut me like an animal! ~Aah~ Show me no mercy!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a sadistic laugh, you do just that, and in time with her high-pitched squeals, you continue roughly slamming your [pc.cock+] in and out of the beautiful matriarch's despoiled cunt...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling as though the time has come to take Helena's virginity, you respond to her provocative movement by leaning down to plant another big, wet kiss on her [helena.pussy+]. From the deeply-aroused moan which the beautiful harpy lets out, you can immediately tell that she's desperate for more attention, and so with this final positive signal, you look up and ask her if she's ready to lose her virginity to you. Nervously blushing, she covers the lower half of her face with one of her big white wings and says, [helena.speechNoEffects(I-I think I'm ready for that, yes... Just please be gentle...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reassuring Helena that you'll be as gentle as possible, you lean down to plant one last kiss on her virgin pussy, before rising to your knees and shuffling forwards between her legs. Reaching down to take a hold of her slender waist, you slowly push your hips forwards and prod your erect cock against her saliva-coated labia. Letting out a nervous gasp as she looks down to see your [pc.cockGirth] shaft pressing against the entrance to her unspoiled pussy, Helena nervously reminds you, [helena.speechNoEffects(J-Just please be gentle, [pc.name]!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Shifting your hips up and down, you can't help but let out an excited [pc.moan] as you slide the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock up and down over Helena's slimy, saliva-coated labia. While you don't want to give her cause to dislike you, your sadistic nature tells you that you need to make sure that the beautiful matriarch remembers this moment, and so despite your repeated assurances that you'd be gentle with her, you can't help but sadistically slam forwards the instant you feel that you're in a position to penetrate her. Tearing through her hymen and spearing her on your [pc.cock+], you find yourself grinning in delight at the sight of Helena's face scrunching up as she lets out a painful scream. Telling her that the pain is normal and that it'll be over in a moment, you immediately start to roughly hammer your cock in and out of her tight cunt, causing her to let out several more frantic wails.
		</p>
		<p>
			Soon enough, Helena's frenzied cries turn into desperate moans, and after slowly relaxing her facial muscles, she looks up to throw a submissive glance your way. Knowing that she's most definitely still finding your rough penetration to be painful, you evilly grin to yourself as you realise that you've turned this once-pure matriarch into your masochistic, slutty cock-sleeve. Burying your [pc.cock+] as deep as possible in her hot little pussy, you ask Helena if she's enjoying this experience. Pushing her hips back against you, she desperately moans, [helena.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes, [pc.name]! ~Mmm!~ Pound my dirty little cunt! ~Aah~ Show me no mercy!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a sadistic laugh, you do just that, and in time with her high-pitched squeals, you continue roughly slamming your [pc.cock+] in and out of the beautiful matriarch's despoiled cunt...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_FROM_NEST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a deeply satisfied moan, Helena collapses down onto her bed, panting, [helena.speech(Fuck... That was just what I needed today...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lying down next to her and catching your breath, you can't help but smile as the horny matriarch rolls over and throws one of her huge, wing-like arms over you, before shuffling up close and nestling in against your chest. After spending several minutes lying next to you in this fashion, Helena pushes herself up and leans over the top of you to plant a hot, wet kiss on your [pc.lips]. Pulling back and flashing you a loving smile, she sighs, [helena.speech(I'd love to spend more time with you here, [pc.name], but I have matters to attend to back up in my nest...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a deeply satisfied moan, Helena collapses down onto her bed, panting, [helena.speech(Fuck... That was amazing...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lying down next to her and catching your breath, you can't help but smile as the horny matriarch rolls over and throws one of her huge, wing-like arms over you, before shuffling up close and nestling in against your chest. After spending several minutes lying next to you in this fashion, Helena pushes herself up and leans over the top of you to plant a hot, wet kiss on your [pc.lips]. Pulling back and flashing you a loving smile, she expectedly asks, [helena.speech(You're going to stay the night here with me, aren't you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE_NEST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Getting the hint, you sit up on Helena's bed and give her one final kiss, before standing up and telling her that you hope to see her again soon. Returning the sentiment, Helena tells you to pay her another visit tomorrow if you want some more action from her, before darting off into her en-suite bathroom to take a quick shower.
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaving the gorgeous matriarch behind, you quickly get your things back in order and [pc.step] back out into the hallway, where you're very quickly approached by a harpy maid. Curtsying respectfully towards you, this harpy dutifully escorts you to the front door, before seeing you out into the hotel's corridor and wishing you a good day. Eager to be on your way, you quickly ride the elevator back down to the ground floor, before making your way across the hotel's foyer and [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling her that you've unfortunately got some urgent matters to attend to which require you to immediately leave, you sit up on Helena's bed and give her one final kiss. Visibly deflating as you say this, the beautiful matriarch pouts and whines, [helena.speech(I was really hoping that you'd sleep here with me tonight...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Offering Helena your apologies, you set about getting your things in order, before turning to say one last goodbye. As you do so, the gorgeous matriarch jumps up off the bed and rushes forwards to give you a big, loving hug. Returning the affectionate gesture, you hold Helena close to your body for a few moments, before letting her pull back and plant one final kiss on your [pc.lips]. Flashing you a smirk, she says in an affectionate tone, [helena.speech(Go on then, don't let me keep you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Returning her smile, you say goodbye and [pc.step] back out into the hallway, where you're very quickly approached by a harpy maid. Curtsying respectfully towards you, this harpy dutifully escorts you to the front door, before seeing you out into the hotel's corridor and wishing you a good day. Eager to be on your way, you quickly ride the elevator back down to the ground floor, before making your way across the hotel's foyer and [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_SLEEP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_SLEEP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling Helena that of course you'll stay the night with her, you can't help but smile as she excitedly grabs you by the hand and leads you into her en-suite bathroom. Telling you that you're not going to sleep in her bed unless you're clean, she has you join her in the shower, where the two of you take great enjoyment in soaping down one another's bodies. Although this close contact quickly results in the two of you getting very turned on again, Helena reluctantly informs you that she's too tired to have any more sex with you tonight.
	</p>
	<p>
		With your shared shower failing to evolve into something more exciting, the two of you step out onto the fluffy bathmat and help to dry one another off. Thankfully, the feathers covering Helena's huge wing-like arms, head, and tail all prove to be very water-repellent, and so you're both able to get completely dry in just a matter of minutes.
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping back out into her bedroom, Helena quickly slips into a pair of striped panties and a sheer, black chemise. Following her over to her bed, you slip under the covers with the gorgeous matriarch, who very quickly throws one of her beautiful white wings over you. Shuffling up to nestle against your chest, she proves how tired she is by almost instantly drifting off into a deep sleep. Finding your own eyelids to be rather heavy, you let out a deep, contented sigh and quickly fall asleep yourself...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_SLEEP_WAKE_UP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_SLEEP_WAKE_UP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Slowly opening your eyes, you blink a few times and let out a yawn as you wake up after a good night's sleep. Suddenly becoming aware of the large, warm presence nestled up against your chest, you look over to see that Helena's woken up at the same time as you. Still sounding half-asleep, she wraps one of her huge, white wings over your body and mumbles, [helena.speech(Mmm... Good morning, [pc.name]...)]
	</p>
	#IF(helena.isSlutty())
		<p>
			As you open your mouth to return her greeting, the surprisingly-horny matriarch suddenly pushes herself up in bed and leans over to plant a sloppy, wet kiss on your [pc.lips+]. Drawing back a little, she runs her feathered fingers down towards your groin and teases,
			#IF(helena.isVaginaVirgin())
				 [helena.speech(So, do you want to go and have breakfast straight away, or do you want to pound my ass again first?)]
			#ELSE
				 [helena.speech(So, do you want to go and have breakfast straight away, or do you want to pound my horny little pussy again first?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_helenaSlutSeen))
				Helena's new sexual experience from the night before has clearly made a lasting change to her personality, and as you wonder what to say to her, she once again plants a passionate kiss on your [pc.lips]. Drawing back, she flashes you an excited smile, and you see that there's a distinctly dirty look in her [helena.eyes+]...
			#ELSE
				As you wonder what to say to her, the horny harpy once again leans down to plant a passionate kiss on your [pc.lips]. Drawing back, she flashes you an excited smile, and you see that there's a distinctly dirty look in her [helena.eyes+]...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			After you've returned her greeting, the sleepy matriarch leans forwards to plant a loving kiss on your cheek, before smiling at you and sitting up in bed. Throwing off the covers, she stretches out her huge, white wings, before asking, [helena.speech(You're going to stay for breakfast, aren't you, [pc.name]?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_SLEEP_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling her that you've unfortunately got to leave straight away, you sit up on Helena's bed and give her one final kiss. Visibly deflating as you say this, the beautiful matriarch pouts and whines, [helena.speech(I was really hoping that you'd at least have breakfast with me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Offering Helena your apologies, you set about getting your things in order, before turning to say one last goodbye. As you do so, the gorgeous matriarch jumps up off the bed and rushes forwards to give you a big, loving hug. Returning the affectionate gesture, you hold Helena close to your body for a few moments, before letting her pull back and plant one final kiss on your [pc.lips]. Flashing you a smirk, she says in an affectionate tone, [helena.speech(Go on then, don't let me keep you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Returning her smile, you say goodbye and [pc.step] back out into the hallway, where you're very quickly approached by a harpy maid. Curtsying respectfully towards you, this harpy dutifully escorts you to the front door, before seeing you out into the hotel's corridor and wishing you a good day. Eager to be on your way, you quickly ride the elevator back down to the ground floor, before making your way across the hotel's foyer and [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_SLEEP_BREAKFAST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(helena.isSlutty())
			Still a little worn out from the previous night's fun, you tell Helena that you're not in the mood to have sex right now, but you would like to have breakfast with her. Playfully pouting at you, the beautiful matriarch whines, [helena.speech(But I'm feeling so horny... Oh well, I'll just go and have a quick wash, hold on one minute...)]
		#ELSE
			More than happy to indulge Helena in her request, you tell her that you'd love to stay and have breakfast with her. Throwing a happy smile your way, the beautiful matriarch exclaims, [helena.speech(Excellent! I'll just have a quick wash, hold on one minute...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As Helena hurries off into her bathroom to get washed, you let out one last yawn and get out of bed. Waiting for her to be finished, you quickly use the bathroom after her, before following her out of her bedroom and through her luxurious apartment to her dining room. Very shortly after taking a seat on the opposite side of the table to Helena, a couple of harpy maids enter the room and swiftly place down a large selection of cereals and other breakfast foods for the two of you to enjoy. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_MORNING_COWGIRL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling just as horny as she is, you tell Helena that you'd love to have sex with her again. Flashing you a delighted grin, the dominant harpy quickly moves to straddle your stomach, before sliding down and rubbing her groin against yours. Letting out an excited moan, she leans down to plant a passionate kiss on your [pc.lips+], and as you return her display of affection, you wonder how the two of you should enjoy yourselves this morning...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_MORNING_MISSIONARY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling just as horny as she is, you tell Helena that you'd love to have sex with her again. Flashing you a delighted grin, the dominant harpy rolls over onto her back, allowing you to
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 move your lower [pc.legRace]'s body over the top of hers and prepare to have sex with her in the missionary position...
		#ELSE
			 kneel down between her legs and lean down to plant a passionate kiss on her [helena.lips+]. As the beautiful harpy returns your display of affection, you wonder how the two of you should enjoy yourselves this morning...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_MORNING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_MORNING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a deeply satisfied moan, Helena collapses down onto her bed, panting, [helena.speech(Morning sex is the best...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lying down next to her and catching your breath, you can't help but smile as the horny matriarch rolls over and throws one of her huge, wing-like arms over you, before shuffling up close and nestling in against your chest. After spending several minutes lying next to you in this fashion, Helena pushes herself up and leans over the top of you to plant a hot, wet kiss on your [pc.lips]. Pulling back and flashing you a loving smile, she expectedly asks, [helena.speech(You're going to stay for breakfast, aren't you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_MORNING_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling her that you've unfortunately got to leave straight away, you sit up on Helena's bed and give her one final kiss. Visibly deflating as you say this, the beautiful matriarch pouts and whines, [helena.speech(I was really hoping that you'd at least have breakfast with me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Offering Helena your apologies, you set about getting your things in order, before turning to say one last goodbye. As you do so, the gorgeous matriarch jumps up off the bed and rushes forwards to give you a big, loving hug. Returning the affectionate gesture, you hold Helena close to your body for a few moments, before letting her pull back and plant one final kiss on your [pc.lips]. Flashing you a smirk, she says in an affectionate tone, [helena.speech(Go on then, don't let me keep you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Returning her smile, you say goodbye and [pc.step] back out into the hallway, where you're very quickly approached by a harpy maid. Curtsying respectfully towards you, this harpy dutifully escorts you to the front door, before seeing you out into the hotel's corridor and wishing you a good day. Eager to be on your way, you quickly ride the elevator back down to the ground floor, before making your way across the hotel's foyer and [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_MORNING_BREAKFAST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		More than happy to indulge Helena in her request, you tell her that you'd love to stay and have breakfast with her. Throwing a happy smile your way, the beautiful matriarch exclaims, [helena.speech(Excellent! I'll just have a quick wash, hold on one minute...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As Helena hurries off into her bathroom to get washed, you let out one last yawn and get out of bed. Waiting for her to be finished, you quickly use the bathroom after her, before following her out of her bedroom and through her luxurious apartment to her dining room. Very shortly after taking a seat on the opposite side of the table to Helena, a couple of harpy maids enter the room and swiftly place down a large selection of cereals and other breakfast foods for the two of you to enjoy.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_APARTMENT_BREAKFAST -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_APARTMENT_BREAKFAST_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Engaging Helena in conversation over breakfast, the time seems to fly by, and before you know it, the harpy maids are returning to clear your empty bowls and plates away. Feeling as though now is the right time to take your leave, you tell Helena that you enjoyed spending the night with her, to which she replies by giving you a quick kiss and saying, [helena.speech(I had a fantastic time as well, [pc.name]. You'll take me out next Friday as well, won't you?)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling Helena that you'll do your best to be available for her next Friday evening, you say one last goodbye, before letting one of the harpy maids escort you to the front door. Eager to be on your way, you step out into the hotel's corridor and quickly ride the elevator back down to the ground floor, before making your way across the foyer and [pc.stepping] out into the streets of Dominion once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
