<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRAGON_BASIC" author="Xuanlong"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Dragon-morphs prefer terrain that naturally isolates them via either remoteness or inhospitableness. They might be found in the desert and around the volcano in the south of Lilith's Realm, deep in the jungles to the north, or up in the Mountains of the Moon to the west. Some may even seek the Youko Forest. They rarely venture outside of these environments and almost never enter civilization. A tough, scaly exterior, flight capability, and powerful breath weapons distinguishes them from other morphs.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="DRAGON_ADVANCED" author="Xuanlong"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although all dragon-morphs differ individually, they are possibly the most solitary race to inhabit the realm and thus tend to be standoffish, even towards other dragon-morphs. Very little is known about their other traits and combined with the fact that they are also by far the least populous mortal race, it is possible for one to go their entire life without seeing one outside of a book. Most dragon-morphs are subsistence farmers, interacting with perhaps a few isolated traders for goods they cannot grow or make.
	</p>
	<p>
		Dragon-morphs have three distinct subspecies with smaller groups of subvariants between them. The base dragon-morph takes on the traditional appearance resembling that of a giant predatory reptile with leathery wings and inhabits the desert, volcanic, and mountainous regions of the realm. The ryu-morph lives among the youko in their forest and possess blunted muzzles decorated with curious whip-like antennae. They are the most social of the dragon-morph subspecies, hoarding knowledge and occasionally granting it to others. The coatl-morph lives deep in the jungle, far north of Itza'aak. Resembling winged serpents, they are the only subspecies with feathers for plumage and are practitioners of powerful air magic. Two notable subvariants of the dragon-morph are the wyvern-morph and drake-morph, which have arm wings and no wings respectively.
	</p>
	<p>
		Like most other mythological races, dragon-morphs are more affected by arcane storms than others. In fact, even from the edges of the realm, dragon-morphs are drawn towards arcane storms and they are an integral part of the dragon-morph reproductive cycle since flying in close proximity to or high above one dramatically increases the chances of finding a mate. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Fifty years ago, when storms were rare and less powerful, only a few dragons would show up to each one, keeping the amount of competition, and thus violence, down. But as storms have become more frequent and more powerful, the number of dragons in the realm have surged as well as the number of participants in each 'storm-orgy' and the associated fights have become increasingly fierce. The year [#~~(game.getStartingDate().getYear() - 3)] saw the most powerful single storm ever recorded and the resulting aerial battles came to be known as 'The Day the Sky Burned'.
	</p>
	<p>
		A dragon-morph's offspring will be a mixture of dragon-morphs and offspring of their partner's race. An important note: dragon-morphs with the requisite equipment lay eggs. Newborn dragon-morphs can break out on their own, but races not naturally possessing a means of breaking the shell will require assistance. It is therefore vital the mother remain present during hatching.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRAGON_SEKRIT" author="Xuanlong"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In antiquity, dragons were the servants and tributaries of Lisophia, who had adopted their image. Under her rule, they terrorized the populace of the badlands and took what little they had for the Glistering Hoard. In return for their service, dragons were made the strongest and longest lived of the mortal races, and some were afforded the privilege of keeping their own hoards. Over time, however, Lisophia could not help but notice that her sisters were actually growing wealthier than herself despite their relative disinterest in riches. Even if she could squeeze every last flame from Thinis, it would be like trying to get blood from a stone. The destitute peasants under her rule had nothing more to give.
	</p>
	<p>	
		A more prosperous Thinis then, would grow her hoard faster. In this new, ostensibly kinder and gentler, strategy, there was little need for the brutish strength of dragons and they certainly wouldn't stoop to working the land. In any case, Lisophia needed scapegoats upon which the populace could release years of pent up resentment and reverse years of population flight.
	</p>
	<p>
		The dragons, furious at the betrayal after so many centuries of loyal service, rose up against their former mistress and her daughters. It was a battle the dragons were doomed to lose from the start, for as strong as they were even the mightiest of them could only overcome the weakest of Lilin. No records of the battle survived, but it is not hard to imagine that it would have been short.
	</p>
	<p>
		Thus began the Dragonfall.
	</p>
	<p>	
		Those who could not escape in time were cast down and largely stripped of their former strength. Whereas they once stood proud atop all the other mortal races, they were now no stronger than other mythological beasts. Ostracised from society and unwelcome in other lands, they fled to the four corners of the realm to scratch out a living in hiding. Dragons that had private hoards took their treasure with them, but with civilization so far away, gold and gemstones proved poor replacements for food or a warm place to sleep.
	</p>
	<p>
		Forced to adapt to their new homes, dragons experienced a massive culture shift. Within a generation, an object's intrinsic worth was no longer of any consideration. Many pieces of fine artwork, luxurious fabrics, and exquisite weapons were exchanged for simple tools and building materials by traders who were not only daring but also unafraid to take advantage of a naive race that had only known plunder as a means of getting what one wanted. In more distant places, physiological changes would also occur as the host biome's arcane began to influence them. Dragons that managed to find shelter in youko lands became introspective and, after reflecting on what the pursuit of the purely material had wrought, became the scholarly ryu. In the jungle, out of reach of even the most hardy traders, dragons turned to air magic to protect their crops and stargazing to time their harvests, eventually becoming the coatl.
	</p>
	<p>
		It is not known what exactly happened to the dragons that fled Lisophia's punishment, but it is known that some of the most powerful were among them and they were not subject to the Dragonfall. As history faded, stories arose of huge piles of treasure hidden in deep in the most inhospitable of places guarded by similarly huge, inhospitable, ancient dragons. These dragons, so the legend goes, slumber the decades away, conserving their strength, biding for the time when they might wreak their revenge...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</bookText>
