<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- BACK_ALLEYS_SAFE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BACK_ALLEYS_SAFE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
			The back alleys in this particular section of Dominion are not only considerably cleaner and wider than those found throughout the rest of the city, but they are also usually far more frequently travelled. As there's an ongoing arcane storm, however, they are currently just as deserted as any other.
		#ELSE
			The back alleys in this particular section of Dominion are not only considerably cleaner and wider than those found throughout the rest of the city, but they are also far more frequently travelled.
			#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_DEMON)
				 While significantly less busy than the main streets of the city, you still often find yourself encountering groups of slow-moving shoppers, who invariably hurry to one side to let you pass as they see that you're [pc.a_race].
			#ELSE
				 While significantly less busy than the main streets of the city, you still often find yourself having to weave your way past groups of slow-moving shoppers, which greatly slows down your progress through these twisting passageways.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
			While there is usually a large Enforcer presence in this area, it doesn't appear to be considered important enough to warrant the presence of demon officers, and so until the arcane storm passes, there will be nobody to come to your aid should you be attacked...
		#ELSE
			The reason for this alleyway being treated as a safe passage is due to an unusually large Enforcer presence in the area. A uniformed officer never seems to be more than one or two corners away, ready to rush to the aid of anyone who would call for it.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BACK_ALLEYS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BACK_ALLEYS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking through labyrinthine alleyways, with not a soul in sight. Back-doors and steaming vents line the dark brick walls, and you often have to navigate around overflowing bins and stacks of empty crates in order to make progress. These less-travelled parts of Dominion have a dangerous feel to them, and you can't shake the feeling that you're being followed.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WAREHOUSE_DISTRICT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WAREHOUSE_DISTRICT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While there are countless industrial buildings scattered all throughout Dominion, there's no higher concentration of them than in the place you currently find yourself travelling through. The official name for this area is proudly displayed in several places as being simply 'Dominion's Warehouse District', which, while being somewhat generic, very accurately describes it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Most of the buildings you see around you are constructed of either red brick or corrugated iron, and almost without exception they have numerous centaur-drawn carts parked outside of them.
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
				 Thanks to its strategic position right next to Dominion's canal and near to one of the main boulevards, this area is typically heaving with industrial traffic, but due to the ongoing arcane storm, all activity has come to a halt, leaving the entire area completely deserted.
			#ELSE
				 Thanks to its strategic position right next to Dominion's canal and near to one of the main boulevards, this area is absolutely heaving with industrial traffic, and you often have to step aside to let goods-filled carts rumble past.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
				 Thanks to its strategic position right next to Dominion's canal and near to one of the main boulevards, this area is typically heaving with industrial traffic, but due to the ongoing arcane storm, all activity has come to a halt, leaving the entire area completely deserted.
			#ELSE
				 Thanks to its strategic position right next to Dominion's canal and near to one of the main boulevards, a large quantity of industrial traffic is still moving through here, even despite the time of day.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WAREHOUSE_DISTRICT_NO_BUSINESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although there are plenty of businesses established in this area, they're of the kind which only provide services to other large companies. With nothing being on offer to passing members of the public, and without having a specific reason to be here, there's not much for you to do except continue on your way elsewhere...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_HOTEL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_HOTEL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[style.boldGold(The Golden Feather:)]
		<br/>Helena's hotel, 'The Golden Feather', is located in this area. Now that you're aware of its existence, you could head inside and make use of the elevator to travel directly up to Helena's nest.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- STREET_SHADED -->

	<htmlContent tag="STREET_SHADED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[style.boldHarpy(Harpy Nests:)]
		<br/>The wooden platforms and bridges of the rooftop Harpy Nests cast a shadow over these streets. Looking up, you see the occasional flash of brightly-coloured feathers as harpies swoop this way and that.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CANAL -->

	<htmlContent tag="CANAL"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.isDayTime())
		<p>
			#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
				You and [com.name] find yourselves travelling down the narrow dirt path which runs alongside the entire length of Dominion's extensive canal network.
			#ELSE
				You find yourself travelling down the narrow dirt path which runs alongside the entire length of Dominion's extensive canal network.
			#ENDIF
			 While the track occasionally widens out or runs past small clearings and gardens, it is for the most part closely flanked by dark, red-bricked buildings. Despite the fact that these high walls create a gloomy, oppressive atmosphere, you find yourself preferring to be in their presence rather than that of the more spacious, foliage-filled areas, as their leafy bushes, wooden fences, and waist-high walls provide ample hiding places from which muggers could launch an ambush.
		</p>
		<p>
			Unlike the city's back-alleys, this canal-side path is not completely deserted, as every now and then you come across a harmless citizen, who invariably averts their gaze as they hurry past you. The wide waterway itself is also extremely busy, with a seemingly never-ending procession of barges slowly trawling past on their way to destinations unknown. While several of them seem to be for recreational purposes, the vast majority of these narrow boats are hauling cargo of one sort or another; their long decks are stacked high with crates, packed with industrial machinery, or filled with tarpaulin-covered mounds of raw materials.
		</p>
		<p>
			Despite the high level of traffic on the canal itself, you get the feeling that nobody would come to your aid if you were to be attacked while travelling on this path. The distinct lack of any Enforcer presence is a clear indication that this area is ripe territory for muggers, and so you make sure to stay alert as you continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
				You and [com.name] find yourselves travelling down the narrow, dimly-lit dirt path which runs alongside the entire length of Dominion's extensive canal network.
			#ELSE
				You find yourself travelling down the narrow, dimly-lit dirt path which runs alongside the entire length of Dominion's extensive canal network.
			#ENDIF
			 While the track occasionally widens out or runs past small clearings and gardens, it is for the most part closely flanked by dark, red-bricked buildings. Despite the fact that the flickering arcane lights fixed to these high walls create a gloomy, sinister atmosphere, you find yourself preferring to be in their presence rather than that of the more spacious, foliage-filled areas, as their leafy bushes, wooden fences, and waist-high walls provide ample pitch-black hiding places from which muggers could launch an ambush.
		</p>
		<p>
			Due to the fact that it's currently night-time, this canal-side path is completely deserted. The wide waterway itself is also far less busy than it is during the day, with just the occasional arcane spotlight sweeping over the gloomy waterway as the barge it's fixed to slowly trawls past. While there may be the infrequent recreational narrow boat to be seen during daylight hours, these night-time barges are invariably hauling cargo of one sort or another; their long decks are stacked high with crates, packed with industrial machinery, or filled with tarpaulin-covered mounds of raw materials.
		</p>
		<p>
			Despite the fact that there are people keeping a lookout up on the decks of these barges, you get the feeling that none of them would come to your aid if you were to be attacked while travelling on this poorly-lit path. The distinct lack of any Enforcer presence is a clear indication that this area is ripe territory for muggers, and so you make sure to stay alert as you continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	

	<!-- CANAL_END -->

	<htmlContent tag="CANAL_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The path before you abruptly ends, and although the canal continues on its way to the outskirts of the city, there's no way for you to continue onwards...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CITY_EXIT_SEWERS -->

	<htmlContent tag="CITY_EXIT_SEWERS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A large stone bridge has been built over Dominion's canal, and as you walk over it, you hear the unmistakable sound of rushing water coming from below. Peering over the side, you see the origin of the noise; a huge, brick-lined opening, covered in metal bars, has been dug out on one side of the waterway, and it's into this that the water from the canal is flowing. Looking closer, you see that on the other side of the bars, there's a wide set of stone steps leading down into the gloom below.
	</p>
	<p>
		Searching for a way to get access to those steps, and the area beyond, you soon find yourself standing before a building marked as 'Submission Enforcer Post'. The doors are wide open, and, peering inside, you see that the origin of the stone staircase is situated in the middle of a large, mostly-empty waiting room.
	</p>
	<p>
		There only appears to be one Enforcer guarding the staircase, who half-heartedly glances up from their newspaper as they catch sight of you. Letting out a sigh, they motion towards the staircase, clearly gesturing that you're able to come and go as you please.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- CITY_EXIT_SEWERS_ENTERING_SUBMISSION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTER_SUBMISSION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping into the building marked as the 'Submission Enforcer Post', you start to make your way towards the staircase. A solitary Enforcer is stationed behind a desk on one side of the room, and he barely even bothers to look up to see who's entering before continuing to read the newspaper in his hands. Obviously not being of any sort of hindrance to you, you ignore the Enforcer and continuing forwards, before starting to descend the stone staircase. The deafening roar of rushing water quickly envelops you, and beneath the orange glow of arcane-powered lamps, you quickly hurry down the damp stone steps.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you reach the bottom, you find yourself confronted by a weathered wooden door, which has a helpful sign tacked to the front, reading; 'Please Enter'. Following the sign's instruction, you push open the door and step forwards into the large, well-lit interior of yet another Enforcer post. This one is far more active than its counterpart on the surface, and all around you, Enforcers are either hurrying to and fro, busily working at one of a dozen or so desks, or standing guard beside the several doors which branch off into internal offices.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTER_SUBMISSION_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As the door swings shut behind you, a short, pink-furred, greater cat-girl Enforcer rushes forwards. Even with the high heels that she's currently wearing, she can't be any more than [units.size(152)] in height, but her breasts, hips, and thighs are without doubt the largest of any of the Enforcers in the room. As she comes to a rather unsteady halt in front of you, a big grin breaks out across her face, and she cries out in a very friendly voice, [claire.speech(Hey, I haven't seen you down here before, so this must be your first time in Submission!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTER_SUBMISSION_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As the door behind you swings shut, you see the familiar, pink-furred figure of Claire busily collecting papers on the other side of the room. As she travels between the desks, you can't help but notice how huge her breasts, hips, and ass are on her short figure, and how even her armoured vest isn't enough to stop her massive [claire.cupSize]-cup boobs from swaying to and fro in time with her hurried movements.
	</p>
	<p>
		If you wanted to, you could walk up to her and ask her more about Submission, or simply ignore her for the time being and continue on through the door on the far side of the room marked as 'Public Access to Submission'...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CITY_EXIT_SEWERS_ENTERING_SUBMISSION_FIRST_TIME -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTER_SUBMISSION_FIRST_TIME_CONFIRMATION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Confirming to the cat-girl that this is indeed your first time visiting Submission, you then ask her how she's so sure that this is your first time coming down here. After all, there are numerous entrances, and you could have previously visited via one of those.
	</p>
	<p>
		A very smug smile quickly settles on the cat-girl's face, and, placing her hands on her hips, she puffs up her chest, thrusting her disproportionately-large breasts out in your general direction. Having assumed this striking pose, she proudly states, [claire.speech(Although not normally granted to someone of my rank, I, sergeant Claire Kasun, have permission to use teleportation pads! Being assigned the job of relaying messages, I can instantaneously travel between any of Submission's Enforcer posts, so nobody who enters Submission escapes my notice! Anyway, now that I've introduced myself, who are you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding that there'd be no harm in giving your name to Claire, you introduce yourself to her, [pc.speech(I'm [pc.name].)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Pleased to meet you, [pc.name]. So, as you're new, I need to let you know a few things! One, please don't go swimming in the waterways. The alligator-morphs can get a little snappy if they think you're barging in on their territory. Two, stay away from Lyssieth's palace. She doesn't receive visitors, and those guards of hers don't take kindly to strangers loitering about the place,)] the cat-girl Enforcer warns, before wagging a finger under your nose and continuing, [claire.speech(Now this third one's the most important of all, so listen up! Whatever you do, stay out of the tunnels!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I was told the same thing about the alleyways in Dominion. I'll be careful,)] you reply, thinking back to the warning Rose gave you shortly after arriving in Dominion.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Don't take my warning so lightly!)] Claire huffs, putting her hands back on her hips and pouting at you, [claire.speech(Dominion's nothing compared to what we have to deal with! Now, we're not meant to go around telling people this, but I can see that you're going to need some extra convincing! The truth is, we Enforcers are extremely under-staffed down here, and we count ourselves lucky if we can send even one patrol through those tunnels per week. As a result, they're absolutely infested with roving gangs of nasty little imps, who love nothing more than to have their wicked ways with innocent travellers.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(If they've formed gangs, then surely they have leaders? Can't you attack and arrest them directly?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(If only! The problem is, their leaders are powerful demons, and they've gone and built fortresses in those tunnels. Although they're not much more than just crude defensive walls, we're not exactly equipped to go and lay siege to them. Just accept that the tunnels are off-limits, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking Claire again for the warning, you wonder to yourself if you'll ever end up having to visit these fortresses.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Oh, and one last thing! We've recently been having some trouble with slimes attacking innocent travellers and then forcibly transforming them into even more slimes,)] the cat-girl says, taking on a stern expression and starting to wag her finger again as she continues, [claire.speech(Now, I know I just told you to stay out of the tunnels, but if you do decide to foolishly ignore my warning and end up venturing into some of the ones not claimed by imps, just be extra careful of any slimes you bump into. And if, by some miracle, you're able to get any information on why these slimes are doing this, there's a five-thousand flame reward being offered if you report it to me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'll keep that in mind,)] you reply, wondering if it would be worth your time to find one of these slimes and ask them about these forced transformations.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(That reward isn't meant to encourage you to go and seek out danger, [pc.name],)] Claire sighs, obviously having picked up on the interested tone of your voice, before smiling and finally stating, [claire.speech(Anyway, if you need anything else, I'm always around, so don't hesitate to come and ask me about anything!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>