<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- DATE_START -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Meet Nyan at her apartment and say you're here to take her on a date.
	</p>
	<p>
		She lets you in and asks you to wait in her lounge.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_START_LOUNGE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_START_LOUNGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You're shown to her lounge. She leaves to get dressed.
	</p>
	<p>
		There's a bookcase on one side of the room filled with romance novels, and on the coffee table there's magazines about fashion and cookery.
	</p>
	<p>
		A couple of paintings on the wall depict countryside scenes.
	</p>
	<p>
		After ten minutes, you hear Nyan approaching from down the hallway...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_START_LOUNGE_NYAN_DRESS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_START_LOUNGE_NYAN_DRESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Nyan returns wearing [nyan.a_slotClothing(TORSO, true)], with a colour-coordinated bow on her headband. She's also wearing red lipstick, black eye-liner, and light blue eye-shadow.
	</p>
	<p>
		You tell her how pretty she looks and she profusely blushes. Coyly shuffling her feet, she asks if you're ready to go.
	</p>
	<p>
		You reply in the affirmative, and the two of you head into the hallway, where Nyan pulls on
		#IF(game.getSeason()==SEASON_SUMMER)
			 her stylish, tan-coloured coat and  a pair of dark brown chelsea boots, before grabbing hold of a cute, frog-styled umbrella.
		#ELSE
			 her stylish, tan-coloured coat, a black scarf, and a pair of dark brown thigh-high boots, before finally grabbing a cute, frog-styled umbrella.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Exiting her apartment, you accompany her down the stairs and towards the apartment building's exit...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_START_RESTAURANT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_START_RESTAURANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
	#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
		<p>
			You see through the windows that there's an ongoing arcane storm. Nyan suggests that you wait for the next clap of thunder, then run for the Shopping Arcade.
		</p>
		<p>
			You do so, and very luckily manage to get there without another clap of thunder affecting your girlfriend.
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_RAIN || game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_SNOW)
		<p>
			[pc.Walking] beside your girlfriend, you see that it's currently
			#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_RAIN)
				 raining.
			#ELSE
				 snowing.
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out an embarrassed little whine, Nyan pops open her cute frog-umbrella and stutters, [nyan.speechNoEffects(T-This is big enough for both of us... S-So we can w-walk close together and share it...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Thanking your girlfriend for her kindness, you do as she suggests and share the umbrella with her. The two of you soon get to the Shopping Arcade.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Thankfully, the weather allows the two of you to get to the Shopping Arcade without issue.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Heading down the wide, marble walkways, you soon arrive at 'The Oaken Glade' and head inside. As soon as you enter, a smartly-dressed greater otter-boy, who is clearly the establishment's maître d', steps forwards and gives Nyan a familiar smile, before greeting the two of you, [style.speechMasculine(Good evening. We have not seen you nor your mother for some time, Ms. [nyan.surname], but as ever, you are most welcome here. Please, follow me; we always have a table for you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the waiter through the restaurant, you see that all of the tables are occupied, despite looking empty from the outside. Realising that this must be another aspect of the illusion to grant diners some privacy, you continue on to the other side of the forest clearing, where you and Nyan are presented with a quiet corner table for two.
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking your girlfriend's coat and umbrella, the waiter seats you both at the table and gives you each a menu, before handing you the wine menu and telling you to take your time in ordering. Slipping off to stand watch over the restaurant, the otter-boy leaves you and Nyan alone.
	</p>
	<p>
		Nyan says that she'd like to order some white wine...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	
	<!-- DATE_END_RETURN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_END_RETURN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		No sooner have you exited her store, Nyan suddenly gasps and exclaims, [nyan.speechNoEffects(I-I forgot my coat! Wait here, [pc.name], I'll j-just be a minute!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as your girlfriend asks, you wait outside her store while she rushes back inside to fetch her coat. Your patience is soon rewarded, as just a couple of minutes later she returns wearing a stylish, tan-coloured coat, which makes her look exceptionally pretty. As she hurries back to stand before you, you see that she's also
		#IF(game.getSeason()==SEASON_SUMMER)
			 swapped her heels for a pair of dark brown chelsea boots, and is also clutching a cute, frog-styled umbrella.
		#ELSE
			 swapped her heels for a pair of dark brown thigh-high boots, and is also wearing a black scarf and clutching a cute, frog-styled umbrella.
		#ENDIF
		 Profusely blushing in response to the compliment you give her on her appearance, your shy girlfriend stutters, [nyan.speechNoEffects(T-Thank you, [pc.name]... C-Come on, let's go...)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
		<p>
			[pc.Walking] beside your girlfriend, you exit the Shopping Arcade to see that there's an ongoing arcane storm. Letting out a little eek, Nyan huddles up to you and whines, [nyan.speechNoEffects(Oh no... My apartment is j-just five minutes from here, so p-perhaps if we hurry, it won't affect me too much...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as the cat-girl suggests, the two of you hurry down the street in the direction of her apartment. By a stroke of particularly good fortune, you manage to avoid both strikes of thunder and horny citizens during your dash towards Nyan's home. As you reach the steps of her apartment building, however, the storm above makes up for its unusual silence by unleashing one of the most powerful claps of arcane thunder you've ever heard. 
		</p>
		<p>
			Despite pulling her through the entrance and slamming the door shut behind you, you're not able to save Nyan from the arousing effects of the storm, and before you know what's happening, the cat-girl is frantically pressing her [nyan.lips+] against your mouth and lustfully grinding herself against your body. Despite knowing that her behaviour is caused by the storm, you can't help but feel aroused by this sudden, passionate display of affection, and happily return your girlfriend's kiss.
		</p>
		<p>
			Protected from any further claps of thunder, Nyan suddenly starts to come back to her senses, and with a little eek, she breaks off the kiss and stammers, [nyan.speechNoEffects(I-I'm so sorry, [pc.name]! I-I couldn't stop myself!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Telling her that there's nothing to be sorry about, you reassuringly stroke Nyan's arm, which has the desired effect of calming her down. Making your way up the flights of stairs to the third floor, the two of you soon arrive at the door to your girlfriend's apartment, where she turns to face you and nervously shuffles her feet, before looking at you with her big, blue eyes and saying, [nyan.speechNoEffects(Y-You can come in if you'd like...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_RAIN || game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_SNOW)
			<p>
				[pc.Walking] beside your girlfriend, you exit the Shopping Arcade to see that it's currently
				#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_RAIN)
					 raining.
				#ELSE
					 snowing.
				#ENDIF
				 Letting out an embarrassed little whine, Nyan pops open her cute frog-umbrella and stutters, [nyan.speechNoEffects(T-This is big enough for both of us... S-So we can w-walk close together and share it...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Thanking your girlfriend for her kindness, you do as she suggests and share the umbrella with her. Engaging your blushing girlfriend in conversation, you then head down the street in the direction of her apartment.
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[pc.Walking] beside your girlfriend, you exit the Shopping Arcade to see that the lack of precipitation renders Nyan's umbrella unnecessary. Engaging your girlfriend in conversation, you head down the street in the direction of her apartment.
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			After five minutes, you arrive at the entrance to her apartment building, and after [pc.walking] up the steps, the two of you push open the front door and enter the lobby. Making your way up the flights of stairs to the third floor, the two of you soon arrive at the door to Nyan's apartment, where she turns to face you and nervously shuffles her feet, before looking at you with her big, blue eyes and saying, [nyan.speechNoEffects(Y-You can come in if you'd like...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DATE_END_RETURN_GOODBYE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_END_RETURN_GOODBYE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You decline and say goodbye, and after she's entered her apartment and closed the door behind her, you travel back down the stairs and out into the streets of Dominion...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DATE_END_RETURN_GOODBYE_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You decline and say goodbye. Wanting to give her a show of affection, you [pc.step] forwards and give your cute, cat-girl girlfriend a parting kiss. Letting out a happy, muffled moan and leaning into your body, Nyan eagerly returns the kiss, before pulling back and bashfully smiling at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		You say goodbye to her again, and after she's entered her apartment and closed the door behind her, you travel back down the stairs and out into the streets of Dominion...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HALLWAY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HALLWAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hallway which leads through the apartment.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ENTRANCE_HALL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE_HALL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Modestly-decorated entrance hall, though large enough to have a cloak-room built into one side.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- NYAN_BEDROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_BEDROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Nyan's bedroom. Light-pink walls and pastel-coloured furniture. An impressive collection of romance novels and cuddly toys. Windows look down onto the courtyard behind the apartment building.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ENSUITE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENSUITE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The ensuite to Nyan's bedroom. Very large bathtub takes up almost half of the room. Windows look down onto the courtyard behind the apartment building.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- SPARE_BEDROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SPARE_BEDROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A spare bedroom, fully furnished and ready for someone to use. Windows look down onto Dominion's streets.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BATHROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BATHROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Small bathroom, containing just a toilet and sink.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- KITCHEN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KITCHEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Open-plan kitchen connected to dining room. Equipped with all the latest arcane gadgets. Just like the dining room, the windows look down onto Dominion's streets.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DINING_ROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DINING_ROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Spacious dining room, containing several cabinets and the expected table and chairs. Windows look down onto Dominion's streets.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LOUNGE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LOUNGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Lounge holds several plush sofas, each of which is covered in colourful cushions. Windows look down onto the courtyard behind the apartment building.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>