<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	
	<!-- EXTERIOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Exterior of Nyan's apartment.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HALLWAY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HALLWAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hallway which leads through the apartment.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ENTRANCE_HALL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE_HALL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Modestly-decorated entrance hall, though large enough to have a cloak-room built into one side.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- NYAN_BEDROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_BEDROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Nyan's bedroom. Light-pink walls and pastel-coloured furniture. An impressive collection of romance novels and cuddly toys. Windows look down onto the courtyard behind the apartment building.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ENSUITE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENSUITE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The ensuite to Nyan's bedroom. Very large bathtub takes up almost half of the room. Windows look down onto the courtyard behind the apartment building.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- SPARE_BEDROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SPARE_BEDROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A spare bedroom, fully furnished and ready for someone to use. Windows look down onto Dominion's streets.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BATHROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BATHROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Small bathroom, containing just a toilet and sink.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- KITCHEN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KITCHEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Open-plan kitchen connected to dining room. Equipped with all the latest arcane gadgets. Just like the dining room, the windows look down onto Dominion's streets.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DINING_ROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DINING_ROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Spacious dining room, containing several cabinets and the expected table and chairs. Windows look down onto Dominion's streets.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LOUNGE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LOUNGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Lounge holds several plush sofas, each of which is covered in colourful cushions. Windows look down onto the courtyard behind the apartment building.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>