<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- Corridor: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		TODO Corridor. Carpeted, beams overhead. Faint musty smell like that found in very old buildings...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- Entrance/Exit: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You're currently standing in a modestly-sized reception area. Just like its exterior suggested, the inside of this building looks to be quite old, with dark wooden beams visible both overhead and set into the walls. Allowing your gaze to wander over the worn, drab-green carpet, you see that a long, free-standing desk has been positioned on the far side of this room. Behind this desk is standing
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_enforcers_sterope_met))
			 the familiar horse-girl, Sterope.
		#ELSE
			 a lesser horse-girl.
		#ENDIF
		 About half a dozen cushioned chairs are lined up along the sides of this area, and although they look to be quite shabby and well used, they're all currently unoccupied.
	</p>
	<p>
		From here, you could proceed forwards to greet
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_enforcers_sterope_met))
			 Sterope,
		#ELSE
			 the horse-girl Enforcer,
		#ENDIF
		 or instead turn around and exit the building via the same way you entered it...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT_INITIAL_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to enter the Enforcer station, you [pc.walk] down the wide path which runs through the knot garden and approach the entrance. The wooden doors have been propped open, allowing you to pass by a couple of friendly-looking Enforcers and enter the building without stopping.
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking a look around as you [pc.step] inside, you see that you're standing in a modestly-sized reception area. Just like its exterior suggested, the inside of this building looks to be quite old, with dark wooden beams visible both overhead and set into the walls. Allowing your gaze to wander over the worn, drab-green carpet, you see that a long, free-standing desk has been positioned on the far side of this room. Behind this desk is standing
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_enforcers_sterope_met))
			 the familiar horse-girl, Sterope.
		#ELSE
			 a lesser horse-girl.
		#ENDIF
		 About half a dozen cushioned chairs are lined up along the sides of this area, and although they look to be quite shabby and well used, they're all currently unoccupied.
	</p>
	<p>
		From here, you could proceed forwards to greet
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_enforcers_sterope_met))
			 Sterope,
		#ELSE
			 the horse-girl Enforcer,
		#ENDIF
		 or instead turn around and exit the building via the same way you entered it...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="EXIT_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having concluded your business within the Enforcer station, you exit via the main entrance. After passing through the propped-open doors, you pass through the knot garden and quickly return to the street beyond.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- Reception area: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_enforcers_sterope_met))
			Crossing through the reception area, you approach the desk and say hello to Sterope.
		#ELSE
			Crossing through the reception area, you approach the desk and introduce yourself to the receptionist.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_fully_furry))
			 Having convinced her to remain as a greater horse-girl, you see that Sterope is in the form of a fully anthropomorphised horse. Both the hair covering her body as well as the mane-like hair which is tied up into a bun is dark brown in colour, while her eyes are the same shade of green that they were when she was mostly human. Her Enforcer uniform is in immaculate condition, and as you finish your greeting, she brushes a speck of dust from her sleeve and fixes you with her stern gaze.
		#ELSE
			 From her dark brown, horse-like ears and tail, it's quite obvious that
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_enforcers_sterope_met))
				 Sterope
			#ELSE
				 this receptionist
			#ENDIF
			 is a horse-girl, but apart from these animal features she's otherwise human in appearance. Her skin is olive in colour, while her dark brown hair is tied up into a bun. Her Enforcer uniform is in immaculate condition, and as you finish your greeting, she brushes a speck of dust from her sleeve and sternly gazes at you with her green eyes.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasAnyEnforcerStatusEffect())
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_enforcers_sterope_met))
			<p>
				[sterope.speech([pc.Name],)] the cold-mannered horse-girl greets you by simply stating your name. Suspiciously looking at your Enforcer uniform, she asks, [sterope.speech(Are you <i>really</i> an Enforcer?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				You assure Sterope that you are, but that you're on a secret assignment from Dominion and so can't say too much to her. Before you can say anything else, Sterope gives you a slightly disdainful look, before
				#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_met_in_tavern))
					 flashing you an icy look and hissing under her breath, [sterope.speech(Don't you <i>dare</i> mention anything about my private life while I'm on duty.)]
				#ELSE
					 asking, [sterope.speech(So, what is it that I can help you with?)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[sterope.speech([pc.Name], is it?)] she replies in a flat tone. Her professional attitude borders on being cold and aloof, and after suspiciously looking at your Enforcer uniform, she taps the nameplate on her chest and reveals, [sterope.speech(I'm Constable Hippos, but as you're an Enforcer as well, I can be 'Sterope' to you... You <i>are</i> an Enforcer, aren't you?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				You assure Sterope that you are, but that you're on a secret assignment from Dominion and so can't say too much to her. Before you can say anything else, Sterope gives you a slightly disdainful look, before asking, [sterope.speech(So, what is it that I can help you with?)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_enforcers_sterope_met))
			<p>
				[sterope.speech([pc.Name],)] the cold-mannered horse-girl greets you by simply stating your name. Before you can say anything else, she gives you a slightly disdainful look, before
				#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_met_in_tavern))
					 flashing you an icy look and hissing under her breath, [sterope.speech(Don't you <i>dare</i> mention anything about my private life while I'm on duty.)]
				#ELSE
					 asking, [sterope.speech(Do you have a crime to report? Or is there something else you're hoping that I can help you with?)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[sterope.speech([pc.Name], is it?)] she replies in a flat tone. Her professional attitude borders on being cold and aloof, and with a slightly disdainful look on her face, she taps the nameplate on her chest and reveals, [sterope.speech(I'm Constable Hippos, but the higher-ups have ruled that members of the public should call us by our first names, so that's 'Sterope' to you. Do you have a crime to report? Or is there something else you're hoping that I can help you with?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Impatiently tapping her fingernails on the desk a couple of times, Sterope waits to hear what it is that you're here for...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not having anything else to discuss with Sterope, you tell her that you've got to be going and [pc.step] away from her desk. Giving you the briefest of nods, the stern horse-girl simply says, [sterope.speech(Stay out of trouble.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_TALK_WORK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know more about what sort of work the Enforcers do here in Elis, you ask Sterope if there's much crime to be dealt with. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(There's some crime, yes,)] she replies. Letting out an impatient sigh as she realises that you were hoping for more information than that, she continues in a flat tone, [sterope.speech(It used to be very peaceful here in Elis, but with the influx of refugees from the Foloi Fields, there's been an increase in criminal activity. We can easily manage it during daylight hours, but we don't have the manpower to keep the alleyways safe after dark, so don't go wandering through the northern part of town at night.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking her for the information, you wonder what to ask of Sterope next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_TALK_CAREER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know more about Sterope's background, you ask her what led to her becoming an Enforcer.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(I don't see how that's any of your business,)] Sterope coldly replies, before sighing, [sterope.speech(You're lucky that the higher-ups have ordered us to be friendly with members of the public.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		If this is her being friendly, you can't help but wonder what Sterope would be like normally as she prepares to reveal her past to you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(If you must know, I joined the Enforcers when I was just nineteen, and I've been stationed here in Elis for almost my entire career,)] she says, before going on to state, [sterope.speech(I've been offered a promotion several times, but I've no interest in going through officer school, and I like my job here. I think that's all you need to know.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeling like trying to push her to reveal any further information would be futile, you wonder what to ask Sterope next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_TALK_LUNETTE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious to hear what an Enforcer has to say about Lunette, you ask Sterope what she thinks of the elder lilin and the chaos she's caused in the Foloi Fields.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(It's Lunette's daughters who are causing the problem, not her,)] Sterope tactfully responds, [sterope.speech(It's certainly not for me to question a daughter of Lilith herself.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Just as you think that Sterope has finished her response, she continues, [sterope.speech(Besides, it's really not so bad for those out in the Fields. There are far worse fates than being taken by a succutaur and turned into her submissive, worthless cock-sleeve...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Suddenly catching herself and realising what it is she's saying, Sterope clears her throat and says, [sterope.speech(Anyway, nevermind about that...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_unlocked))
			Before you can tease her about what she's just said, Sterope flashes you a stern look and hisses, [sterope.speech(Don't say a word...)]
		#ELSE
			It seems as though the horse-girl has inadvertently revealed a secret desire of hers. Perhaps you could push her a little further and get her to admit this desire to you?
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seizing upon what Sterope has just said, you tease the horse-girl by asking her if she thinks about succutaurs turning people into submissive, worthless cock-sleeves often. Although she blushes a little as you say this, Sterope maintains her composure and looks down her nose at you as she prepares her response.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(I'm on duty at the moment, so this sort of conversation is entirely unacceptable,)] she cooly states, before glancing around to make sure that no other Enforcers are nearby. Satisfied that nobody's going to overhear her, she says under her breath, [sterope.speech(If you like that sort of thing, then you can find me in 'The Centaur's Sword' after nine each evening...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can ask her any more about this, the Enforcer clears her throat and asks in a stern tone, [sterope.speech(Is there anything else I can help you with?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_SWORD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		TODO You tell Sterope that you've been sent by Minotallys to make contact with the group of SWORD Enforcers who are staioned here. Sterope doesn't believe you, but when you show her your access pass to the town hall, she accepts what you're saying as the truth.
	</p>
	<p>
		You ask her what she knows about the SWORD Enforcers.
	</p>
	<p>
		She says that they don't mix well with the rest of the Enforcers, and that the rumour is that they caused a fuss in Dominion about five years ago and were demoted and sent here.
	</p>
	<p>
		There was talk that a recognised daughter of the elder lilin Lasielle, who'd been given a high-ranking position in the Enforcers, had been arrested. That elder daughter hasn't been seen since, and a week later the group arrived here in Elis.
	</p>
	<p>
		She says that she doesn't know any more, and you can just ask them. Says that you can come and go as you please, and that the SWORD Enforcer office is straight ahead down the corridor.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_SWORD_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		TODO Thanking Sterope for the information, you head on past her desk and into the station's interior.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Locked door: -->

	<htmlContent tag="LOCKED_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		TODO This door is locked...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="LOCKED_DOOR_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		TODO You [pc.step] back into the corridor...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Cells: -->

	<htmlContent tag="CELLS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		TODO Four cells are where the town's criminals are held while awaiting trial...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Office: -->

	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		TODO In this office Enforcers fill out paperwork and plan their patrols...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- SWORD: -->

	<htmlContent tag="SWORD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		TODO A group of dangerous-looking SWORD Enforcers...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

</dialogue>
