<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- All of these are linked to the 'dialogue/innoxia/places/fields/elis/market.xml' dialogue nodes. -->
	
	<!-- Centre of market, livestock on Wednesdays and Saturdays, games on all other days. -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CENTRE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDayOfWeek()==DOW_SATURDAY || game.getDayOfWeek()==DOW_WEDNESDAY)
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
			<p>
				As it's past closing time, the wooden fencing which had been erected to keep the livestock separated is being disassembled and packed away. Not wanting to trouble any of the farmers who's finished their business for the day, you decide to leave them to it and continue on your way through the market...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				As you approach the very centre of the Farmer's Market, you see that a large, square area has been cordoned off and partitioned into small pens by means of wooden fencing. Notice boards attached to this fencing reveal that today is a livestock market day, which is stating the obvious due to the fact that you're able to see for yourself the countless animals being bought, sold, and auctioned off within this area.
			</p>
			<p>
				As you're not a farmer, and therefore have no use for livestock, there's really very little for you to do here. Perhaps if you were to come back on a day other than a Wednesday or Saturday, then you'd be able to see what this area is used for when not acting as a livestock market...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
			<p>
				As it's past closing time, the stalls which line the market's central square are all being disassembled and packed away. Not wanting to trouble any of the stall operators, you decide to leave them to it and continue on your way through the Farmer's Market...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				The closer you get to the centre of the Farmer's Market, the more jovial and festive the surrounding shoppers seem to become. The cause of their enjoyment is soon made apparent, for as you arrive at this central square, you see that it resembles more of a festival than a normal market. Numerous colourful stalls have been set up along all four sides of this space, with each one offering a different kind of carnival game. Cheap plastic hats, balloons, and stickers are being handed out by a couple of officials, while the source of the market's background music can be seen here in the form of a four-man band.
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.Walking] around the area to survey the dozen or so games that are on offer, you come to the conclusion that there are only two which are of any real interest. One of these is staffed by [nizhoni.name], who's running a game of darts, while the other is a traditional form of strength tester that's being operated by [moreno.name]. If you wanted to have a go at playing either of these games, you could [pc.step] up and say hello...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Darts: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_DARTS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!nizhoni.isPlayerKnowsName())
		<p>
			After taking a moment to look around, you decide to approach the stall that's offering a game of darts. Leaning against one of the posts beneath its orange canvas awning, the operator of this stall takes the form of a grey-and-white furred greater raccoon-girl, who stands at about [nizhoni.heightValue] and looks to be slightly chubby in both body and face. Her huge, [nizhoni.cupSize]-cup breasts are covered up by an orange, sleeveless turtleneck sweater, while her huge ass and wide hips are contained by a black skirt.
		</p>
		<p>
			Noticing your approach, this raccoon-girl turns to face you, and as her hazel eyes gaze out at you from behind a pair of black, thick-rimmed glasses, you notice that she's sporting a significant amount of bronze jewellery, including hoop earrings, nose ring, bangle, anklet, gemstone ring, necklace, and even a pair of dragonfly-style bobby pins. Reaching up to brush an orange-dyed strand of her otherwise-black hair out of her face, she flashes you a big grin and calls out, [nizhoni.speech(Heya! I haven't seen you around here before. I'm Nizhoni. Are you here to play a game of darts?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Seeing no harm in giving this slovenly-spoken raccoon-girl your name, you introduce yourself to her and ask what a game of darts entails. Holding up three of the small missiles, Nizhoni grins and explains, [nizhoni.speech(It costs twenty-five flames to have a go, and you get these three darts to throw at the board behind me. If you hit the bullseye, you win a Faire ticket, and you can trade in any Faire tickets you've got for a prize. These prizes are subsidised by Elis's tourism board, so don't feel guilty if you want to claim a lot of them! So, you up for a go?)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			With Nizhoni holding out the darts in an encouraging manner, you wonder whether it's worth spending twenty-five flames on this game of darts...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			After taking a moment to look around, you decide to approach the stall that's offering a game of darts. Leaning against one of the posts beneath its orange canvas awning, the operator of this stall takes the form of a grey-and-white furred greater raccoon-girl, who stands at about [nizhoni.heightValue] and looks to be slightly chubby in both body and face. Her huge, [nizhoni.cupSize]-cup breasts are covered up by an orange, sleeveless turtleneck sweater, while her huge ass and wide hips are contained by a black skirt.
		</p>
		#IF(nizhoni.isVisiblyPregnant())
			#IF(!nizhoni.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
				<p>
					Noticing your approach, Nizhoni turns to face you, and you see her hazel eyes light up as she recognises you. Pointedly rubbing her hands down over her visibly-swollen belly, she calls out, [nizhoni.speech(Heya, [pc.name]! Look! Stuffing my pussy has consequences, you know!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Looking down at the raccoon-girl's pregnant belly, you ask her if she's sure that it was you who got her pregnant. Letting out a good-natured laugh, she replies, [nizhoni.speech(It's not like I've got people queuing up to fuck me, you know? You're the only one I've had sex with recently.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Feeling responsible, you ask Nizhoni if there's anything you can do to help her through her pregnancy, but with a wave of her hand she dismissively replies, [nizhoni.speech(Nah, I don't need anything. Now, what can I do for you today?)]
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Noticing your approach, Nizhoni turns to face you, and you see her hazel eyes light up as she recognises you. Pointedly rubbing her hands down over her visibly-swollen belly, she calls out, [nizhoni.speech(Heya, [pc.name]! Look; I'm still carrying our kids around!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Looking down at the raccoon-girl's pregnant belly, you ask her if there's anything you can do to help her through her pregnancy. Letting out a good-natured laugh, she waves her hand and dismissively replies, [nizhoni.speech(Nah, I don't need anything. Now, what can I do for you today?)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Noticing your approach, Nizhoni turns to face you, and you see her hazel eyes light up as she recognises you. Reaching up to brush an orange-dyed strand of her otherwise-black hair our of her face, she flashes you a big grin and calls out, [nizhoni.speech(Heya, [pc.name]! What can I do for you?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Returning the raccoon-girl's greeting, you ask her if her day is going well. Holding up three darts, Nizhoni grins and teases, [nizhoni.speech(Yeah, it's going fine, thanks, but it'd be even better if you'd hand over twenty-five flames to play a game! Remember, if you hit the bullseye, you win a Faire ticket, and you can trade in any Faire tickets you've got for a prize. These prizes are subsidised by Elis's tourism board, so don't feel guilty if you want to claim a lot of them! So, you up for a go?)] 
			</p>
			<p>
				With Nizhoni holding out the darts in an encouraging manner, you wonder whether it's worth spending twenty-five flames on this game of darts...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_DARTS_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not having anything else to do here, you say goodbye to Nizhoni and [pc.step] away from her stall. Moving off into the centre of the Farmer's Market once again, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_DARTS_PLAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to play a game of darts, you hand over the twenty five flames which Nizhoni has asked for, and in return you're given the three missiles. Stepping aside, the raccoon-girl reminds you of the rules, [nizhoni.speech(Ok, you get to throw these three darts, and you only need to hit the bullseye once to win. Good luck!)]
	</p>
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_darts_won))
		<p>
			#IF(pc.getAttributeValue(ATTRIBUTE_DAMAGE_RANGED_WEAPON)>=66)
				Thanks to your exceptional skill at using ranged weaponry, you proceed to hit the bullseye on your first throw. Gasping in impressed awe, Nizhoni watches as you show off by proceeding to hit the bullseye again with both the second and third darts. Happily clapping her hands, she exclaims, [nizhoni.speech(Wow! You made that look so easy! You're really good at this, [pc.name]. Let me get you your Faire ticket...)]
			#ELSEIF(pc.getAttributeValue(ATTRIBUTE_DAMAGE_RANGED_WEAPON)>=33)
				Although you miss with your first throw, thanks to your skill at using ranged weaponry you're able to hit the bullseye on your second attempt. Gasping in impressed awe, Nizhoni watches as you show off by proceeding to hit the bullseye again with your third dart. Happily clapping her hands, she exclaims, [nizhoni.speech(Wow! That was great! You're good at this, [pc.name]. Let me get you your Faire ticket...)]
			#ELSE
				Although you miss with both your first and second throws, you're thankfully able to hit the bullseye on your final attempt. Happily clapping her hands, Nizhoni exclaims, [nizhoni.speech(Hooray! Good throw, [pc.name]! Let me get you your Faire ticket...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			As the raccoon-girl bends down to fetch a ticket from under the counter, you wonder whether to accept that as your prize, or instead ask Nizhoni if she'll go on a walk with you instead...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(pc.getAttributeValue(ATTRIBUTE_DAMAGE_RANGED_WEAPON)>=66)
				Although you have exceptional skill at using ranged weaponry, you find yourself being distracted by a particularly loud crowd of shoppers standing right behind you, and so despite your abilities, you somehow manage to just barely miss the bullseye with all three of your darts.
			#ELSEIF(pc.getAttributeValue(ATTRIBUTE_DAMAGE_RANGED_WEAPON)>=33)
				Although you have some skill at using ranged weaponry, you find yourself being distracted by a particularly loud crowd of shoppers standing right behind you, and so despite your abilities, you end up missing the bullseye with all three of your darts.
			#ELSE
				This game turns out to be far harder than it looks, and not only miss the bullseye with all three of your darts, but even completely miss the board with your final throw.
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out a sad sigh, Nizhoni whines, [nizhoni.speech(Aww, bad luck, [pc.name]. If you've got another twenty five flames, you could try again...)]
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
			<i>You've spent [style.italicsBad([#flags.getSavedLong('market_game_flames_spent')] flames)] so far on trying to win...</i>
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_DARTS_PRIZE_CHOCOLATES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to trade in your Faire ticket for a prize, you hand the small slip of paper to Nizhoni and ask for a box of chocolates. Flashing you a happy smile, the chubby raccoon-girl turns to fetch your chosen prize from the shelves behind her, and as she hands it to you, she happily exclaims, [nizhoni.speech(Here you go, [pc.name]! Enjoy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking her for the prize, you safely put your chocolates away and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_DARTS_PRIZE_PERFUME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to trade in your Faire ticket for a prize, you hand the small slip of paper to Nizhoni and ask for a bottle of perfume. Flashing you a happy smile, the chubby raccoon-girl turns to fetch your chosen prize from the shelves behind her, and as she hands it to you, she happily exclaims, [nizhoni.speech(Here you go, [pc.name]! Enjoy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking her for the prize, you safely put your perfume away and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_DARTS_PRIZE_TEDDY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to trade in your Faire ticket for a prize, you hand the small slip of paper to Nizhoni and ask for a stuffed teddy bear toy. Flashing you a happy smile, the chubby raccoon-girl turns to fetch your chosen prize from the shelves behind her, and as she hands it to you, she happily exclaims, [nizhoni.speech(Here you go, [pc.name]! Enjoy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking her for the prize, you safely put your stuffed toy away and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_DARTS_WON"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking the Faire ticket from Nizhoni, you thank her and safely put it away. Flashing you a smile, the chubby raccoon-girl asks, [nizhoni.speech(Now, did you want to trade in your ticket for a prize, or are you going to hold on to it to spend at a different stall?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the smiling raccoon-girl waiting to hear what it is you'll do with the ticket, you wonder whether to trade it in for a prize right here, or hold on to it for use elsewhere...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_DARTS_LOST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to waste any more time and money on trying to win, you tell Nizhoni that you've had enough. After letting out a disappointed whine, the raccoon-girl winks at you and says, [nizhoni.speech(If you change your mind, just let me know. Oh, and remember, if you've got a Faire ticket from somewhere else, you can trade it in for a prize...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking a quick look over the prizes that are stacked up on the shelves behind Nizhoni, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NIZHONI_WALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Before Nizhoni can retrieve your Faire ticket, you stop her by asking if you're able to get a different type of prize. Straightening up, the chubby raccoon-girl gives you a questioning look and asks, [nizhoni.speech(Oh? What sort of thing did you have in mind?)]
	</p>
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_nizhoni_walked))
		<p>
			Giving her your most charming smile, you tell Nizhoni that you'd like to spend some time with her and get to know her a little better. Encouraged by the happy grin that quickly settles on her face, you proceed to ask her if she'd like to go for a walk with you around the market again. Letting out a little laugh, the raccoon-girl places her hands on her hips and replies, [nizhoni.speech(You really want to spend more time with me? Well, sure I guess!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Asking a neighbouring stall owner to watch her stall while she's gone, Nizhoni locks the coin box that's securely fastened beneath her counter, before stepping around and walking up beside you. Happily taking hold of your [pc.hand], she excitedly declares, [nizhoni.speech(Let's go to the same spot as last time! Come on, let's go!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Thinking to yourself that your plan has turned out perfectly, you keep hold of the raccoon-girl's hand as she walks along beside you past the many colourful stalls of the Farmer's Market. As you engage her in small talk, you once again start to detect a familiar, musky odour, and after a few minutes spent in her company, you again realise that this smell is coming from Nizhoni. Although this pungent, slightly-sweet aroma seems to be getting stronger and more noticeable by the minute, you don't find it to be an unpleasant one, and so you happily continue to [pc.walk] close beside Nizhoni as she leads you to your destination. 
		</p>
		<p>
			[nizhoni.speech(Here we are!)] the raccoon-girl suddenly declares, before stopping beside a rather plain and uninteresting market stall. By now knowing what to expect, you look over towards the opposite side of the path, where a couple of tall, bamboo screens are shielding most of what looks to be the market's rubbish dump. As Nizhoni leads you right up to the entrance between these screens, you see that there are at least two dozen large, metal wheelie bins, about half of which are absolutely full to the brim with cardboard packaging, empty cans, and all other sorts of waste. Turning to look at you with a clear flash of excitement in her hazel eyes, Nizhoni declares, [nizhoni.speech(You can find all sorts of cool stuff here! Come on, let's see if we can find something good together! Sometimes some of the stalls even throw out food that they weren't able to sell, so we could even get a bite to eat!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Knowing that she's absolutely dead serious about inviting you to go dumpster diving with her, you only have a moment in which to decide whether to go along with Nizhoni or tell her that you'd rather not be doing this. As you wonder what to say, the musky smell emanating from the raccoon-girl starts to get even stronger, and you realise that joining her in the tight spaces between the bins will undoubtedly expose you to an even higher concentration of her natural odour...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Giving her your most charming smile, you tell Nizhoni that you'd like to spend some time with her and get to know her a little better. Encouraged by the happy grin that quickly settles on her face, you proceed to ask her if she'd like to go for a walk with you around the market, and perhaps get a drink or something to eat together. Letting out a little laugh, the raccoon-girl places her hands on her hips and replies, [nizhoni.speech(You really want to spend time with me? Well, sure I guess!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Asking a neighbouring stall owner to watch her stall while she's gone, Nizhoni locks the coin box that's securely fastened beneath her counter, before stepping around and walking up beside you. Happily taking hold of your [pc.hand], she excitedly declares, [nizhoni.speech(I know a great spot over on the south side of the market. Come on, let's go!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Thinking to yourself that your plan has turned out perfectly, you keep hold of the raccoon-girl's hand as she walks along beside you past the many colourful stalls of the Farmer's Market. As you engage her in small talk, you start to notice a strange, musky odour, and after a few minutes spent in her company, you eventually realise that this smell is coming from Nizhoni. Although this pungent, slightly-sweet aroma seems to be getting stronger and more noticeable by the minute, you don't find it to be an unpleasant one, and so you happily continue to [pc.walk] close beside Nizhoni as she leads you to your destination. 
		</p>
		<p>
			[nizhoni.speech(Here we are!)] the raccoon-girl suddenly declares, before stopping beside a rather plain and uninteresting market stall. Seeing what it is you're looking at, Nizhoni laughs and pulls you away from this stall, saying, [nizhoni.speech(No, not there; over on this side!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking over to where Nizhoni is headed, you see that there are a couple of tall, bamboo screens shielding most of what looks to be the market's rubbish dump. As she leads you right up to the entrance between these screens, you see that there are at least two dozen large, metal wheelie bins, about half of which are absolutely full to the brim with cardboard packaging, empty cans, and all other sorts of waste. Turning to look at you with a clear flash of excitement in her hazel eyes, Nizhoni reveals, [nizhoni.speech(You can find all sorts of cool stuff here! Come on, let's see if we can find something good together! Sometimes some of the stalls even throw out food that they weren't able to sell, so we could even get a bite to eat!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Realising that she's absolutely dead serious about inviting you to go dumpster diving with her, you only have a moment in which to decide whether to go along with Nizhoni or tell her that you'd rather not be doing this. As you wonder what to say, the musky smell emanating from the raccoon-girl starts to get even stronger, and you realise that joining her in the tight spaces between the bins will undoubtedly expose you to an even higher concentration of her natural odour...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NIZHONI_WALK_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you really don't like the idea of rummaging through bins with Nizhoni, you also don't want to upset her by telling her exactly what you think of this kind of activity. Gently releasing her hand, you make up an excuse for having to suddenly leave, before wishing her luck with her exploration of the market's waste. Pouting at you for a moment, Nizhoni whines, [nizhoni.speech(Aww, it's not as fun when I do it alone... I guess I'll come back some other time... Bye, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not giving you any chance to change your mind, the raccoon-girl runs off in the direction of her stall, leaving you standing alone wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NIZHONI_BINS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to go with it, you tell Nizhoni to lead the way, and follow her into the screened-off area which contains the bins. Practically skipping with excitement, the slightly-chubby raccoon-girl heads straight over to the far side of the area, and with a confidence cleared gained from having done this countless times before, she bends down into one of the large metal bins and starts rummaging around in it. Straightening up for a moment, she turns back to look at you and say, [nizhoni.speech(Come on, [pc.name]! There's bound to be something good in here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she says, you [pc.step] up beside Nizhoni and join her in rummaging through the bin. As is to be expected in an area like this, you notice that there's a background smell of slightly rotten waste, which gets noticeably stronger as you stick your head down into the metal bin and join Nizhoni in rummaging through layers of cardboard, metal, and canvas waste. This odour is almost completely overpowered, however, by the raccoon-girl's natural, musky scent. As she moves around to your side, you find yourself being hit by wave after wave of her pungent, slightly-sweet smell, which far from being nauseating or unpleasant, seems to awaken some sort of primal desire within you, and you find yourself happily breathing in her natural musk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[nizhoni.speech(Hey! Someone threw out most of their burger!)] the raccoon-girl suddenly cries out, and you look over to see her take a big bite out of the burger she's just retrieved. After chewing for a moment and then swallowing, she laughs and says, [nizhoni.speech(Oh, yeah, now I see why they threw it away... I bet there's something better tasting in here somewhere...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Unfortunately for Nizhoni, neither of you find anything worth taking or eating in the rest of this bin. With her enthusiasm undeterred by this initial failure, the raccoon-girl leads you over to the next bin, and then the next, and before you know it you've spent a good fifteen minutes rummaging around through the market's rubbish dump. The whole time you've been searching, Nizhoni's natural, musky scent has been getting stronger and stronger, and as she bends down over the next bin, her skirt starts to ride up and you're hit by an intense wave of her heady odour.
	</p>
	<p>
		[nizhoni.speech(You can take a break if you want,)] she calls back over her shoulder. Deciding to do just that, you stop and [pc.step] back, before looking over at the raccoon-girl's large ass. Although you thought that it'd naturally ridden up as she leant in over the edge of the bin, you suddenly see Nizhoni reach back to pull her skirt up even more, and you realise that she's deliberately putting on a show for you. Looking down between her legs, you see that Nizhoni isn't wearing any underwear, and her dark-lipped pussy and similarly-dark-rimmed asshole are now fully exposed.
	</p>
	<p>
		[nizhoni.speech(Hey, [pc.name]... You can... You can do whatever you'd like, you know...)] Nizhoni hesitantly calls out, before spreading her legs a little wider and fully presenting you with her hot, wet pussy and asshole. Her musky odour is definitely coming from down here, for as she finishes fully exposing herself, you find your senses being completely overpowered by her strong, heady scent. Clearly wanting you to make a move on her, Nizhoni lifts her ass up and lets out a little moan, and although she pretends to continue rummaging through the bin, you can tell that she's far more interested in what you'll decide to do about her lewd presentation...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NIZHONI_BINS_IGNORE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to do anything lewd with Nizhoni, you ignore the raccoon-girl's display and wait for her to finish searching through the bin. A few minutes later, and she's done just that, and after standing back upright, she briefly pouts at you and pulls her skirt back down, before saying, [nizhoni.speech(I suppose I'd better be getting back to work now... This was fun, [pc.name], but we could have done so much more together...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she skips alongside you as the two of you exit the bins area, before turning and waving goodbye. Telling her that you'll see her again soon, you watch the raccoon-girl rush off in the direction of her stall, before setting off through the Farmer's Market and continuing on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NIZHONI_BINS_ORAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to resist Nizhoni's musky, dark-lipped pussy, you [pc.step] forwards and drop down behind her, before leaning in and giving her hot cunt a big, wet kiss. Squealing in delight, the chubby raccoon-girl pushes her hips back into your face, completely drowning you in her heady, feminine musk as she squeals, [nizhoni.speech(Oh, [pc.name]! ~Mmm!~ How naughty... Please, keep going...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she asks, you reach up and take hold of Nizhoni's thighs, before pushing her legs apart and burying your face in her smelly, hot cunt. Planting kiss after kiss on her [nizhoni.labia+], you dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start greedily eating her out. With her upper-half still bent down into the big metal bin, Nizhoni's cries echo around a little as she moans, [nizhoni.speech(~Ooh!~ Yes! You really like the taste of my pussy? ~Mmm!~ Please, don't stop!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite the fact that her cunt tastes just as musky and sour as it smells, you find yourself unable to pull away from it, and with the raccoon-girl continuing to moan and squeal into the bin, you passionately eat her out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NIZHONI_BINS_FUCK_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to resist Nizhoni's musky, dark-lipped pussy, you [pc.step] forwards and expose your [pc.cock+], before lining it up to her hot cunt and pressing your [pc.cockHead+] against her [nizhoni.labia+]. Squealing in delight, the chubby raccoon-girl looks back over her shoulder, and as you start to drown in her heady, feminine musk, she squeals, [nizhoni.speech(Oh, [pc.name]! ~Mmm!~ How naughty... Go on, stick it in...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she asks, you start to thrust forwards, sinking your [pc.cock+] into her smelly, hot cunt and causing her wet lips to spread out and squeeze down around your hard shaft. With her upper-half still bent down into the big metal bin, Nizhoni's cries echo around a little as she moans, [nizhoni.speech(~Ooh!~ Yes! You really liked the look of my pussy? ~Mmm!~ Please, don't stop! Give it to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite the fact that her smelly cunt is filling the air around you with the overpowering odour of her feminine musk, you find yourself unable to pull away, and with the raccoon-girl continuing to moan and squeal into the bin, you start desperately fucking her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NIZHONI_BINS_FUCK_ASS_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to resist Nizhoni's dark-rimmed asshole, you [pc.step] forwards and expose your [pc.cock+], before lining it up to her rear entrance and pressing your [pc.cockHead+] against it. Squealing in delight, the chubby raccoon-girl looks back over her shoulder, and as you start to drown in her heady, feminine musk, she squeals, [nizhoni.speech(Oh, [pc.name]! ~Mmm!~ How naughty... Go on, stick it in...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she asks, you start to thrust forwards, sinking your [pc.cock+] into her back door and causing her asshole to spread out and squeeze down around your hard shaft. With her upper-half still bent down into the big metal bin, Nizhoni's cries echo around a little as she moans, [nizhoni.speech(~Ooh!~ Yes! You really liked the look of my ass? ~Mmm!~ Please, don't stop! Give it to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite the fact that her smelly cunt is filling the air around you with the overpowering odour of her feminine musk, you find yourself unable to pull away, and with the raccoon-girl continuing to moan and squeal into the bin, you start desperately fucking her ass...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NIZHONI_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun, you give Nizhoni's big ass a playful squeeze, before [pc.stepping] back and telling her that you've finished.
		#IF(nizhoni.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			 Letting out a deeply-satisfied sigh in response, the raccoon-girl backs out of the bin and turns to face you, before pulling her skirt down to cover her dripping pussy and teasing, [nizhoni.speech(I don't normally have this much fun when I go dumpster diving...)]
		#ELSE
			 Letting out a frustrated sigh in response, the raccoon-girl backs out of the bin and turns to face you, before pulling her skirt down to cover her dripping pussy and complaining, [nizhoni.speech(That was fun and all, but I'm really not satisfied, you know...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Getting your things back in order, the two of you agree to leave the rest of the bins untouched, before heading over to the exit together. Telling her that you'll see her again soon, you say goodbye to Nizhoni and watch as the raccoon-girl skips off in the direction of her stall. Letting out a contented sigh, you take a moment to think about the sex you've just had, before setting off through the Farmer's Market and continuing on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Strength: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_STRENGTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although there are many stalls to be found here in the centre of the Farmer's Market, there's one which visually dominates the area. Its red canvas awning stands significantly higher than those beside it, which allows it to fully cover an old-fashioned strength tester. Consisting primarily of a tall, metal runner with a bell fixed to its top, this machine operates by having its base plate struck with a wooden hammer, which causes a small puck to be sent flying up the runner to hit the bell.
	</p>
	#IF(!moreno.isPlayerKnowsName())
		<p>
			Standing beside this machine is the stall's operator, who takes the form of a masculine, greater horse-boy. Wearing a tank top and a pair of sporty shorts, this black-haired horse-boy stands at a towering [moreno.heightValue], and you can't help but notice how his massive muscles bulge out with each of his movements. As you approach this huge horse-boy, his [moreno.eyeColour] eyes flick over towards you, and after flashing you a smile, he greets you in a deep, booming voice, [moreno.speech(Hello there, stranger! My name is Moreno! Do you think you have what it takes to beat my supreme strength tester and ring its bell?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Greeting Moreno and giving him your name in return, you [pc.step] up to the plate and ask the horse-boy what the rules are. Crossing his arms over his huge pectoral muscles, and flexing his gigantic biceps in the process, Moreno booms, [moreno.speech(The rules are simple! It costs twenty five flames to have a go at striking the base plate, and if you manage to get the puck to ring the bell, you win a Faire ticket. You can trade in these tickets right here for a prize, or spend them at one of the many other stalls found throughout the Farmer's Market. So, how about it? Do you think you have what it takes to win?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Standing beside this machine is the stall's masculine operator, Moreno. Wearing a tank top and a pair of sporty shorts, this black-haired horse-boy stands at a towering [moreno.heightValue], and you can't help but notice how his massive muscles bulge out with each of his movements. As you approach him, Moreno's [moreno.eyeColour] eyes flick over towards you, and after flashing you a smile, he greets you in a deep, booming voice, [moreno.speech(Hello again, [pc.name]! Are you here to try and beat my supreme strength tester?)]
		</p>
		#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(moreno))
			#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(moreno))
				<p>
					As you rub your [pc.hands] over your swollen belly and [pc.step] up to Moreno, he suddenly notices the fact that you're pregnant, and, realising that he must be the father, he exclaims, [moreno.speech(I got you pregnant?! Hey, is there anything I can do to help? I'm not one for shirking responsibility; just tell me if there's anything I can do.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Thanking Moreno for his offer, you tell him that you can handle things yourself, to which he replies, [moreno.speech(Well, ok. So, did you want to play, or are you here for a prize?)]
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					As you rub your [pc.hands] over your swollen belly and [pc.step] up to Moreno, he suddenly notices the fact that you're still pregnant, and asks, [moreno.speech(Are you sure that there's nothing I can do to help? Just tell me if there's anything I can do.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Thanking Moreno for his offer, you tell him that you can handle things yourself, to which he replies, [moreno.speech(Well, ok. So, did you want to play, or are you here for a prize?)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_STRENGTH_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you don't want to have a go at Moreno's strength tester, you say goodbye to the towering horse-boy, before turning around and taking your leave. As you [pc.step] away from his stall, you wonder where to go next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_STRENGTH_PRIZE_MEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to trade in one of your Faire tickets for a prize, you hand over the small slip of paper and ask Moreno for a 'meat hamper'. Taking the ticket and tearing it in half, the horse-boy turns towards the shelves behind him, before picking up a small basket and handing it over to you. With a handsome smile on his face, he says in a booming voice, [moreno.speech(Congratulations on your prize, [pc.name]. These are subsidised by Elis's tourism board, so please feel free to trade in as many tickets here as you'd like! Oh, and enjoy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Opening up the meat hamper, you find a couple of pieces of quality meat, along with a bottle of equine cider. Thanking the muscular horse-boy for the food and drink, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_STRENGTH_PRIZE_BAT_WOODEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to trade in one of your Faire tickets for a prize, you hand over the small slip of paper and ask Moreno for one of the wooden bats he's got on display. Taking the ticket and tearing it in half, the horse-boy turns towards the shelves behind him, before picking up one of the bats and handing it over to you. With a handsome smile on his face, he says in a booming voice, [moreno.speech(Congratulations on your prize, [pc.name]. These are subsidised by Elis's tourism board, so please feel free to trade in as many tickets here as you'd like! Oh, and enjoy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hefting the wooden bat in your [pc.hands], you take a couple of swings into mid-air, before safely putting the weapon away. Thanking the muscular horse-boy for the prize, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_STRENGTH_PRIZE_BAT_METAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to trade in one of your Faire tickets for a prize, you hand over the small slip of paper and ask Moreno for one of the metal bats he's got on display. Taking the ticket and tearing it in half, the horse-boy turns towards the shelves behind him, before picking up one of the bats and handing it over to you. With a handsome smile on his face, he says in a booming voice, [moreno.speech(Congratulations on your prize, [pc.name]. These are subsidised by Elis's tourism board, so please feel free to trade in as many tickets here as you'd like! Oh, and enjoy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hefting the metal bat in your [pc.hands], you take a couple of swings into mid-air, before safely putting the weapon away. Thanking the muscular horse-boy for the prize, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_STRENGTH_PLAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Handing over twenty five flames to Moreno, you tell him that you'd like to have a go at beating his strength tester. Putting the money safely away, the huge horse-boy picks up a large, wooden hammer from behind the machine, and as he presents it to you, he explains, [moreno.speech(Strike the plate right here, and if you hit it hard enough, the puck will go all the way up to ring the bell. If it rings, then you win a Faire ticket. Oh, and you only get one go at this, so make it count!)]
	</p>
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_strength_won))
		<p>
			Taking the hammer from Moreno, you [pc.step] up to the strength tester and take your stance, before swinging down and striking the plate with as much force as you can possibly muster.
			#IF(pc.getAttributeValue(ATTRIBUTE_MAJOR_PHYSIQUE)>=66)
				 Thanks to your incredible strength, the puck flies all of the way up its rail, and not only hits the bell at the top, but strikes it with such force that it's knocked completely off and crashes to the ground with a loud, metallic ring. Letting out a booming laugh, Moreno picks up the bell and declares, [moreno.speech(It's not often that that happens! Well done, [pc.name]; you've decisively won!)]
			#ELSEIF(pc.getAttributeValue(ATTRIBUTE_MAJOR_PHYSIQUE)>=33)
				 Thanks to your strength, the puck flies all of the way up its rail and collides with the bell with some force, causing a loud, metallic ring to sound out. Letting out a booming laugh, Moreno declares, [moreno.speech(Well done, [pc.name]; you've won!)]
			#ELSE
				 Although you're not the strongest, you manage to make the puck fly all of the way up its rail and collide with the bell, causing a metallic ring to sound out. Letting out a booming laugh, Moreno declares, [moreno.speech(Well done, [pc.name]; you've won!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_moreno_sex))
				Reaching into the pocket of his sport shorts, Moreno produces a Faire ticket and holds it out to you as he teases, [moreno.speech(I wish I had more time in which to have some fun with you today, [pc.name]... Come back and win tomorrow, and perhaps we can do some intimate 'training' together...)]
			#ELSEIF(pc.isFeminine())
				Reaching into the pocket of his sport shorts, Moreno fumbles about a little, making you to look down to see what's causing the trouble. As your gaze flicks down to his groin, you see that there's the unmistakable shape of a huge, flaccid horse cock pressing out beneath the fabric of his shorts. Seeing that you've noticed what he's packing, Moreno finally produces the Faire ticket from out of his pocket, and as he hands it to you, he grins and flirts, [moreno.speech(There's nothing sexier than watching a hot, strong [pc.race] showing off her strength... Say, how about you have another go at this game? I could watch you flexing your muscles all day...)]
			#ELSE
				Reaching into the pocket of his sport shorts, Moreno produces a Faire ticket and holds it out to you as he exclaims, [moreno.speech(Good job!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Taking the hammer from Moreno, you [pc.step] up to the strength tester and take your stance, before swinging down and striking the plate with as much force as you can possibly muster.
			#IF(pc.getAttributeValue(ATTRIBUTE_MAJOR_PHYSIQUE)>=66)
				 Despite the fact that you possess incredible strength, you find yourself being distracted by some particularly noisy people loitering around just behind you, and so you end up slightly missing the strength tester's plate. Despite this slip-up, you still manage to hit the machine with such force that the puck flies half way up its rail, but, much to your disappointment and frustration, it fails to hit the bell.
			#ELSEIF(pc.getAttributeValue(ATTRIBUTE_MAJOR_PHYSIQUE)>=33)
				 Despite the fact that you possess considerable strength, you find yourself being distracted by some particularly noisy people loitering around just behind you, and so you end up hitting the plate at an odd angle and only transferring a fraction of your strike's power into it. Despite this slip-up, you still manage to make the puck fly a half way up its rail, but, much to your disappointment and frustration, it fails to hit the bell.
			#ELSE
				 Despite the fact that you put all of your effort into it, your strike doesn't hit with nearly as much force as you'd like, and you watch in dismay as the puck flies only half way up its rail, before falling back down without even coming close to ringing the bell.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[moreno.speech(That's a shame,)] Moreno laments, before taking the wooden hammer from you and saying in his deep, booming voice, [moreno.speech(I'm sure you've got what it takes to win. Would you like to pay another twenty five flames for another go?)]
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
			<i>You've spent [style.italicsBad([#flags.getSavedLong('market_game_flames_spent')] flames)] so far on trying to win...</i>
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_STRENGTH_WON"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isFeminine() && !flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_moreno_sex))
			Ignoring Moreno's flirtatious remarks, you safely put your ticket away and take a [pc.step] away from the horny horse-boy. Seeing that you're not interested in flirting with him, Moreno lets out a disappointed grunt and reminds you, [moreno.speech(You can trade that ticket in for a prize here, or at any of the other stalls in the market which offer rewards. Or do you want to play again?)]
		#ELSE
			Safely putting your ticket away, you take a [pc.step] away from the huge horse-boy and wonder what to do next. Flashing you a friendly smile, Moreno reminds you, [moreno.speech(You can trade that ticket in for a prize here, or at any of the other stalls in the market which offer rewards. Or do you want to play again?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAME_STRENGTH_LOST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to waste any more money on trying to win, you take a [pc.step] back and wonder what to do next. Seeing that you don't want to play any more, Moreno flashes you a friendly smile and reminds you, [moreno.speech(If you've already got any tickets, you can trade them in for a prize here.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MORENO_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the look of what's in Moreno's pants, you flit back and tease him by saying that you were showing your strength off in order to get him excited. Looking down at the expanding bulge in his shorts, you tell him that you're pleased to see his cock appears to be nicely proportioned to his huge muscles and towering height.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your words cause Moreno to let out a horny grunt, and in an attempt to regain control of the conversation, he motions down to his groin and states, [moreno.speech(Well, I've shown you something of mine, so you should give me something in return. Tell me, [pc.name], what's your secret? How did you get to be so strong?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MORENO_FLIRT_STOP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling like things have gone too far, you playfully wink at Moreno and tell him that some things are best left as secrets, before moving away from him and making it clear that your flirting has coe to an end.
	</p>
	<p>
		[moreno.speech(You shouldn't tease people like that,)] Moreno grunts in frustration, but after letting out a deep sigh, he quickly calms down and asks, [moreno.speech(Anyway, do you want to trade your ticket in for a prize? Or maybe you'd like to play again?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MORENO_ORAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] right up in front of Moreno, you run your [pc.hand] down over his muscular abs, before stroking his rapidly-hardening cock and teasing, [pc.speech(My secret? Well, if you really want to know... I make sure to consume lots of extra protein on a regular basis. Oh, and I do so straight from the tap...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving Moreno's huge horse-cock a playful squeeze through his sport shorts, and making him let out a deep, horny grunt in response, you bite your lip and continue, [pc.speech(Speaking of which, I could really do with getting a big, hot load of protein right about now. Could you help me with that?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not needing to be asked twice, the horse-boy calls out for the neighbouring stall owner to watch over his business while he's gone, before pulling you along after him as he hurries around behind the back of his stall. Pulling down his shorts and underwear, he presents you with his massive, [moreno.cockLengthValue] horse-cock and [moreno.ballSize] balls. Leaning back against a stack of crates, he motions down towards his exposed genitalia and grunts, [moreno.speech(Come on then, you can get your protein right from the tap, just as you like it...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Happily dropping down in front of the muscular horse-boy, you lick your [pc.lips] as you gaze over his throbbing, [moreno.cockColour] cock and heavy, dangling pair of cum-filled balls. Leaning forwards, you give his flared head a quick kiss, before moving down and breathing in the musky, masculine scent of his slightly-sweaty balls. Letting out [pc.a_moan+], you dart out your [pc.tongue+] and give the underside of Moreno's heavy, thick shaft a long, loving lick, before opening wide and taking his cock into your mouth.
	</p>
	<p>
		[moreno.speech(~Mmm!~ You're good at this...)] Moreno moans, which encourages you push forwards and start taking his hot, throbbing shaft down your throat. A mixture of saliva and salty precum starts to drool from the corners of your mouth, and you begin eagerly bobbing your head up and down in time with the muscular horse-boy's grunts and groans...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MORENO_VAGINAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] right up in front of Moreno, you run your [pc.hand] down over his muscular abs, before stroking his rapidly-hardening cock and teasing, [pc.speech(My secret? Well, if you really want to know... I make sure to do a thorough, intimate workout with a partner or two every day.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving Moreno's huge horse-cock a playful squeeze through his sport shorts, and making him let out a deep, horny grunt in response, you bite your lip and continue, [pc.speech(You know, I haven't done my exercise yet today... Do you think that you could help me with that?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not needing to be asked twice, the horse-boy calls out for the neighbouring stall owner to watch over his business while he's gone, before pulling you along after him as he hurries around behind the back of his stall. Pulling down his shorts and underwear, he presents you with his massive, [moreno.cockLengthValue] horse-cock and [moreno.ballSize] balls. Letting out a happy [pc.moan] as you see what it is you've got to work with, you tell Moreno to lie down on his back so that you can use him for your exercise. Grabbing a heavy sheet of canvas from out of a nearby crate, the horse-boy lays it down on the ground, before lying back on it and grunting, [moreno.speech(Come on then, show me how you ride cock...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Exposing your [pc.pussy+], you [pc.step] forwards and straddle Moreno, before lowering yourself down and teasing your [pc.labia+] back and forth over the flared head of his huge horse-cock. Sliding back, you look down at the precum that's started to ooze from the horse-boy's throbbing, [moreno.cockColour] cock, and after commenting on the size of his heavy pair of cum-filled balls, you reposition yourself such that your [pc.pussy+] is pressing lightly down against the tip of his hard shaft. Unable to hold back and longer, you let out [pc.a_moan+] and slowly drop down, causing your [pc.labia+] to spread out around Moreno's thick, hard cock as you take it deep inside of your [pc.pussy+].
	</p>
	<p>
		[moreno.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes, that's it!)] Moreno moans, which encourages you drop fully down and take his hot, throbbing shaft as deep into your hungry cunt as possible. After spending a moment to enjoy the feeling of the huge, hard shaft inside of you, you begin lifting yourself up and down in time with the muscular horse-boy's grunts and groans, forcing his hot dick in and out of your [pc.pussy+] as you show him how you ride cock...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MORENO_ANAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] right up in front of Moreno, you run your [pc.hand] down over his muscular abs, before stroking his rapidly-hardening cock and teasing, [pc.speech(My secret? Well, if you really want to know... I make sure to do a thorough, intimate workout with a partner or two every day.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving Moreno's huge horse-cock a playful squeeze through his sport shorts, and making him let out a deep, horny grunt in response, you bite your lip and continue, [pc.speech(You know, I haven't done my anal exercises yet today... Do you think that you could help me with that?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not needing to be asked twice, the horse-boy calls out for the neighbouring stall owner to watch over his business while he's gone, before pulling you along after him as he hurries around behind the back of his stall. Pulling down his shorts and underwear, he presents you with his massive, [moreno.cockLengthValue] horse-cock and [moreno.ballSize] balls. Letting out a happy [pc.moan] as you see what it is you've got to work with, you tell Moreno to lie down on his back so that you can use him for your exercise. Grabbing a heavy sheet of canvas from out of a nearby crate, the horse-boy lays it down on the ground, before lying back on it and grunting, [moreno.speech(Come on then, show me how you ride cock...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Exposing your [pc.asshole+], you [pc.step] forwards and straddle Moreno, before lowering yourself down and teasing your ass back and forth over the flared head of his huge horse-cock. Sliding back, you look down at the precum that's started to ooze from the horse-boy's throbbing, [moreno.cockColour] cock, and after commenting on the size of his heavy pair of cum-filled balls, you reposition yourself such that your [pc.asshole+] is pressing lightly down against the tip of his hard shaft. Unable to hold back and longer, you let out [pc.a_moan+] and slowly drop down, causing your [pc.asshole+] to spread out around Moreno's thick, hard cock as you take it deep inside of your ass.
	</p>
	<p>
		[moreno.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes, that's it!)] Moreno moans, which encourages you drop fully down and take his hot, throbbing shaft as deep into your hungry butt as possible. After spending a moment to enjoy the feeling of the huge, hard shaft inside of you, you begin lifting yourself up and down in time with the muscular horse-boy's grunts and groans, forcing his hot dick in and out of your [pc.asshole+] as you show him how you ride cock...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MORENO_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun, you give Moreno a playful kiss, before [pc.stepping] back and telling him that you've finished.
		#IF(moreno.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			 Letting out a deeply-satisfied groan in response, the horse-boy pulls his shorts up and grunts, [moreno.speech(That was great... Thanks for the fun, [pc.name].)]
		#ELSE
			 Letting out a frustrated groan in response, the horse-boy pulls his shorts up and grunts, [moreno.speech(That really wasn't enough to satisfy me... Damn it...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Getting your things back in order, the two of you prepare to head back out from behind the rear of Moreno's stall and return to the public centre of the Farmer's Market...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MORENO_AFTER_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leading the way, Moreno steps back out from behind the canvas that was shielding the two of you from the market's shoppers. Following in the muscular horse-boy's footsteps, you find yourself once again standing in front of his strength tester.
	</p>
	<p>
		[moreno.speech(I'll see you around, [pc.name],)] Moreno booms, before flashing you a grin and saying, [moreno.speech(I won't have time for more of that today, but come back tomorrow and win again, and we could have some more fun...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling Moreno that you might just do that, you say goodbye and [pc.step] away from his stall, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Clothing -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=19)
		<p>
			As it's well past closing time, all of the stalls in the Farmer's Market have been packed up and taken away. As a result, there's nothing for you to do here except head back into Elis...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(fae.isPlayerKnowsName())
			#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
				<p>
					As it's past closing time, you see that Fae and Silvia are busily packing their stall away. Not wanting to trouble them, you decide to leave them to it and head back into the Farmer's Market...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				#IF(fae.isVisiblyPregnant())
					<p>
						#IF(!fae.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
							You once again find yourself approaching the clothing stall, 'Rainbow's End'. Fae is the first to spot you as you draw near, and as you come to a halt in front of the counter, she points down to her swollen belly and declares, [fae.speech(Look, [pc.name], you got me knocked up!)]
						#ELSE
							You once again find yourself approaching the clothing stall, 'Rainbow's End'. Fae is the first to spot you as you draw near, and as you come to a halt in front of the counter, she points down at her rounded belly and declares, [fae.speech(Look, [pc.name], I'm still pregnant with our kids!)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ENDIF
				#IF(silvia.isVisiblyPregnant())
					<p>
						#IF(fae.isVisiblyPregnant())
							Hearing her sister greet you, Silvia looks over at you and flashes you a big grin, before pointing down at her own pregnant bump and teasing,
						#ELSE
							You once again find yourself approaching the clothing stall, 'Rainbow's End'. Silvia is the first to spot you as you draw near, and as you come to a halt in front of the counter, she runs her hands over her pregnant bump and teases,
						#ENDIF
						#IF(!silvia.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
							 [silvia.speech(Look what you did, you naughty [pc.girl]... These are your kids in here...)]
						#ELSE
							 [silvia.speech(I'm still carrying our kids around...)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ENDIF
				#IF(fae.isVisiblyPregnant())
					<p>
						#IF(silvia.isVisiblyPregnant())
							The two pregnant sisters step up beside one another, and with their swollen bellies gently touching, Fae lets out a little laugh and asks, [fae.speech(So then, [pc.name], are you here to buy something?)]
						#ELSE
							Hearing her sister greet you, Silvia looks over at you and flashes you a big grin. Seeing her sister's reaction, Fae lets out a little laugh, before asking, [fae.speech(So then, [pc.name], are you here to buy something?)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ELSEIF(silvia.isVisiblyPregnant())
					<p>
						Hearing her sister greet you, Fae looks over at you and flashes you a big grin, before asking, [fae.speech(So then, [pc.name], are you here to buy something?)]
					</p>
				#ELSE
					<p>
						You once again find yourself approaching the clothing stall, 'Rainbow's End'. The foxtauress sisters, Fae and Silvia, are standing behind the counter, and as they see you approach Fae waves you over and calls out, [fae.speech([pc.Name]! Are you here to buy something?)]
					</p>
				#ENDIF
				#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(fae))
					<p>
						#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(fae))
							At that moment, the two sisters suddenly notice that you're sporting a swollen, pregnant belly. Telling Fae that she's the one who knocked you up, you smile as the foxtauress teases, [fae.speech(It's not my fault; your pussy was just so good, I didn't want to pull out! Hey, are you wanting to buy some clothing for our kids?)]
						#ELSE
							At that moment, the two sisters look down at your swollen, pregnant belly. Knowing that she's the one who knocked you up, Fae smirks and teases, [fae.speech(Still carrying our kids around, huh? Hey, are you wanting to buy some clothing for them?)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ELSEIF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(silvia))
					<p>
						#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(silvia))
							At that moment, the two sisters suddenly notice that you're sporting a swollen, pregnant belly. Telling Silvia that she's the one who knocked you up, you smile as the foxtauress teases, [silvia.speech(It's not my fault; your pussy was just so good, I didn't want to pull out!)]
						#ELSE
							At that moment, the two sisters look down at your swollen, pregnant belly. Knowing that she's the one who knocked you up, Silvia smirks and teases, [silvia.speech(Still carrying our kids around, huh?)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
					<p>
						Sensing that there's an opportunity to get some business from you, Fae asks, [fae.speech(Hey, are you wanting to buy some clothing for your kids?)]
					</p>
				#ENDIF
				<p>
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_fae_passionate))
						[silvia.speech(Or are you here to try and win another kiss?)]
					#ELSE
						[silvia.speech(Or are you here to try and win a kiss?)]
					#ENDIF
					 Silvia adds, before shyly smiling at you and seductively biting her lip.
				</p>
				<p>
					[fae.speech(That's right, remember that you get a kiss from each of us if you roll a six on my dice,)] Fae says, before reminding you, [fae.speech(Remember that it costs one 'Faire ticket' for a roll, and you win a prize on a four, five, or six. So, are you going to buy anything, or do you have a ticket to trade in with us?)] 
				</p>
				<p>
					Happily smiling at you, the foxtauress sisters look at you with their blue and green eyes and wait to hear what it is you want...
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
				<p>
					As it's past closing time, you see a pair of foxtauresses are busily packing their stall away in this area. Not wanting to trouble them, you decide to leave them to it and head back into the Farmer's Market...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Although there are many stalls throughout the Farmer's Market which offer clothing for sale, the one before you is by far the largest and most colourful. Consisting of a long counter covered by a rainbow-coloured, canvas awning, the stall before you is packed full of clothing of all sorts and colours. Looking up, you see that the wooden sign that's attached to the canvas awning displays this stall's name as 'Rainbow's End'. 
				</p>
				<p>
					Looking over the counter, you see that the stall's owners are a pair of orange-furred greater foxtauresses, who each look to be in their early thirties. While both of them stand at [fae.heightValue] and have remarkably similar facial appearances, one of them has bright blue eyes, while the other's are a mossy shade of green.
				</p>
				<p>
					The green-eyed foxtauress has a head of long, dark brown hair, that's been highlighted with streaks of red dye and tied back into a pony tail by means of a red-and-black scrunchie. She's wearing a black leather jacket, which is unzipped to reveal a dark red crop top, the fabric of which is tightly hugging her [fae.cupSize]-cup breasts. Aside from those three items of clothing, she's wearing nothing else except a significant amount of gold jewellery. Rings in her ears and nose, as well as a gemstone barbell in her navel, are joined by a necklace, a wrist bangle, and an anklet around one of her paws, all in gold. There are even the unmistakable bumps of a pair of nipple barbells pressing out from under her tight crop top.
				</p>
				<p>
					The blue-eyed foxtauress has hair of a similar length and dark brown shade as her companion, although hers is woven into a braid and dyed with streaks of pink instead of red. She's wearing the same kind of stylish leather jacket as the green-eyed foxtauress, although hers is brown, and instead of a red crop top she's wearing an equally tight-fitting white tube top. The fabric of this top is similarly stretched out by a pair of nipple piercings, although instead of barbells, hers look to be rings. She's wearing a similar amount and style of jewellery as her companion, although instead of gold hers is all silver.
				</p>
				<p>
					As they see you stop and look at their stall, these foxtauresses exchange a cheeky glance and smirk with one another. Before you can react, they quickly turn around on the spot and flick their huge, fluffy tails aside, shamelessly flashing you their animalistic fox-pussies and assholes. Even without any kind of stimulation, each of their cunts looks to be wet and begging to be fucked. Continuing to look down, you see that these foxtauresses both have a complete set of male genitalia in addition to their female sexes, and from the considerable size of their furry sheaths, you can tell that their cocks must be quite large when erect.
				</p>
				<p>
					Turning her head back to smile at you, the green-eyed foxtauress winks and teases, [fae.speech(See anything you like, hun? I haven't seen you around before, and my sister and I like to give first timers a bit of a treat... So come on, what do we call you?)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seeing no reason not to give these exhibitionists your name, you respond to the green-eyed foxtauress and ask her for her name in return. Having had their fun, the two of them drop their tails back down, before turning to face you once again. Clearly being the more confident of the two, the green-eyed foxtauress is again the one to speak, and reveals, [fae.speech(I'm Fae, and this here's my sister Silvia.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(Hi,)] Silvia says, before flashing you a shy smile and batting her eyelids at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(So, you're here to buy some clothing, right?)] Fae asks, [fae.speech(We've got a special deal thanks to Elis's tourism board; you buy any item for over five hundred flames, and we give you one 'Faire ticket'! You can trade a ticket in for a roll of a dice, and depending on what you roll, you get a special reward. Better than any old normal clothing shop, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Curious to know more about these 'special rewards', you ask Fae what you could potentially win from a roll of her dice. Flashing you a smirk, she explains, [fae.speech(You roll a one, two, or three, and you get nothing, I'm afraid. Roll a four and you get a pair of socks, roll a five and you get a cap, and roll a six...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(And you get to kiss us!)] Silvia excitedly interjects, before falling silent and expectedly looking over at her sister.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(That's right, you get a kiss from each of us if you roll a six. You can instead choose to have a ring as your prize, but nobody ever chooses that...)] Fae says, before finishing by revealing, [fae.speech(The tourism board compensates us for all prizes given out, so we really don't mind giving away as many socks, caps, or rings as you can win. Just remember that it costs one 'Faire ticket' for a roll! So, are you going to buy anything, or do you already have any tickets from elsewhere to trade in with us?)] 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING_TRANSACTION_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you [pc.step] forwards and take a look at what Fae and Silvia have for sale, the green-eyed foxtauress flashes you a grin and asks, [fae.speech(So, what's caught your fancy? Remember, if you spend over five hundred flames, on an item, you get a 'Faire ticket'!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING_TRANSACTION_NO_TICKET"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your flames in exchange for the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0], Fae pouts and says, [fae.speech(Sorry, [pc.name], but you need to spend at least five hundred flames in order to get a Faire ticket... Why don't you try buying something more expensive?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING_TRANSACTION_TICKET"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your flames in exchange for the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0], Fae flashes you a happy smile and gives you a small paper Faire ticket, before exclaiming, [fae.speech(Thanks for shopping with us, [pc.name]! You can trade in your ticket for a roll of the dice at any time to try and win a prize!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING_DICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to take a shot at winning a prize, you place a Faire ticket on the counter and tell Fae that you'd like to have a roll of her dice. The foxtauress's green eyes light up as she hears this, and after taking your ticket and tearing it in half, she hands you her dice and teases, [fae.speech(You're hoping to roll a six, right? Silvia and I could do with a kiss right now...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(That's right,)] Silvia happily nods, before fixing her blue eyes down on the dice in your hand.
	</p>
	#IF(flags.getSavedLong('fae_dice_roll')<4)
		<p>
			Seeing no reason to wait, you give the dice a good shake and roll it onto the counter. The three of you watch as it tumbles across the wooden surface, before bumping off a piece of clothing and clattering to a stop. Looking down at it, you see that it's landed on a [style.italicsMinorBad([style.intFormat([#flags.getSavedLong('fae_dice_roll')])])], meaning that you unfortunately [style.colourMinorBad(win nothing)].
		</p>
		<p>
			Picking up her dice, Fae consoles you on your loss, [fae.speech(Aww, that's a shame... Better luck next time, [pc.name]! Why don't you buy some expensive clothing to get another ticket?)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('fae_dice_roll')==4)
		<p>
			Seeing no reason to wait, you give the dice a good shake and roll it onto the counter. The three of you watch as it tumbles across the wooden surface, before clattering to a sudden stop. Looking down at it, you see that it's landed on a [style.italicsMinorGood(four)], meaning you [style.colourMinorGood(win a pair of socks)].
		</p>
		<p>
			Picking up her dice, Fae flashes you a big smile and exclaims, [fae.speech(Congratulations, [pc.name]!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[silvia.speech(Here you go, [pc.name]. These are the socks that the tourism board supplies us with as a prize,)] Silvia says as she hands you a pair of lime-green socks.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(!pc.hasLegs())
				As you don't have any feet on which to wear them, you're not exactly sure what to do with this pair of socks, but nevertheless take them from Silvia and thank her for the prize.
			#ELSE
				You're not entirely convinced that you'll end up wearing these offensively-coloured socks, but nevertheless take them from Silvia and thank her for the prize.
			#ENDIF
			 Leaning forwards and flashing you a cheeky smile, Fae asks, [fae.speech(Hey, why don't you buy some expensive clothing to get another ticket? I'm sure you'd like to keep rolling until you win a kiss from the two of us, right?)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('fae_dice_roll')==5)
		<p>
			Seeing no reason to wait, you give the dice a good shake and roll it onto the counter. The three of you watch as it tumbles across the wooden surface, before clattering to a stop just before it was about to fall off the edge. Looking down at it, you see that it's landed on a [style.italicsGood(five)], meaning you [style.colourGood(win a cap)].
		</p>
		<p>
			Picking up her dice, Fae flashes you a big smile and exclaims, [fae.speech(Congratulations, [pc.name]!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[silvia.speech(Here you go, [pc.name]. This is one of the caps that the tourism board supplies us with as a prize,)] Silvia says as she hands you a lime-green cap.
		</p>
		<p>
			You're not entirely convinced that you'll end up wearing this offensively-coloured piece of headgear, but nevertheless take it from Silvia and thank her for the prize. Leaning forwards and flashing you a cheeky smile, Fae asks, [fae.speech(Hey, why don't you buy some expensive clothing to get another ticket? I'm sure you'd like to keep rolling until you win a kiss from the two of us, right?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Seeing no reason to wait, you give the dice a good shake and roll it onto the counter. The three of you watch as it tumbles across the wooden surface, before eventually clattering to a halt. Looking down at it, you see that it's landed on a [style.italicsExcellent(six)], meaning you've [style.colourExcellent(won either a ring or a kiss from the two foxtauresses)].
		</p>
		<p>
			Picking up her dice, Fae flashes you a big smile and exclaims, [fae.speech(Congratulations, [pc.name]! Now, do you want some lame old silver ring as your prize...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[silvia.speech(Or would you rather get a kiss from each of us?)] Silvia finishes.
		</p>
		<p>
			With both of the foxtauresses hungrily eyeing you up, you wonder whether to ask for the silver ring or the kiss as your prize...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING_DICE_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking a [pc.step] back from the counter, you wonder whether to do as Fae suggests and buy some clothing in order to get another Faire ticket, or instead head off and forget about trying to win
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('fae_dice_roll')<4)
			 a prize...
		#ELSE
			 another prize...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING_DICE_END_RING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not being interested in getting a kiss from the two foxtauresses, you tell them that you'd like the ring as your prize. As they hear you say this, both Fae and Silvia pout at you and let out a disappointed whine. Placing her hands on her hips, Fae sighs, [fae.speech(I can't believe that you'd rather have some old ring than getting to kiss us...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(Here you go, [pc.name]...)] Silvia whines as she hands you a silver ring. [silvia.speech(These are what the tourism board gives us to hand out as a prize.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Quick to change her attitude, Far leans forwards and flashes you a smile, before asking, [fae.speech(Hey, why don't you buy some expensive clothing to get another ticket? I'm sure you're regretting not choosing a kiss, right? You should keep on rolling until you get a six again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking a [pc.step] back from the counter, you wonder whether to do as Fae suggests and buy some clothing in order to get another Faire ticket, or instead head off and forget about trying to win another prize...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to miss this opportunity, you tell the foxtauresses that you want to kiss them. Their faces light up as they hear you say this, and Fae and Siliva quickly step forwards and lean over the counter in anticipation of what's about to happen. Batting her eyelids, Fae teases, [fae.speech(Come on, [pc.name]. I'll be your first...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving forwards, you lean in towards Fae, and as you bring your mouth towards hers, she reaches forwards and takes hold of your head, before pulling you in and planting a big, wet kiss on your [pc.lips+]. The scent of delicate perfume surrounds you as the horny foxtauress continues to press her lips against yours, and she lets out a muffled, happy little moan as she kisses you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(Come on, Fae, it's my turn now!)] Silvia impatiently declares, before playfully pushing her sister aside. Fae's lips pull away from yours with a loud, wet smacking noise, and before you can do or say anything, Silvia leans forwards and presses her own lips against your mouth. Happily leaning in to you, the blue-eyed foxtauress continues where her sister left off, and plants a series of big, wet kisses on your [pc.lips].
	</p>
	<p>
		Just as you're really starting to enjoy the experience, Silvia pulls back and sighs, [silvia.speech(You're a good kisser, [pc.name]...)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		With more than a hint of jealousy in her voice, Fae declares, [fae.speech(Well, <i>my</i> kiss was better than yours, Silvia.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the two foxtauresses continuing to lean forwards over the counter, and with their eyes continuing to hungrily roam over your body, you wonder whether to take things further or to end things here...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING_KISS_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun, you [pc.step] back from the counter and thank Fae and Silvia for the prize. Standing upright once again, Fae flashes you a cheeky smile and asks, [fae.speech(Hey, why don't you buy some expensive clothing to get another ticket? I'm sure you'd like to win another kiss from the two of us, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the two foxtauresses waiting to hear what your response will be, you wonder whether to do as Fae suggests and buy some clothing in order to get another Faire ticket, or instead head off and forget about trying to win another kiss...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLOTHING_KISS_END_PASSION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not yet satisfied, you lean back over towards Fae and once again press your [pc.lips+] against her mouth, before taking hold of her head and starting to passionately kiss her. Her bushy fox-tail excitedly twists around behind her, and with a happy, muffled moan, she desperately returns your kiss. Parting her lips, the foxtauress thrusts her tongue into your mouth and leans even further forwards over her counter in her desperation to make out with you. As her tongue slides over yours, you feel that she's got a barbell piercing through it, and as you experimentally run your tongue over it, she lets out a muffled giggle.
	</p>
	<p>
		After watching your lewd display for a couple of minutes, Silvia lets out a loud, frustrated sigh, before rudely butting in and pushing her sister away. Before either of you can react, the blue-eyed foxtauress impatiently grabs hold of your head and desperately presses her mouth against yours. Happy to give Silvia a turn, you spend another few minutes making out with her, during which time you discover that she too has a barbell piercing through her tongue. Eventually, at the incessant prompting of her sister, Silvia reluctantly pulls back, bringing an end to your fun.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(We don't get customers like you very often...)] Fae whines, before flashing Siliva a questioning glance. After her sister has given her an approving nod, the green-eyed foxtauress looks back at you and says, [fae.speech(The two of us go to 'The Centaur's Sword' every evening after work. If you want more than just a kiss, then you can find us in there between seven and ten...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(I hope we'll see you in there soon,)] Silvia says, before letting out a playful giggle and asking, [silvia.speech(Did you want to buy anything, [pc.name]? Or if you've got another ticket, then maybe you could roll to earn another kiss...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the two foxtauresses waiting to hear what your response will be, you wonder whether to do as Silvia suggests, or instead say goodbye and take your leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- Alcoholic drinks -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_ALCOHOL"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=19)
		<p>
			As it's well past closing time, all of the stalls in the Farmer's Market have been packed up and taken away. As a result, there's nothing for you to do here except head back into Elis...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Consisting of a long table and an orange-and-white canvas awning, the stall in front of you bears a large wooden sign that reads 'The Beer Brigade'. As to be expected, this business sells alcoholic beverages, and you're able to see bottles of beer, cider, and perry within the portable arcane refrigeration units that are lined up at the rear of the stall.
		</p>
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
			<p>
				As it's past closing time, the trio of boisterous, broad-shouldered dog-boys who work here are busily packing away their stall. If you wanted to buy anything from them, you'll have to return here tomorrow...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				A trio of boisterous, broad-shouldered bog-boys are manning the counter, and as you watch, they call out to the passing crowds, [style.speechMasculine(Cold beers for sale!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[style.speechMasculineStrong(Get your perry and cider here!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[style.speechMasculine(All locally brewed!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Pausing for a moment, you wonder whether to [pc.step] up to the stall and buy a drink from these dog-boys... 
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_ALCOHOL_BEER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a drink of beer, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a bottle of 'Canine Crush' from one of the dog-boys behind the counter. After you've handed over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, the dog-boy pops off the cap and hands you the bottle of beer that you've asked for.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_ALCOHOL_CIDER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a drink of cider, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a bottle of 'Equine Cider' from one of the dog-boys behind the counter. After you've handed over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, the dog-boy pops off the cap and hands you the bottle of cider that you've asked for.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_ALCOHOL_PERRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a drink of perry, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a bottle of 'Black Stripes Perry' from one of the dog-boys behind the counter. After you've handed over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, the dog-boy pops off the cap and hands you the bottle of perry that you've asked for.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_ALCOHOL_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] away from the counter, you find a quiet spot in which to relax and drink your alcoholic beverage. After five minutes of watching the crowds of shoppers amble past, you've emptied the entire bottle, and after throwing it away in a nearby recycling bin, you wonder what to do next.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDayMinutes() + 5 >= 18 * 60)
			As the time has passed six while you were busy drinking, 'The Beer Brigade' stall is now closed for the day, and you look across to see the three dog-boys packing up. As all of the other stalls in the Farmer's Market will similarly be closed, there's not much for you to do here except head off back into Elis...
		#ELSE
			With 'The Beer Brigade' stall still open for business, you hear the three dog-boys behind its counter continuing to call out to passersby. You could always buy another drink if you wanted to, or instead head off into the market once again...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Soft drinks -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_SOFT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=19)
		<p>
			As it's well past closing time, all of the stalls in the Farmer's Market have been packed up and taken away. As a result, there's nothing for you to do here except head back into Elis...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			You find yourself standing before a particularly long stall, which has a yellow-and-white canvas awning and a white cloth decorated with colourful flowers draped over its counter. A large canvas sign attached to the awning displays the words 'Freshly Squeezed' beside embroidered images of oranges and carrots. Behind the counter, there are several arcane refrigeration units filled with all sorts of non-alcoholic beverages.
		</p>
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
			<p>
				As it's past closing time, the family of rabbit-morphs who operate the business 'Freshly Squeezed' are busily packing away their stall. If you wanted to buy anything from them, you'll have to return here tomorrow...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				A family of rabbit-morphs are running this stall, and alongside two older-looking individuals, who you assume to be the mother and father, you count no less than eight rabbit-girls and boys. Every last one of them looks to be having fun running their business, which gives this stall a wholesome, friendly atmosphere.
			</p>
			<p>
				Pausing for a moment, you wonder whether to [pc.step] up to the stall and join one of the stall's many customers in buying a drink from these rabbit-morphs... 
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_SOFT_WATER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a drink, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a bottle of 'Vanilla Water' from one of the rabbit-morphs behind the counter. After you've handed over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, the happy rabbit-morph hands you the bottle of water that you've asked for.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_SOFT_ORANGE_JUICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a drink, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a can of 'Fizzy Orange Juice' from one of the rabbit-morphs behind the counter. After you've handed over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, the happy rabbit-morph hands you the can of carbonated orange juice that you've asked for.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_SOFT_BERRY_SODA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a drink, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a can of 'Berry Soda' from one of the rabbit-morphs behind the counter. After you've handed over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, the happy rabbit-morph hands you the can of berry soda that you've asked for.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_SOFT_COLA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a drink, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a bottle of 'Porcine Pop' from one of the rabbit-morphs behind the counter. After you've handed over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, the happy rabbit-morph hands you the bottle of cola that you've asked for.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_SOFT_CARROT_JUICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a drink, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a bottle of 'Bunny Juice' from one of the rabbit-morphs behind the counter. After you've handed over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, the happy rabbit-morph hands you the bottle of carrot juice that you've asked for.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DRINKS_SOFT_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] away from the counter, you find a quiet spot in which to relax and enjoy your drink. After five minutes of watching the crowds of shoppers amble past, you've finished off your refreshing beverage, and after throwing it away in a nearby recycling bin, you wonder what to do next.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDayMinutes() + 5 >= 18 * 60)
			As the time has passed six while you were busy drinking, the 'Freshly Squeezed' stall is now closed for the day, and you look across to see the family of rabbit-morphs packing up. As all of the other stalls in the Farmer's Market will similarly be closed, there's not much for you to do here except head off back into Elis...
		#ELSE
			With the 'Freshly Squeezed' stall still open for business, you see the family of rabbit-morphs behind its counter continuing to serve the many customers which are drawn to it. You could always buy another drink if you wanted to, or instead head off into the market once again...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Exit -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing at one of the four entrances to the Farmer's Market. A large, touristy-looking sign positioned near to this entrance reveals that many stalls throughout the Farmer's Market have signed up to be part of a promotional activity designed and run by Elis's Tourism Board. Apparently, you can either earn or spend 'Faire tickets' at the stalls which are taking part, which will allow you to receive special rewards or engage in unique activities.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=19)
			ATurning your attention away from this sign, you see that the market has closed for the day, and as such all of the stalls have been packed up and taken away, leaving the square before you all but completely deserted. As all of the stalls are gone, there's really very little for you to do here except head back out into the rest of Elis...
		#ELSEIF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
			Turning your attention away from this sign, you see that the market has closed for the day, and as such all of the stalls are in the process of being packed up and taken away. As all of the stalls are soon to be gone, there's really very little for you to do here except head back out into the rest of Elis...
		#ELSE
			Turning your attention away from this sign and towards the market itself, you see that rows of colourful canvas stalls are arrayed before you, while shoppers of all races wander between them to either browse or purchase the many goods on offer. If you wanted to, you could proceed into the market and take a look around, or instead head back out into the rest of Elis...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having concluded your business, you exit the Farmer's Market and head back out into Elis...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Hot meals -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_MEALS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=19)
		<p>
			As it's well past closing time, all of the stalls in the Farmer's Market have been packed up and taken away. As a result, there's nothing for you to do here except head back into Elis...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			A metal sign attached to the counter of the stall in front of you declares that it's selling 'Burgers, Fries, & Pies'. This fact could also have been ascertained from the smell of greasy, fried food that's emanating from its ovens and deep-fat fryers. The canvas awning which covers this business is a solid shade of dark green, which you imagine might have been chosen due to its ability to conceal splashes of oil.
		</p>
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
			<p>
				As it's past closing time, the pair of pig-boys who operate the hot food business are busily packing away their stall. If you wanted to buy anything from them, you'll have to return here tomorrow...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				A pair of portly pig-boys are stationed behind the counter, and you watch for a moment as they busily flip burgers and serve up plates of greasy fries. Although the food served here is far from what anyone would consider to be healthy, you see that there's a relatively constant trickle of hungry customers placing orders.
			</p>
			<p>
				Pausing for a moment, you wonder whether to [pc.step] up to the stall and buy some kind of hot meal from these pig-boys... 
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_MEALS_FISH_CHIPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a serving of 'Fish and Chips' from one of the pig-boys behind the counter. After you've given him the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, the rotund pig-boy asks you to wait while he cooks your meal. Thankfully, it only takes him five minutes to get your order ready, and with a big smile on his chubby face, he hands you the box of fish and chips that you've ordered.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_MEALS_SAUSAGES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a serving of 'Sausages' from one of the pig-boys behind the counter. After you've given him the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, the rotund pig-boy asks you to wait while he cooks your meal. Thankfully, it only takes him five minutes to get your order ready, and with a big smile on his chubby face, he hands you the box of sausages that you've ordered.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_MEALS_BURGER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a 'Brown Rat's Burger' with 'Oinkers Fries' from one of the pig-boys behind the counter. After you've given him the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, the rotund pig-boy asks you to wait while he cooks your meal. Thankfully, it only takes him five minutes to get your order ready, and with a big smile on his chubby face, he hands you the greasy burger and side of curly fries that you've ordered.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_MEALS_CHICKEN_PIE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a 'Chicken Pot Pie' from one of the pig-boys behind the counter. After you've given him the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, the rotund pig-boy asks you to wait while he cooks your meal. Thankfully, it only takes him five minutes to get your order ready, and with a big smile on his chubby face, he hands you the pie that you've ordered.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_MEALS_STEAK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and order a 'Meat and Marrow' steak sandwich from one of the pig-boys behind the counter. After you've given him the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, the rotund pig-boy asks you to wait while he cooks your meal. Thankfully, it only takes him five minutes to get your order ready, and with a big smile on his chubby face, he hands you the steak sandwich that you've ordered.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_MEALS_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] away from the counter, you find a quiet spot in which to relax and enjoy your meal. After fifteen minutes of watching the crowds of shoppers amble past, you've finished off your food, and after throwing the paper packaging into a nearby recycling bin, you wonder what to do next.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDayMinutes() + 5 >= 18 * 60)
			As the time has passed six while you were busy eating, the stall is now closed for the day, and you look across to see the pig-boys packing up. As all of the other stalls in the Farmer's Market will similarly be closed, there's not much for you to do here except head off back into Elis...
		#ELSE
			With the stall still open for business, you see the pig-boys behind its counter continuing to flip burgers and cook up plates of fries. You could always buy another meal if you wanted to, or instead head off into the market once again...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Snacks -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=19)
		<p>
			As it's well past closing time, all of the stalls in the Farmer's Market have been packed up and taken away. As a result, there's nothing for you to do here except head back into Elis...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			The canvas awning which covers the stall in front of you is patterned in alternating stripes of light-green and white, while the cloth that's draped over its counter is a pretty, delicate shade of yellow. Numerous wicker baskets have been placed on the counter's surface, each one of which is full of different types of individually-packaged snacks. The stall's name has been hand sewn into the table's cloth, which reveals it to be 'Sweets & Treats'.
		</p>
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
			<p>
				As it's past closing time, the sheep-girls who operate 'Sweets & Treats' are busily packing away their stall. If you wanted to buy anything from them, you'll have to return here tomorrow...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				A group of pretty sheep-girls are stationed behind the counter, and are busily serving the many customers who've decided to make a quick stop and buy a snack.
			</p>
			<p>
				Pausing for a moment, you wonder whether to [pc.step] up to the stall and buy a snack from these sheep-girls... 
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_CANDY_FLOSS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and pick up a 'Woolly Goodness' from one of the wicker baskets. The nearest sheep-girl behind the counter asks you for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and after you've handed over the money, she flashes you a big smile and says that she hopes that you'll enjoy your candy floss.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_POPCORN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and pick up a bag of 'Popcorn' from one of the wicker baskets. The nearest sheep-girl behind the counter asks you for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and after you've handed over the money, she flashes you a big smile and says that she hopes that you'll enjoy your popcorn.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_CANINE_CRUNCH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and pick up an individually-wrapped 'Canine Crunch' from one of the wicker baskets. The nearest sheep-girl behind the counter asks you for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and after you've handed over the money, she flashes you a big smile and says that she hopes that you'll enjoy your cookie.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_BREAD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and pick up an individually-wrapped 'Bread Roll' from one of the wicker baskets. The nearest sheep-girl behind the counter asks you for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and after you've handed over the money, she flashes you a big smile and says that she hopes that you'll enjoy your bread roll.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_NUTS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and pick up a bag of 'Round Nuts' from one of the wicker baskets. The nearest sheep-girl behind the counter asks you for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and after you've handed over the money, she flashes you a big smile and says that she hopes that you'll enjoy your mixed nuts.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_CARROT_CAKE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and pick up an individually-wrapped 'Bunny Carrot-Cake' from one of the wicker baskets. The nearest sheep-girl behind the counter asks you for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and after you've handed over the money, she flashes you a big smile and says that she hopes that you'll enjoy your cake.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_EGGS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and pick up a box of 'Boiled Eggs' from one of the wicker baskets. The nearest sheep-girl behind the counter asks you for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and after you've handed over the money, she flashes you a big smile and says that she hopes that you'll enjoy your eggs.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_HONEY_BREAD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and pick up an individually-wrapped slice of 'Honey Bread' from one of the wicker baskets. The nearest sheep-girl behind the counter asks you for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and after you've handed over the money, she flashes you a big smile and says that she hopes that you'll enjoy your honey bread.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_BERRY_TRIFLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and pick up a pot of 'Berry Trifle' from one of the wicker baskets. The nearest sheep-girl behind the counter asks you for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and after you've handed over the money, she flashes you a big smile and says that she hopes that you'll enjoy your trifle.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_BROWNIE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get something to eat, you [pc.step] up to the counter and pick up an individually-wrapped slice of 'Chocolate Brownie' from one of the wicker baskets. The nearest sheep-girl behind the counter asks you for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and after you've handed over the money, she flashes you a big smile and says that she hopes that you'll enjoy your brownie.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOOD_SNACKS_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] away from the counter, you find a quiet spot in which to relax and enjoy your snack. After five minutes of watching the crowds of shoppers amble past, you've finished off your food, and after throwing the packaging into a nearby recycling bin, you wonder what to do next.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDayMinutes() + 5 >= 18 * 60)
			As the time has passed six while you were busy eating, the stall is now closed for the day, and you look across to see the sheep-girls packing up. As all of the other stalls in the Farmer's Market will similarly be closed, there's not much for you to do here except head off back into Elis...
		#ELSE
			With the stall still open for business, you see the sheep-girls behind its counter continuing to serve their many customers. You could always buy another meal if you wanted to, or instead head off into the market once again...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- heather's 'The Third Eye' stall: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=19)
		<p>
			As it's well past closing time, all of the stalls in the Farmer's Market have been packed up and taken away. As a result, there's nothing for you to do here except head back into Elis...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(heather.isPlayerKnowsName())
			#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
				<p>
					As it's past closing time, you see that Heather is busily packing [heather.her] tent away. Not wanting to trouble [heather.herHim], you decide to leave [heather.herHim] to it and head back into the Farmer's Market...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Although they differ in length and height, all of the businesses in the Farmer's Market operate out of a stall of the same design, consisting of a counter-top covered by a colourful canvas awning. That is, all except the one before you. Instead of an open-sided stall, the space in front of you is occupied by a small yurt, the sides and roof of which are made out of canvas that's been dyed a deep shade of blue and painted with stars and moons. The opening to this yurt has been left wide open, and a sign placed to the side of this entrance declares this business to be called 'The Third Eye'.
				</p>
				<p>
					Wanting to pay Heather another visit, you approach the entrance to this yurt and look inside the dimly-lit interior. A few bookcases have been positioned around the edges of this interior space, and upon their shelves you see numerous potion bottles and odd-looking mystical instruments. What draws your attention the most, however, is Heather, who's sitting behind the centrally-positioned table, and as you look over towards [heather.herHim], [heather.she] calls out in a soft voice, [heather.speech(Your return was foretold, [pc.name]... Please, enter...)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Seeing no reason not to take [heather.herHim] up on this invitation, you [pc.step] into the yurt and take a good look at Heather once again. Wearing a grey witch's hat, dress, and thigh-high boots, [heather.her] outfit fits in perfectly with the mystical theme created by the atmosphere within [heather.her] star-strewn yurt. As [heather.she] looks up at you with [heather.her] [heather.eyeColour] eyes, [heather.she] brushes a loose strand of brown hair from out of [heather.her] face. As [heather.she] flashes you a smile, you find your gaze being drawn down to the light pink choker that's securely fastened around [heather.her] neck, the colour of which perfectly matches [heather.her] fingernails, lipstick, and eyeshadow to give [heather.her] otherwise-androgynous features a touch of the feminine.
				</p>
				<p>
					#IF(heather.isAttractedTo(pc))
						#IF(heather.getSexCount(pc).getTotalTimesHadSex()>0)
							Unable to contain [heather.her] arousal, [heather.she] lets out a little moan as [heather.she] looks you up and down and asks, [heather.speech(What can I do for you this day, [pc.name]? Would you care to purchase something? Or, if you've got a Faire ticket, I could read your fortune... Or... You could put me in my place again and give me a good, hard fuck...)]
						#ELSE
							Clearly liking the look of you, [heather.she] lets out a little moan as [heather.she] looks you up and down and asks, [heather.speech(What can I do for you this day, [pc.name]? Would you care to purchase something? Or, if you've got a Faire ticket, I could read your fortune...)]
						#ENDIF
					#ELSE
						After quickly looking you up and down, [heather.she] asks, [heather.speech(What can I do for you this day, [pc.name]? Would you care to purchase something? Or, if you've got a Faire ticket, I could read your fortune...)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
				<p>
					As it's past closing time, you see a [heather.race] busily packing her stall away in this area. Not wanting to trouble [heather.herHim], you decide to leave [heather.herHim] to it and head back into the Farmer's Market...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Although they differ in length and height, all of the businesses in the Farmer's Market operate out of a stall of the same design, consisting of a counter-top covered by a colourful canvas awning. That is, all except the one before you. Instead of an open-sided stall, the space in front of you is occupied by a small yurt, the sides and roof of which are made out of canvas that's been dyed a deep shade of blue and painted with stars and moons. The opening to this yurt has been left wide open, and a sign placed to the side of this entrance declares this business to be called 'The Third Eye'.
				</p>
				<p>
					Curious to discover what lies within, you approach the entrance to this yurt and look inside the dimly-lit interior. A few bookcases have been positioned around the edges of this interior space, and upon their shelves you see numerous potion bottles and odd-looking mystical instruments. What draws your attention the most, however, is the androgynous character who's sitting behind the centrally-positioned table, and as you look over towards [heather.herHim], [heather.she] calls out in a soft voice, [heather.speech(Your coming was foretold... Enter, and discover your destiny...)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Seeing no reason not to take [heather.herHim] up on this invitation, you [pc.step] into the yurt and take a good look at this mysterious individual. Wearing a grey witch's hat, dress, and thigh-high boots, [heather.her] outfit fits in perfectly with the mystical theme created by the atmosphere within [heather.her] star-strewn yurt. As [heather.she] looks up at you with [heather.her] [heather.eyeColour] eyes, you realise that this androgynous individual looks to be fully human. As [heather.she] brushes a loose strand of brown hair from out of [heather.her] face, your gaze is drawn down to the light pink choker that's securely fastened around [heather.her] neck, the colour of which perfectly matches [heather.her] fingernails, lipstick, and eyeshadow to give [heather.her] otherwise-androgynous features a touch of the feminine.
				</p>
				<p>
					[heather.speech(Those who wish for me to glance into the mists of their future name me as Heather,)] [heather.she] reveals in a quiet voice.
					#IF(heather.isAttractedTo(pc))
						 Clearly liking the look of you, [heather.she] flashes you a sly smile and asks, [heather.speech(Who do I have the pleasure of entertaining today?)]
					#ELSE
						 As you move forwards, [heather.she] flashes you a quick smile and asks, [heather.speech(May I ask for your name?)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_TRANSACTION_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you move to take a closer look at what Heather has for sale, [heather.she] reminds you, [heather.speech(If you buy one of my items of clothing, I'll give you a Faire ticket...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_TRANSACTION_NO_TICKET"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your flames in exchange for the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0], Heather says, [heather.speech(Thank you for the business... I wish I could give you a Faire ticket, but those are reserved for when people buy clothing from me...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_TRANSACTION_TICKET"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your flames in exchange for the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0], Heather hands you a Faire ticket and excitedly exclaims, [heather.speech(Thanks for the business, [pc.name]! Here's one of the tickets I've been given to hand out. You can trade it in with me if you want a fortune reading...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_DEMAND_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have sex with Heather again, you dominantly demand that [heather.she] submit to you so that you can give [heather.herHim] a good fuck. Letting out a submissive whine, [heather.she] stands up and skips over to close the curtain of [heather.her] yurt, before falling into your [pc.arms] and moaning, [heather.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes, dominate me, [pc.name]! Put me in my place and fuck me good and hard!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As Heather grinds her hot body up against you, she continues letting out a series of horny moans, and you find yourself quickly getting turned on and desperate to give [heather.herHim] what [heather.she] wants...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seeing no reason not to give Heather you name, you introduce yourself to [heather.herHim], before asking what it is that [heather.her] business offers. Gesturing to the shelves which line the interior of [heather.her] yurt, Heather explains, [heather.speech(I offer potions and a few items of specially-enchanted clothing. If you buy an item of my special clothing, then you earn a Faire ticket.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reaching down beneath [heather.her] table, Heather lifts up a crystal ball, and after showing it off for a moment, she continues, [heather.speech(You may trade in a Faire ticket in return for having your fortune read. I have no real skill with the arcane, but I do have an extremely strong affinity for harnessing the power of this artefact. I can show you any future you desire...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Putting the crystal ball away beneath [heather.her] table, Heather leans forwards and asks, [heather.speech(So, what can I do for you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_CRYSTAL_BALL"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_heather_fortune_read))
		<p>
			Wanting to experience Heather's fortune reading again, you hand over one of your Faire tickets and tell [heather.herHim] that you'd like to see another vision of your future. Taking your ticket and tearing it in half, she stands up and skips over to close the curtain of [heather.her] yurt, before returning to [heather.her] seat and motioning for you to sit down opposite [heather.herHim]. As you move to do so, [heather.she] reaches down under [heather.her] table and once again produces [heather.her] crystal ball.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to experience Heather's fortune reading, you hand over one of your Faire tickets and tell [heather.herHim] that you'd like to see a vision of your future. Taking your ticket and tearing it in half, she stands up and skips over to close the curtain of [heather.her] yurt, before returning to [heather.her] seat and motioning for you to sit down opposite [heather.herHim]. As you move to do so, [heather.she] reaches down under [heather.her] table and produces the crystal ball which [heather.she]'s previously showed to you.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		[heather.speech(There are only a couple of people in a thousand who are able to harness the power of this artefact,)] Heather proudly declares as [heather.she] places the glass orb down on the table between the two of you. Swirling [heather.her] hands over it in a rhythmic figure of eight, she lowers [heather.her] voice and starts to utter a series of incomprehensible words and phrases. As [heather.she] does this, a series of twinkling lights start to glitter within the crystal ball, and upon seeing that it's coming to life, Heather breaks off from [heather.her] incantations to instruct, [heather.speech(Place your [pc.hands] on the globe, and imagine what you want to see the most in your future, and the globe will reveal it to you...)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're instructed, you take hold of the crystal ball and wonder what to think of...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_CRYSTAL_BALL_POWER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Concentrating on the idea of possessing ultimate power, you watch as the lights within the crystal ball start to swirl around and take on a deep red hue. Unable to look away from the mesmerising display within this glass globe, you watch in awe as a fully 3D scene starts to play out within it...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		You see yourself sitting on a grand, golden throne, with the beautiful form of Lilith herself chained up and kneeling down at your side. Countless lilin, demons, and all other powerful representatives from throughout your realm are queueing up to kneel down and pay homage to you. The one who's leading them forwards and instructing them to take their turn before you is none other than Heather, and you watch with amusement as [heather.she] prostrates [heather.herself] before you...
	</i></p>
	<p>
		After spending a good five minutes watching this scene unfold within the crystal ball, the red lights start to fade away, and then as quickly as it started, it's all over. As the orb returns to an inert lump of glass, Heather flashes you a cheeky grin and asks, [heather.speech(Was that to your satisfaction, <i>my [pc.Lord]?</i>)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_CRYSTAL_BALL_FAME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Concentrating on the idea of being incredibly famous and respected, you watch as the lights within the crystal ball start to swirl around and take on a silver tone. Unable to look away from the mesmerising display within this glass globe, you watch in awe as a fully 3D scene starts to play out within it...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		You see yourself walking down one of the main boulevards which run through Dominion. Huge crowds line either side of the red-carpeted road, and as you pass, they cry out for you to give them your autograph, with some of the more desperate women bearing their naked breasts for you to sign. You occasionally stop to humour your adoring fans, and whenever you do so, Heather is right there by your side to advise you on the appropriate level of contact with the public. As you progress down the boulevard, you see the beautiful form of Lilith herself pushing people out of her way as she tries to get your attention...
	</i></p>
	<p>
		After spending a good five minutes watching this scene unfold within the crystal ball, the silver lights start to fade away, and then as quickly as it started, it's all over. As the orb returns to an inert lump of glass, Heather flashes you a cheeky grin and asks, [heather.speech(Was that to your satisfaction, <i>[pc.Sir]?</i>)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_CRYSTAL_BALL_FORTUNE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Concentrating on the idea of being incredibly wealthy, you watch as the lights within the crystal ball start to swirl around and take on a golden hue. Unable to look away from the mesmerising display within this glass globe, you watch in awe as a fully 3D scene starts to play out within it...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		You see yourself relaxing in a jacuzzi within the grounds of an absolutely enormous palace. Surrounded by the absolute cream of high society, you find yourself being the centre of attention as everyone asks you how you managed to obtain more wealth than anyone who's ever lived. At that moment, Heather appears to inform you that your purchase of Lilith's tower has been finalised, before gesturing towards the dishevelled figure of Lilith herself as she waits for you to notice her. Taking pity on the queen of all demons, you toss her a solid gold coin, before suggesting to her that she come and work for you in some part of your global business empire...
	</i></p>
	<p>
		After spending a good five minutes watching this scene unfold within the crystal ball, the golden lights start to fade away, and then as quickly as it started, it's all over. As the orb returns to an inert lump of glass, Heather flashes you a cheeky grin and asks, [heather.speech(Was that to your satisfaction, <i>boss</i>?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_CRYSTAL_BALL_SEX_NO_ATTRACTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Concentrating on the idea of having non-stop sex with the fittest and most attractive partners in all of Lilith's Realm, you watch as the lights within the crystal ball start to swirl around and take on a pink hue. Unable to look away from the mesmerising display within this glass globe, you watch in awe as a fully 3D scene starts to play out within it...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		You see yourself surrounded by the hottest sexual partners imaginable, each one of which is either presenting themselves to you or begging for you to fuck them. Happy to give them what they want, you move between each one, indulging yourself in your most carnal desires as you turn each one of these individuals into a quivering, satisfied wreck. When all of your partners have been well and truly exhausted, Heather shows in the next group of willing participants, and the orgy starts all over again...
	</i></p>
	<p>
		After spending a good five minutes watching this scene unfold within the crystal ball, the pink lights start to fade away, and then as quickly as it started, it's all over. As the orb returns to an inert lump of glass, Heather flashes you a cheeky grin and asks, [heather.speech(Was that to your satisfaction?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_CRYSTAL_BALL_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Duly impressed by the vision you've just witnessed, you give Heather your honest reply in the affirmative. With a look of satisfaction on [heather.her] face, [heather.she] puts the crystal ball back safely beneath [heather.her] table, before skipping over to open the entrance flap to [heather.her] yurt. Returning to [heather.her] seat as you stand up, [heather.she] asks, [heather.speech(Is there anything else I can do for you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_CRYSTAL_BALL_END_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Duly impressed by the vision you've just witnessed, you give Heather your honest reply in the affirmative. With a look of satisfaction on [heather.her] face, [heather.she] puts the crystal ball back safely beneath [heather.her] table, before skipping over to open the entrance flap to [heather.her] yurt. Returning to [heather.her] seat as you stand up, [heather.she] asks, [heather.speech(Is there anything else I can do for you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking a quick look around the interior of Heather's yurt, you wonder whether to buy anything from [heather.herHim] or take your leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_CRYSTAL_BALL_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Concentrating on the idea of having non-stop sex with the fittest and most attractive partners in all of Lilith's Realm, you watch as the lights within the crystal ball start to swirl around and take on a pink hue. Unable to look away from the mesmerising display within this glass globe, you watch in awe as a fully 3D scene starts to play out within it...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		Instead of the sort of orgy you were expecting, you see yourself within a girly, pink-themed bedroom, watching Heather as [heather.she] slowly strips out of [heather.her] clothes. Shrugging off [heather.her] dress and quickly removing [heather.her] bra, [heather.she] reveals [heather.her] tiny, almost-completely flat breasts, upon each of which stands a big, puffy nipple. Looking down between [heather.her] legs, you see that [heather.sheHas] got [heather.her] small cock locked up in a silver chastity cage, and
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 after turning around and bending over, [heather.she] pulls out [heather.her] silver buttplug and moans for you to start fucking [heather.her] ass...
		#ELSE
			 after stepping forwards and dropping down before you, [heather.she] moans for you to let [heather.herHim] perform oral on you...
		#ENDIF
	</i></p>
	<p>
		Your vision is suddenly interrupted as the real-life Heather lets out
		#IF(heather.getSexCount(pc).getTotalTimesHadSex()>0)
			 a deeply horny whine and asks, [heather.speech(You want to fuck me again, huh? J-Just keep imagining that, and I won't be able to say no...)]
		#ELSE
			 an embarrassed gasp. [heather.Her] cheeks flush bright red, and from the desperate look in [heather.her] eyes, you can tell that [heather.sheIs] getting madly turned on as [heather.she] stutters, [heather.speech(H-Hey! T-Think of something else! I get a bit of feedback from these visions, and you're making me... I won't be able to hold back...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_CRYSTAL_BALL_SEX_ORAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking where this is going, you concentrate as hard as you can on intensifying the vision within the crystal ball, and you watch in delight as the lewd scene becomes both clearer and more explicit in nature...
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
		<p><i>
			You see yourself still within the same girly, pink-themed bedroom, although this time you've already exposed your [pc.cock+] and are presenting it to a desperate-looking Heather. Dropping down before you, [heather.she] wastes no time in parting [heather.her] [heather.lips+] and planting a big, wet kiss on the [pc.cockHead+] of your throbbing shaft. Completely submitting to you, [heather.she] then quickly drops [heather.her] head down, taking your [pc.cock+] down [heather.her] throat as [heather.she] starts to give you an enthusiastic, sloppy blowjob...
		</i></p>
		<p>
			[heather.speech(Oh, fuck...)] the real-life Heather moans, interrupting your vision once again. With your imagination clearly having had a deeply arousing impact on [heather.herHim], [heather.she] doesn't even stop to ask for your consent in [heather.her] rush to skip around to your side of the table and kneel down before you. With a look of overwhelming lust in [heather.her] [heather.eyeColour] eyes, [heather.she] frantically begs, [heather.speech(Come on... ~Mmm!~ Give me your cock! I'll take it deep down my throat... Fuck my face and make me your bitch! ~Aah!~ Come on, give it to me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Turned on by the vision you've just witnessed, and now by Heather's enthusiasm to replicate what you've seen now in real life, you decide to do as [heather.she] asks,
			#IF(pc.isTaur())
				 and after standing up, you take out your [pc.cock+] and present it to [heather.herHim].
			#ELSE
				 and after turning your chair to face [heather.herHim], you take out your [pc.cock+] and present it to [heather.herHim].
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out a hungry moan, Heather immediately pounces, and before you have time to react, [heather.her] tongue is sliding up and down the length of your erect shaft. Taking inspiration from the crystal ball's vision, [heather.she] parts [heather.her] [heather.lips+] and plants a big, wet kiss on the [pc.cockHead+] of your cock. Letting out a desperate, horny squeal, [heather.she] then proceeds to open [heather.her] mouth wide, and by dropping [heather.her] head down, [heather.she] takes your [pc.cock+] deep down [heather.her] throat.
		</p>
		<p>
			As Heather starts to give you a desperate, loving blowjob, you can't help but let out a deeply satisfied [pc.moan] of your own and reflect for a moment on how well this has all turned out...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p><i>
			You see yourself still within the same girly, pink-themed bedroom, although this time you've already exposed your [pc.pussy+] and are presenting it to a desperate-looking Heather. Dropping down before you, [heather.she] wastes no time in parting [heather.her] [heather.lips+] and planting a big, wet kiss on your [pc.labia+]. Completely submitting to you, [heather.she] quickly moves [heather.her] head up to suck on and kiss your sensitive clit, before burying [heather.her] face in your groin and starting to enthusiastically eat you out...
		</i></p>
		<p>
			[heather.speech(Oh, fuck...)] the real-life Heather moans, interrupting your vision once again. With your imagination clearly having had a deeply arousing impact on [heather.herHim], [heather.she] doesn't even stop to ask for your consent in [heather.her] rush to skip around to your side of the table and kneel down before you. With a look of overwhelming lust in [heather.her] [heather.eyeColour] eyes, [heather.she] frantically begs, [heather.speech(Come on... ~Mmm!~ Give me your pussy! I'll get my tongue deep in your hot cunt... Make me your bitch and have me eat you out! ~Aah!~ Come on, give it to me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Turned on by the vision you've just witnessed, and now by Heather's enthusiasm to replicate what you've seen now in real life, you decide to do as [heather.she] asks,
			#IF(pc.isTaur())
				 and after standing up, you expose your [pc.pussy+] and present it to [heather.herHim].
			#ELSE
				 and after turning your chair to face [heather.herHim], you expose your [pc.pussy+] and present it to [heather.herHim].
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out a hungry moan, Heather immediately pounces, and before you have time to react, [heather.her] tongue is sliding up and down the length of your [pc.labia+]. Taking inspiration from the crystal ball's vision, [heather.she] parts [heather.her] [heather.lips+] and plants a big, wet kiss on your sensitive clit, before starting to greedily suck on it. Letting out a desperate, horny squeal, [heather.she] then proceeds to open [heather.her] mouth wide, and by dropping [heather.her] head down a little, [heather.she] slides [heather.her] tongue into your hot cunt and starts to frantically eat you out.
		</p>
		<p>
			As Heather starts to perform cunnilingus, you can't help but let out a deeply satisfied [pc.moan] of your own and reflect for a moment on how well this has all turned out...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_CRYSTAL_BALL_SEX_ANAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking where this is going, you concentrate as hard as you can on intensifying the vision within the crystal ball, and you watch in delight as the lewd scene becomes both clearer and more explicit in nature...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		You see yourself still within the same girly, pink-themed bedroom, although this time you've already exposed your [pc.cock+] and are presenting it to a desperate-looking Heather. Bending over the edge of [heather.her] bed, [heather.she] wastes no time in reaching back and pulling [heather.her] ass cheeks apart in order to present you with [heather.her] asshole. Moving forwards, you rub the [pc.cockHead+] of your throbbing shaft up against [heather.her] back door, and as [heather.she] declares [heather.her] complete submission, you thrust forwards and push your [pc.cock+] into [heather.her] ass...
	</i></p>
	<p>
		[heather.speech(Oh, fuck...)] the real-life Heather moans, interrupting your vision once again. With your imagination clearly having had a deeply arousing impact on [heather.herHim], [heather.she] doesn't even stop to ask for your consent in [heather.her] rush to skip around to the side of the table and pull up the skirt of [heather.her] dress. With a look of overwhelming lust in [heather.her] [heather.eyeColour] eyes, [heather.she] reveals that [heather.sheIs] wearing the exact same toys as in the vision scene, and after showing off her tiny, caged cock, [heather.she] turns around and pulls out [heather.her] silver butt plug, before bending over the table and frantically begging, [heather.speech(Come on... ~Mmm!~ Give me your cock! I'll take it deep in my ass... Fuck my butt and make me your bitch! ~Aah!~ Come on, give it to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turned on by the vision you've just witnessed, and now by Heather's enthusiasm to replicate what you've seen now in real life, you decide to do as [heather.she] asks, and after standing up, you take out your [pc.cock+] and [pc.step] forwards to rub it up and down over [heather.her] ass. Letting out a hungry moan, Heather reaches back and pulls [heather.her] cheeks apart, before raising [heather.her] [heather.hips+] and preparing [heather.herself] for what's to come.
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing no reason to wait, you thrust forwards and push your [pc.cock+] into Heather's [heather.asshole+], causing [heather.herHim] to let out [heather.a_moan+]. Encouraged by [heather.her] lewd cries, you start bucking your hips and thrusting your [pc.cock+] in and out of [heather.her] [heather.ass+]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(heather.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			Letting out a deeply satisfied sigh, Heather steps away from you and collapses down into [heather.her] chair. With a big smile on [heather.her] face, [heather.she] pants, [heather.speech(That was... Wow... You're good, [pc.name]... Real good...)]
		#ELSE
			Letting out a frustrated whine, Heather steps away from you and collapses down into [heather.her] chair. Pouting at you in annoyance, [heather.she] complains, [heather.speech(You didn't even satisfy me, [pc.name]... You need to do better next time...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling in response to Heather's words, you start to get your things back in order...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FORTUNES_AFTER_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun, you move away from Heather, allowing [heather.herHim] to stand up and skip over to open the entrance flap to [heather.her] yurt. Quickly returning to [heather.her] seat, [heather.she] asks, [heather.speech(So, [pc.name], is there anything else I can do for you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking a quick look around the interior of Heather's yurt, you wonder whether to buy anything from [heather.herHim] or take your leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Kissing booth: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=19)
		<p>
			As it's well past closing time, all of the stalls in the Farmer's Market have been packed up and taken away. As a result, there's nothing for you to do here except head back into Elis...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_ziva_met))
			#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
				<p>
					As it's past closing time, you see that [ziva.namePos] slaves are busily packing their stall away. Not wanting to trouble them, you decide to leave them to it and head back into the Farmer's Market...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Positioned on the corner of two intersecting paths through the Farmer's market, the stall before you is remarkably different from all of the others which surround it. Instead of offering goods or services for sale, an informative sign labels this business as the market's 'Kissing Booth', and briefly states that one Faire ticket can be handed in here in exchange for a kiss.
				</p>
				<p>
					The ones who are to deliver this promised kiss take the form of a trio of beautiful cow-girls, each one of which looks to be in their late teens or early twenties, and who are lined up and patiently waiting behind the stall's counter. As you take a closer looks at these cow-girls, you see that each of them is wearing a heavy metal slave collar, which is matched to the colour of their red, light-pink, and purple lipstick. Their skimpy bikinis are barely able to contain their massive breasts, and as they catch you looking at them, the one with the red lipstick winks at you and blows you a kiss.
				</p>
				#IF(ziva.isVisiblyPregnant())
					<p>
						[ziva.speech(You really do like getting my girls excited, don't you, [pc.name]?)] [ziva.name] calls out from off to one side of these cow-girls, and you look across to see the black-furred, greater goat-girl, who looks to be in her late forties, peering at you through her half-rim glasses. Her dark red plunge blouse strains to contain her huge, [ziva.cupSize]-cup breasts as she laboriously rises from her chair, and as she rubs her hands over her visibly-swollen belly, she teases, 
						#IF(!ziva.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
							 [ziva.speech(I was first made a mother many years ago, but you've gone and given me that experience all over again... Yes, you were the one who got me pregnant, hun, and no, I don't need anything from you... Well, other than more of your flames, that is. You like mature goat-girls, so surely you like pregnant, mature goat-girls too, right?)]
						#ELSE
							 [ziva.speech(Yes, thanks to you I'm still pregnant, hun, and no, I don't need anything from you... Well, other than more of your flames, that is. You like mature goat-girls, so surely you like pregnant, mature goat-girls too, right?)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
					<p>
						Nodding in agreement, you tell [ziva.name] that you're still attracted to her, which causes her to let out an amused chuckle and say, [ziva.speech(So come on then, prove it. If you've got any tickets left, hand them over and then pay up, and if you can afford it, you can soon find yourself balls-deep in my mature goat-pussy...)]
					</p>
				#ELSE
					<p>
						[ziva.speech(You really do like getting my girls excited, don't you, [pc.name]?)] [ziva.name] calls out from off to one side of these cow-girls, and you look across to see the black-furred, greater goat-girl, who looks to be in her late forties, peering at you through her half-rim glasses. Her dark red plunge blouse strains to contain her huge, [ziva.cupSize]-cup breasts as she leans forwards in her chair, and as her yellow, goat-like eyes look you up and down, she
						#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_ziva_kissed))
							 teases, [ziva.speech(But we both know that you're not interested in my sexy, young slaves. No, you prefer mature goat-girls, don't you, hun? Now hand over one of your Faire tickets and get ready to pay up so that you can kiss me again...)]
						#ELSE
							 asks, [ziva.speech(So then, hun, have you got a Faire ticket to trade in for a kiss from one of my girls?)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
				<p>
					As it's past closing time, you see a trio of cow-girls busily packing their stall away in this area. Not wanting to trouble them, you decide to leave them to it and head back into the Farmer's Market...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Positioned on the corner of two intersecting paths through the Farmer's market, the stall before you is remarkably different from all of the others which surround it. Instead of offering goods or services for sale, an informative sign labels this business as the market's 'Kissing Booth', and briefly states that one Faire ticket can be handed in here in exchange for a kiss.
				</p>
				<p>
					The ones who are to deliver this promised kiss take the form of a trio of beautiful cow-girls, each one of which looks to be in their late teens or early twenties, and who are lined up and patiently waiting behind the stall's counter. As you take a closer looks at these cow-girls, you see that each of them is wearing a heavy metal slave collar, which is matched to the colour of their red, light-pink, and purple lipstick. Their skimpy bikinis are barely able to contain their massive breasts, and as they catch you looking at them, the one with the red lipstick winks at you and blows you a kiss.
				</p>
				<p>
					[ziva.speech(You've got my girls excited,)] a voice calls out from off to one side of these cow-girls, and you look across to see a black-furred, greater goat-girl, who looks to be in her late forties, peering at you through her half-rim glasses. Her dark red plunge blouse strains to contain her huge, [ziva.cupSize]-cup breasts as she leans forwards in her chair, and as her yellow, goat-like eyes look you up and down, she asks, [ziva.speech(Do you have any Faire tickets? If you do, you can trade them in for a kiss from one of my girls. Oh, and you may address me as Ms. [ziva.surname]. What shall I call you, hun?)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seeing no reason not to do so, you greet [ziva.name] and give her your name. Leaning back in her chair, she grins at you and repeats, [ziva.speech(If you've got a Faire ticket, you can trade it in here and get a kiss from one of my girls in return. I can assure you that they're very passionate about their duties, and your tickets won't be better spent anywhere else.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking over at the three cow-girls, you see them expectedly glancing your way, and as [ziva.name] notices this interaction, she laughs and says, [ziva.speech(See, hun, they're eager to get a taste of your lips! Now come on, hand over your tickets already. I've got a deal with the tourism board where they pay me in cash for every ticket I collect, so I need as many as I can get my hands on...)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		With [ziva.namePos] motivation for running this stall now revealed, you wonder whether it's worth giving her a Faire ticket in return for a kiss from one of her cow-girls...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_CHOICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it's worth giving up one of your Faire tickets to be able to get a kiss, you hand the slip of lime green paper over to [ziva.name]. The mature goat-girl grins in delight as she pockets the ticket, before gesturing to her cow-gir slaves and
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_ziva_kiss_offered))
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_ziva_kissed))
				 teasing, [ziva.speech(You can choose any of them to kiss, I really don't care which it is... But let's be honest with one another; you're not interested in those hot, young sluts, are you, hun? No, you've got a thing for mature goat-girls. Now hand over a thousand flames, and I'll let you kiss me again...)]
			#ELSE
				 saying, [ziva.speech(You can choose any of them to kiss, hun, I really don't care which it is. Oh, and if you're still really interested in wanting a kiss from me, then it'll be a thousand flames...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 saying, [ziva.speech(You can choose any of them to kiss, hun, I really don't care which it is. Just make sure to have fun and come back again for more later on, I could always do with more tickets!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking across at the three cow-girls, you see that while each of them is roughly the same height, age, and cup-size, they differ from one another by their attitude. The one wearing red lipstick looks to be the most normal, and is happily smiling at you as she tries to get your attention. The one wearing light-pink lipstick seems to be absolutely desperate for you to choose her, for as you look over at her, she bats her eyelids at you and blows you a big kiss, before biting her lip and impatiently squirming about on the spot. Finally, the one wearing purple lipstick doesn't seem to be all that happy with her lot in life, for as you glance her way she scowls at you a little, before pouting and turning away.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_ziva_kiss_offered))
			Although these three cow-girls are undeniably beautiful, you find yourself looking back towards [ziva.name], and you wonder if it's worth paying a thousand flames to get a kiss from her...
		#ELSE
			Although these three cow-girls are undeniably beautiful, you find yourself briefly looking back towards [ziva.name], and you wonder if it's worth asking whether it'd be possible to get a kiss from her...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_CHOICE_RED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Making up your mind, you [pc.step] over to where the cow-girl wearing the red collar and lipstick is standing. Happily smiling at you, she excitedly asks, [style.speechFeminineStrong(You're picking me?! Ooh, yay! Come on then, get a taste of my lips...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Bending down over the counter, the cow-girl purses her lips, and you lean forwards to plant a kiss on her mouth. Letting out a happy sigh, your partner lifts her hands up and gently takes hold of you, before tilting her head to one side and sliding her tongue into your mouth. Continuing to let out a series of muffled moans, the cow-girl desperately presses her mouth against yours, smearing her red lipstick all over your lips in the process.
	</p>
	<p>
		A few minutes, and a lot of passionate kissing later, and you hear [ziva.name] call out, [ziva.speech(That's enough, slave!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a disappointed whine, the cow-girl pulls back and brings and end to your makeout session. Looking across to [ziva.name], you see her flash you a devious grin before stating, [ziva.speech(If you want more, hun, then hand over another ticket...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_CHOICE_PINK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Making up your mind, you [pc.step] over to where the cow-girl wearing the light pink collar and lipstick is standing. With a huge grin on her pretty face, she excitedly asks, [style.speechFeminineStrong(You want to kiss me?! Yes! Oh, please, I <i>love</i> getting to kiss people! Come on, get a taste of my lips!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Desperately bending down over the counter, the cow-girl purses her lips, and you lean forwards to plant a kiss on her mouth. Letting out an ecstatic squeal, your partner lifts her hands up and firmly takes hold of you, before tilting her head to one side and greedily pushing her tongue into your mouth. Continuing to let out a series of muffled moans, the cow-girl desperately presses her mouth against yours, smearing her light pink lipstick all over your lips in the process.
	</p>
	<p>
		A few minutes, and a lot of frantic, passionate kissing later, and you hear [ziva.name] call out, [ziva.speech(That's enough, slave!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an extremely disappointed whine, the cow-girl reluctantly pulls back and brings and end to your makeout session. Looking across to [ziva.name], you see her flash you a devious grin before stating, [ziva.speech(If you want more, hun, then hand over another ticket...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_CHOICE_PURPLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Making up your mind, you [pc.step] over to where the cow-girl wearing the purple collar and lipstick is standing. Rolling her eyes, she asks in a dead-pan voice, [style.speechFeminineStrong(You choose me, right? Fine... Come on then, let's get this over with...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Bending down over the counter, the cow-girl purses her lips, and you lean forwards to plant a kiss on her mouth. Letting out a defeated sigh, your partner lifts her hands up and takes hold of you, before tilting her head to one side and slowly pushing her tongue into your mouth. Continuing to let out a series of deep moans, the cow-girl dutifully presses her mouth against yours, smearing her purple lipstick all over your lips in the process.
	</p>
	<p>
		A few minutes, and a lot of reluctant kissing later, and you hear [ziva.name] call out, [ziva.speech(That's enough, slave!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a relieved sigh, the cow-girl quickly pulls back and brings and end to your makeout session. Looking across to [ziva.name], you see her flash you a devious grin before stating, [ziva.speech(If you want more, hun, then hand over another ticket...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_CHOICE_ZIVA_OFFER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although the three cow-girls are tempting targets, you can't help but feel more attracted to [ziva.name], and so after returning your gaze to her, you ask the mature goat-girl if you could kiss her instead of one of her slaves. For a moment, the goat-girl's face twists into a look of confused annoyance, but as she starts to reply in the negative, she catches herself and pauses to think for a moment. As an idea forms in her head, [ziva.namePos] annoyed scowl shifts into a devious grin, and she asks, [ziva.speech(You'd rather kiss a mature goat-girl than one of her sexy, young slaves?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Responding in the affirmative, you tell [ziva.name] that you find her to be more attractive than the three cow-girls, and repeat your request to kiss her. Seeing that you're serious, the goat-girl grins at you and offers, [ziva.speech(Sure thing, hun, if you're that desperate to get a taste of my lips, then I'll let you. However, as I'm far more experienced than my slaves, my kisses are worth a lot more than theirs. I couldn't simply kiss you for free, you understand... How about... A thousand flames, and I'll let you kiss me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As [ziva.name] leans back in her chair and continues to flash you a sly grin, you wonder whether it would be worth paying a thousand flames in return for a kiss from her. Then again, you could simply [pc.step] over to one of the cow-girls and get a kiss at no additional cost...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_CHOICE_NONE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you don't want a kiss after all, you tell [ziva.name] that you've changed your mind, to which she tuts and quickly states, [ziva.speech(Sorry, hun, but you're not getting your ticket back, if that's what you're after. Check the bottom of the information board; the small print explicitly states that there are no refunds...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking over to the information board which [ziva.name] is gesturing towards, you see that there is indeed a small section at the bottom which states, among several other things, that tickets cannot be refunded. With a triumphant grin on her face, the goat-girl leans back in her chair and states, [ziva.speech(That's just business, hun; no hard feelings. Now, if you think that you've missed out, all you need to do is hand over another of your tickets and you can have your kiss...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With [ziva.name] continuing to flash you a sly grin, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_ZIVA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it's worth it to pay a thousand flames to be able to get to kiss [ziva.name], you give her the money and repeat your claim that you prefer her to her three cow-girl slaves. Greedily stashing the flames away in a nearby strongbox, the goat-girl beckons for you to come around to her side of the counter, and as you eagerly do so, she laughs, [ziva.speech(You really prefer older women? I can't believe you actually paid for this... You must be really desperate, huh?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The mature goat-girl's womanly hips sway from side to side as she saunters forwards, and as she comes to a halt in front of you, you can't help but once again notice how her plunge blouse is straining to contain her huge breasts. Seeing your quick glance at her chest, [ziva.name] tuts and reprimands you, [ziva.speech(Don't get carried away, hun; you're only getting what you paid for.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can respond, the goat-girl steps forwards and dominantly grabs your head, before pulling you into a fiercely-passionate kiss. Parting her lips, [ziva.name] forces her tongue into your mouth, and as you let out a muffled [pc.moan], she continues moving forwards and starts grinding her up body up against yours. As she crushes her massive, pillowy tits into your chest, she starts exploring the inside of your mouth with her tongue, letting out a series of approving moans and sighs as she does so.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a couple of minutes of dominantly making out with you in this manner, [ziva.name] pulls back, breaking off your kiss with a deep sigh and asking, [ziva.speech(How was that? Feel like you got your money's worth?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeling incredibly aroused from the intensity of [ziva.namePos] kiss, you quickly respond in the positive, before leaning forwards to give her one last kiss. Letting out an amused chuckle, the mature goat-girl pushes you away, before wagging her finger in front of your face and scolding you, [ziva.speech(Oh no you don't! You've got what you paid for already. You still want more, hun? Then give me another ticket and another thousand flames.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the mature goat-girl lets out another laugh, you find your gaze once again drawn down to her exposed cleavage. Despite her apparent reluctance to give you another kiss for free, you see a clear sign that she enjoyed your intimate interaction just as much as you did; her massive, thick nipples are quite visibly erect and pushing out against the silky fabric of her plunge blouse.
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_ziva_strip_offered))
			 Seeing what it is you're looking at, [ziva.name] smirks and offers in a husky, seductive voice, [ziva.speech(You want to suck on my tits again, hun? Five thousand flames, and they're all yours...)]
		#ELSE
			 Feeling incredibly turned-on from the passionate kiss, your horny mind immediately jumps to the question of whether or not to ask her if you can suck on her tits...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_ZIVA_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having got what you wanted, you [pc.step] back and thank [ziva.name] for the kiss. After flashing you a smug smirk, she gestures for you to move back around to the other side of her counter, saying, [ziva.speech(We can do this again any time, hun, so long as you've got the cash. Now shoo, I've got a business to run.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] back around to the public side of the stall, you look back at [ziva.name] as she says, [ziva.speech(There's no time limit, by the way. Just give me the ticket and the flames, and I'll stick my tongue down your throat again right now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the mature goat-girl sits back down and continues to gaze your way, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_ZIVA_MORE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to look away from the sight of [ziva.namePos] massive, thick nipples pressing out beneath the thin fabric of her plunge blouse, you give in to your horny thoughts and ask the mature goat-girl if you can kiss them. Letting out a shocked sigh, [ziva.name] starts to admonish you for your outrageous request, but once again quickly stops herself. Narrowing her gaze a little, she peers at you through her glasses and slowly says, [ziva.speech(Let me get this straight, hun. You're telling me that you want me to take my tits out, so you can kiss my nipples? That's seriously what you're asking me right now?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Responding in the positive, you confirm to [ziva.name] that that's what you want. Letting out a laugh in disbelief at what she's hearing, the mature goat-girl gestures towards her young, voluptuous cow-girl slaves and asks, [ziva.speech(You're asking to kiss <i>my</i> tits, when you could have asked me about fucking one of my slaves instead? You've really got a thing for older goat-girls, huh? And here I was thinking that you'd be happy with just a kiss from me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reiterating your desire to kiss [ziva.namePos] naked breasts, you tell her that you find her to be far more attractive than her young slaves. Flashing you a devious smirk as she realises that you're not simply teasing her, the goat-girl states, [ziva.speech(Alright then, hun, I'll let you suck on my tits for a while, but it's going to cost you. My time's not cheap, so I'm going to have to demand five thousand flames. Pay up, and I'll let you suck on my tits for half an hour...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_ZIVA_BREASTS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		More than happy to pay up for the opportunity to suck on [ziva.namePos] tits, you hurriedly produce the five thousand flames which she's asked for. Briefly laughing in disbelief at how desperate you are, the mature goat-girl takes your money and secures it away in her lockbox, before turning her back on you and ordering, [ziva.speech(Follow me, hun. We can get some privacy around the back of my stall.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following in [ziva.namePos] footsteps, you quickly find yourself in a relatively spacious square behind her stall, with stacks of crates forming three sides and the canvas of the stall's backing constituting the fourth. Turning to face you, the goat-girl flashes you a sly smile, before pulling on the knot of her plunge blouse and allowing her huge, round tits to finally escape from their fabric confines. Just like the rest of her body, her breasts are covered in black fur that's highlighted here and there with streaks of grey. Hefting her breasts in both hands, [ziva.name] teases her fingers up to playfully squeeze and pinch her huge, ebony nipples. Letting out an amused moan, she pushes her chest out towards you and asks, [ziva.speech(What are you waiting for, hun? Come and get your money's worth...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not needing to be told twice, you rush forwards and drop your head down to [ziva.namePos] naked breasts. Planting kiss after kiss on her huge, black-furred breasts, you make your way down towards her massive, thick nipples, and after giving one of them an experimental lick, you take it into your mouth and start to greedily suck on it. Much to your surprise and delight, your actions cause the mature goat-girl to let out a deeply erotic moan, and she affectionately strokes the top of your head as she teases, [ziva.speech(~Mmm!~ You really prefer my tits to those of my young slaves? ~Aah!~ Oh, you're making me feel young again, hun... Don't stop...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With no intention of stopping, you continue lewdly sucking and kissing [ziva.namePos] huge, ebony nipples, moving back and forth between them as she pants and moans in excitement. You get so caught up in the fun of playing with the goat-girl's tits that the time seems to fly by, and before you know it your half an hour is up. After letting you plant one big kiss on each of her thoroughly-sucked teats, [ziva.name] steps back and pants, [ziva.speech(That felt far better than I thought it would... Say, hun, you really like my tits, but do you like mature goat-pussy, too?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly turned on from your oral attention, [ziva.name] reaches up beneath her pencil skirt and quickly slides her dark red thong all the way down her legs. Kicking it off to one side, she pulls up her skirt and presents you with her pussy, teasing, [ziva.speech(It's got some mileage, but I know you're horny for it. Looking's not going to cost you anything, but if you want a taste, that'll be ten thousand flames.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down between [ziva.namePos] legs, you see that her massive, dangling labia are of a similar ebony shade to her nipples. Letting out a soft moan, the goat-girl teases her fingers down to spread her pussy lips apart, revealing the fact that her slightly-loose cunt is already slimy and glistening with girlcum. Although it certainly does look like it's 'got some mileage' on it, you can't help but feel extremely turned on as you get a good look at [ziva.namePos] mature cunt. Smirking as she sees that you're unable to take your eyes away from it, the goat-girl teases,
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 [ziva.speech(Come on, hun, we both know that you're desperate for a taste of mature goat-pussy. Ten thousand flames, and you can stick your tongue in my cunt or ass 'til you make me cum.)]
		#ELSE
			 [ziva.speech(Come on, hun, we both know that you're desperate for a taste of mature goat-pussy. Ten thousand flames, and you can stick your tongue in my cunt 'til you make me cum.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You can't help but let out a quiet [pc.moan] as you imagine burying your face between the goat-girl's legs and getting a good taste of her sloppy cunt.
		#IF(pc.hasPenis())
			 Seeing the hungry look in your eyes, [ziva.name] bites her lip and offers you another deal,
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				 [ziva.speech(Bump it up to fifty thousand, and I'll let you stick your cock in both my pussy and my ass... I'll even let you finish inside if you want... How about that, hun? You want to try and knock me up? Or pump my ass full of cum? Come on, you know you want it...)]
			#ELSE
				 [ziva.speech(Bump it up to fifty thousand, and I'll let you stick your cock in my pussy... I'll even let you finish inside if you want... How about that, hun? You want to try and knock me up? Come on, you know you want it...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 Then again, you can't help but wonder if it's really worth spending ten thousand flames to do so...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_KISS_ZIVA_BREASTS_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Tearing your gaze away from [ziva.namePos] slimy, mature pussy, you tell her that you can't afford to pay her right now. Tutting in annoyance, she grabs her thong from off the floor and pulls it back up her legs, before flattening her skirt and tying her plunge blouse back into position. Pouting at you for a moment, she mutters, [ziva.speech(I thought you'd like mature goat-pussy... Anyway, I guess the show's over then, hun. Now shoo, I've got a business to run.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as [ziva.name] says, you [pc.step] out from the secretive storage area and return to the public side of the stall. Stepping over to her chair, [ziva.name] smirks at you and says, [ziva.speech(If you want a repeat performance, just say so. Give me another ticket and the flames, and I'll stick my tongue down your throat again right now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the mature goat-girl sits back down and continues to gaze your way, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZIVA_CUNNILINGUS_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Mesmerised by the sight of [ziva.namePos] sloppy goat-pussy, you hurry to hand over the ten thousand flames she's asking for. Letting out an amused laugh as she takes your cash, the goat-girl puts it to one side and beckons towards her cunt, teasing, [ziva.speech(Come on then, hun, tell me how much you love mature goat-pussy, and I'll let you get started!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping down in front of her, you look up at the goat-girl and [pc.moan], [pc.speech(I love your pussy, [ziva.name]! Please, let me get a taste of it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a triumphant smirk on her face, [ziva.name] leans back against a nearby stack of crates, before reaching down to once again spread her dangling, ebony labia. Presenting her slimy cunt to you, she moans, [ziva.speech(Get started then, hun. I want to feel your tongue <i>deep</i> in my cunt... Oh, and you're not to stop until I say so. Understood?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, [ziva.name],)] you reply as you shuffle forwards and drop your head down between the mature goat-girl's thighs. Breathing in her feminine musk, you dart out your tongue and give her massive labia a quick lick, before planting a big, wet kiss on her clit. Your actions draw out a long, deep moan from [ziva.name], which encourages you to bury your face in between her legs and start to greedily eat her out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZIVA_ANILINGUS_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you're captivated by the sight of [ziva.namePos] sloppy goat-pussy, it's her ass that you're really desperate for, and so as you hurry to hand over the ten thousand flames she's asking for, you tell the goat-girl that you want to perform anilingus on her. Letting out an amused laugh as she takes your cash, the goat-girl puts it to one side and turns around, showing off her [ziva.assSize] ass as she teases, [ziva.speech(Come on then, hun, tell me how much you love mature goat-ass, and I'll let you get started!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping down behind her, you look up at the goat-girl and [pc.moan], [pc.speech(I love your ass, [ziva.name]! Please, let me get a taste of it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a triumphant smirk on her face, [ziva.name] leans forwards against a nearby stack of crates, before reaching back to spread her ass cheeks. Presenting her [ziva.asshole+] to you, she moans, [ziva.speech(Get started then, hun. I want to feel your tongue <i>deep</i> in my ass... Oh, and you're not to stop until I say so. Understood?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, [ziva.name],)] you reply as you shuffle forwards and drop your head down towards the mature goat-girl's butt. Breathing in her feminine musk, you dart out your tongue and give her exposed asshole a quick lick, before planting a series of big, wet kisses on it. Your actions draw out a long, deep moan from [ziva.name], which encourages you to bury your face in between her cheeks and start to greedily give her a rimjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZIVA_VAGINAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Mesmerised by the sight of [ziva.namePos] sloppy goat-pussy, you hurry to hand over the fifty thousand flames she's asking for. Letting out an amused laugh as she takes your cash, the goat-girl steps over to a nearby crate, and after lying back on it, she spreads her legs and presents you with her cunt, teasing, [ziva.speech(Come on then, hun, tell me how much you love mature goat-pussy, and I'll let you stick your dick in it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Exposing your cock and [pc.stepping] up to her, you eagerly [pc.moan], [pc.speech(I love your pussy, [ziva.name]! Please, let me fuck it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a triumphant smirk on her face, [ziva.name] leans back, before reaching down to once again spread her dangling, ebony labia. Presenting her slimy cunt to you, she moans, [ziva.speech(Get started then, hun. I want to feel your cock <i>deep</i> in my cunt... Oh, and you're not to stop until I say so. Understood?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, [ziva.name],)] you reply as you move forwards and press the [pc.cockHead+] of your rapidly-hardening cock against the mature goat-girl's pussy. Breathing in her feminine musk, you slide your throbbing shaft up and down over her massive labia a few times, before pushing forwards and starting to sink your [pc.cockGirth] cock into her slimy twat. As she feels you entering her, [ziva.name] lets out long, deep moan, which encourages you to push forwards and sink your cock deep into her slimy pussy, before quickly pulling back and thrusting forwards once again. Within moments, the goat-girl is panting and moaning beneath you as you repeatedly thrust your [pc.cock+] in and out of her mature cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZIVA_ANAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you're captivated by the sight of [ziva.namePos] sloppy goat-pussy, it's her ass that you're really desperate for, and so as you hurry to hand over the fifty thousand flames she's asking for, you tell the goat-girl that you want to fuck her butt. Letting out an amused laugh as she takes your cash, the goat-girl steps over to a nearby crate, and after leaning down over it, she spreads her legs and presents you with her [ziva.ass+], teasing, [ziva.speech(Come on then, hun, tell me how much you love mature goat-ass, and I'll let you stick your dick in it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Exposing your cock and [pc.stepping] up to her, you eagerly [pc.moan], [pc.speech(I love your ass, [ziva.name]! Please, let me fuck it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a triumphant smirk on her face, [ziva.name] reaches back to spread her ass cheeks, presenting you with her ebony-rimmed asshole. Presenting her back door to you, she moans, [ziva.speech(Get started then, hun. I want to feel your cock <i>deep</i> in my butt... Oh, and you're not to stop until I say so. Understood?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, [ziva.name],)] you reply as you move forwards and press the [pc.cockHead+] of your rapidly-hardening cock against the mature goat-girl's ass. Breathing in her feminine musk, you slide your throbbing shaft up and down over her rear entrance a few times, before pushing forwards and starting to sink your [pc.cockGirth] cock into her ass. As she feels you entering her, [ziva.name] lets out long, deep moan, which encourages you to push forwards and sink your cock deep into her asshole, before quickly pulling back and thrusting forwards once again. Within moments, the goat-girl is panting and moaning beneath you as you repeatedly thrust your [pc.cock+] in and out of her ass...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a deeply-satisfied sigh, [ziva.name] pushes you away and declares, [ziva.speech(I think you've got your money's worth by now...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Still wanting a little more, you move towards the mature goat-girl's pussy, but she playfully pushes you away once again and tuts, [ziva.speech(I don't think so! This goat-pussy is expensive; I don't give out freebies. If you want more, you'll have to come back later and pay me again. )]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reluctantly [pc.stepping] away, you watch as [ziva.name] pulls her clothing back into position, concealing her slimy, mature pussy in the process.After flattening her skirt and tying her plunge blouse back into place, she waits for you to get your things back in order and declares, [ziva.speech(The show's over, hun. Now shoo, I've got a business to run.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KISSING_AFTER_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as [ziva.name] says, you [pc.step] out from the secretive storage area and return to the public side of the stall. Stepping over to her chair, [ziva.name] smirks at you and says, [ziva.speech(If you want a repeat performance, just say so. Give me another ticket and the flames, and I'll stick my tongue down your throat again right now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the mature goat-girl sits back down and starts to playfully count the money you've given her, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="PATH"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
		<p>
			As you [pc.walk] through the market, you see that all of the stallholders are packing up their goods and disassembling their stalls. With the day's market coming to an end, there's really very little left for you to do here. You should probably head back out into the rest of Elis and return tomorrow if you wanted to do any more shopping.
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
			[style.italicsMinorBad(The market is closed, and will reopen at [units.time(8)] tomorrow...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As you [pc.walk] through the busy avenues formed between countless brightly-coloured stalls, you see all manner of food, drink, and other items for sale. Unlike a regular farmer's market, the one here in Elis seems to have evolved into a type of low-key festival, complete with a band somewhere in the distance playing live music.
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_lunetteTerrorEnded))
				 While there are certainly exceptions, almost everyone you pass looks to be in high spirits,
				#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_RAIN)
					 with not even the rain being able to bring the mood down.
				#ELSEIF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_SNOW)
					 with not even the snow being able to bring the mood down.
				#ELSE
					 with the smiles on their faces making it clear that they're greatly enjoying the market's festive atmosphere.
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				 Although a lot of the people who you pass look to be in high spirits, there are many whose forlorn expressions seem to be unaffected by the market's festive atmosphere, and you can only assume that they're victims in one way or another of Lunette's raiding.
			#ENDIF
			 While races of all kinds can be seen if you search hard enough, the vast majority of the shoppers and vendors consist of all manner of domesticated animal morphs.
		</p>
		#IF(pc.getOccupation()==OCCUPATION_TOURIST)
			<p>
				Unable to resist the urge to take a photo, you pull out your phone and take a picture of the busy market, talking to yourself as you do so, [pc.speech([game.random(
				The folks back home will love this.
				| Neat, it's like a Medieval Times back home.
				| These Europeans sure look funny.
				| So this is what they have instead of malls in Europe.)])]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_lunetteTerrorEnded))
				Thanks to the fact that Lunette is no longer raiding the surrounding farmland, the market seems to be busier than ever. Catching brief snippets of conversation as you [pc.walk] past some of the stalls, you soon get the impression that the quantity and quality of produce which the vendors are able to acquire is better than it's ever been. Thanks to this, there are a good deal of stalls which look to be offering something interesting, and you wonder whether you should take some time out of your day in which to do a spot of shopping...
			#ELSE
				Although it's very busy, with crowds of shoppers occupying large parts of the market, you can't help but notice that some of the stalls look to be quite low on goods for sale. Catching brief snippets of conversation as you [pc.walk] past, you soon get the impression that Lunette's raiding is having an effect on both the quantity and quality of produce which the vendors are able to acquire. Despite this, however, there are still a good deal of stalls which look to be offering something interesting, and you wonder whether you should take some time out of your day in which to do a spot of shopping...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF(game.getMinutesUntilTimeInMinutes(1080)<30)
			<p style='text-align:center;'>
				[style.italicsMinorBad(The market closes at [units.time(18)], so you should hurry up and finish your business here before all the stalls shut for the day...)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Yui's 'Yui's Toys' stall: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=19)
		<p>
			As it's well past closing time, all of the stalls in the Farmer's Market have been packed up and taken away. As a result, there's nothing for you to do here except head back into Elis...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(yui.isPlayerKnowsName())
			#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
				<p>
					As it's past closing time, you see that Yui is busily packing her stall away. Not wanting to trouble her, you decide to leave her to it and head back into the Farmer's Market...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					You once again find yourself standing before the stall 'Yui's Toys'. Its dark-purple awning and curtains, combined with the black cloth draped over its counter, gives business a very ominous appearance. Yui herself, the demonic, yellow-and-black striped spider-girl, is standing behind the counter, and fixes her eight glowing-crimson eyes on your face as you draw near.
				</p>
				<p>
					[yui.speech(Back for some of my toys, are you?)] she asks. Swiftly smacking her riding crop down against the counter-top, she flashes you a wild, sadistic grin and teases, [yui.speech(Or are you here for some punishment?)] 
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
				<p>
					As it's past closing time, you see a demonic spider-girl busily packing her stall away in this area. Not wanting to trouble her, you decide to leave her to it and head back into the Farmer's Market...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					In stark contrast to the colourful canvas seen throughout most of the Farmer's Market, the awning which covers the stall in front of you is a dark shade of purple. The counter upon which dozens of sex toys are on display is draped in a black cloth, which combined with the dark purple curtains that hang from three of the stall's four sides, gives this business a very ominous appearance. Thick strands of white spider webbing have not only been spun into webs in each of the corners of this stall, but also have been skilfully woven into the words 'Yui's Toys'.
				</p>
				<p>
					You almost don't notice this stall's unusual dcor, as your attention is immediately drawn to the demonic spider-girl who's standing behind the counter. Although she's standing at a relatively small [yui.heightValue], this [yui.race] gives off an incredibly threatening vibe. It's not the striking, black-and-yellow stripes of her chitinous skin that sends a shudder down your spine, nor the jet-black leather fetish gear that she's wearing, nor even the fact that she's got six arms that are all quickly moving as they play with strands of thin spider webbing shot out of the spinneret at the end of her bulbous, spider-like tail. What really makes you stop dead in your tracks is the fact that this spider-girl has eight glowing-crimson eyes spread across her upper face, each one of which is gazing at you with a look of petrifying malice.
				</p>
				<p>
					[yui.speech(Don't you know that it's rude to stare?)] she asks, her voice dripping with patronising amusement. Using one of her six arms to tuck a loose strand of her black-and-red head back into her bun, this small spider-girl leans forwards over her counter and beckons you forwards. With a thin smirk on her pretty face, she demands, [yui.speech(So go on then, tell me who you are.)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to do as she says, you tell this demonic spider-girl who you are, to which she replies, [yui.speech([pc.Name]... I don't think I've had a toy called [pc.name] before... Anyway, you can call me Yui. Are you here to buy something?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Gesturing over her stall's counter, she draws your attention to the numerous sex toys and leather fetish gear that's on display. Picking up a black riding crop from under the table, Yui swiftly strikes it down against the counter, before letting out an evil laugh and revealing, [yui.speech(If you're here looking to earn a Faire ticket, then you can submit to me for an hour. I do enjoy playing with toys, and you look like you'll be a fun one...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As if this wasn't enough to reveal to you that she has some strong sadistic urges, Yui bites her lip and continues, [yui.speech(You can also trade in a Faire ticket to have a very personal demonstration of one of my sex toys. I'll tie you up and give you some real punishment... ~Mmm!~ Yes, I can tell that your squirming and screams will be simply delicious...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the sadistic spider-girl hungrily gazing at you with her eight glowing-crimson eyes, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_TRANSACTION_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[yui.speech(Interested in my goods, are you?)] Yui asks, [yui.speech(Perhaps you've got a slave or two who could do with being locked up and punished? If so, please do give them a reason to scream and let them know that it's from me...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DOMINATION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to earn a Faire ticket from Yui, you tell her that you're willing to submit to her. Immediately upon hearing this, each of her eight, glowing-crimson eyes narrow down, and she flashes you an evil grin before demanding, [yui.speech(Kneel down and call me 'Mistress Yui', and I'll consider playing with you.)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she asks, you drop down in front of the demonic spider-girl and beg, [pc.speech(Please, Mistress Yui, I want you to dominate me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an amused, high-pitched laugh, the small sadist swipes her riding crop down at the floor beside her and orders, [yui.speech(Crawl around here, toy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Once again doing as you're told, you crawl around to the other side of the counter. Licking her lips in anticipation of getting to dominate you, Yui 
		#IF(game.isFootContentEnabled())
			 raises one of her feet, before pushing the gothic boot that she's wearing into your face and sneering,
			#IF(game.isArmpitContentEnabled())
				 [yui.speech(So, what'll it be, toy? You want me to sit on your face, or smother your mouth with my feet or armpits? I'm in a good mood today, so I'll let you choose...)]
			#ELSE
				 [yui.speech(So, what'll it be, toy? You want me to sit on your face, or smother your mouth with my feet? I'm in a good mood today, so I'll let you choose...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(game.isArmpitContentEnabled())
			 raises one of her arms, showing off her chitinous armpit and sneering, [yui.speech(So, what'll it be, toy? You want me to sit on your face, or smother your mouth with my pits? I'm in a good mood today, so I'll let you choose...)]
		#ELSE
			 drops two of her hands down towards her groin and plays with the zip on her leather panties as she sneers, [yui.speech(Tell me that you want me to sit on your face, toy...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DOMINATION_FOOT_WORSHIP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As Yui continues pushing her gothic boot into your face, you find yourself moaning, [pc.speech(Please, Mistress Yui, I want to worship your feet...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(What a kinky little toy you are,)] Yui laughs, before reaching back to her spinneret and squirting out a stream of thick, sticky webbing. As she begins to elegantly run this thread out between her six hands, she suddenly kicks you down onto the ground, before stepping over you and sneering down, [yui.speech(Toys don't get to move, do they?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(No, Mistress Yui,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at you with her eight glowing eyes, Yui lets out another high-pitched laugh, before dropping down and attaching her sticky web to several points of your body. Shooting several other threads up at the metal frame of her stall, the small spider-girl starts pulling on her webbing, and before you can react, you find yourself being lifted off the ground and spun around over and over again in mid-air. Stopping your dizzying rotation with a forceful slap, Yui once again laughs and orders, [yui.speech(Try to move, toy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you try to move your [pc.arms] and [pc.legs], but quickly discover that they're completely wrapped up in strong, sticky webbing. Sadistically grinning at you as she watches you struggle, Yui pulls on a strand of webbing with two of her six arms, which causes you to tumble down to the floor. Dropping down and using her many limbs to reposition you into a kneeling pose, the small [yui.race] grabs a small, padded seat from under her counter and sits down on it. Kicking off her heavy, gothic boots to reveal her latex stockings, she lifts her feet and places them down onto your still-exposed [pc.hands].
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(Be a good toy for me, and I'll let you taste my bare feet later,)] she sneers, before sadistically pushing her stocking-clad feet down against your [pc.hands]. Swiping her riding crop down to slap your side, she orders, [yui.speech(Now get started, toy. Massage my feet.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Almost entirely unable to move, you really have no choice but to do exactly as Yui commands, and so for the next half an hour you massage the [yui.race]'s stocking-clad feet. During this time several customers come up to Yui's stall to purchase toys from her, and they all make derogatory comments on how pathetic you look as you stroke and squeeze your Mistress's feet.
	</p>
	<p>
		Eventually, Yui seems to have had enough of your massaging, and after delivering a quick smack to your side with her riding crop, she says, [yui.speech(You've been a good toy. Now, are you ready for your reward? Tell me that you'd like to lick my sweaty feet, and I'll let you have your fun...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DOMINATION_FOOT_WORSHIP_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Getting madly turned on at the thought of being able to orally worship this demonic spider-girl's feet, you tell her what she wants to hear, [pc.speech(Yes, Mistress Yui! Please, I want to lick your sweaty feet!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(Good toy...)] she says with a big smirk on her face. Tucking her thumbs into the top of her latex stockings, she slowly slides them down her legs, before pulling them off and revealing her shiny, chitin-coated feet. Having been encased in latex or such a length of time, they're coated in a fine layer of glistening sweat, and as Yui lifts them up to your face, she teases, [yui.speech(You really are such a dirty little toy, aren't you? You like your Mistress's feet being all hot and sweaty? Go on then, toy, have a good smell of them...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as Yui commands, and being unable to move away due to the fact that you're almost completely encased in her web cocoon, you take in a deep breath. Thanks to the fact that her feet are covered in an insect-like chitin, Yui's feet aren't nearly as smelly as you might have expected, although they do have a subtle, sweaty odour to them. Turned on at the thought of being able to worship these delicate, feminine feet, you do your best to lean forwards and kiss them. Letting out a laugh as she sees how eager you are, Yui gives you what you want, and sadistically pushes her feet into your face.
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(You like that, toy? Go on, lick them clean!)] she squeals. Clearly getting almost as turned on as you are, she reaches down between her legs and unzips her latex panties, before sliding them off and revealing her tight, dripping-wet pussy. Shaking her finger at you, she teases, [yui.speech(No, no, no. My tight, wet pussy isn't for you. You'll have to make do with servicing my feet.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Yui slides her fingers into her cunt and starts fingering herself, while at the same time pushing her sweaty feet into your face. Left with no other choice, you start licking and kissing your Mistress's feet, and as the salty taste of her sweat fills your mouth, you watch her slender fingers slide in and out of her drooling cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DOMINATION_ARMPIT_WORSHIP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As Yui glares down at you with her eight glowing-crimson eyes, you find yourself moaning, [pc.speech(Please, Mistress Yui, I want to worship your armpits...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(What a kinky little toy you are,)] Yui laughs, before reaching back to her spinneret and squirting out a stream of thick, sticky webbing. As she begins to elegantly run this thread out between her six hands, she suddenly kicks you down onto the ground, before stepping over you and sneering down, [yui.speech(Toys don't get to move, do they?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(No, Mistress Yui,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		Smirking down at you and biting her lip, Yui lets out another high-pitched laugh, before dropping down and attaching her sticky web to several points of your body. Shooting several other threads up at the metal frame of her stall, the small spider-girl starts pulling on her webbing, and before you can react, you find yourself being lifted off the ground and spun around over and over again in mid-air. Stopping your dizzying rotation with a forceful slap, Yui once again laughs and orders, [yui.speech(Try to move, toy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you try to move your [pc.arms] and [pc.legs], but quickly discover that they're completely wrapped up in strong, sticky webbing. Sadistically grinning at you as she watches you struggle, Yui pulls on a strand of webbing with two of her six arms, which causes you to stand up straight in front of her. Lifting one of her arms, she presents you with her sweaty armpit and sneers, [yui.speech(This is what you wanted, then? You filthy little toy...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		before you can reply, Yui sadistically pushes her sweaty armpit over your face, forcing you to breathe in the odour of her smelly pit. Using one of her other arms to swipe her riding crop down to slap your side, she orders, [yui.speech(Now get started, toy. Lick my pits clean.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Almost entirely unable to move, you really have no choice but to do exactly as Yui commands, and so for the next half an hour you're made to alternate between all six of the [yui.race]'s sweaty pits as you lick and kiss them clean. During this time several customers come up to Yui's stall to purchase toys from her, and they all make derogatory comments on how pathetic you look as you continue to orally service your Mistress's armpits.
	</p>
	<p>
		Eventually, Yui seems to get quite turned on by getting to dominate you in this fashion, and after delivering a quick smack to your side with her riding crop, she reaches down between her legs and unzips her latex panties, before sliding them off and revealing her tight, dripping-wet pussy. Shaking her finger at you, she teases, [yui.speech(No, no, no. My tight, wet pussy isn't for you. You'll have to make do with servicing my pits.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Yui slides her fingers into her cunt and starts fingering herself, while at the same time pushing her sweaty armpit into your face. Left with no other choice, you continue licking and kissing your Mistress's pit, and as the salty taste of her sweat fills your mouth, you look down to see her slender fingers slide in and out of her drooling cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DOMINATION_FACE_SITTING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As Yui glares down at you with her eight glowing-crimson eyes, you find yourself moaning, [pc.speech(Please, Mistress Yui, I want you to sit on my face...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(What a kinky little toy you are,)] Yui laughs, before reaching back to her spinneret and squirting out a stream of thick, sticky webbing. As she begins to elegantly run this thread out between her six hands, she suddenly kicks you down onto the ground, before stepping over you and sneering down, [yui.speech(Toys don't get to move, do they?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(No, Mistress Yui,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		Smirking down at you and biting her lip, Yui lets out another high-pitched laugh, before dropping down and attaching her sticky web to several points of your body. Shooting several other threads up at the metal frame of her stall, the small spider-girl starts pulling on her webbing, and before you can react, you find yourself being lifted off the ground and spun around over and over again in mid-air. Stopping your dizzying rotation with a forceful slap, Yui once again laughs and orders, [yui.speech(Try to move, toy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you try to move your [pc.arms] and [pc.legs], but quickly discover that they're completely wrapped up in strong, sticky webbing. Sadistically grinning at you as she watches you struggle, Yui grabs a padded bench from under her counter, before pulling on a strand of webbing with two of her six arms, which causes you to tumble down onto this seat. Using her many limbs to reposition you so that you're lying down on your back, the small [yui.race] steps over the top of you and roughly plants her latex panties down over your face.
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(Be a good toy for me, and I'll let you get a taste of me later,)] she sneers, before sadistically grinding her ass down against your mouth. Swiping her riding crop down to slap your side, she orders, [yui.speech(Now get started, toy. Lick my panties.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Almost entirely unable to move, you really have no choice but to do exactly as Yui commands, and so for the next half an hour you lick and kiss the [yui.race]'s latex panties. During this time several customers come up to Yui's stall to purchase toys from her, and they all make derogatory comments on how pathetic you look as your Mistress continues to grind her ass down over your face.
	</p>
	<p>
		Eventually, Yui seems to have had enough, and after delivering a quick smack to your side with her riding crop, she says,
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			[yui.speech(You've been a good toy. Now, are you ready for your reward? Tell me if you'd rather get a taste of my pussy or ass, and I'll let you have some real fun...)]
		#ELSE
			[yui.speech(You've been a good toy. Now, are you ready for your reward? Tell me how desperate you are to taste my pussy, and I'll let you have some real fun...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DOMINATION_FACE_SITTING_PUSSY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having endured Yui's latex panties being pressed down against your mouth for the past half an hour, you desperately plead, [pc.speech(Please, Mistress Yui, let me taste your pussy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a derisive laugh, the demonic spider-girl lifts her hips, before unzipping her latex panties and sliding them off. Looking up at her now-exposed groin, you see that there's a steady stream of slick girlcum tricking out of Yui's tight cunt, and as she sees what you're staring at, she teases, [yui.speech(Bet you've never seen a pussy as wet as mine, huh? You want a taste? Go on, toy, beg for it!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		As you open your mouth to start begging for a taste of your Mistress's pussy, she suddenly drops down onto your face with a loud, wet squelch. The copious amount of girlcum being produced by her hot cunt immediately squirts out all over you, and you let out [pc.a_moan+] as you start licking up every last drop your tongue can reach. Firmly planting her pussy down over your mouth, Yui squeals, [yui.speech(That's it, toy! ~Mmm!~ Get your tongue in my tight little pussy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you obediently start eating Yui out, you're vaguely aware of the fact that several passing shoppers have stopped to watch the show, and as they loudly comment on the lewd scene in front of them, Yui teases, [yui.speech(That's it, show the nice strangers what a good little toy you are!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DOMINATION_FACE_SITTING_ASSHOLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having endured Yui's latex panties being pressed down against your mouth for the past half an hour, you desperately plead, [pc.speech(Please, Mistress Yui, let me taste your ass!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a derisive laugh, the demonic spider-girl lifts her hips, before unzipping her latex panties and sliding them off. Looking up at her now-exposed groin, you see that there's a steady stream of slick girlcum tricking out of Yui's tight cunt, and as she sees what you're staring at, she drops one of her hands down to spread the slimy mixture over her tight asshole, teasing as she does so, [yui.speech(Bet you've never seen a pussy as wet as mine, huh? Regretting your decision to go for my ass? Well, too late, toy, my asshole's all you're going to be getting today! Now beg for it!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		As you open your mouth to start begging for a taste of your Mistress's ass, she suddenly drops down onto your face with a loud, wet squelch. The copious amount of girlcum being produced by her hot cunt immediately squirts out all over you, and you let out [pc.a_moan+] as you start licking up every last drop your tongue can reach. Firmly planting her asshole down over your mouth, Yui squeals, [yui.speech(That's it, toy! ~Mmm!~ Get your tongue in my ass!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you obediently start performing anilingus on Yui, you're vaguely aware of the fact that several passing shoppers have stopped to watch the show, and as they loudly comment on the lewd scene in front of them, Yui teases, [yui.speech(That's it, show the nice strangers what a good little toy you are!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_AFTER_DOMINATION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(sex.getSexTypeCount(yui, pc, sex.newSexType(ORIFICE_VAGINA, PENETRATION_TONGUE))>0)
		<p>
			Satisfied from her orgasms, Yui lets out one last moan and sighs, [yui.speech(You're good at eating pussy, toy. Now lick me clean.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifting her hips a little, the demonic spider-girl holds still as you obediently lick up every last drop of girlcum from around her still-quivering cunt. After you've finished, she uses a tissue to wipe herself completely clean, and only after pulling her latex panties back on does she think about releasing you from your cocoon.
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(sex.getSexTypeCount(yui, pc, sex.newSexType(ORIFICE_ANUS, PENETRATION_TONGUE))>0)
		<p>
			Satisfied from her orgasms, Yui lets out one last moan and sighs, [yui.speech(You're good at eating ass, toy. Now lick my cunt clean.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Lifting her hips a little, the demonic spider-girl holds still as you obediently lick up every last drop of girlcum from around her still-quivering cunt. After you've finished, she uses a tissue to wipe herself completely clean, and only after pulling her latex panties back on does she think about releasing you from your cocoon.
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(sex.getSexTypeCount(yui, pc, sex.newSexType(ORIFICE_ARMPITS, PENETRATION_TONGUE))>0)
		<p>
			Satisfied from her orgasms, Yui lets out one last moan and sighs, [yui.speech(You really are a dirty little toy, aren't you? Loving my sweaty pits like that... Now before you go, you're to lick my cunt clean.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With a few tugs on the strands of silk that are connected to your cocoon, the demonic spider-girl repositions you so that you're kneeling down in front of her tight, slimy pussy. Being given no say in the matter, you find yourself having to lick up every last drop of girlcum from around Yui's still-quivering cunt. After you've finished, she uses a tissue to wipe herself completely clean, and only after pulling her latex panties back on does she think about releasing you from your cocoon.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Satisfied from her orgasms, Yui lets out one last moan and sighs, [yui.speech(You really are a dirty little toy, aren't you? Loving my sweaty feet like that... Now before you go, you're to lick my cunt clean.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With a few tugs on the strands of silk that are connected to your cocoon, the demonic spider-girl repositions you so that you're kneeling down in front of her tight, slimy pussy. Being given no say in the matter, you find yourself having to lick up every last drop of girlcum from around Yui's still-quivering cunt. After you've finished, she uses a tissue to wipe herself completely clean, and only after pulling her panties, stockings and boots back on does she think about releasing you from your cocoon.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		[yui.speech(It would be fun to keep you as my toy,)] she muses with an evil smirk on her face, [yui.speech(but I've already got a few tied up and waiting to be played with back home. I suppose I'll let you go...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a flick of her wrists, the [yui.race] severs the webbing that's been binding your cocoon in place, and as the strands fall away from your body, you suddenly find yourself able to move freely again. Reaching under the counter, Yui produces a Faire ticket, and as she hands it to you, she says, [yui.speech(There you go, toy. It should really be reward enough just getting to be dominated by me, but the tourism board thinks otherwise... Now go on, back around to the other side of my counter.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_AFTER_DOMINATION_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as Mistress Yui says, you [pc.step] back around to the other side of the counter. Quickly clearing up the remains of the cocoon which you were encased in just moments ago, the sadistic spider-girl crosses all six of her arms, and with a sly smirk on her face, asks, [yui.speech(So, would you like to buy something, 'toy'? Oh, and don't get too addicted to being dominated by me; I limit these little sessions to one per person per day.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Ball gag: -->
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_BALLGAG"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting Yui to demonstrate how to use a ballgag, you give her one of your Faire tickets and make your request. Narrowing her eight, glowing-crimson eyes, a sadistic smirk settles on the demonic spider-girl's face, and with a swift crack of her riding crop, she orders, [yui.speech(Come around to my side of the counter, toy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] around to the other side of the stall's counter. Reaching back to the spinneret at the tip of her large, spider-like tail, Yui starts to pull out a long, sticky silken thread. Without any warning, she starts patting this sticky thread onto your body, before grabbing hold of you and spinning you around. Before you know what's happening, Yui's tightly wrapped you up in a cocoon, and after pulling on a couple of threads, she lifts you into the air so that your [pc.ass+] is pointing towards the open side of the stall.
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(That's a good toy,)] she sneers as she steps around in front of you. Holding up a hot-pink ball gag, she places four of her arms down on her hips and explains in a mock-patronising voice, [yui.speech(Ball gags are very useful for keeping toys quiet. Open wide, so that I can demonstrate this to you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having specifically asked for this, you're more than willing to obey Yui's command. Opening your mouth, you stay still as the demonic spider-girl fastens the ball gag into place. Stepping around behind you, Yui lifts her riding crop and uses it to deliver a sharp smack to your rear end. Your surprised cry is almost completely muffled by the gag that's now in your mouth, and as she hears that it's working, Yui teases, [yui.speech(See? You're almost completely unable to make any protests while wearing that. Now be a good toy and raise your ass so that I can give you a good public whipping and further demonstrate the gag's effectiveness.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_BALLGAG_OBEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Happy to do as you're told, you muster what little amount of control you're left with within Yui's cocoon and obediently raise your ass towards the passing shoppers behind you. Stepping around beside you, the sadistic spider-girl uses her riding crop to deliver another sharp, stinging slap to your exposed butt, and as she hears your cry being muffled by the ball gag that's in your mouth, she teases, [yui.speech(Go on, toy, scream and squirm all you want... ~Mmm!~ I'm going to enjoy humiliating you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Yui starts using her riding crop to relentlessly swat your ass, and as her painful blows alternate between your cheeks, you can't help but [pc.moan] and cry out into your ball gag. Your public display of complete submission soon starts to draw a crowd, and you hear several shoppers loudly laughing and commenting on your predicament. This public attention suits Yui's business well, as her demonstration leads to several shoppers asking to buy the same style of ball gag that you're currently wearing.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_BALLGAG_RESIST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unwilling to do as you're told, you muster what little amount of control you're left with within Yui's cocoon and try to move your ass away from the passing shoppers behind you. Stepping around beside you, the sadistic spider-girl uses her riding crop to deliver another sharp, stinging slap to your exposed butt, and as she hears your cry being muffled by the ball gag that's in your mouth, she teases, [yui.speech(Did you really think that you'd avoid your fate, toy? Go on, scream and squirm all you want... ~Mmm!~ I'm going to enjoy humiliating you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Yui tugs on a couple of threads, and you feel your ass being lifted up against your will. Letting out an amused giggle, the demonic spider-girl starts using her riding crop to relentlessly swat your ass, and as her painful blows alternate between your cheeks, you can't help but [pc.moan] and cry out into your ball gag. Your public display of complete submission soon starts to draw a crowd, and you hear several shoppers loudly laughing and commenting on your predicament. This public attention suits Yui's business well, as her demonstration leads to several shoppers asking to buy the same style of ball gag that you're currently wearing.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_BALLGAG_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After a good fifteen minutes of being publicly whipped, with your only respite being the brief pauses as Yui deals with interested customers, the [yui.race] lets out a satisfied sigh and declares, [yui.speech(I've had my fun, toy. Play time's over.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a level of finesse clearly having been gained from performing this routine countless times before, Yui swipes her fingers this way and that, severing the threads holding you in place. As the cocoon falls away from your body, you find yourself tumbling down onto the floor, but with the ballgag still locked in place, you're only able to let out a muffled yelp.
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(Your little performance helped me sell lots of ballgags. As a reward, I'll let you keep the one that you're wearing,)] Yui says, before swiping her riding crop down to deliver one final strike to your still-exposed ass. As you stand up on trembling [pc.legs], the sadistic spider-girl flashes you a wicked grin and snaps, [yui.speech(Now get back to the other side of the counter.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Chastity: -->
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_CHASTITY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting Yui to demonstrate the proper use of a chastity cage, you hand over one of your Faire tickets and tell her what you'd like. An amused smirk settles on the spider-girl's face as she hears what it is you're after, and she narrows her eight, glowing-crimson eyes at you as she orders, [yui.speech(Come around to my side of the counter, toy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] around to the other side of the stall's counter. Reaching back to the spinneret at the tip of her large, spider-like tail, Yui starts to pull out a long, sticky silken thread. Without any warning, she starts patting this sticky thread onto your body, before grabbing hold of you and spinning you around. Before you know what's happening, Yui's tightly wrapped you up in a cocoon, and after pulling on a couple of threads, she lifts you up off the ground.
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(That's a good toy,)] she sneers as she steps around to the side of you. Holding up a hot-pink chastity cage, her eyes light up in sadistic delight as she uses her riding crop to give you a quick smack, before using her threads to pull you towards her and tease, [yui.speech(Now let's see what I've got to work with...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping her hands down to your groin, the demonic spider-girl quickly gains access to your cock, and
		#IF(pc.getPenisRawSizeValue() < PENIS_LENGTH_TWO_AVERAGE.getMedianValue())
			 as she sees how small it is, she lets out a cruel, mocking laugh. Flicking your cock and looking down at it with a look of disgusted amusement on her face, she sneers, [yui.speech(How utterly pathetic... You'd never be able to satisfy anyone with this little thing... Now hold still so I can lock it up. I can't wait to see how you'll squirm and beg for release...)]
		#ELSEIF(pc.getPenisRawSizeValue() < PENIS_LENGTH_FOUR_HUGE.getMedianValue())
			 as she sees its above-average size, she lets out a disapproving tut. Flicking your cock and looking down at it with a look of disgusted amusement on her face, she sneers, [yui.speech(I bet you actually think your cock's big, don't you? Trust me, this thing's not worth being proud of... Now hold still so I can lock it up. I can't wait to see how you'll squirm and beg for release...)]
		#ELSE
			 as she sees how big it is, she lets out an approving hum. Flicking your cock and looking down at it with a look of disgusted amusement on her face, she sneers, [yui.speech(You're quite big, I'll admit... That doesn't make it any less pathetic, though... Now hold still so I can lock it up. I can't wait to see how you'll squirm and beg for release...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_CHASTITY_SUBMIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Happy to do as she says, you hold still while Yui clips the bright pink chastity cage into place over your cock. Letting out an amused laugh, the demonic spider-girl uses her riding crop to deliver a quick smack to your side, before teasing, [yui.speech(Now to demonstrate to you the real purpose of a chastity cage...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_CHASTITY_RESIST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unwilling to do as she says, you squirm about and try to prevent Yui from locking you into chastity. Letting out an angry huff, the demonic spider-girl pulls on a couple of threads and tightens the cocoon that's binding you in place. Completely and utterly immobilised, you're unable to do anything more to prevent Yui from clipping the bright pink chastity cage into place over your cock. With a mocking sneer on her face, the demonic spider-girl uses her riding crop to deliver a series of quick, sharp smacks to your side, before teasing, [yui.speech(You really thought you could stop me from using you in any way I desire? Silly toy... Now I shall demonstrate to you the real purpose of a chastity cage...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_CHASTITY_LOCKED_UP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Reaching down to her groin, Yui unzips her latex panties and slowly slides them down her legs before completely taking them off. As she exposes her tight pussy, you see that a copious amount of slimy girlcum is literally dripping from it, and as she sees you staring, she laughs and teases, [yui.speech(What's the matter, toy? You want to get a closer look at my hot little cunt?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply, the spider-girl manipulates her threads and suddenly tilts you back and drops you down towards the ground, stopping your fall just before you hit the floor. Stepping forwards and straddling your face, Yui presents you with her sopping-wet pussy. As you look up at her tight, wet cunt, the spider-girl reaches down to tease her fingers over her labia, which causes a significant amount of slimy girlcum to drool out and drip down all over your face. Almost immediately, you feel your cock straining against your chastity cage as it tries to get an erection, which causes you to let out a frustrated [pc.moan].
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(Oh, you're trying to get hard already? I haven't even started yet! How pathetic...)] Yui sadistically teases, [yui.speech(Seeing as you're so desperate already, I suppose I should move on to the main performance...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the spider-girl moves away from your face, and down towards your groin. Dropping down over your caged cock, she once again starts teasing her fingers over her pussy, which causes yet more girlcum to leak out and drip down directly onto your caged cock. As you feel the hot, slimy liquid drooling down over your groin, you let out an incredibly frustrated whine, which causes Yui to laugh, [yui.speech(See, toy? This is what a cage is for; I can tease you as much as I want, and there's never any threat of having your disgusting cock being shoved inside of me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping her hips down, Yui presses her hot, wet cunt down against your chastity cage, before starting to grind up and down over it. As her hot juices continue to leak down all over your groin, she glares down at you with her eight, glowing-crimson eyes and sadistically teases, [yui.speech(Just imagine... If you weren't caged, your cock would be thrusting inside of my hot, wet pussy right now... ~Mmm!~ Can you imagine it, toy? Imagine how it would feel to have my tight cunt gripping down around your hard cock... ~Mmm!~ But as you're caged, all you can do is imagine it... You're never going to be allowed to fuck my pussy, even though it's practically kissing your cock and begging for you to be inside of it...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_CHASTITY_LOCKED_UP_ENDURE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to displease Mistress Yui, you do your very best to endure her teasing and manage to prevent yourself from instinctively bucking your hips up and trying to hump her. After letting out a mocking laugh as she sees how hard you're trying not to give in to your desires, the demonic spider-girl decides to take advantage of your predicament to drum up some business, and after quickly turning around so as to move into a reverse cow-girl position, she calls out to the passing shoppers, [yui.speech(Step up, don't be shy! Come and see how fun it is to play with chastity cages!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_CHASTITY_LOCKED_UP_HUMP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to hold back any longer, you give in to Mistress Yui's teasing and start to instinctively buck your hips up in order to try and hump her. After letting out a mocking laugh as she sees that you've given in to your desires, the demonic spider-girl decides to take advantage of your predicament to drum up some business, and after quickly turning around so as to move into a reverse cow-girl position, she calls out to the passing shoppers, [yui.speech(Step up, don't be shy! Come and see how fun it is to play with chastity cages!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_CHASTITY_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As the sadistic spider-girl continues to grind her dripping cunt over your caged cock, you hear the animated chatter of numerous members of the public getting louder. Before long, there's a sizeable crowd gathered around Yui's stall, and as they watch, they loudly laugh and comment on your predicament. This public attention suits Yui's business well, as her demonstration leads to several of these shoppers asking to buy the same style of chastity cage that you're currently wearing.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a good fifteen minutes of being publicly humiliated in this fashion, and with your only respite from the teasing being the brief pauses as Yui deals with interested customers, the [yui.race] lets out a satisfied sigh and declares, [yui.speech(I've had my fun, toy. Play time's over.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a level of finesse clearly having been gained from performing this routine countless times before, Yui swipes her fingers this way and that, severing the threads holding you in place. As the cocoon falls away from your body, you find yourself tumbling down onto the floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(Your little performance helped me sell lots of cages. As a reward, I'll let you keep the one that you're wearing,)] Yui says, before swiping her riding crop down to deliver a sharp swat to your side. As you stand up on trembling [pc.legs], the sadistic spider-girl flashes you a wicked grin and snaps, [yui.speech(Now get back to the other side of the counter.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Dildo: -->
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_DILDO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting Yui to demonstrate the proper use of a dildo, you hand over one of your Faire tickets and tell her what you'd like. An amused smirk settles on the spider-girl's face as she hears what it is you're after, and she narrows her eight, glowing-crimson eyes at you as she orders, [yui.speech(Come around to my side of the counter, toy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] around to the other side of the stall's counter. Reaching back to the spinneret at the tip of her large, spider-like tail, Yui starts to pull out a long, sticky silken thread. Without any warning, she starts patting this sticky thread onto your body, before grabbing hold of you and spinning you around. Before you know what's happening, Yui's tightly wrapped you up in a cocoon, and after pulling on a couple of threads, she lifts you up off the ground.
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(That's a good toy,)] she sneers as she steps around to the side of you. Holding up a hot-pink dildo, her eyes light up in sadistic delight as she uses her riding crop to give you a quick smack, before using her threads to pull you towards her and tease, [yui.speech(Now let's see what I've got to work with...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Manipulating her threads, the demonic spider-girl twists you
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			 around and pulls your legs apart,
		#ELSE
			 around,
		#ENDIF
		 exposing your pussy not only to her, but also to any member of the public who so happens to be walking past her stall. Letting out a little laugh, Yui reaches up and spreads your [pc.labia+], before commenting,
		#IF(pc.hasHymen())
			 [yui.speech(Ooh, what's this? You've still got your hymen? What a dirty little virgin, wanting your first penetration to be in public like this...)]
		#ELSE
			 [yui.speech(Hmm, not bad, toy... I can't wait to stuff this dildo deep into your dirty little cunt...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With two of her six hands still being used to keep your labia spread wide, Yui lifts the pink dildo up to your pussy and starts to tease its head over your [pc.pussy+]. Moaning in anticipation, you can't help but lift your hips a little as the demonic spider-girl continues to tease you with the promise of penetration. Giving your exposed ass a quick smack, Yui starts to push the dildo into your [pc.pussy+],
		#IF(pc.hasHymen())
			 laughing in sadistic delight as she tears through your hymen and causes you to let out a pained wail.
		#ELSE
			 laughing in delight as she causes you to let out [pc.a_moan+].
		#ENDIF
		 Stopping with the dildo only half-inserted into your [pc.pussy+], she demands, [yui.speech(Now push back, toy. Take it deep into your slutty pussy!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_DILDO_PUSH_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Driven to please Mistress Yui by the incredible feeling of the hot pink dildo being pushed half-way into your hot pussy, you desperately push back and force the rest of the toy into your hungry cunt. As you squeal and moan in pleasure, the spider-girl teases, [yui.speech(That's a good toy! Take it deep!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she starts to pull the dildo back out of your pussy, before suddenly and roughly shoving it back in as deep as it will go. Letting out a wild [pc.moan], you buck your hips in time with Yui's movements as she starts to repeatedly pump the dildo in and out of your quivering cunt. Sneering in sadistic delight, she delivers a sharp slap to your exposed ass, before turning to the passing members of the public behind you and calling out, [yui.speech(Step up, don't be shy! Come and see how fun it is to play with dildos!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_DILDO_PULL_AWAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to take it any deeper, you try to pull away from the dildo that's been pushed half-way into your hot pussy. Letting out an annoyed tut as she sees that you're refusing to obey her commands, Mistress Yui pushes forwards and roughly forces the rest of the toy into your hungry cunt. As you squeal in surprise, the spider-girl sneers, [yui.speech(Bad toy! You really think you get to choose what happens?! Your dirty pussy's going to take this dildo as deep as it can, and there's nothing you can do to stop it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she starts to pull the dildo back out of your pussy, before suddenly and roughly shoving it back in as deep as it will go. Letting out a wild [pc.moan], you desperately try, and fail, to pull away from Yui as she starts to repeatedly pump the dildo in and out of your quivering cunt. Sneering in sadistic delight, she delivers a sharp slap to your exposed ass, before turning to the passing members of the public behind you and calling out, [yui.speech(Step up, don't be shy! Come and see how fun it is to play with dildos!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_DILDO_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As the sadistic spider-girl continues to pump the pink dildo in and out of your [pc.pussy+], you hear the animated chatter of numerous members of the public coming from somewhere behind you. Before long, there's a sizeable crowd gathered around Yui's stall, and as they watch, they loudly laugh and comment on your predicament. This public attention suits Yui's business well, as her demonstration leads to several of these shoppers asking to buy the same style of dildo that's being shoved deep into your exposed cunt.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a good fifteen minutes of being publicly humiliated in this fashion, and with your only respite from the teasing being the brief pauses as Yui deals with interested customers, the [yui.race] lets out a satisfied sigh and declares, [yui.speech(I've had my fun, toy. Play time's over.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a level of finesse clearly having been gained from performing this routine countless times before, Yui swipes her fingers this way and that, severing the threads holding you in place. As the cocoon falls away from your body, you find yourself tumbling down onto the floor, and with a gasp you realise that the hot pink dildo is still completely inserted into your pussy.
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(Your little performance helped me sell lots of dildos. As a reward, I'll let you keep the one that you've been enjoying,)] Yui says, before swiping her riding crop down to deliver a sharp swat to your side. As you stand up on trembling [pc.legs], you realise that the dildo that's still inserted into your pussy is carrying a sealing enchantment, for as you reach down and take hold of it, you find that you're unable to pull it out of your abused cunt. Letting out an amused laugh as she watches you try to remove the dildo, the sadistic spider-girl sneers, [yui.speech(You won't be getting rid of it in a hurry! Now get back to the other side of the counter.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Anal beads: -->
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_ANAL_BEADS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting Yui to demonstrate the proper use of anal beads, you hand over one of your Faire tickets and tell her what you'd like. An amused smirk settles on the spider-girl's face as she hears what it is you're after, and she narrows her eight, glowing-crimson eyes at you as she orders, [yui.speech(Come around to my side of the counter, toy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] around to the other side of the stall's counter. Reaching back to the spinneret at the tip of her large, spider-like tail, Yui starts to pull out a long, sticky silken thread. Without any warning, she starts patting this sticky thread onto your body, before grabbing hold of you and spinning you around. Before you know what's happening, Yui's tightly wrapped you up in a cocoon, and after pulling on a couple of threads, she lifts you up off the ground.
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(That's a good toy,)] she sneers as she steps around to the side of you. Holding up a chain of hot-pink anal beads, her eyes light up in sadistic delight as she uses her riding crop to give you a quick smack, before using her threads to pull you towards her and tease, [yui.speech(Now let's see what I've got to work with...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Manipulating her threads, the demonic spider-girl twists you 
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			 around and pulls your legs apart,
		#ELSE
			 around,
		#ENDIF
		 exposing your ass not only to her, but also to any member of the public who so happens to be walking past her stall. Letting out a little laugh, Yui reaches up and spreads your cheeks, before commenting, [yui.speech(Hmm, not bad, toy... I can't wait to stuff these beads deep into your hot ass...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With two of her six hands still being used to keep your ass cheeks spread wide, Yui lifts the pink beads up to your rear end and starts to tease the first of them over your [pc.asshole+]. [pc.Moaning] in anticipation, you can't help but lift your hips a little as the demonic spider-girl continues to tease you with the promise of penetration. Giving your exposed ass a quick smack, Yui starts to push the first bead into your [pc.asshole+], laughing in delight as she causes you to let out [pc.a_moan+]. Stopping with only the first bead inserted into your [pc.ass+], she demands, [yui.speech(Relax, toy. Stop clenching your ass so that I can shove all of them inside!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_ANAL_BEADS_RELAX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Driven to please Mistress Yui by the incredible feeling of the first bead being pushed into your ass, you do as you're told and relax your asshole. As you do this, the spider-girl starts to push the next bead into your [pc.asshole+], teasing, [yui.speech(That's a good toy! Take them all!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she continues pushing bead after bead into your ass, causing you to let out a series of [pc.moans+]. Sneering in sadistic delight after inserting the last of the beads, Yui delivers a sharp slap to your exposed ass, before turning to the passing members of the public behind you and calling out, [yui.speech(Step up, don't be shy! Come and see how fun it is to play with anal beads!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_ANAL_BEADS_CLENCH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to take any more of the beads, you try to pull away from Yui and firmly clench your asshole shut. Letting out an annoyed tut as she sees that you're refusing to obey her commands, Mistress Yui pushes forwards and roughly forces the next bead into your reluctant asshole. As you squeal in surprise, the spider-girl sneers, [yui.speech(Bad toy! You really think you get to choose what happens?! Your ass is going to take all of these beads, and there's nothing you can do to stop it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she starts to force bead after bead into your ass, causing you to let out a series of [pc.moans+]. Sneering in sadistic delight after forcefully inserting the last of the beads, Yui delivers a sharp slap to your exposed ass, before turning to the passing members of the public behind you and calling out, [yui.speech(Step up, don't be shy! Come and see how fun it is to play with anal beads!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_DEMONSTRATION_ANAL_BEADS_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As the sadistic spider-girl starts to slowly pull the beads out of your [pc.asshole+], you hear the animated chatter of numerous members of the public coming from somewhere behind you. Before long, there's a sizeable crowd gathered around Yui's stall, and as they watch the spider-girl start to push the beads back inside of your ass, they loudly laugh and comment on your predicament. This public attention suits Yui's business well, as her demonstration leads to several of these shoppers asking to buy the same style of beads that are being shoved deep into your exposed asshole.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a good fifteen minutes of being publicly humiliated in this fashion, and with your only respite from the teasing being the brief pauses as Yui deals with interested customers, the [yui.race] lets out a satisfied sigh and declares, [yui.speech(I've had my fun, toy. Play time's over.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a level of finesse clearly having been gained from performing this routine countless times before, Yui swipes her fingers this way and that, severing the threads holding you in place. As the cocoon falls away from your body, you find yourself tumbling down onto the floor, and with a gasp you realise that the hot pink anal beads are still completely inserted into your ass.
	</p>
	<p>
		[yui.speech(Your little performance helped me sell lots of beads. As a reward, I'll let you keep the ones that you've been enjoying,)] Yui says, before swiping her riding crop down to deliver a sharp swat to your side. As you stand up on trembling [pc.legs], you realise that the beads that are still inserted into your ass are carrying a sealing enchantment, for as you reach down and take hold of the exposed end of them, you find that you're unable to pull them out of your abused asshole. Letting out an amused laugh as she watches you try to remove the beads, the sadistic spider-girl sneers, [yui.speech(You won't be getting rid of those in a hurry! Now get back to the other side of the counter.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOYS_AFTER_DEMONSTRATION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, and with the demonstration toy still in your possession, you [pc.step] back around to the other side of Yui's counter. Playfully weaving a strand of her web between all six of her hands, the sadistic spider-girl flashes you a devious grin and asks, [yui.speech(So, what do you want now? I only do one of those demonstrations per day, so if you want some more fun, you'll have to come back tomorrow...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking over the display of sex toys that are arrayed across the stall's counter, you wonder whether to buy anything from the demonic spider-girl or turn around and take your leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Kazik's 'Golden Treasures' stall: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=19)
		<p>
			As it's well past closing time, all of the stalls in the Farmer's Market have been packed up and taken away. As a result, there's nothing for you to do here except head back into Elis...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(kazik.isPlayerKnowsName())
			#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
				<p>
					As it's past closing time, you see that Kazik is busily packing his stall away. Not wanting to trouble him, you decide to leave him to it and head back into the Farmer's Market...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					You once again find yourself approaching the jewellery stall, 'Golden Treasures', and you see that the handsome ferret-boy, Kazik, is once again standing behind the counter with his arms crossed.
				#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(kazik))
						#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(kazik))
							 As he sees you approaching, he immediately notices your swollen belly, and after taking a drag on the cigarette which he must have lit just before you arrived, he asks, [kazik.speech(You got knocked up after I finished inside of you? Come here, let me have a feel.)]
						#ELSE
							 As he sees you approaching, he immediately notices your swollen belly, and after taking a drag on the cigarette which he must have lit just before you arrived, he asks, [kazik.speech(Still pregnant with our kids? Come here, let me have a feel.)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
					<p>
						Replying in the affirmative, you [pc.step] forwards and present Kazik with your pregnant bump. Reaching over the counter, he gently runs one of his furry hands over your tummy, before pulling back and flashing you a charming smile. Exhaling another cloud of smoke that quickly dissipates into the air, he reveals, [kazik.speech(I love knocking hot babes like you up... Anyway, what're you here for? Wanting to buy something, or did you just want to check in with the father of your kids? Oh, and if you've got a Faire ticket to trade in, I guess I could also cast a spell for you.)]
					</p>
				#ELSE
						 As he sees you approaching, he takes a long drag on the cigarette which he must have lit just before you arrived, before calling out, [kazik.speech(Hi, [pc.name]. What're you here for? Wanting to buy something, or you got a Faire ticket to trade in to see me cast a spell?)]
					</p>
				#ENDIF
				<p>
					Continuing to casually smoke, the ferret-boy waits to hear what it is you want...
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=18)
				<p>
					As it's past closing time, you see a handsome ferret-boy busily packing his stall away in this area. Not wanting to trouble him, you decide to leave him to it and head back into the Farmer's Market...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Although the stall before you is definitely one of the smallest you've seen throughout the Farmer's Market, you find yourself drawn towards it due to the interesting assortment of jewellery and small items of clothing that are scattered across its counter. Although a sign hanging from its orange canvas awning declares this stall to be called 'Golden Treasures', only a few of the goods on offer actually look to be made out of gold.
				</p>
				<p>
					The owner of this stall is standing behind the counter with his arms crossed, and takes the form of a strikingly-handsome greater ferret-boy. Sporting a black leather jacket, navy-blue jeans, and a pair of aviators, he looks like some kind of biker, although as motor vehicles don't exist in this reality, his fashion sense must have come from somewhere else. Tapping a cigarette out of an already opened pack, he lights it up and takes a deep drag, before slowly exhaling and casting his [kazik.eyeColour] eyes over in your direction.
				</p>
				<p>
					[kazik.speech(See something you like?)] he calls out in a deep voice. Flashing you a smile, he beckons you forwards, and after taking another drag on his cigarette, he says, [kazik.speech(If you're looking for jewellery, then this is the place. What's your name? I haven't seen you around before.)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After greeting this ferret-boy and giving him your name,
		#IF(pc.getSexualOrientation().isAttractedToMasculine())
			 you feel your heart skip a beat as he flashes you one of the most charming smiles you've ever seen and
		#ELSE
			 he flashes you a charming smile and
		#ENDIF
		 reveals, [kazik.speech(I'm Kazik, pleased to meet you, [pc.name]. Say... You know how to use the arcane, don't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Surprised to hear this question, you cautiously confirm that you do indeed know how to use the arcane, before asking Kazik how he could tell. With the hint of a smirk on his face, he explains, [kazik.speech(I spent five years studying at the arcane university down at Thinis, so I'm able to sense when someone's got a strong arcane affinity. I know, I know, I don't look like the typical arcane user, do I?)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking like a rebellious biker, this ferret-boy doesn't give off any impression of being an accomplished practitioner of the arcane, and so you honestly respond to his question by telling him that you'd never have known. Letting out a deep chuckle, he takes another drag on his cigarette and reveals, [kazik.speech(I enchant some of the stuff I've got here for sale myself. The Elis tourism board sure were happy to find out about my skills, and as part of the contract for running this stall, I have to perform a spell demonstration to anyone who gives me one of their 'Faire' tickets. I also give one of those tickets out to anyone who buys enchanted stuff from me, so if you want to see a spell being fired off, you can buy one of the enchanted items I've got for sale.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Gesturing down to the items scattered over the counter before him, Kazik takes another drag on his cigarette and waits to hear if you'll want to buy anything or trade in a ticket for a spell demonstration...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_TRANSACTION_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you move to take a closer look at what Kazik has for sale, he reminds you, [kazik.speech(If you buy one of my enchanted items, I'll give you a Faire ticket.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_TRANSACTION_NO_TICKET"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your flames in exchange for the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0], Kazik says, [kazik.speech(Thanks for the business, [pc.name]. Although as that wasn't an enchanted item, I can't give you a Faire ticket...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_TRANSACTION_TICKET"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your flames in exchange for the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0], Kazik hands you a Faire ticket and says, [kazik.speech(Thanks for the business, [pc.name]. Here's one of the tickets I've been given to hand out. You can trade it in with me if you want a spell demonstration...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting Kazik to demonstrate his arcane abilities, you give him one of your Faire tickets and ask him to cast a spell for you. Tearing the ticket in half and discarding it in a bin beneath his counter, the handsome ferret-boy asks, [kazik.speech(What spell would you like to see? I can cast 'Fireball', 'Flash', 'Ice Shard', and 'Rain Cloud'.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_kazik_arcane_cast))
			Knowing that Kazik can also cast 'Arcane Arousal', you open your mouth to ask him about that one, but he anticipates your question and states, [kazik.speech(No, I'm not casting any more arcane spells today. Perhaps tomorrow. Now which one of the four I said would you like to see?)]
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_market_kazik_arcane))
			Knowing that Kazik can also cast an arcane spell, you open your mouth to ask him about that one, but he anticipates your question and states, [kazik.speech(Yes, I know, I can cast 'Arcane Arousal' as well, but that's really not a responsible thing for me to be doing, is it? Now which one of the four I said would you like to see?)]
		#ELSE
			Thinking that Kazik is holding something back, you ask him if those are all the spells he knows, to which he states, [kazik.speech(I do know an arcane spell as well, but it's not suitable for a demonstration. Now which one of the four I said would you like to see?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_FIREBALL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be fun to see Kazik cast 'Fireball', you tell him that you'd like him to perform that one. Stepping around from behind his counter, the ferret-boy calls out to the surrounding shoppers, [kazik.speech(Gather around! Thanks to [pc.name] here, you've got an opportunity to see an arcane fireball! Come on, don't be shy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly wanting to make the most of this event in order to drum up business, Kazik spends the next couple of minutes calling for members of the public to stop and watch his performance. After about two dozen shoppers have gathered around in a semicircle, the ferret-boy starts the show, and with a series of fancy steps and swirling hand movements, you see the distinctive orange glow of arcane fire start to materialise around his right arm. Drawing out the incantation to create as much of a spectacle as possible, Kazik slowly builds up the arcane energy around his arm, before focusing it into a huge ball of roiling flames.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(Now for the grand finale!)] the handsome ferret-boy shouts, before thrusting his arm skywards and launching the massive fireball directly up into the sky. You and the rest of the crowd watch as this incandescent arcane maelstrom shoots off towards the heavens, and a collective gasp rings out as, after travelling high up over Elis, the fireball explodes in a fantastic, dazzling array of sparks and swirls. As the arcane manifestation fades away, the crowd breaks out in applause, and Kazik takes a small bow before stepping back around to the other side of his counter.
	</p>
	<p>
		Flashing you a confident smile, he asks, [kazik.speech(So, how was that?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_FLASH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be fun to see Kazik cast 'Flash', you tell him that you'd like him to perform that one. Nodding his head, he says, [kazik.speech(A fully-powered flash isn't a pleasant thing to witness, so I'll cast a few of them at a fraction of their usual strength. It's not the most impressive spell I'm capable of, but it's still a bit of fun.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the ferret-boy starts the show, and with a series of exaggerated hand movements, you see the distinctive orange glow of arcane fire start to materialise around both of his arms. Drawing out the incantation to create as much of a spectacle as possible, Kazik slowly builds up the arcane fire around his arms, before starting to release it in tiny, concentrated bursts of energy. The resulting sparkles and flashes remind you of the type of hand-held sparkler associated with fireworks, and as the ferret-boy continues to produce a crackling series of flashes, several passing shoppers stop to watch.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(Now for the grand finale!)] Kazik shouts, before thrusting his arms skywards and launching his remaining arcane energy into the air. You and the rest of the shoppers watch as this arcane fire shoots up and bursts into an impressive shower of multicoloured flashes. As the arcane manifestation fades away, the people around you break out in applause, and Kazik takes a small bow before crossing his arms and smirking at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(So, how was that?)] he asks.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ICE_SHARD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be fun to see Kazik cast 'Ice Shard', you tell him that you'd like him to perform that one. Stepping around from behind his counter, the ferret-boy calls out to the surrounding shoppers, [kazik.speech(Gather around! Thanks to [pc.name] here, you've got an opportunity to see an arcane ice shard! Come on, don't be shy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly wanting to make the most of this event in order to drum up business, Kazik spends the next couple of minutes calling for members of the public to stop and watch his performance. After about two dozen shoppers have gathered around in a semicircle, the ferret-boy starts the show, and with a series of fancy steps and swirling hand movements, you see the distinctive light blue glow of arcane ice start to materialise around his right arm. Drawing out the incantation to create as much of a spectacle as possible, Kazik slowly builds up the arcane energy around his arm, before focusing it into a huge, javelin-like spike of glistening ice.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(Now for the grand finale!)] the handsome ferret-boy shouts, before thrusting his arm skywards and launching the massive shard of ice directly up into the sky. You and the rest of the crowd watch as this freezing arcane projectile shoots off towards the heavens, and a collective gasp rings out as, after travelling high up over Elis, the ice shard explodes in a fantastic, dazzling array of water vapour and ice crystals. As the arcane manifestation fades away, the crowd breaks out in applause, and Kazik takes a small bow before stepping back around to the other side of his counter.
	</p>
	<p>
		Flashing you a confident smile, he asks, [kazik.speech(So, how was that?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_RAIN_CLOUD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be fun to see Kazik cast 'Rain Cloud', you tell him that you'd like him to perform that one. Nodding his head, he says, [kazik.speech(This is the least impressive spell I can cast, but I'll see if I can put on a show for you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the ferret-boy starts casting the spell, and with a series of exaggerated hand movements, you see the distinctive light blue glow of arcane water start to materialise around both of his arms. Drawing out the incantation to create as much of a spectacle as possible, Kazik slowly builds up the arcane water around his arms, before starting to release it in a concentrated burst of energy. The maelstrom of twisting clouds which form before you looks like a miniature hurricane, and as the ferret-boy continues to produce this localised atmospheric anomaly, several passing shoppers stop to watch.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(Now let's get it started!)] Kazik shouts, before thrusting his arms skywards and launching his remaining arcane energy into the air. You and the rest of the shoppers watch as this tiny cloud formation suddenly starts to produce multicoloured rain, which falls down to form a rainbow before heavily splashing on the ground. After about thirty seconds of this sustained miniature downpour, the arcane manifestation fades away, and the people around you break out in applause. Taking a small bow, Kazik crosses his arms and smirks at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(So, how was that?)] he asks.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_REVEAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious to know more about Kazik's knowledge of arcane spells, you ask him exactly which one he knows. Shaking his head, he flatly states, [kazik.speech(I already told you; it's not suitable for a demonstration. Just pick one of the spells I named already.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not taking no for an answer, you ask him why this mysterious spell can't be demonstrated. Lowering his aviators and glaring at you for a moment, Kazik lets out a sigh and reveals, [kazik.speech(Fine. I know how to cast 'Arcane Arousal', and it's not suitable as I need to cast it on a person for it to work. I don't want you getting so turned on that you start masturbating right here in front of my stall or something. It'd be bad for business if people saw that.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Satisfied with Kazik's answer, you push him a little further by asking him exactly what would happen if he were to cast it on you. Letting out a short laugh, he replies,
		#IF(pc.isFeminine())
			 [kazik.speech(You're a persistent one... Fine, I'll tell you; if I cast arcane arousal on you then you'd get an overwhelming urge to have sex. You'd either have to spend a while really focusing on calming down, or, more likely, beg me to have sex with you. Thing is, you're kind of hot, so if that happened then who knows what we'd end up doing together...)]
		#ELSE
			 [kazik.speech(You're a persistent one... Fine, I'll tell you; if I cast arcane arousal on you then you'd get an overwhelming urge to have sex. You'd either have to spend a while really focusing on calming down, or, more likely, beg me to have sex with you. I'm only into girls, so you'd have to deal with it yourself.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With all of his secrets revealed, Kazik impatiently taps his foot on the ground and asks for the last time, [kazik.speech(So, what spell do you want me to cast?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_CAST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Flashing Kazik a sly grin, you tell him that he already knows which one you want him to cast. Shaking his head, he warns,
		#IF(pc.isFeminine())
			 [kazik.speech(Look, if you really want me to cast arcane arousal on you, then I can't be held responsible for what happens afterwards. If you get horny, then you're going to make me horny, and then I think we can all guess where that will end.)]
		#ELSE
			 [kazik.speech(Look, if you really want me to cast arcane arousal on you, then I can't be held responsible for what happens afterwards. If you get horny, then you're going to make me feel pretty uncomfortable; I'm only into girls, so I'm not doing anything sexual with you.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling Kazik to get on with it already, you gesture for him to hit you with the spell. Letting out a defeated sigh, the handsome ferret-boy reluctantly does as you ask, and after making a wide, sweeping gesture with both hands, he starts to summon forth a few wisps of bright pink arcane energy around his arms. Focusing all of his power into the spell, Kazik unleashes the arousing force, and you watch as the pink energy shoots up into your head. Instantly, you feel that your receptivity to the spell has magnified its power, and you're presented with extremely graphic, vivid images of
		#IF(pc.getSexualOrientation().isAttractedToMasculine())
			 Kazik fucking you
		#ELSE
			 hot girls having sex with you
		#ENDIF
		 right here in the middle of the Farmer's Market.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_CAST_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(Hey! Are you ok?)] Kazik shouts, snapping you out of your arcane-induced daydream. Letting out an extremely horny [pc.moan] in response, you tell the ferret-boy that you need a good hard fuck.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(See? I told you this would happen,)] he replies with a sigh.
		#IF(pc.isFeminine())
			 As you let out another lewd squeal and tell him that you're getting absolutely desperate for sex, the ferret-boy starts getting visibly agitated, and he lowers his voice to offer, [kazik.speech(I can help you out, I guess. You like cock? All your moaning's got me hard...)]
		#ELSE
			 As you let out another lewd squeal and tell him that you're getting absolutely desperate for sex, the ferret-boy shakes his head and says, [kazik.speech(I'm not interested in helping you out. I've demonstrated the spell for you, now deal with the consequences.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out another [pc.moan+], you wonder what to do...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_FINISHED_IMPRESSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Duly impressed by Kazik's proficiency with the arcane, you tell him that his spell was a sight to behold. Puffing himself up as he hears your praise, the ferret-boy boasts, [kazik.speech(Well, I <i>was</i> one of the best students in my year at the university. I was even able to achieve higher grades than some demons!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've made another comment about how fantastic his spell was, Kazik crosses his arms and asks, [kazik.speech(So, now that the show's over, did you want to buy something, [pc.name]?)] 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_FINISHED_BORING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not at all impressed by Kazik's measly arcane abilities, you tell him that his spell was not at all what you were hoping for. Letting out an annoyed grunt as he hears your negative feedback, the ferret-boy states, [kazik.speech(What do you know? <i>I</i> was one of the best students in my year at the university. I was even able to achieve higher grades than some demons!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've made another dismissive comment about how disappointing his spell was, Kazik crosses his arms and huffs, [kazik.speech(Whatever. Everyone else liked it... So did you want to buy something, or just keep on insulting me?)] 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With Kazik unwilling to offer you a hand in dealing with your intense arousal, you do your best to focus on anything but sex and try to calm your overwhelming libido. At first it seems like nothing is going to work, and it's only as you're just on the verge of breaking down and masturbating right here in public when you finally feel yourself starting to regain control. A few deep breaths and a moment spent in silence later, and you feel your lust starting to fade away.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(All done?)] Kazik asks. After taking one last deep breath, you respond in the affirmative, and the ferret-boy shakes his head and says, [kazik.speech(I told you what would happen... Anyway, do you want to buy something?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_REFUSE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to take Kazik up on his offer of helping you to deal with your intense arousal, you do your best to focus on anything but sex and try to calm your overwhelming libido. At first it seems like nothing is going to work, and it's only as you're just on the verge of breaking down and masturbating right here in public when you finally feel yourself starting to regain control. A few deep breaths and a moment spent in silence later, and you feel your lust starting to fade away.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(You actually managed to overcome my spell?)] Kazik asks with one eyebrow raised. After taking one last deep breath, you respond in the affirmative, and the ferret-boy lets out a huff and says, [kazik.speech(I told you what would happen. That's why I don't offer that spell as a demonstration. Anyway, do you want to buy something?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hearing Kazik say that he's got an erection from all your moaning only turns you on even more, and after [pc.stepping] right up to his counter, you lick your lips and tell the handsome ferret-boy that you could do with his cock in your mouth right about now. Looking down over the table, you tell him to get his cock out and let you see what you'll be sucking in a moment.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(I shouldn't be doing this...)] he muses, but despite his words, he unzips his jeans and unbuttons his boxers, before taking out his rapidly-hardening cock and showing it to you. Biting your lip and letting out a hungry moan, you look down to see that his [kazik.cockColour], [kazik.cockGirth] shaft is [kazik.cockLengthValue] long, and there's already a bead of slimy precum starting to ooze out of the tip.
	</p>
	<p>
		The intense effect of Kazik's spell, combined with the sight of his hardening cock, is far too much for you to resist, and you desperately demand that the ferret-boy lets you give him a blowjob. Looking around to make sure that nobody's watching, he gestures around to the side of his stall and says, [kazik.speech(Come on then... There's a space behind some crates back there where we can do it.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_ORAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Kazik's instructions, you [pc.step] around to the side of his stall, and after squeezing through a gap between two high stacks of wooden crates, you find yourself in a spacious alcove that's formed between the rear of several other stalls. Swinging and locking a long, glass cover shut over his goods, the ferret-boy steps around to join you in the hidden alcove, before taking hold of his hard cock and saying, [kazik.speech(Get to it then.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping down in front of the handsome ferret-boy, you open your mouth and deliver a big, wet kiss to the [kazik.cockHead+] of his throbbing shaft. Darting out your [pc.tongue+], you happily lick up his salty precum, which causes him to let out a deep groan and grunt, [kazik.speech(Stop teasing... Just get to it already...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a little giggle, you press your mouth against his cock and give it a loud, wet kiss. Parting your [pc.lips+], you take his [kazik.cockHead] into your mouth with the intention of teasing him a little longer, but Kazik impatiently takes hold of your head and pulls you forwards, sliding his hard, hot shaft down your throat and grunting, [kazik.speech(Yes... That's it...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a muffled, spluttering moan, you decide to forgo any more foreplay and start bobbing your head up and down as you happily give the handsome ferret-boy a blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_VAGINAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hearing Kazik say that he's got an erection from all your moaning only turns you on even more, and after [pc.stepping] right up to his counter, you
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 turn around and
		#ENDIF
		 shamelessly flash the handsome ferret-boy your [pc.pussy+]. Biting your lip, you seductively moan that you're desperate to feel his cock thrusting deep into your horny little cunt. Looking down over the table, you tell him to get his cock out and let you see what's going to be stuffed inside of you in a moment.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(I shouldn't be doing this...)] he muses, but despite his words, he unzips his jeans and unbuttons his boxers, before taking out his rapidly-hardening cock and showing it to you. Biting your lip and letting out a hungry moan, you look down to see that his [kazik.cockColour], [kazik.cockGirth] shaft is [kazik.cockLengthValue] long, and there's already a bead of slimy precum starting to ooze out of the tip.
	</p>
	<p>
		The intense effect of Kazik's spell, combined with the sight of his hardening cock, is far too much for you to resist, and you desperately demand that the ferret-boy fucks you. Looking around to make sure that nobody's watching, he gestures around to the side of his stall and says, [kazik.speech(Come on then... There's a space behind some crates back there where we can do it.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_VAGINAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Kazik's instructions, you [pc.step] around to the side of his stall, and after squeezing through a gap between two high stacks of wooden crates, you find yourself in a spacious alcove that's formed between the rear of several other stalls. Swinging and locking a long, glass cover shut over his goods, the ferret-boy steps around to join you in the hidden alcove, before taking hold of his hard cock and ordering, [kazik.speech(Present yourself.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			Desperate to get started, you obediently turn around and flash your pussy to Kazik, before dropping down onto all fours and telling him to rut you like an animal.
		#ELSE
			Desperate to get started, you obediently face the nearby crates and lean against them, pushing your ass out behind you and spreading your [pc.legs] so as to present yourself to Kazik. Looking back over your shoulder, you let out another lewd moan and tell him to start pounding your hot cunt.
		#ENDIF
		 The sight of your exposed pussy is too much for the ferret-boy to resist, and he quickly steps forwards to rub the [kazik.cockHead+] of his hard cock up and down over your [pc.labia+]. Letting out a deep groan, he grunts, [kazik.speech(Come on... Ask for it...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeling that you're just a moment away from being penetrated, you push your [pc.ass+] back and desperately beg for the handsome ferret-boy to give you his cock. Happy to oblige, he grabs hold of your [pc.hips+] and lines his shaft up to your pussy, before thrusting forwards and stuffing you full of his [kazik.cockGirth], throbbing cock. Letting out a delighted, horny squeal, you start pushing back against him as he proceeds to start eagerly fucking you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_ANAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hearing Kazik say that he's got an erection from all your moaning only turns you on even more, and after [pc.stepping] right up to his counter, you
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 turn around and
		#ENDIF
		 shamelessly flash the handsome ferret-boy your [pc.asshole+]. Biting your lip, you seductively moan that you're desperate to feel his cock thrusting deep into your [pc.assSize] butt. Looking down over the table, you tell him to get his cock out and let you see what's going to be stuffed inside of you in a moment.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kazik.speech(I shouldn't be doing this...)] he muses, but despite his words, he unzips his jeans and unbuttons his boxers, before taking out his rapidly-hardening cock and showing it to you. Biting your lip and letting out a hungry moan, you look down to see that his [kazik.cockColour], [kazik.cockGirth] shaft is [kazik.cockLengthValue] long, and there's already a bead of slimy precum starting to ooze out of the tip.
	</p>
	<p>
		The intense effect of Kazik's spell, combined with the sight of his hardening cock, is far too much for you to resist, and you desperately demand that the ferret-boy fucks your ass. Looking around to make sure that nobody's watching, he gestures around to the side of his stall and says, [kazik.speech(Come on then... There's a space behind some crates back there where we can do it.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_SPELLS_ARCANE_ANAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Kazik's instructions, you [pc.step] around to the side of his stall, and after squeezing through a gap between two high stacks of wooden crates, you find yourself in a spacious alcove that's formed between the rear of several other stalls. Swinging and locking a long, glass cover shut over his goods, the ferret-boy steps around to join you in the hidden alcove, before taking hold of his hard cock and ordering, [kazik.speech(Present yourself.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			Desperate to get started, you obediently turn around and flash your rear entrance to Kazik, before dropping down onto all fours and telling him to rut you like an animal.
		#ELSE
			Desperate to get started, you obediently face the nearby crates and lean against them, pushing your ass out behind you and spreading your [pc.legs] so as to present yourself to Kazik. Looking back over your shoulder, you let out another lewd moan and tell him to start pounding your rear entrance.
		#ENDIF
		 The sight of your exposed asshole is too much for the ferret-boy to resist, and he quickly steps forwards to rub the [kazik.cockHead+] of his hard cock up and down over your butt. Letting out a deep groan, he grunts, [kazik.speech(Come on... Ask for it...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeling that you're just a moment away from being penetrated, you push your [pc.ass+] back and desperately beg for the handsome ferret-boy to give you his cock. Happy to oblige, he grabs hold of your [pc.hips+] and lines his shaft up to your [pc.asshole+], before thrusting forwards and stuffing you full of his [kazik.cockGirth], throbbing cock. Letting out a delighted, horny squeal, you start pushing back against him as he proceeds to start eagerly fucking your ass...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(sex.getSexTypeCount(kazik, pc, sex.newSexType(PENETRATION_PENIS, ORIFICE_VAGINA))>0)
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, kazik))
				#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
					Letting out a deeply satisfied groan, Kazik takes one last moment to rub the head of his cock up and down over your cum-stuffed pussy, teasing, [kazik.speech(Shame you're already pregnant, but I still love giving hot babes like you a nice big creampie...)]
				#ELSE
					Letting out a deeply satisfied groan, Kazik takes one last moment to push his fingers into your cum-stuffed pussy, and as he pushes his seed deep into your cunt, he teases, [kazik.speech(Here's hoping that you'll get pregnant from this... I want to see you with a big, round belly...)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				Letting out a deeply satisfied groan, Kazik takes one last moment to rub the head of his cock up and down over your [pc.labia+], teasing, [kazik.speech(Your pussy was a real good fuck...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a happy moan, you lean back into the handsome ferret-boy and tell him that you loved having your pussy stuffed full of his cock. Grunting in approval at your words, Kazik leans in to plant a quick kiss on your [pc.lips+], before stepping back and cleaning himself off with a tissue.
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(sex.getSexTypeCount(kazik, pc, sex.newSexType(PENETRATION_PENIS, ORIFICE_ANUS))>0)
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_ANUS, kazik))
				Letting out a deeply satisfied groan, Kazik takes one last moment to rub the head of his cock up and down over your cum-stuffed asshole, teasing, [kazik.speech(I love giving hot babes like you a nice big anal creampie...)]
			#ELSE
				Letting out a deeply satisfied groan, Kazik takes one last moment to rub the head of his cock up and down over your [pc.asshole+], teasing, [kazik.speech(Your ass was a real good fuck...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a happy moan, you lean back into the handsome ferret-boy and tell him that you loved having your butt stuffed full of his cock. Grunting in approval at your words, Kazik leans in to plant a quick kiss on your [pc.lips+], before stepping back and cleaning himself off with a tissue.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Letting out a deeply satisfied groan, Kazik takes one last moment to rub the head of his cock up and down over your [pc.lips+], teasing, [kazik.speech(You sure know how to suck cock...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a happy moan, you plant a big, wet kiss on his softening shaft and tell him that you loved having your throat stuffed full of his cock. Grunting in approval at your words, Kazik leans in to plant a quick kiss on your forehead, before stepping back and cleaning himself off with a tissue.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		After you've similarly cleaned yourself up and get your things back in order, the ferret-boy asks, [kazik.speech(Ready to head out?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TRINKETS_AFTER_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling Kazik that you're ready to go, you join him in [pc.stepping] out of the alcove and returning to his stall. As the ferret-boy takes his usual place behind his counter, you continue on around to the other side, before turning to flash him a sly smile.
	</p>
	<p>
		With a smirk on his face, he says, [kazik.speech(Ok, that turned out a lot better than I thought, I'll admit. I'm not going to cast that spell again today, though. If you want to do this again, then come back tomorrow.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've flirtily suggested to Kazik that you might just do that, he lets out a short laugh and asks, [kazik.speech(So, are you going to buy anything?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>