<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- All of these are linked to the 'dialogue/innoxia/places/fields/elis/tavern_taur.xml' dialogue nodes. -->
	
	<!-- Place dialogues -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A huge, circular bar is positioned right in the very centre of the tavern, and it's from here that drinks are served to the tauric clientèle. So as to accommodate the taurs who frequent this establishment, the bar's wooden counter is quite tall, and there's not a single bar stool to be seen anywhere around its circumference.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF((game.getHourOfDay()>=15 && game.getHourOfDay()<=23))
			As it's currently the busy time of day, there's almost no space at all at the bar. Well over a dozen taurs of all kinds are either standing or sitting around the counter, and as you approach you hear them either ordering drinks or flirting and talking with one another.
		#ELSE
			As it's currently the quiet time of day, there's plenty of space at the bar. Only a couple of taurs are standing at the counter, and as you approach you hear them talking with one another.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
			#IF(kheiron.isPlayerKnowsName())
				[pc.Stepping] up to the bar, you see Kheiron himself trot around from behind the bar's central pillar, and as he catches sight of you, he flashes you a smile and asks, [kheiron.speech(What can I get for you today, [pc.name]?)]
			#ELSE
					[pc.Stepping] up to the bar, you see a huge, olive-skinned centaur, who looks to be in his mid-forties, trot around from behind the bar's central pillar. His muscular, lower horse's body is covered in dark brown hair, which is a similar shade to the short, curly hair on his head. Thanks to the fact that he's only wearing a short-sleeved shirt, you're able to see that his exposed horse-cock and balls are absolutely massive. Just like his horse-half, this centaur's human body is extremely muscular, which, combined with the fact that he's standing at no less than [kheiron.heightValue], leaves you with no doubt that he must be one of the strongest people in all of Elis.
				</p>
				<p>
					Glancing around the bar, this centaur's hazel eyes catch yours, and after flashing you a handsome smile, he steps forwards and speaks in a low, booming voice, [kheiron.speech(I haven't seen you here before. First time in Elis, or is this just your first time visiting my tavern?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			[pc.Stepping] up to the bar, you see that Kheiron isn't here at the moment, and instead there's a large, muscular centauress working behind the counter. Catching sight of you, she steps forwards and asks, [style.feminineSpeech(Hey there, can I get you something?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seeing no reason not to introduce yourself to this friendly centaur, you tell him your name and
		#IF(pc.isQuestProgressLessThan(QUEST_LINE_MAIN, QUEST_MAIN_3_C_MEETING_MINOTALLYS))
			 confirm that this is indeed your first time here in Elis.
		#ELSE
			 explain that you've already spent some time in Elis, but that you're not a native to the town.
		#ENDIF
		 Nodding as he listens, this centaur responds, [kheiron.speech(It's good to meet you, [pc.name]. My name's Kheiron, and I'm the owner of this tavern. If you need anything, don't hesitate to ask. Oh, and you say that you're not from Elis? Did you come from Dominion, by any chance?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've confirmed to Kheiron that you have indeed come from the Realm's capital city, the centaur steps right up to the counter and leans in to ask, [kheiron.speech(Did you see a couple of centaurs offering transport out there? They're called Astrapi and Vronti. Know them?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_centaur_transport_introduced))
			Having met the centaurs he's asking about, you tell Kheiron that you do know who he's talking about, and that they've recently set up a transportation service between Elis and Dominion. Letting out a relieved sigh, Kheiron steps back and explains, [kheiron.speech(I'm their father, you see. They're not very good at keeping in touch, and as we don't get many visitors from Dominion these days I don't often hear if they're still doing ok out there.)]
		#ELSE
			Having not met the centaurs he's asking about, you tell Kheiron that you don't know who he's talking about. Letting out a sigh, Kheiron steps back and explains, [kheiron.speech(I'm their father, you see. They're not very good at keeping in touch, and as we don't get many visitors from Dominion these days I don't often hear if they're still doing ok out there. I guess I'll have to head out and check on them myself some time this week.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isHourBetween(8, 24))
			With several customers waiting nearby to be served, Kheiron smiles at you and asks, [kheiron.speech(So, can I get you a drink, [pc.name]?)]
		#ELSE
			With your brief talk now over, Kheiron smiles at you and reveals, [kheiron.speech(I'm normally in bed at this hour, but I had to come downstairs to get a leaky beer tap fixed. Anyway, can I get you a drink before I head off, [pc.name]?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to make some small talk and get to know Kheiron a little better, you ask him how his day has been going so far.
		#IF(game.isHourBetween(8, 24))
			 Despite the fact that there are many customers waiting to be served, the centaur leaves business to his other employees and chooses to engage you in conversation, and replies, 
		#ELSE
			 As there's nobody at the bar who requires his attention, the centaur chooses to engage you in conversation, and replies, 
		#ENDIF
		 [kheiron.speech(Everything's going well, today, [pc.name]. Thanks for asking. How about yourself?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Happy to continue talking with him, you respond to Kheiron's question and then continue to engage him in conversation. Talking about everything from the weather to recent events in Elis, the two of you spend the next fifteen minutes talking with one another over the bar's counter. Eventually, however, the muscular centaur declares, [kheiron.speech(It's been good talking with you, [pc.name], but I've got things to be getting on with. Is there anything else I can do for you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_TALK_LUNETTE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to hear what Kheiron thinks about Lunette, you ask him what he knows of the elder lilin. His eyes narrow a little as he hears your question, and after spending a moment in thought, he replies, [kheiron.speech(Best not to be mentioning that name too loudly in here. You'll not find one person in all of Elis who has a good word to say about Lunette, but taurs can get particularly angry when they start speaking about her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to know more, you ask the muscular centaur why that's the case, to which he sighs and replies, [kheiron.speech(Lunette's daughters seem to have a particular fondness for taurs. Many of the folk in here used to live out in the fields, and so have been the target of those demonic centaurs' affections, whether they wanted it or not. Let's just leave it at that, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As Kheiron is clearly unwilling to say any more about the subject, you decide to move on to something else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_TALK_HISTORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious about Kheiron's history, you ask him about his past and how he came to own this tavern. After taking a moment to think about where to start, he begins, [kheiron.speech(There's not really much to tell about most of my life. I used to live out in the woods with a group of other centaurs, but we ended up going our separate ways after Lunette's raiders started taking an interest in us. That was well before they started really getting out of control, but even all those years ago Lunette's daughters were a real pain to deal with.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After taking a moment to think, the muscular centaur continues, [kheiron.speech(Everyone else ended up going to Dominion, but I stuck around here in Elis. To cut a long story short, after many years doing all sorts of jobs here in Elis I ended up being given the opportunity to buy this tavern. It was on the verge of being shut down and demolished when I took over, but by converting it into a place that caters for taurs, I managed to turn its fortunes around.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to know a little more about his past, you ask Kheiron whether his son and daughter used to work with him here in Elis, to which he replies, [kheiron.speech(Oh, no. Astrapi and Vronti had no interest in staying in Elis. They went off to Dominion to try and make their own way there. I keep on telling them that they can come and work here with me, but they have no interest.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having had enough of recounting his past, the muscular centaur quickly follows up on his last sentence by asking, [kheiron.speech(Anyway, can I get you a drink, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_TALK_FAE_SILVIA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that Fae and Silvia frequent this establishment, you ask Kheiron if he's met the two foxtauresses, and if so, what he can tell you about them.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kheiron.speech(I've done a lot more than meet them,)] he grunts in response, [kheiron.speech(and so have plenty of my other customers. I can tell you that Fae's the more talkative of the two, but that sister of hers is the real minx once she gets going... Anyway, all I know is that they're sisters and that I've never seen the two of them apart.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to know more, you ask Kheiron if there's anything else at all that he can tell you about them.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kheiron.speech(Not really, no. Sure, I've slept with them, but that was a long time ago, and I've got someone else I'm interested in these days...)] The centaur pauses at this point and clears his throat, before turning the conversation away from his private life, [kheiron.speech(If you want to know more about them, why not ask them yourself? I'm sure they'd be happy to receive your attention. They're usually somewhere in here between seven and ten each evening.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking him for the information, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_TALK_STEROPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wondering if Kheiron can tell you anything about Sterope, you ask him what he knows about the Enforcer.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kheiron.speech(Oh, she's here every evening, usually after about nine,)] the centaur responds,
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 before looking you up and down and grunting in amusement, [kheiron.speech(As you're a taur yourself, you'd better watch out. That girl's got a thing for our kind, and makes it her mission to end every evening by being led off to the stable by a taur.)]
		#ELSE
			 before grunting, [kheiron.speech(That girl's got a thing for taurs, and makes it her mission to end every evening by being led off to the stable by one.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you get the chance to ask him anything about the stable he's just mentioned, Kheiron explains, [kheiron.speech(The stable's out back, behind the locked door near the toilets. It was standing empty before Sterope convinced me to rent it out to her. Although she's tried to get me in there, she's not my type, so I don't know for sure what she gets up to in there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isInnocent())
			Your innocent speculation that perhaps she's got some kind of Enforcer assignment that requires her to interrogate taurs is met by a loud laugh from Kheiron.
		#ELSE
			Your speculation that she's probably having a good time, seeing that she comes back for more every evening, is met by a loud laugh from Kheiron.
		#ENDIF
		 Shaking his head, he grunts in amusement, [kheiron.speech(She's getting what she wants in there, all right. Honestly, the less I know about it, the better. So long as she keeps paying rent, she can do whatever she pleases.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Sensing that there's no more to be said on this topic, you wonder what to ask Kheiron next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_TALK_GOLIX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to hear what Kheiron has to say about Oglix's elemental, you ask him what kind of relationship he has with Golix.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kheiron.speech(Well, I don't see how that's any of your business,)] the centaur snorts, before crossing his arms and firmly stating, [kheiron.speech(I'm not going to say anything more on the matter.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_oglix_kheiron_spectated))
			Having witnessed Kheiron's and Golix's meeting in the old stables behind 'The Crossed Blades', you can't help but give the centaur a knowing look as he says this. Realising that you're aware of at least some of the details of his relationship with the elemental, he lowers his voice and admits, [kheiron.speech(Fine, Golix and I are, well, I suppose you could say that we're dating... Now I'm serious; no more questions about this. Is there anything else can I do for you, [pc.name]?)]
		#ELSE
			Not wanting to pry too far into his personal affairs and risk getting on his bad side, you decide to leave it at that for now. Nodding as he sees that you're not going to press him on the matter, the centaur asks, [kheiron.speech(So, what else can I do for you, [pc.name]?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_BARRELS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to bring back good news to Oglix as soon as possible, you ask Kheiron if he has four large barrels which you could have. Raising his eyebrow as he hears you ask this, the centaur asks, [kheiron.speech(What would you need those for? I'd be happy to give you some if it's for a good reason.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As he'd find out the barrels' destination one way or another, and with no reason to lie, you truthfully tell Kheiron that Oglix wants them so that she could use them to house some more beer-bitches. Snorting in disgust as he hears the name 'Oglix', the muscular centaur shakes his head and firmly states, [kheiron.speech(In that case, no. I don't hold anything against you for working for her, but I'm not going to do anything to help Oglix.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_BARRELS_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Realising that you have no other choice, you use the phrase which Oglix's elemental gave you, and tell Kheiron that 'Golix says to be a good horsie'. As he hears you say this, Kheiron's eyes open wide, and with a loud snort, he starts forcefully pawing at the ground with one of his huge, strong hoofs.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kheiron.speech(Golix told you to say that?!)] he asks, with a tone of frustrated desperation in his voice. Letting out another snort as you reply in the positive, the centaur grinds his teeth for a moment, before grunting, [kheiron.speech(Fine... I'll bring the four barrels over as soon as I can, but on one condition. You're not to tell a soul about the relationship I have with Golix, understand?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_BARRELS_END_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you don't know any details about Golix's relationship with Kheiron, you see no reason not to agree to keep quiet about it. After you've given Kheiron your word that you won't mention their relationship to anyone, the centaur lets out a relieved sigh and grunts, [kheiron.speech(Good. As I said, I'll get those barrels over to Oglix's place as soon as I can.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking the centaur for his cooperation, you wonder whether to order anything from the bar before you head off and report back to Oglix...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Ordering drinks: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_WATER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
			Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of water. Grabbing a clean glass from under the bar, he quickly fills it with clean, cold water, before placing it down before you and saying, [kheiron.speech(Here you go, [pc.name]. There's no charge for water.)]
		#ELSE
			Feeling thirsty, you get the centauress's attention and ask her for a glass of water. Grabbing a clean glass from under the bar, she quickly fills it with clean, cold water, before placing it down before you and saying, [style.speechFeminine(There you go. The water's free.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Bringing the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips], you quickly gulp down the cool, refreshing water. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_ORANGE_JUICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
			Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of orange juice. Grabbing a clean glass, he opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a can of carbonated orange juice. Using his large fingers to fold down the tab, he opens the can and pours the fizzy beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be twenty flames, please.)]
		#ELSE
			Feeling thirsty, you get the centauress's attention and ask her for a glass of orange juice. Grabbing a clean glass, she opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a can of carbonated orange juice. Folding down the tab, she opens the can and pours the fizzy beverage into the glass, saying, [style.speechFeminine(That'll be twenty flames, please.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the twenty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and quickly gulp down the cool, refreshing beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_BERRY_SODA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
			Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of berry soda. Grabbing a clean glass, he opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a can of berry soda. Using his large fingers to fold down the tab, he opens the can and pours the fizzy beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be twenty flames, please.)]
		#ELSE
			Feeling thirsty, you get the centauress's attention and ask her for a glass of berry soda. Grabbing a clean glass, she opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a can of berry soda. Folding down the tab, she opens the can and pours the fizzy beverage into the glass, saying, [style.speechFeminine(That'll be twenty flames, please.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the twenty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and quickly gulp down the cool, refreshing beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_COLA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
			Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of cola. Grabbing a clean glass, he opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a bottle of fizzy cola. Using his large fingers to operate a bottle opener, he pops off the cap and pours the brown beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be twenty-five flames, please.)]
		#ELSE
			Feeling thirsty, you get the centauress's attention and ask her for a glass of cola. Grabbing a clean glass, she opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a bottle of fizzy cola. Using a bottle opener, she pops off the cap and pours the brown beverage into the glass, saying, [style.speechFeminine(That'll be twenty-five flames, please.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the twenty-five flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and quickly gulp down the cool, refreshing beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_COFFEE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
			Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of cold-brew coffee. Grabbing a clean glass, he opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a bottle of dark black coffee. Using his large fingers to twist off the cap, he pours the caffeinated beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be thirty flames, please.)]
		#ELSE
			Feeling thirsty, you get the centauress's attention and ask her for a glass of cold-brew coffee. Grabbing a clean glass, she opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a bottle of dark black coffee. Twisting off the cap, she pours the caffeinated beverage into the glass, saying, [style.speechFeminine(That'll be thirty flames, please.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the thirty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and quickly gulp down the cool, refreshing beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_BEER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a pint of beer. Grabbing a clean glass, he places it under the tap and pours the alcoholic beverage, 'Canine Crush', into it, before placing your pint down on the bar and saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be forty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the forty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and quickly gulp down the cool, refreshing beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_CIDER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a pint of cider. Grabbing a clean glass, he places it under the tap and pours the alcoholic beverage, 'Equine Cider', into it, before placing your pint down on the bar and saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be forty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the forty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and quickly gulp down the cool, refreshing beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_PERRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a pint of pear cider. Grabbing a clean glass, he opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a bottle of 'Black Stripes Perry'. Using his large fingers to operate a bottle opener, he pops off the cap and pours the alcoholic beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be forty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the forty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and quickly gulp down the cool, refreshing beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_WINE_RED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of red wine. Grabbing a clean wine glass, he reaches back to the shelves positioned behind the bar and grabs a bottle of red wine. Using his large fingers to operate a bottle opener, he removes the cork and pours the alcoholic beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be sixty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the sixty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and spend a few minutes slowly drinking the delicious beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_WINE_WHITE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of white wine. Grabbing a clean wine glass, he opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a bottle of white wine. Using his large fingers to operate a bottle opener, he removes the cork and pours the alcoholic beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be sixty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the sixty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and spend a few minutes slowly drinking the delicious beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_VODKA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of vodka. Grabbing a clean glass, he reaches back to the shelves positioned behind the bar and grabs a bottle of vodka. Using his large fingers to unscrew the cap, he pours the alcoholic beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be a hundred flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the hundred flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and spend a few minutes slowly drinking the delicious, highly-alcoholic beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_RUM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of rum. Grabbing a clean glass, he reaches back to the shelves positioned behind the bar and grabs a bottle of rum. Using his large fingers to unscrew the cap, he pours the alcoholic beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be a hundred and twenty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the one hundred and twenty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and spend a few minutes slowly drinking the delicious, highly-alcoholic beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_WHISKEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of whiskey. Grabbing a clean glass, he reaches back to the shelves positioned behind the bar and grabs a bottle of whiskey. Using his large fingers to unscrew the cap, he pours the alcoholic beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be a hundred and twenty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the one hundred and twenty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and spend a few minutes slowly drinking the delicious, highly-alcoholic beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_DRINK_CHAMPAGNE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling thirsty, you ask Kheiron for a glass of champagne. Grabbing a clean champagne flute, he opens one of the arcane fridges positioned behind the bar and produces a bottle of 'Pan's Flute'. Using his large fingers to twist off the cork, he opens the bottle with a loud pop, before pouring the fizzy beverage into the glass, saying, [kheiron.speech(That'll be a hundred and sixty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the one hundred and sixty flames, you bring the glass up to your waiting [pc.lips] and spend a few minutes slowly drinking the delicious beverage. Leaving the now-empty glass on the bar, you wonder whether to order anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Ordering food: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_BREAD"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
		<p>
			Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order some bread rolls. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be fifty flames, please.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One bread basket ready!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the bread basket down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the freshly-baked bread rolls...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so you call over the centauress behind the bar and order some bread rolls. Nodding as you give her your order, she smiles and says, [style.speechFeminine(That'll be fifty flames, please.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Handing over the money, you wait as the centauress hurries into the kitchen, and then a minute later she returns carrying your order. Setting the bread basket down on the counter in front of you, she flashes you a smile and steps over to the next customer, leaving you to tuck in to the delicious bread rolls...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_NUTS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
		<p>
			Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order some mixed nuts. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be fifty flames, please.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One order of mixed nuts ready!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the bowl down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious assortment of mixed nuts...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so you call over the centauress behind the bar and order some mixed nuts. Nodding as you give her your order, she smiles and says, [style.speechFeminine(That'll be fifty flames, please.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Handing over the money, you wait as the centauress hurries into the kitchen, and then a minute later she returns carrying your order. Setting the bread basket down on the counter in front of you, she flashes you a smile and steps over to the next customer, leaving you to tuck in to the delicious assortment of mixed nuts...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_FRIES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order some curly fries. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be fifty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One order of curly fries ready!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the bowl down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious bowl of greasy, curly fries...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_SHRIMP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order a shrimp cocktail. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be seventy-five flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One order of shrimp cocktail ready!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the glass down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious shrimp cocktail...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_PATE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
		<p>
			Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order some pâté and crackers. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be eighty flames, please.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One order of pâté and crackers ready!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the plate down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious plate of meat pâté and crackers...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so you call over the centauress behind the bar and order some pâté and crackers. Nodding as you give her your order, she smiles and says, [style.speechFeminine(That'll be eighty flames, please.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Handing over the money, you wait as the centauress hurries into the kitchen, and then a minute later she returns carrying your order. Setting the bread basket down on the counter in front of you, she flashes you a smile and steps over to the next customer, leaving you to tuck in to the delicious plate of meat pâté and crackers...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_FISH_CHIPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling quite hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order a serving of fish and chips. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be a hundred and fifty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One order of fish and chips ready!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the plate down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious plate of freshly-cooked fish and chips...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_SAUSAGES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling quite hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order some sausages. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be a hundred and fifty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One order of sausages ready!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the plate down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious plate of freshly-cooked, high-quality sausages...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_BURGER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling quite hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order a burger. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be a hundred and fifty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One burger ready!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the plate down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious burger...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_CHICKEN_PIE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling quite hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order a chicken pie. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be a hundred and eighty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One order of chicken pie ready!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the plate down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious, freshly-cooked chicken pie...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_STEAK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling quite hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order a steak. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be two hundred and fifty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One steak ready!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the plate down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious, freshly-cooked steak...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_FRUIT_SALAD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order a fruit salad. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be eighty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One order of fruit salad ready!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the bowl down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the bowl of delicious, refreshing fruit salad...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_HONEY_BREAD"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
		<p>
			Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order some honey bread. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be eighty flames, please.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One order of honey bread ready!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the plate down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious plate of honey bread...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so you call over the centauress behind the bar and order some honey bread. Nodding as you give her your order, she smiles and says, [style.speechFeminine(That'll be eighty flames, please.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Handing over the money, you wait as the centauress hurries into the kitchen, and then a minute later she returns carrying your order. Setting the bread basket down on the counter in front of you, she flashes you a smile and steps over to the next customer, leaving you to tuck in to the delicious plate of honey bread...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_BERRY_TRIFLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order a berry trifle. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be eighty flames, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One order of berry trifle ready!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the bowl down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the bowl of delicious berry trifle...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_FOOD_BROWNIE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(kheiron))
		<p>
			Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so ask Kheiron if you can order a brownie. Jotting your order down on a slip of paper, he nods and says, [kheiron.speech(That'll be eighty flames, please.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Handing over the money, you wait for a few minutes as your order is processed, before a centauress steps out from the kitchen door and calls out, [style.speechFeminine(One brownie ready!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pointing over at you, Kheiron watches as this centauress sets the plate down on the counter in front of you, before smiling at her and saying, [kheiron.speech(Remember to take a break if you're feeling tired.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at Kheiron, the centauress reassures him that she's still full of energy, before trotting back into the kitchen and leaving you to tuck in to the delicious chocolate brownie...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling a little hungry, you decide to order something to eat, and so you call over the centauress behind the bar and order a chocolate brownie. Nodding as you give her your order, she smiles and says, [style.speechFeminine(That'll be eighty flames, please.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Handing over the money, you wait as the centauress hurries into the kitchen, and then a minute later she returns carrying your order. Setting the bread basket down on the counter in front of you, she flashes you a smile and steps over to the next customer, leaving you to tuck in to the delicious chocolate brownie...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leading off from the main floor of the tavern, this corridor is clearly signposted as leading to the public toilet facilities. Just like every other aspect of this building, this corridor appears to have been constructed with taurs in mind, as it's far wider than a simple passageway would otherwise need to be.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing beside one of the two entrances to 'The Centaur's Sword'. Being specially designed so as to accommodate taurs of all sizes, the entrance's wooden doors are especially tall and wide, and the doormat which is recessed into the floor looks to be of an extremely heavy-duty design.
	</p>
	<p>
		Over to one side of the large double-doors, there's a wooden umbrella rack fixed to the wall at waist-height,
		#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_RAIN)
			 which, due to the fact that it's currently raining outside, is full of wet umbrellas.
		#ELSE
			 which, due to the fact that it's not currently raining outside, only has a few umbrellas stored in it.
		#ENDIF
		 From here, you could either [pc.step] forwards into the main area of the tavern, or instead make use of the door to head back out into Elis.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it's time for you to leave, you push open the door and head back outside, before continuing forwards into the street outside the tavern...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KITCHEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Over on one side of the tavern's main floor, a pair of wide doors each display a sign that reads 'Kitchen: Staff Only'. [pc.Stepping] over to these doors, you look through one of their circular windows and see that the tavern's kitchen looks to be very large and well organised.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF((game.getHourOfDay()>=15 && game.getHourOfDay()<=23))
			As it's currently the busy time of the day, there are several centauresses working in the kitchen, and you watch them for a moment as they prepare ingredients, stir pots, and move food in and out of the ovens.
		#ELSE
			As it's currently the quiet time of the day, there's only one centauress working in the kitchen, and you watch her for a moment as she takes her time preparing ingredients, stirring pots, and moving food in and out of the ovens.
		#ENDIF
		 Respecting the sign on the door, and not wanting to disturb the tavern's cooking staff, you decide to [pc.step] away from the door and do something else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Seating, with Fae & Silvia content:-->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Running along one side of the tavern's main floor, an area has been set aside in which customers can sit and relax. Numerous large, taur-compatible sofas have been scattered throughout this area for people who want something to sit on, while clean mats have been laid out across the rest of the available space for taurs who prefer to lie down.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isHourBetween(15, 24))
			As it's currently the busy time of the day, this seating area is almost completely full of taurs of every type imaginable. Making use of the sofas, or lying and sitting on the mats, these taurs are happily drinking, talking, and flirting with one another. Looking around, you also see that there are several along the edges of the seating area who are making out with one another or even trying to stealthily perform sexual acts.
		#ELSE
			As it's currently the quiet time of the day, this seating area is almost completely empty. There are however a couple of taurs who are making use of the sofas, and you watch for a moment as they happily drink and talk with one another.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(fae))
			Taking one last look around, you suddenly spot Fae and Silvia sitting on a sofa over on the other side of this seating area. They haven't noticed you yet, and so you could either head over and say hello to them or turn around and continue on your way elsewhere...
		#ELSE
			With little to do here, you soon decide to turn around and head back into the rest of the tavern...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(fae.isVisiblyPregnant())
		<p>
			#IF(!fae.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
				Recognising the two foxtauresses over on the far side of the seating area as none other than Fae and Silvia, you [pc.walk] over to them and say hello. Fae is the first to react to your greeting, and with a big smile on her face, she points down to her swollen belly and declares, [fae.speech(Look, [pc.name], you got me knocked up!)]
			#ELSE
				Recognising the two foxtauresses over on the far side of the seating area as none other than Fae and Silvia, you [pc.walk] over to them and say hello. Fae is the first to react to your greeting, and with a big smile on her face, she points down at her rounded belly and declares, [fae.speech(Look, [pc.name], I'm still pregnant with our kids!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(silvia.isVisiblyPregnant())
		<p>
			#IF(fae.isVisiblyPregnant())
				Letting out a soft moan, Silvia looks over at you and bites her lip, before pointing down at her own pregnant bump and teasing,
			#ELSE
				Recognising the two foxtauresses over on the far side of the seating area as none other than Fae and Silvia, you [pc.walk] over to them and say hello. Silvia is the first to react to your greeting, and with a big smile on her face, she runs her hands over her pregnant bump and teases,
			#ENDIF
			#IF(!silvia.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
				 [silvia.speech(Look what you did, you naughty [pc.girl]... These are your kids in here...)]
			#ELSE
				 [silvia.speech(I'm still carrying our kids around...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(fae.isVisiblyPregnant())
		<p>
			#IF(silvia.isVisiblyPregnant())
				The two pregnant sisters shuffle along on the low sofa and pat the empty space between them. Winking at you, Fae says, [fae.speech(Come and sit down, [pc.name]. Let's get you nice and comfortable...)]
			#ELSE
				Letting out a soft moan, Silvia looks over at you and bites her lip, before shuffling along on the low sofa and patting the empty space between her and Fae. Winking at you, the pregnant foxtauress says, [fae.speech(Come and sit down, [pc.name]. Let's get you nice and comfortable...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(silvia.isVisiblyPregnant())
		<p>
			Letting out a soft moan, Silvia looks over at you and bites her lip, before shuffling along on the low sofa and patting the empty space between her and Fae. Winking at you, the green-eyed foxtauress says, [fae.speech(Come and sit down, [pc.name]. Let's get you nice and comfortable...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Recognising the two foxtauresses over on the far side of the seating area as none other than Fae and Silvia, you [pc.walk] over to them and say hello. The moment they see you, each of the sisters flash you a sly grin, before shuffling along on the low sofa and patting the empty space between them. Winking at you, Fae says, [fae.speech(Come and sit down, [pc.name]. Let's get you nice and comfortable...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(fae))
		<p>
			#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(fae))
				At that moment, the two sisters suddenly notice that you're sporting a swollen, pregnant belly. Telling Fae that she's the one who knocked you up, you smile as the foxtauress teases, [fae.speech(It's not my fault; your pussy was just so good, I didn't want to pull out! Now come over here and take a rest...)]
			#ELSE
				At that moment, the two sisters look down at your swollen, pregnant belly. Knowing that she's the one who knocked you up, Fae smirks and teases, [fae.speech(Still carrying our kids around, huh? Come over here and take a rest...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(silvia))
		<p>
			#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(silvia))
				At that moment, the two sisters suddenly notice that you're sporting a swollen, pregnant belly. Telling Silvia that she's the one who knocked you up, you smile as the foxtauress teases, [silvia.speech(It's not my fault; your pussy was just so good, I didn't want to pull out!)]
			#ELSE
				At that moment, the two sisters look down at your swollen, pregnant belly. Knowing that she's the one who knocked you up, Silvia smirks and teases, [silvia.speech(Still carrying our kids around, huh?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Impatiently continuing to pat the sofa, Fae says, [fae.speech(Come over here and take a rest, [pc.name]...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Accepting Fae's invitation, you sit between the two sisters, and the moment that you do so, they shuffle forwards and start playfully brushing up against you. Seeming to have a little more confidence than she did while at work, Silvia teases, [silvia.speech(You know, [pc.name], Fae and I were just talking about how good you are at kissing. I was wondering if you were good at other stuff, too...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(Why don't you just say you want to fuck [pc.her]?)] Fae says to her sister, [fae.speech(That's why we're all here, isn't it?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a giggle, Silvia nods her head and bats her eyelids at you. Finally given a moment in which to make a move, you wonder whether to take things slow or start by diving right in and kissing the horny sisters...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling like you've made a mistake, you think up some excuse as to why you suddenly need to leave, before standing up and telling Fae and Silvia that you'll have to do this another time. The foxtauresses both pout at you as they hear they're not going to be getting any action tonight, and with a look of disappointment on her face, Fae sighs, [fae.speech(Fine, I guess we'll be heading off as well then. Catch us here at the same time another day, [pc.name].)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the two foxtauresses stand up and walk off into the tavern. After watching them cross the floor and make their exit, you wonder what to do in here now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to rush things, you lean back on the sofa and ask the two foxtauresses how their day has been. Pouting at you, Fae whines, [fae.speech(Come on, [pc.name], don't tease us like this... You know we're all here just to have a good fuck...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(I don't mind having a bit of a chat,)] Silvia declares, before happily smiling at you and continuing in a hushed, seductive tone, [silvia.speech(I'd like to know more about the [pc.race] who I'll be fucking tonight...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With both of the foxtauresses clearly only being interested in sex, your attempts to make small talk don't get very far, and while you're able to get them to tell you how their day has been, they refuse to engage you in any further conversation. Letting out a defeated sigh, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_DRINKS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be nice to have a drink with the two foxtauresses, you ask them if you can get them anything. After briefly smirking at her sister, Fae looks at you and teases, [fae.speech(You're not escaping that easily. Siliva will keep you company while <i>I</i> go and get us some drinks.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Grabbing hold of your [pc.arm], Silvia lets out a playful giggle and says, [silvia.speech(I've got [pc.herHim], Fae. You go and get us some wine.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Allowing the sisters to have their fun, you remain seated while Fae heads off to the bar to get some wine. Leaning into you, Silvia gazes at you with her big, blue eyes and sighs, [silvia.speech(I can't wait for later... Fae and I will give you a real good fuck...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Returning the horny foxtauress's affections, you allow her to guide your [pc.hand] up to her [silvia.breastSize] breasts, and after a couple of minutes spent feeling her up, you see her sister heading back over from the bar. Clearly having seen what you were doing with Silvia, Fae sinks down onto the sofa beside you and demands, [fae.speech(Feel my tits too!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to make her upset, you do as Fae says and give her [fae.cupSize]-cup tits a good grope, while Silvia opens the bottle of wine and pours out three glasses. With the two horny sisters continuing to grind up against you, you spend the next ten minutes drinking and alternating between groping Fae's and Silvia's breasts...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_TAILS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having the lower bodies of oversized feral foxes, Fae and Silvia possess exceptionally fluffy tails. Knowing that it'd feel amazing to get to stroke both of them at once, you ask the sisters if they like having their tails played with. An amused smirk settles on Fae's face as she hears you say this, and she teases, [fae.speech(You like big fluffy tails, huh? What do you think, Silvia? Should we let [pc.name] stroke them?)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(I suppose, so long as [pc.she] shows the same enthusiasm towards the rest of our bodies later this evening,)] Silvia replies, before letting out a giggle and spinning around on the sofa. Following her sister's lead, Fae similarly turns around, and you suddenly find yourself flanked by the sisters' rear ends.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(Go on then, touch our fluffy tails!)] Fae laughs, before twisting her big, furry tail around to stroke it over your face. Not wanting to be left out, Silvia copies her sister and lifts her tail up to brush it over your torso.
	</p>
	<p>
		With Fae and Silvia giggling in delight, you spend the next ten minutes stroking, fluffing, and playing with their large, fluffy fox-tails. Their orange fur is exceptionally smooth and luxurious, and you can't help but smile every time you touch their white tips and cause the sisters to let out an excited little laugh in response. Eventually, however, all three of you get tired of this game, and so Fae and Silvia turn back around and lean into you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(That was fun, but when are we going to go and fuck?)] Silvia asks, before winking and pouting at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(Yeah, I really need some sex tonight,)] Fae adds, [fae.speech(Having my tail fondled isn't going to cut it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the two sisters clearly getting impatient for the evening's main event, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get the two foxtauresses turned on and eager as can be for what's coming, you start making several flirtatious remarks about Fae's and Silvia's appearances. More than happy to respond in kind, the two of them start grinding up against you, and as they press their equally-large, [fae.cupSize]-cup breasts into your body, the two sisters start taking things up a notch.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(Do you prefer fox cock or pussy?)] Fae bluntly asks, before stroking her hand down towards your groin.
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(We don't mind which you want to use,)] Silvia adds, [silvia.speech(Oh, and we like having our tits fucked too.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out synchronised, horny moans, the two sisters heavily lean into you and start excitedly feeling you up. With your flirting having a far greater impact than you'd hoped for, you're left wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get on with it, you lean over towards Fae and press your [pc.lips+] against her mouth, before giving her a big, wet kiss. Instantly, she responds by desperately clambering forwards into your lap, pressing her lips firmly against yours and forcing her tongue into your mouth. Grinding up against you, she starts letting out a series of high-pitched, muffled whines, and after spending a moment passionately making out with you, she pulls back and breathlessly pants, [fae.speech(Oh yeah... That's what I've been wanting...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not one to sit back and miss out on the fun, Silvia reaches up and grabs your head, before pulling your face towards hers and desperately pressing her lips against yours. Just like her sister, the horny foxtauress forces her pierced tongue into your mouth, and after pushing her sister back, she takes Fae's place in your lap and starts wildly grinding up against you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(That's not fair. I want another go,)] Fae complains, before moving forwards and jostling against her sister for the prime position on your lap. With the two foxtauresses fighting over your mouth, you find yourself suddenly switching between making out with Silvia, then Fae, then Silvia again. After ten minutes of this awkward, passionate make out session, the two sisters call a truce, and both look down at you with a hungry gleam in their green and blue eyes.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(Come on, [pc.name],)] Fae whines.
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(Let's go somewhere where we can fuck,)] Silvia finishes.
	</p>
	<p>
		With the two sisters clearly desperate for sex, you wonder whether or not to invite them back to your room at 'The Red Dragon'...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_TAKE_HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to do more than just kiss these horny sisters, you ask Fae and Silvia if they'd like to accompany you back to your room in 'The Red Dragon'. Happily responding in the positive, the two foxtauresses stand up on either side of you, and with a firm grip on your [pc.arms], they join you in crossing the tavern's floor and heading towards the exit. 
	</p>
	<p>
		With the two of them telling you all sorts of lewd things they'd like to do with you tonight, you lead Fae and Silvia down the street to 'The Red Dragon', and after heading through the building and up the stairs, you soon find yourself at the door to your room. After waiting for you to unlock the door, the sisters step inside, after which Fae turns to face you and moan, [fae.speech(I've been looking forward to this...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(My pussy's so wet,)] Silvia adds, [silvia.speech(I <i>need</i> a good fuck!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your foxtauress companions absolutely desperate to get started, you wonder whether to take the lead or submit to them...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_TAKE_HOME_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to stay in control of the situation, you [pc.step] forwards and dominantly take hold of Fae and Silvia. Pulling them into your body, you tell them to be good girls for you tonight.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(Very well,)] Fae moans, [fae.speech(But you'd better be able to satisfy us...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(I hope you don't mind if we make a mess in your room,)] Silvia giggles, motioning back towards both her and Fae's rapidly-hardening fox-cocks.
	</p>
	<p>
		Planting a quick, dominant kiss on each of their lips, you wonder how best to start things off...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_TAKE_HOME_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to be the one who's in control of the situation, you [pc.step] forwards and submissively ask Fae and Silvia to take the lead. Grabbing hold of you, they pull you forwards and squish their [fae.cupSize]-cup breasts into either side of your torso.
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(Very well,)] Fae moans, [fae.speech(We'll be sure to have our fun with you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(I hope you don't mind if we make a mess in your room,)] Silvia giggles, motioning back towards both her and Fae's rapidly-hardening fox-cocks.
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the two foxtauresses take turns to plant a wet, dominant kiss on your lips, before starting to really get things going...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_TAKE_HOME_DOGGY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to submit to these horny sisters, you tell them that you'd like them to dominantly fuck you in the doggy-style position. Smirking as she hears you say this, Fae grabs hold of you and firmly, yet carefully, pushes you down onto the floor. Quickly gaining access to your pussy, she moans, [fae.speech(Sure thing, [pc.name]. I wouldn't mind railing this hot cunt of yours tonight...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(You can use your mouth on me, then,)] Silvia decides, before trotting around in front of you and flicking her tail aside to present you with her
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 [silvia.pussy+], [silvia.asshole+], and rapidly-hardening scarlet fox-cock.
		#ELSE
			 [silvia.pussy+] and rapidly-hardening scarlet fox-cock.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Wasting no further time, Fae steps over the top of you and starts rubbing the head of her [fae.cock+] up and down over your exposed pussy. Letting out an excited moan, she thrusts forwards, sinking her throbbing length into your cunt and causing you to let out a desperate, deep moan.
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(Don't forget me!)] Silvia exclaims, and before you can react, she steps back and pushes her sopping-wet pussy against your mouth. Forced to perform cunnilingus on her, you start kissing and licking the blue-eyed foxtauress's cunt while her green-eyed sister relentlessly pounds your pussy from behind...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_TAKE_HOME_DOGGY_ANAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to submit to these horny sisters, you tell them that you'd like them to dominantly fuck your ass in the doggy-style position. Smirking as she hears you say this, Fae grabs hold of you and firmly, yet carefully, pushes you down onto the floor. Quickly gaining access to your asshole, she moans, [fae.speech(Sure thing, [pc.name]. I wouldn't mind railing this hot butt of yours tonight...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(You can use your mouth on me, then,)] Silvia decides, before trotting around in front of you and flicking her tail aside to present you with her [silvia.pussy+], [silvia.asshole+], and rapidly-hardening scarlet fox-cock.
	</p>
	<p>
		Wasting no further time, Fae steps over the top of you and starts rubbing the head of her [fae.cock+] up and down over your exposed asshole. Letting out an excited moan, she thrusts forwards, sinking her throbbing length into your ass and causing you to let out a desperate, deep moan.
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(Don't forget me!)] Silvia exclaims, and before you can react, she steps back and pushes her sopping-wet pussy against your mouth. Forced to perform cunnilingus on her, you start kissing and licking the blue-eyed foxtauress's cunt while her green-eyed sister relentlessly pounds your [pc.asshole+] from behind...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(fae.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			#IF(silvia.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
				Both of the foxtauress sisters let out an extremely satisfied sigh, before stepping over to collapse down onto your bed. Panting for breath, Fae says, [fae.speech(That was... amazing... We really needed that tonight, [pc.name]...)]
			#ELSE
				Having had her fun, Fae lets out an extremely contented sigh and steps over to collapse down onto your bed. On the other hand, Silvia doesn't seem to have been satisfied by tonight's sex, and whines, [silvia.speech(How disappointing... I expected more from you, [pc.name]...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(silvia.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			Having had her fun, Silvia lets out an extremely contented sigh and steps over to collapse down onto your bed. On the other hand, Fae doesn't seem to have been satisfied by tonight's sex, and whines, [fae.speech(How disappointing... I expected more from you, [pc.name]...)]
		#ELSE
			Neither of the foxtauress sisters seem to have been satisfied by tonight's sex, and Fae whines in annoyance, [fae.speech(How disappointing... I expected more from you, [pc.name]...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As the three of you take a moment in which to recover your stamina, you wonder whether to invite the two sisters to stay the night with you, or instead simply say goodbye and have them leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting the foxtauresses to stay over tonight, you tell them that you enjoyed your evening and that you hope to do it again another time.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(fae.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			#IF(silvia.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
				Taking the hint, the satisfied sisters put their clothing back on and step forwards to plant one last pair of kisses on your [pc.lips+]. Smiling at you, Fae sighs, [fae.speech(We really had a lot of fun tonight, [pc.name]. Thanks for everything...)]
			#ELSE
				Taking the hint, the sisters put their clothing back on and step forwards to plant one last pair of kisses on your [pc.lips+]. Pouting at you, Silvia sighs, [silvia.speech(Please try to satisfy me the next time we do this, [pc.name]...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(silvia.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			Taking the hint, the sisters put their clothing back on and step forwards to plant one last pair of kisses on your [pc.lips+]. Pouting at you, Fae sighs, [fae.speech(Please try to satisfy me the next time we do this, [pc.name]...)]
		#ELSE
			Taking the hint, the sisters put their clothing back on and step forwards to plant one last pair of kisses on your [pc.lips+]. After both sisters have taken a moment in which to pout at you, Fae sighs, [fae.speech(Please try to satisfy us the next time we do this, [pc.name]...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the two of them step out of your room and head off down the corridor, leaving you wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_SLEEP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have some company tonight, you ask the sisters if they'd like to sleep here with you. Exchanging a happy smirk with one another, Fae and Silvia strip out of their remaining clothes, throw back the covers, and slide into your bed. Patting the space between them, Silvia sighs, [silvia.speech(Come on, [pc.name]... Plenty of room for all three of us in here...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Stripping naked, you drop down onto the bed between the two foxtauresses. Letting out a synchronised moan, Fae and Silvia flick their big, fluffy tails over the top of you, before pulling the covers up and snuggling in against you. With their big, naked breasts squished up against you on either side, and with their fluffy tails providing you with an extra layer of comfort, the two foxtauresses let out satisfied sighs and join you in quickly falling asleep...
	</p>
	<p>
		...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		You dream of a huge mass of soft, orange fur chasing you throughout the streets of Elis. Every time you seem to escape, the sentient mass manages to catch you and envelop you in its soft fur. Just as you start to despair, a huge fox-cock falls from the sky and scatters the fur into the wind. With the furry ball defeated, this huge cock turns its attention towards you, and relentlessly starts slapping itself against your face...
	</i></p>
	<p>
		...
	</p>
	<p>
		[fae.speech(Come on, [pc.name], it's not going to suck itself...)] Fae's voice wakes you from your slumber, and you open your eyes to see that the foxtauress has stepped over the top of you and lowered her groin down over your face. A bead of salty, musky precum is beading from the tip of her massive erection, and as she playfully slaps it against your face, she moans, [fae.speech(Come on, [pc.name], you'll help me out, won't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment you become aware of hot breath falling on your groin, and you hear Silvia call out from down the bed, [silvia.speech(Help Fae out and I'll return the favour for her...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the tip of Fae's cock dropping down towards your [pc.lips+], you only have a moment in which to articulate your response...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_SLEEP_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to suck Fae's cock, you roll over to one side and tell her that you're not interested. Letting out a disappointed whine, she steps off your bed before pouting at you and huffing, [fae.speech(Fine... Guess I'll have to go and find someone downstairs who's willing to jerk me off or something...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the two sisters put their clothing back on, before stepping forwards to plant one last pair of kisses on your [pc.lips+]. As Fae says goodbye and heads towards the door, Silvia smiles at you and says, [silvia.speech(Thanks for the fun last night, and for letting us sleep over. See you around, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping over to the door, Fae and Silvia give you one last wave, and then with a swish of their big, fluffy fox tails, they head out of your room and head off down the corridor, leaving you wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_SLEEP_SEX_COCK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to make Fae happy, you tell her that you'll help her get some release, before opening your mouth and waiting for her to make the next move. Letting out a delighted moan as she sees how eager you are, Fae drops her hips down and slides the [fae.cockHead+] of her [fae.cock+] into your waiting mouth. Wrapping your [pc.lips+] around her hot shaft, you start eagerly sucking her off, which causes her to desperately pant, [fae.speech(~Mmm!~ Oh yes... ~Aah!~ You're good at this...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			As you start to suck Fae's cock, Silvia lets out a hungry moan, and the next thing you know you're feeling her [silvia.lips+] planting a big, wet kiss on the [pc.cockHead] of your own cock. Letting out a happy giggle as she watches your cock stand to attention, Fae's blue-eyed sister opens wide and takes your [pc.cock+] into her mouth. With you sucking Fae's cock, and Silvia doing the same to yours, you lie back and enjoy this unexpected form of a morning wakeup...
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasVagina())
			As you start to suck Fae's cock, Silvia lets out a hungry moan, and the next thing you know you're feeling her [silvia.lips+] planting a big, wet kiss on your [pc.labia+]. Letting out a happy giggle as she slides her tongue over the length of your pussy, Fae's blue-eyed sister leans forwards and presses her mouth against your exposed cunt. With you sucking Fae's cock, and Silvia starting to eat you out, you lie back and enjoy this unexpected form of a morning wakeup...
		#ELSE
			[silvia.speech(I can't do anything down here...)] Silvia calls out as you start to suck Fae's cock. With no way to perform oral on you, Silvia simply lets out a frustrated sigh and watches as her sister fucks your throat...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_SLEEP_SEX_PUSSY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to make Fae happy, but not willing to suck her cock, you tell her that you'll help her get some release by eating her out, before opening your mouth and waiting for her to make the next move. Letting out a delighted moan as she sees how eager you are, Fae drops her hips down and presses her [fae.labia+] down over your mouth. Planting a big, wet kiss on her [fae.pussy+], you start eagerly eating her out, which causes her to desperately pant, [fae.speech(~Mmm!~ Oh yes... ~Aah!~ You're good at this...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			As you start to service Fae's pussy, Silvia lets out a hungry moan, and the next thing you know you're feeling her [silvia.lips+] planting a big, wet kiss on the [pc.cockHead] of your [pc.cock+]. Letting out a happy giggle as she watches your cock stand to attention, Fae's blue-eyed sister opens wide and takes your [pc.cock+] into her mouth. With you licking and kissing Fae's cunt, and Silvia starting to give you a blowjob, you lie back and enjoy this unexpected form of a morning wakeup...
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasVagina())
			As you start to service Fae's pussy, Silvia lets out a hungry moan, and the next thing you know you're feeling her [silvia.lips+] planting a big, wet kiss on your [pc.labia+]. Letting out a happy giggle as she slides her tongue over the length of your pussy, Fae's blue-eyed sister leans forwards and presses her mouth against your exposed cunt. With you licking and kissing Fae's cunt, and Silvia doing the same to yours, you lie back and enjoy this unexpected form of a morning wakeup...
		#ELSE
			[silvia.speech(I can't do anything down here...)] Silvia calls out as you start to service Fae's pussy. With no way to perform oral on you, Silvia simply lets out a frustrated sigh and watches as her sister sits on your face...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_SLEEP_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(fae.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			#IF(silvia.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
				Both of the foxtauress sisters let out an extremely satisfied sigh, before Fae rolls over onto your bed and moans, [fae.speech(~Mmm!~ That was just what I needed... Thanks, [pc.name]...)]
			#ELSE
				Having had her fun, Fae lets out an extremely contented sigh and rolls over onto your bed. On the other hand, Silvia doesn't seem to have been satisfied by this morning's sex, and whines, [silvia.speech(I kind of wanted more than that...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(silvia.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			Having had her fun, Silvia lets out an extremely contented sigh and rolls over onto your bed. On the other hand, Fae doesn't seem to have been satisfied by this morning's sex, and whines, [fae.speech(I needed more than that...)]
		#ELSE
			Neither of the foxtauress sisters seem to have been satisfied by this morning's sex, and Fae whines in annoyance, [fae.speech(I needed more than that...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Spending the next few minutes getting your breath back and fully waking up, the three of you prepare to start your day...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING_FAE_SLEEP_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that the foxtauress sisters need to head off and get their stall at the Farmer's Market set up, you say goodbye to them and tell them that you had a lot of fun with them last night.
	</p>
	<p>
		[silvia.speech(We had fun too,)] Silvia replies, before joining her sister in leaning forwards and planting one last pair of kisses on your [pc.lips+]. Heading over to the door, the two of them give you one last wave, and then with a swish of their big, fluffy fox tails, they head out of your room and set off down the corridor, leaving you wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Misc.: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STAIRS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Opposite the toilets, there's a particularly wide staircase leading up to the tavern's upper floor. As you don't have any business up there, you decide that there's no point in travelling up these stairs, and instead turn around and prepare to head back into the tavern...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TABLES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In order to accommodate the large bodies of its tauric patrons, this tavern's floor area has been extended on all sides in order to make it as spacious as possible. Dozens of tables have been placed throughout this vast area, and you see that instead of chairs, each of them is surrounded by comfortable floor mats upon which taurs can either sit or lie.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isHourBetween(15, 24))
			As it's currently the busy time of the day, the tavern is almost completely full of taurs of every type imaginable. All but a couple of the tables before you are occupied by these tauric customers, who are happily drinking and filling the room with sounds of their drunken revelry. 
		#ELSE
			As it's currently the quiet time of the day, the tavern is almost completely empty. There are however a few taurs who are sitting at a couple of the tables, and you watch for a moment as they happily drink and talk with one another.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(sterope))
		<p>
			Although she's almost unrecognisable from how she appears while on duty, you notice that one of the people sitting at a nearby table is none other than the [sterope.race] Enforcer, Sterope. Instead of her smart uniform, she's wearing a hot pink plunge-neck clubbing dress, strappy sandals, and a whole host of rose gold jewellery. Around her neck she's wearing a bdsm-style leather collar, and although you're not close enough to see what's written on its tag, you get the impression that it's something degrading. Pink nail polish, as well as a heavy layer of pink lipstick, finishes off her rather slutty look.
		</p>
		<p>
			She appears to be alone at the moment, and so if you wanted to, you could freely [pc.walk] up to her and say hello...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LOCKED_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself at the end of the corridor, you're confronted by a locked door. A sign beside this door declares that it leads to the tavern's stable, with the word 'Private' written beneath that.
	</p>
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_with_centaur))
		<p>
			Over the background noise of the tavern, you can hear noises coming from the other side of the door. It sounds like a combination of frenzied neighing and rhythmic thudding, and you realise that you're hearing
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_met_in_tavern))
				 Sterope getting fucked hard by the taur she's chosen to be with this evening.
			#ELSE
				 someone getting fucked hard.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		As you don't have the key to this door, there's little else for you to do except turn around and head back into the tavern...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LOCKED_DOOR_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You [pc.step] back from the locked door and wonder where to go next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STABLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		<i>You're not supposed to be able to get here! >:(</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Toilets: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing before the door to the tavern's toilets, and subsequently find yourself with the rather limited options of either heading inside or turning around and returning to the corridor...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS_INTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to make use of the tavern's toilets, you push open the wide door and head inside. Consisting of several huge stalls and a few tall sinks, these facilities are quite clearly designed with taurs in mind, and look to be kept in an admirably clean condition.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF((game.getHourOfDay()>=15 && game.getHourOfDay()<=23))
			Due to the busy time of day there are already a few taurs in here, and so if you wanted to use one of the toilets it looks like you'll have to wait for a minute or two before one of the occupied stalls becomes available.
		#ELSE
			Due to the quiet time of day there's nobody else in here, and so if you wanted to use one of the toilets there's nothing stopping you from entering one of the free stalls.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having no further need of the tavern's toilet facilities, you swiftly head over to the door and make your exit...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS_USE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF((game.getHourOfDay()>=15 && game.getHourOfDay()<=23))
			After waiting for a couple of minutes, one of the stalls becomes available, and so after [pc.stepping] into it and locking the door behind you, you make use of the toilet.
		#ELSE
			[pc.Stepping] into one of the empty stalls, you turn and lock the door behind you, before making use of the toilet.
		#ENDIF
		 After you've finished, you flush the toilet before making your way over to one of the sinks and washing your [pc.hands]. Grabbing a paper towel from the nearby dispenser, you quickly dry yourself off, before turning to face the room and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS_WASH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling like you could do with having a quick clean, you step over to the sinks and thoroughly wash your [pc.hands], before splashing some water on your [pc.face]. Grabbing a paper towel from the nearby dispenser, you quickly dry yourself off, before turning to face the room and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Sterope: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_with_centaur))
		<p>
			Deciding to see what Sterope is up to this evening, you head on over to the [sterope.race]'s table.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you draw near, [centaur.a_fullRace(true)] suddenly returns to the table carrying two drinks. [centaur.She] puts one down before Sterope, before sitting down beside her and brazenly slipping a hand down into the top of her dress.
		</p>
		<p>
			As her companion starts roughly molesting her breasts, Sterope suddenly catches sight of you.
			#IF(pc.isTaur())
				 Looking you up and down with a hungry gleam in her [sterope.eyes+], she calls out,
			#ELSE
				 Looking you up and down, she sighs and calls out,
			#ENDIF
			 [sterope.speech(Hey, [pc.name]... ~Mmm!~ I've already got company tonight...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pulling one of Sterope's [sterope.breasts+] out of her dress, the [centaur.race] grunts as [centaur.she] squeezes it, before tugging on her nipple rings. Ignoring Sterope's lewd moans, [centaur.she] continues playing with her [sterope.nipples+] as [centaur.she] looks you in the eye and
			#IF(pc.isFeminine())
				 asks, [centaur.speech(So, are you a dumb bitch here to be fucked like this worthless cunt? Come and join us, slut.)]
			#ELSE
				 snaps, [centaur.speech(Fuck off. This worthless cunt's mine tonight. Unless you want to join her and submit to me?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Now close enough to see what's written on the tag of Sterope's collar, you see that it reads 'Worthless Cunt'. Realising that Sterope is all too happy to be treated in such a degrading manner, you
			#IF(pc.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE) && pc.isAttractedTo(centaur))
				 wonder whether to join her and submit to this [centaur.race]...
			#ELSEIF(pc.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT) || pc.hasFetish(FETISH_SADIST))
				 wonder whether to take the [centaur.race]'s place by telling [centaur.herHim] that the [sterope.race] is yours...
			#ELSE
				 wonder what to do about it...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(sterope.getSexCount(pc).getTotalTimesHadSex()>0)
			<p>
				Deciding to see what Sterope is up to this evening, you head on over to the [sterope.race]'s table.
				#IF(pc.isTaur())
					  Catching sight of you, she looks you up and down with a hungry gleam in her [sterope.eyes+], before greeting you, [sterope.speech(Hi, [pc.name]. You know, I'm kind of into taurs... And we both know you're kind of into me...)]
				#ELSE
					  Catching sight of you, she looks you up and down, before sighing and greeting you, [sterope.speech(Hi, [pc.name]. You know, I'm normally only into taurs, but thinking back on the last evening we spent together, I think I can make an exception for you...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				Now close enough to see what's written on the tag of Sterope's collar, you see that it reads 'Worthless Cunt'. Before you can respond to her greeting, she licks her lips and flatly states, [sterope.speech(You know the drill. No flirting, small talk, or any of that bullshit. You want to dominate me, punish me, and fuck me hard? Then claim me.)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Deciding to see what Sterope is up to this evening, you head on over to the [sterope.race]'s table.
				#IF(pc.isTaur())
					  Catching sight of you, she looks you up and down with a hungry gleam in her [sterope.eyes+], before greeting you, [sterope.speech(Hi, [pc.name]. You know, I'm kind of into taurs...)]
				#ELSE
					  Catching sight of you, she looks you up and down, before sighing and greeting you, [sterope.speech(Hi, [pc.name]. You know, I'm normally only into taurs, but I think I can make an exception for you...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				Now close enough to see what's written on the tag of Sterope's collar, you see that it reads 'Worthless Cunt'. Before you can respond to her greeting, she licks her lips and flatly states, [sterope.speech(I'm not here for judging pick-up lines, making small talk, or flirting for hours on end. You want to fuck me hard? You ready to tie me up and make me your obedient sex slave? You want to spank me, whip me, shove a dildo in my cunt and fuck my face?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Leaning back in her chair and allowing a smirk to settle on her face, she ends by stating, [sterope.speech(If you want me, then claim me. If not, then fuck off.)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_with_centaur))
		<p>
			Deciding that you'll leave Sterope to her dominant partner, you say a brief goodbye and [pc.step] away from their table.
		</p>
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(I'm ready to fuck you now, bitch. Let's get you tied up in the stable,)] you hear the [centaur.race] grunt as you depart. Looking back, you see the excitement on Sterope's face as she's dragged over to one corner of the tavern by her partner. As the two of them disappear from sight, you wonder what to do next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Deciding that you don't want to spend the evening with Sterope, you say a brief goodbye and [pc.step] away from her table.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(Suit yourself, but don't blame me if you change your mind later and come back to find that I'm gone,)] the [sterope.race] states, [sterope.speech(I'm going with the first taur who hits on me.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Continuing to put some distance between yourself and Sterope's table, you wonder where to go next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CLAIMED"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_with_centaur))
		<p>
			Wanting Sterope for yourself, you tell the [centaur.race] that she's yours, and that you're going to be claiming her tonight. Letting out a laugh as [centaur.she] continues to molest Sterope's breasts, the [centaur.race] declares, [centaur.speech(It doesn't matter what you say; this slut's with me, and she's going to get fucked by me tonight, aren't you, you dumb cunt?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Squealing in delight as her dominant partner tugs on her nipple rings, Sterope submissively moans, [sterope.speech(Yes... I'm yours...)]
		</p>
		#IF(pc.hasFetish(FETISH_SADIST))
			<p>
				Deciding that the best way to handle this is by putting the bitch in her place, you [pc.step] forwards and deliver a sharp slap across Sterope's face. Grabbing hold of her wrist, you roughly yank her to her feet, before pulling her into your body and asking her who's going to be the one fucking her tonight.
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Deciding that the best way to handle this is by asserting your dominance over Sterope, you [pc.step] forwards and grab hold of the [sterope.race]'s wrist. Pulling her to her feet, you use one [pc.arm(true)] to hug her into your body, before asking her who's going to be the one fucking her tonight.
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(You, [pc.name],)] the fickle [sterope.race] submissively moans.
		</p>
		<p>
			Having had Sterope taken from [centaur.herHim] in such a dominant manner, the [centaur.race] decides that it's not worth the escalation to try and take her back. Pushing the table away from [centaur.herHim] as [centaur.she] stands up, [centaur.she] grunts, [centaur.speech(Whatever. I'll find some other slut.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After watching the [centaur.race] leave, Sterope turns to look at you and desperately pants, [sterope.speech(Come on, I've rented the stable behind this place. Take me there, tie me up, and fuck me hard!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With your prize eagerly grinding up against you, all that's left now is to take Sterope to the stable and give her the hard fucking she wants...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Liking the sound of what Sterope wants, you [pc.step] forwards and tell her that she's going to be yours tonight. Smirking as she hears this, the insolent [sterope.race] teases, [sterope.speech(Oh, really? Words aren't going to cut it. Show me what you've got.)]
		</p>
		#IF(pc.hasFetish(FETISH_SADIST))
			<p>
				Deciding that the best way to handle this is by putting the bitch in her place, you [pc.step] forwards and deliver a sharp slap across Sterope's face. Grabbing hold of her wrist, you roughly yank her to her feet, before pulling her into your body and asking her who's going to be the one fucking her tonight.
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Deciding that the best way to handle this is by asserting your dominance over Sterope, you [pc.step] forwards and grab hold of the [sterope.race]'s wrist. Pulling her to her feet, you use one [pc.arm(true)] to hug her into your body, before asking her who's going to be the one fucking her tonight.
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(You, [pc.name],)] she submissively moans, [sterope.speech(Come on, I've rented the stable behind this place. Take me there, tie me up, and fuck me hard!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With your prize eagerly grinding up against you, all that's left now is to take Sterope to the stable and give her the hard fucking she wants...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- STEROPE_ATTRACT_TAUR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_ATTRACT_TAUR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting a repeat of the threesome you and Sterope previously had, you tell the [sterope.race] that you aren't here to claim her, but instead were hoping to join her in the stable in a submissive role.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(You want it, you'll have to earn it,)] Sterope states, before gesturing to the room and ordering, [sterope.speech(Get a taur to come over here and claim us, and you can tag along for a good, hard fuck.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eagerly doing as you're told, you look around the tavern, trying to find a taur who's both alone and who seems to be looking for company. Thankfully, you quickly spot [centaur.a_fullRace(true)] who's drinking alone at a table nearby. Catching [centaur.her] eye, you flash your potential partner a coy look, before gesturing for [centaur.herHim] to come on over.
	</p>
	<p>
		[centaur.speech(You two looking for a good time?)] [centaur.she] asks as [centaur.she] [centaur.walks] up to where you and Sterope are sitting.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(That depends,)] the [sterope.race] replies, [sterope.speech(on whether or not you want to tie us up, spank us, and give us the hardest, roughest fucking of our lives.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a hungry growl, the [centaur.race] sits down between the two of you, and within moments [centaur.her] [centaur.hands] are roughly groping Sterope's [sterope.breasts+]. From the lewd noises and submissive comments the [sterope.race] starts making, it seems as though she's happy with your choice of taur.
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning to you, [centaur.name] grabs your [pc.breasts+] and starts giving you the same treatment, before asking, [centaur.speech(You're the one who called me over, so are you going to submit to me like your slut of a friend here?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- TODO -->
	
	<!-- STEROPE_STABLES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You keep a firm grip on Sterope and tell her to be a good, submissive slut for you as the two of you head over to the far corner of the tavern.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(I've got the key,)] the [sterope.race] declares as you pass by the toilets and come to a halt in front of a locked door. Quickly unlocking it, the [sterope.race] steps into the stable beyond, calling over her shoulder as she does so, [sterope.speech(Here's where the fun happens...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following your partner inside, you lock the door behind you, before taking a good look at your surroundings. The stable appears to be nothing more than what you'd expect, and comes complete with the usual wooden stalls, hay-covered stone floor, and a couple of wooden tables. Beside one of these tables, there's a good deal of rope sitting on top of a wooden chest, and you realise that this is what's to be used to tie Sterope up.
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning your attention back to the [sterope.race], you see her slipping out of her dress, before kicking off her strappy heels and sliding her thong down her legs. After removing her earrings, she ends up being completely naked, except for the pink leather collar around her neck and the multitude of other piercings over her body. Playfully teasing her fingers over her [sterope.breasts+] and [sterope.pussy+], she winks at you and lets out a playful giggle.
	</p>
	#IF(sterope.getRaceStage()!=RACE_STAGE_GREATER)
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(I'm kind of into transformations,)] she coyly teases as she opens the chest and produces a glass bottle. Excitedly biting her lip, she reveals, [sterope.speech(If I drink this, I'll transform into a greater horse-girl. It makes it sexier being dominated when I'm turned into more of an animal...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As she playfully sways the bottle from side to side, you wonder whether to tell Sterope to drink the contents and turn into a greater horse-girl, or to instead get right on with tying her up...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(game.isFeralContentEnabled())
		<p>
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_transformed_into_feral))
				[sterope.speech(I'd like to transform into a mare again...)] she breathlessly moans as she throws the sheet off of a small boulder in one corner of the stable. As the beast stone is revealed, she reminds you, [sterope.speech(These used to be super popular years ago, but they fell out of favour and are now pretty taboo. For every ten minutes spent touching it, you get transformed into a feral form for four hours. Fifteen minutes should be enough for me to turn into a mare until morning... That is, if you're up for it?)]
			#ELSE
				[sterope.speech(Having spent time in my new form, I feel like I need to transform more...)] she breathlessly moans as she runs her hands over her anthropomorphic body. Excitedly biting her lip, she throws a sheet off of what turns out to be a small boulder in one corner of the stable, before revealing, [sterope.speech(A beast stone. They used to be super popular years ago, but they fell out of favour and are now pretty taboo. For every ten minutes spent touching it, you get transformed into a feral form for four hours. Fifteen minutes should be enough for me to turn into a mare until morning... That is, if you're up for it?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF(pc.getTrueRace()!=RACE_HORSE_MORPH && !pc.isAbleToHaveRaceTransformed())
			<p>
				Looking over at the beast stone, you wonder whether to tell Sterope to transform herself into a feral mare for the rest of the night, or to instead remain in her anthropomorphic form...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				#IF(pc.getTrueRace()!=RACE_HORSE_MORPH)
					As you look over at the beast stone, Sterope produces a potion from out of the chest. Enthusiastically clutching it in her hands, she offers, [sterope.speech(If you drink this, it'll turn you into a greater #IF(pc.isFeminine())horse-girl,#ELSEhorse-boy,#ENDIF and then you can join me in touching the beast stone. We could fuck as animals all night long...)]
				#ELSE
					As you look over at the beast stone, Sterope makes another suggestion, [sterope.speech(You could always join me in touching the beast stone... We could fuck as animals all night long...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				As she impatiently waits to hear what your choice will be, you wonder whether to have Sterope transform herself into a feral mare for the rest of the night, join her in that transformation, or to instead tell her to remain in her anthropomorphic form...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having already been permanently transformed into a greater horse-girl, there's no suggestion of further transformations from Sterope. Instead, she simply asks, [sterope.speech(So, are you going to tie me up and make me your bitch, or do you want me to beg for it?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smirking at her words, you advance on Sterope and prepare to tie her up...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_TIE_UP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(sterope.getRaceStage()!=RACE_STAGE_GREATER || game.isFeralContentEnabled())
			Not wanting Sterope to transform herself, you grab hold of the [sterope.race] and tell her that she's going to stay the way she is.
		#ELSE
			Wanting to get on with it, you grab hold of the [sterope.race] and tell her that she's your bitch.
		#ENDIF
		 Letting out a horny moan, she begs, [sterope.speech(Come on then, tie me up and punish me!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_TRANSFORM_TIE_UP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting Sterope to transform into a greater horse-girl, you command her to drink the potion and become your slutty mare. Letting out a horny moan as she hears you say this, she quickly downs the liquid and pants, [sterope.speech(Yes... I'll be your good little mare...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Right before your eyes, you watch [sterope.skinColour] horse-like hair spread all over Sterope's body. Her legs transform into anthropomorphic equine ones, complete with hoofs, and after the her arms and torso have transformed into their horse-like counterparts, her face begins to change. Elongating and transforming into a muzzle, her face takes on the look of an anthropomorphic horse. The transformation is over almost as quickly as it began, and now standing before you is [sterope.a_raceFull(true)].
	</p>
	<p>
		Coyly shuffling her hoofs around on the stone floor, Sterope lets out a horny little neigh, before begging, [sterope.speech(Come on then, tie your little mare up and punish her!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_TIE_UP_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Giving her what she wants, you grab hold of the rope that's been left beside one of the tables. Following Sterope's guidance, you wrap the rope around her limbs, tying it in knots as you go. Soon enough you've bound her from head to toe, and after pushing her down over the table and securing the rope to the wooden legs, you've left her completely unable to move. Thanks to the table's small top, Sterope's upper half is hanging over the edge, leaving her [sterope.breasts+] dangling and swaying about as she struggles against her bindings.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Fuck!)] she cries out. Looking down at her ass, you see that Sterope has been inked with a black, tribal-style tramp-stamp tattoo, complete with the words <i>'Break this bitch!'</i>. Your attention is swiftly drawn away from this, however, as the horny [sterope.race] lets out another moan and reveals, [sterope.speech(There are some toys in the chest. Or you can just fuck me. Do whatever you want to me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Opening the chest, you see a riding crop, nipple clamps, a ring gag, a blindfold,
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 a dildo, and a string of anal beads.
		#ELSE
			 and a dildo.
		#ENDIF
		 Delivering a quick slap to Sterope's [sterope.ass+], you wonder whether to use these toys on her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_TRANSFORM_FERAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of getting to fuck Sterope in the form of a feral mare, you tell her to touch the beast stone. Letting out an excited whimper, she takes off her leather collar and obediently drops to her knees beside the small boulder, before placing one of her hands on it. A faint purple glow washes over the [sterope.race]'s body, and she excitedly moans, [sterope.speech(I'll be ready in fifteen minutes...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eagerly anticipating what's to come, you pace around the stable as you wait for the fifteen minutes to pass. Finally, Sterope calls out, [sterope.speech(I'm ready now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Returning to where she's kneeling down on the floor, you watch as the [sterope.race] lets go of the beast stone. The purple glow which was surrounding her suddenly shoots into her body, and she lets out a desperate, shuddering moan as she starts to transform.
	</p>
	<p>
		Her transformation starts with a second pair of horse legs growing out of her lower stomach. Accompanying this alarming change, her ass begins to swell and grow in size. Within seconds, her lower body from the waist down has transformed into the form of a full-sized horse. Sterope's arms then rapidly shrink into her torso, before her upper body shrinks down and transforms into a long, thick neck. Her horse-like face then increases in size, losing its anthropomorphic qualities as it transforms into that of a feral horse.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Fuck...)] the feral mare pants as she stands up on her four, shaking legs. Although she's now in the form of an animal, Sterope is clearly still able to speak, and as she turns to face you, you notice that there's a distinct look of intelligence in her otherwise horse-like eyes. Letting out a playful whinny, she trots forwards and teases, [sterope.speech(This is what you wanted, right? Now tie me up and fuck me like the dumb mare I am...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving her what she wants, you grab hold of the rope that's been left beside one of the tables. Following Sterope's guidance, you wrap the rope around her limbs, tying it in knots as you go. Soon enough you've bound her legs and tied her down to four metal rings that are set into the floor. Giving her ass a hard slap, you watch as she struggles against her bonds and see that she's now completely unable to move.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Fuck!)] the mare cries out as she flicks her tail to one side in order to show off her feral horse pussy. Letting out another horny whinny, she reveals, [sterope.speech(There are some toys in the chest. Or you can just fuck me. Do whatever you want to me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Opening the chest, you see a riding crop, nipple clamps, a blindfold,
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 a dildo, and a string of anal beads.
		#ELSE
			 and a dildo.
		#ENDIF
		 Beside these toys, there's also a full set of tack equipment, consisting of a bridle, saddle, horseshoes, and tail bandage. Delivering another quick slap to Sterope's [sterope.ass+], you wonder whether to use these toys on her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_TRANSFORM_FERAL_BOTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of transforming into a feral #IF(pc.isFeminine())mare#ELSEstallion#ENDIF and then getting to fuck Sterope in the form of a feral mare,
		#IF(pc.getTrueRace()!=RACE_HORSE_MORPH)
			 you take the transformative potion and drink it all in one long gulp. Sterope playfully bites her lip and lets out an eager moan as you tell her that you'll join her in touching the beast stone.
		#ELSE
			 you tell her that you'll join her in touching the beast stone.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(pc.getTrueRace()!=RACE_HORSE_MORPH)
		<p>
			As you finish saying this, you feel your transformation begin. Horse-like hair quickly grows to cover your entire body, before your feet transform and shift into hoofs. A horse-like tail grows out from just above your ass, while your face pushes out into a long muzzle. Your ears drift up to sit on top of your head and grow up into horse ears, before your head finishes its transformation into becoming that of an anthropomorphised horse.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Eagerly anticipating what's to come, Sterope takes off her leather collar and quickly drops to her knees beside the small boulder, before placing one of her hands on it. A faint purple glow washes over the [sterope.race]'s body, and she excitedly moans, [sterope.speech(Come on, [pc.name]. Join me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she says, you join Sterope in touching the beast stone, and as you place your horse-like hand on its cool surface, you feel a surge of arcane energy wash over you. Along with Sterope, you maintain contact with the beast stone for fifteen minutes, before letting go of it at the same time. The purple glow which was surrounding both of you suddenly shoots into your bodies, and you each let out desperate, shuddering cries as you start to transform.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your transformation starts with a second pair of horse legs growing out of your lower stomach. Accompanying this alarming change, your ass begins to swell and grow in size. Within seconds, your lower body from the waist down has transformed into the form of a full-sized horse. You gasp as your arms then rapidly shrink into your torso, before your upper body shrinks down and transforms into a long, thick neck. Your horse-like face then increases in size, losing its anthropomorphic qualities as it transforms into that of a feral horse.
		#IF(pc.hasPenis())
			 Your feel your sheathed, horse-like cock swaying beneath your feral 
			#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				 body, and as a slight breeze passes over your fully-feral mare pussy,
			#ELSE
				 body, and
			#ENDIF
			 you find yourself letting out a primal, animalistic neigh, before finding your voice and telling Sterope that you're going to rut her hard.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasVagina())
			 As a slight breeze passes over your fully-feral mare pussy, you find yourself letting out a primal, animalistic neigh, before finding your voice and telling Sterope that you're going to fuck her hard.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Fuck...)] Sterope moans. Looking over to the now-feral mare, you watch her as she stands up on her four, shaking legs. Although she's now in the form of an animal, Sterope, just like you, is clearly still able to speak, and as she turns to face you, you notice that there's a distinct look of intelligence in her otherwise horse-like eyes. Letting out a playful whinny, she trots forwards and teases, [sterope.speech(This is what you wanted, right? Now you can mount and rut me like the dumb mare I am...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the mare turns around, before flicking her tail to one side in order to show off her feral horse pussy. Looking back over her shoulder, she moans, [sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Come on... Fuck me!)] 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- STEROPE_STABLES_CORE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_SPANKING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that Sterope is in need of a good, hard spanking, you grab her [sterope.tail] in one [pc.hand(true)] and pull it upwards.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(~Aah!~)] the [sterope.race] moans, before looking back over her shoulder and panting, [sterope.speech(Yes... Punish me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getArmRows()>1)
			Giving her what she wants, you raise your other [pc.hands], and by swinging them down one after the other in quick succession, you deliver a constant stream of sharp, stinging slaps to Sterope's [sterope.ass+].
		#ELSE
			Giving her what she wants, you raise your other [pc.hand(true)], and by swinging it down with considerable force, you deliver a sharp, stinging slap to Sterope's [sterope.ass+].
		#ENDIF
		 The [sterope.race] lets out a high-pitched cry as you begin administering her physical punishment, but you notice that it's more of a horny squeal than a painful shriek.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Fuck! ~Aah!~)] she screams as you continue slapping her ass. Encouraged by the lewd tone in her voice, you increase the intensity, and as you give the masochistic [sterope.race] a thorough spanking, she continues to cry out, [sterope.speech(~Ooh!~ Ow, ow, ow! ~Aah!~ Fuck! More!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You keep this up for some time, and after five minutes Sterope's ass
		#IF(sterope.getRaceStage()!=RACE_STAGE_GREATER)
			 is bright red.
		#ELSE
			 has been well and truly beaten.
		#ENDIF
		 As you bring an end to the spanking session, the [sterope.race] collapses down with a lewd, satisfied moan. Not yet finished with her, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_WHIPPING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Picking up the riding crop from out of the chest of toys, you experimentally flex it between your [pc.hands], before swinging it down through the air with considerable force. Hearing the distinctive swoosh of air as it cuts through the air, Sterope turns her head back and sees you holding the rod.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Fuck! ~Aah!~)] she cries out, before excitedly struggling against her rope bindings and moaning, [sterope.speech(Punish me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving the masochist what she wants, you swing the riding crop down again, but this time instead of cutting through thin air you direct it at the [sterope.race]'s [sterope.ass+]. A sharp, slapping <i>'crack'</i> rings out as the short whip strikes down against your target's [sterope.assSkin]. Immediately afterwards, Sterope lets out a shocked cry, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Encouraged to repeat the punishment as you hear that there's an underlying, horny tone to the [sterope.race]'s squeal, you raise the riding crop and swing it down again. Cracking the whip against Sterope's [sterope.ass+] over and over again, you've soon reduced her to a moaning, screaming wreck, who squeals with each strike, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Fuck!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After five minutes of administering this punishment, Sterope's ass
		#IF(sterope.getRaceStage()!=RACE_STAGE_GREATER)
			 is bright red.
		#ELSE
			 has been well and truly thrashed.
		#ENDIF
		 Finally setting the riding crop down, you give the [sterope.race]'s [sterope.ass+] a squeeze, making her let out a lewd, satisfied moan. With still more planned for her, you wonder what to do to Sterope next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_DEGRADING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to make sure that Sterope knows exactly how worthless she is, you grab her [sterope.ass+] and start greedily groping it, telling her as you molest her what a dumb slut she is.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Yes... I'm a worthless little cunt...)] she submissively moans in response. Pushing her ass back against you, she breathlessly pants, [sterope.speech(I'm all yours...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(sterope.isFeral())
			Moving your [pc.hands] down to grab hold of her crotch-boobs, you roughly squeeze them and tug on her thick teats. After degrading her by telling her what a filthy animal she is,
		#ELSE
			Moving your [pc.hands] beneath her to grab hold of her [sterope.breasts+], you roughly squeeze them and tug on her thick nipples. After degrading her by telling her what a filthy bitch she is,
		#ENDIF
		 you make sure to interrupt her response by sternly telling her that you didn't give her permission to talk. Quietly moaning in response, the [sterope.race] silently endures your degrading treatment of her.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(sterope.isFeral())
			After a couple of minutes of roughly squeezing her crotch-boobs, you move your attention elsewhere, and begin to tease your [pc.fingers+] over her feral, dripping horse-pussy. Cruelly pinching her winking clit, you finally give the slutty mare your permission to talk again, and she instantly cries out, [sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Fuck! Yes... I'm your filthy little mare... ~Aah!~ Punish me more...)]
		#ELSE
			After a couple of minutes of roughly squeezing her tits, you move your attention elsewhere, and begin to tease your [pc.fingers+] over her dripping cunt. Cruelly pinching her clit, you finally give the horny slut your permission to talk again, and she instantly cries out, [sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Fuck! Yes... I'm your filthy slut... ~Aah!~ Punish me more...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Slapping her [sterope.pussy+], you continue to call Sterope a whole host of degrading names, before making her obediently tell you what a dumb, worthless cunt she is. After five minutes of this treatment, Sterope is lewdly moaning and submissively agreeing with whatever you say. Satisfied with her behaviour, you decide to put an end to this degrading treatment, but you still have more planned for her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF(sterope.isFeral())
		<p>
			Feeling as though now is the right time to get on with main event, you slide your [pc.fingers+] up and down over Sterope's feral mare pussy. Aroused and ready to be fucked, her clit winks at you as you push your digits into her dripping cunt and ask her if she's ready to be
			#IF(pc.hasPenis())
				 rutted
			#ELSE
				 taken
			#ENDIF
			 like the animal she is.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Fuck me!)] she desperately whinnies, before pushing her ass back against you and panting, [sterope.speech(Treat me like the dumb mare I am...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling as though now is the right time to get on with main event, you slide your [pc.fingers+] up and down over Sterope's dripping pussy. Aroused and ready for it, she pushes back against you as you ask her if she's ready to be fucked like the worthless cunt she is.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Fuck me!)] she desperately whines, before pushing her ass back against you and panting, [sterope.speech(Treat me like the dumb slut I am...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Slapping her [sterope.ass+] with considerable force, you make the horny bitch let out an eager squeal, before preparing to give her what she wants...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_CLOTHING_NIPPLE_CLAMPS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(sterope.isFeral())
		<p>
			Looking down at Sterope's crotch boobs, you feel like they could do with being punished. Reaching down to grab hold of them, you start to roughly squeeze and grope them. Quickly moving your touch down to pinch and tug on her thick teats, you grin as the mare squeals and pants, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Yes...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Not yet done with her, you reach down into the chest and grab the pair of nipple clamps. After giving her crotch boobs another squeeze, you tug at her feral nipples, before opening one of the clamps and pinching it down over one of her teats. Thanks to the clamp's attached weight, you're able to let gravity do the work for you, and as you let go, Sterope squeals, [sterope.speech(~Ooh!~ Ow! Fuck...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After giving her [sterope.ass+] a sharp slap, you repeat the procedure for her other crotch boob. With both of her thick teats now being painfully pinched by the weighted clamps, Sterope squirms and moans in masochistic delight, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Yes... Punish me more!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Intending to do just that, you give the dirty mare's crotch boobs another rough grope, before wondering what to do next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Looking down at Sterope's [sterope.breasts+], you feel like they could do with being punished. Reaching down to grab hold of them, you start to roughly squeeze and grope her dangling tits. Quickly moving your touch down to pinch and tug on her thick nipples, you grin as the slut squeals and pants, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Yes...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Not yet done with her, you reach down into the chest and grab the pair of nipple clamps. After giving her boobs another squeeze, you tug at her nipples, before opening one of the clamps and pinching it down over one of them. Thanks to the clamp's attached weight, you're able to let gravity do the work for you, and as you let go, Sterope squeals, [sterope.speech(~Ooh!~ Ow! Fuck...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After giving her [sterope.ass+] a sharp slap, you repeat the procedure for her other breast. With both of her thick nipples now being painfully pinched by the weighted clamps, Sterope squirms and moans in masochistic delight, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Yes... Punish me more!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Intending to do just that, you give the horny [sterope.race]'s tits another rough grope, before wondering what to do next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_CLOTHING_TACKED_UP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to really make Sterope feel like the submissive mare she is, you grab the tack equipment from out of the chest. Instead of a typical black, brown, or other dull colour, the leather straps have been coloured bright pink, and as you lift the gear up, you feel that it's been imbued with several enchantments to make the wearer even more submissive.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes, dress me up like an animal...)] Sterope moans as you place the bridle around her head. Pushing the metal bit into her mouth, you tighten up the straps, before lying the reins over her neck. Next, you place the saddle on her back, before securing it in place and lowering the stirrups. Letting out a submissive little whinny, the horny slut moans, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ I'll be your good little mare...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After that, you make Sterope step onto each of the four horseshoes, which automatically attach themselves to her hoofs via an arcane enchantment. Finally, you wrap the bandage around her tail, before lifting it up and sliding your [pc.fingers+] over her dripping mare pussy.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Yes! ~Mmm!~)] she moans, pushing her ass back out against you as you pinch her winking clit.
	</p>
	<p>
		With the mare now fully tacked up with a bridle, saddle, horseshoes, and tail bandage, you wonder what to do to her next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_CLOTHING_RING_GAG"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting Sterope's mouth to always be open and available for use, you grab the ring gag from out of the chest. Grabbing hold of the [sterope.race]'s chin, you turn her face towards you, and as you do so she obediently opens her mouth. Running your thumb over her [sterope.lips+], you grin as she submissively sucks on it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Lifting the gag, you push the ring into Sterope's mouth, before fastening the straps behind her head. Letting out a whine as a thin stream of saliva drools out over the metal loop, the [sterope.race] moans, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Yes, fuck my face...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving the masochist's face a quick slap to put her in her place, you tell her that you'll do what you want, when you want...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_CLOTHING_BLINDFOLD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be good to deprive Sterope of her vision, you grab the bindfold from out of the chest. Dropping it down over her face, you tightly secure the straps at the back to hold it in place.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(~Aah!~ I'll be your good slut...)] the horny [sterope.race] moans as her world is plunged into darkness. Giving her [sterope.ass+] a hard slap, you tell her what a worthless cunt she is, which makes her let out another lewd squeal.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at the chest, and then back to Sterope, you wonder what to do to her next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_CLOTHING_DILDO"><![CDATA[
	#IF(sterope.isFeral())
		<p>
			Deciding to give Sterope's feral pussy some attention, you slowly slide your [pc.fingers] over her [sterope.labia+]. Her clit winks at you as she desperately moans, [sterope.speech(Yes! ~Aah!~ Fuck me...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Giving the horny mare's cunt a quick slap and telling her to behave, you reach down and grab the dildo from out of the chest. Rubbing its head over her dripping twat, you thumb her twitching clit and tell the slut to beg for it.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(Please! I need it! ~Aah!~ Fuck me!)] the desperate mare squeals. Giving her what she wants, you ram the dildo deep into her hot, wet cunt, causing her to let out an ecstatic, high-pitched whinny. Not giving her a moment in which to recover, you draw the dildo back and then thrust it deep into her again. As you do so, you suddenly notice that the toy has a vibrating enchantment, and as you hilt it in the mare's feral pussy, it starts buzzing away in a rapidly oscillating motion.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Fuck! ~Ooh!~ Yes! ~Aa!~ Fuck me!)] the slut squeals as you repeatedly slam the dildo in and out of her drooling twat. Grabbing Sterope's tail in one [pc.hand(true)], you lift it up as you continue to rapidly fuck her quivering cunt with the vibrating toy. It doesn't take long before she reaches her climax, and as the mare neighs and whinnies in orgasmic bliss, you hilt the dildo in her spasming cunt and leave it there.
		</p>
		<p>
			As the toy continues to vibrate deep inside Sterope's pussy, you wonder what to do with her next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Deciding to give Sterope's hot pussy some attention, you slowly slide your [pc.fingers] over her [sterope.labia+]. She pushes her hips back as she desperately moans, [sterope.speech(Yes! ~Aah!~ Fuck me...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Giving the horny slut's cunt a quick slap and telling her to behave, you reach down and grab the dildo from out of the chest. Rubbing its head over her dripping twat, you thumb her clit and tell the bitch to beg for it.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(Please! I need it! ~Aah!~ Fuck me!)] the desperate [sterope.race] squeals. Giving her what she wants, you ram the dildo deep into her hot, wet cunt, causing her to let out an ecstatic, high-pitched cry. Not giving her a moment in which to recover, you draw the dildo back and then thrust it deep into her again. As you do so, you suddenly notice that the toy has a vibrating enchantment, and as you hilt it in Sterope's pussy, it starts buzzing away in a rapidly oscillating motion.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Fuck! ~Ooh!~ Yes! ~Aa!~ Fuck me!)] the slut squeals as you repeatedly slam the dildo in and out of her drooling twat. Grabbing Sterope's tail in one [pc.hand(true)], you lift it up as you continue to rapidly fuck her quivering cunt with the vibrating toy. It doesn't take long before she reaches her climax, and as the horny [sterope.race] screams in orgasmic bliss, you hilt the dildo in her spasming cunt and leave it there.
		</p>
		<p>
			As the toy continues to vibrate deep inside Sterope's pussy, you wonder what to do with her next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_STABLES_CLOTHING_ANAL_BEADS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(sterope.isFeral())
		<p>
			Unable to resist such a tempting target, you grab hold of Sterope's tail and lift it up to reveal her puffy, feral asshole. Rubbing your thumb around it, you smirk as the horny mare lets out an excited whinny and moans, [sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes... Fuck my ass...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Wanting to play with her asshole for a while before fucking it, you grab the anal beads from out of the chest and start to rub the first sphere against Sterope's rear entrance. Moaning and panting as she feels what it is you're doing, the horny mare pushes her ass back against you. Slowly pressing the bead against her butt, you smirk as it stretches out her puffy rim, before suddenly slipping inside.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(~Ooh!~ Fuck...)] Sterope squeals and pants as she feels the sphere entering her ass. Her feral asshole instinctively clenches and relaxes several times, and you use this opportunity to start pushing the next bead inside. Rubbing it firmly against her puffy asshole, you wait until she relaxes before pushing it in. As the mare's asshole clenches once more, the bead is pulled inside, causing her to cry out, [sterope.speech(Fuck! ~Aah!~ How many more are there?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Telling her that she'll have to wait and find out, you proceed to push the remaining four beds into her asshole. The beads increase in size the further up the chain they are, and so by the time you're at the last one, it's so large that it barely fits. The horny mare squeals and pants as you struggle to push this final sphere into her, but after her puffy rim has been stretched impossibly wide to accommodate it, it finally slips inside.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Fuck...)] the slut moans as you tell her that all six beads are now inside of her. She continues to moan and pant as you then tease her by grabbing the ring on the end and beginning to pull the huge bead back out. Just as her puffy, feral asshole is almost stretched wide enough to allow the bead to escape, you let go, allowing it to slip back inside of her.
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting go of the ring, you give Sterope's ass a sharp slap, before wondering what to do with her next... 
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Unable to resist such a tempting target, you grab hold of Sterope's tail and lift it up to reveal her [sterope.asshole+]. Rubbing your thumb around it, you smirk as the horny slut lets out an excited whinny and moans, [sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes... Fuck my ass...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Wanting to play with her asshole for a while before fucking it, you grab the anal beads from out of the chest and start to rub the first sphere against Sterope's rear entrance. Moaning and panting as she feels what it is you're doing, the horny bitch pushes her ass back against you. Slowly pressing the bead against her butt, you smirk as it stretches out her rim, before suddenly slipping inside.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(~Ooh!~ Fuck...)] Sterope squeals and pants as she feels the sphere entering her ass. Her asshole instinctively clenches and relaxes several times, and you use this opportunity to start pushing the next bead inside. Rubbing it firmly against her [sterope.asshole+], you wait until she relaxes before pushing it in. As the [sterope.race]'s asshole clenches once more, the bead is pulled inside, causing her to cry out, [sterope.speech(Fuck! ~Aah!~ How many more are there?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Telling her that she'll have to wait and find out, you proceed to push the remaining four beds into her asshole. The beads increase in size the further up the chain they are, and so by the time you're at the last one, it's so large that it barely fits. The horny [sterope.race] squeals and pants as you struggle to push this final sphere into her, but after her rim has been stretched impossibly wide to accommodate it, it finally slips inside.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Fuck...)] the slut moans as you tell her that all six beads are now inside of her. She continues to moan and pant as you then tease her by grabbing the ring on the end and beginning to pull the huge bead back out. Just as her hot, greedy asshole is almost stretched wide enough to allow the bead to escape, you let go, allowing it to slip back inside of her.
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting go of the ring, you give Sterope's ass a sharp slap, before wondering what to do with her next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- STEROPE_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isFeral())
			Having had enough of fucking Sterope, you step back and declare that you've finished with her.
		#ELSE
			Having had enough of fucking Sterope, you give her [sterope.ass+] one final, stinging slap, before [pc.stepping] back and declaring that you're done.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(sterope.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			[sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ That was amazing...)]
		#ELSE
			[sterope.speech(~Aah!~ You tease, you didn't even satisfy me...)]
		#ENDIF
		 Sterope moans, before taking on a more authoritative tone and stating,
		#IF(pc.isFeral())
			 [sterope.speech(As the fun's over, it's time to get cleaned up.)]
		#ELSE
			 [sterope.speech(As the fun's over, you'll need to untie me now.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isFeral())
			Moving to one side as the mare takes a couple of steps on trembling legs, you follow her as she trots down to a stall at the far end of the stable. 
		#ELSE
			Doing as she says, you loosen the knots and release the rope which has been holding the [sterope.race] in place. Supporting her as she takes a couple of steps on trembling legs, you follow Sterope's instructions and lead her to a stall at the far end of the stable. 
		#ENDIF
		 It turns out to have been converted into a crude yet functional shower, and after knocking the tap on with her hips, the four ceiling-mounted shower heads come to life. As the water falls all over and around her, Sterope starts to give herself a thorough clean.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(You joining me or what?)] she asks over the sound of the falling water. Seeing that there's plenty of room in this stall for the two of you to get clean, you wonder whether or not to take her up on her offer...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_AFTER_SEX_SHOWER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Realising that you could do with a clean as well, you [pc.step] into the stall and allow the water to fall over your body. Despite having just shared an intimate experience together, Sterope doesn't seem interested in helping you clean yourself, and so you're left to scrub your body alone.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a few minutes, the two of you are as clean as you're going to get, and so the [sterope.race] turns the tap off with another well-placed swing of her hips.
		#IF(sterope.isFeral())
			#IF(pc.isFeral())
				 You copy her as she rubs her flanks against bales of hay to dry herself off, before [pc.stepping] out of the shower.
			#ELSE
				 You use a couple of nearby towels to dry yourself off as the mare rubs her flanks against bales of hay to get the same effect.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 The two of you then use some nearby towels to dry yourselves off.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_AFTER_SEX_SHOWER_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not interested in cleaning yourself off, you tell Sterope that you don't need to use the shower. Shrugging her shoulders in a gesture of indifference, she sets about scrubbing her body clean beneath the falling water, before turning the taps off and
		#IF(sterope.isFeral())
			 drying herself off by rubbing her flanks against bales of hay.
		#ELSE
			 drying herself off with a couple of nearby towels.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_AFTER_SEX_SHOWER_END"><![CDATA[
	#IF(sterope.isFeral())
		#IF(sterope.hasStatusEffect(SE_PREGNANT_0))
			<p>
				[sterope.speech(Now let's find out if you got me pregnant,)] she bluntly states. Trotting over to a nearby shelf, she picks up an arcane pregnancy tester using her teeth, before bending around and holding it near her stomach. A second later, the device lets out a short beep, after which Sterope spits it out onto a nearby table so that she can take a look at the readout. [pc.Stepping] forwards, you look down to see what the device is displaying.
			</p>
			[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
			#IF(sterope.isPregnant())
				<p>
					[sterope.speech(I lost count of how many times I've been knocked up in this stable a long time ago,)] the mare casually reveals, before explaining, [sterope.speech(I can't perform all my duties at work if I'm pregnant, so I'll have #IF(sterope.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()==1)this brat#ELSEthese brats#ENDIF pumped out and sent packing before morning. Don't like it? #IF(sterope.getPregnantLitter().getFertilisationType()==FERTILISATION_TRIBBING)Then don't make me drink Amazon's Secret next time.#ELSEThen pull out or use a condom next time.#ENDIF)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Leaving you for a moment to think on your decision to
					#IF(sterope.getPregnantLitter().getFertilisationType()==FERTILISATION_TRIBBING)
						 trib with her while she was under the effects of Amazon's Secret,
					#ELSE
						 creampie her,
					#ENDIF
					 Sterope trots over to the pile of her clothing, before turning to face you and say,
			#ELSE
				<p>
					[sterope.speech(Great, getting knocked up's hot in the moment, but it's a pain to deal with afterwards,)] the mare casually says, before explaining, [sterope.speech(I can't perform all my duties at work if I'm pregnant, so if I get knocked up in one of these sessions, I pump the brat out and send them packing before morning.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Leaving you for a moment to think on her words, Sterope trots over to the pile of her clothing, before turning to face you and say,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Trotting over to the pile of her clothing, Sterope turns to face you and simply says,
		#ENDIF
			 [sterope.speech(I'll have to wait for a little while for this feral transformation to end. We're done here. If you visit me while at work again, don't you dare mention my private life. If you do, then you'll never get to do this with me again.)]
		</p>
		#IF(pc.isFeral())
			<p>
				As you're also going to have to wait for your feral transformation to expire before being able to retrieve your clothing and belongings, it looks like you're going to have to spend a little more time with Sterope...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				With nothing more to do here now that the two of you have had your fun, all that's left is for you to head back out into the tavern...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF(sterope.hasStatusEffect(SE_PREGNANT_0))
			<p>
				[sterope.speech(Now let's find out if you got me pregnant,)] she bluntly states. Swiftly striding over to a nearby shelf, she picks up an arcane pregnancy tester, before holding it near her stomach. A second later, the device lets out a short beep, after which Sterope places it down onto a nearby table so that she can take a look at the readout. [pc.Stepping] forwards, you look down to see what the device is displaying.
			</p>
			[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
			#IF(sterope.isPregnant())
				<p>
					[sterope.speech(I lost count of how many times I've been knocked up in this stable a long time ago,)] the [sterope.race] casually reveals, before explaining, [sterope.speech(I can't perform all my duties at work if I'm pregnant, so I'll have #IF(sterope.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()==1)this brat#ELSEthese brats#ENDIF pumped out and sent packing before morning. Don't like it? #IF(sterope.getPregnantLitter().getFertilisationType()==FERTILISATION_TRIBBING)Then don't make me drink Amazon's Secret next time.#ELSEThen pull out or use a condom next time.#ENDIF)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Leaving you for a moment to think on your decision to
					#IF(sterope.getPregnantLitter().getFertilisationType()==FERTILISATION_TRIBBING)
						 trib with her while she was under the effects of Amazon's Secret,
					#ELSE
						 creampie her,
					#ENDIF
					 Sterope steps over to the pile of her clothing, and as she gets dressed, she simply says,
			#ELSE
				<p>
					[sterope.speech(Great, getting knocked up's hot in the moment, but it's a pain to deal with afterwards,)] the [sterope.race] casually says, before explaining, [sterope.speech(I can't perform all my duties at work if I'm pregnant, so if I get knocked up in one of these sessions, I pump the brat out and send them packing before morning.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Leaving you for a moment to think on her words, Sterope steps over to the pile of her clothing, and as she gets dressed, she simply says,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Stepping over to the pile of her clothing, Sterope starts to get dressed, and as she does so, she simply says,
		#ENDIF
			 [sterope.speech(We're done here. If you visit me while at work again, don't you dare mention my private life. If you do, then you'll never get to do this with me again.)]
		</p>
		#IF(sterope.getRaceStage()==RACE_STAGE_GREATER && !flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_fully_furry))
			<p>
				As you tell her that you'll refrain from mentioning this while she's at work, the [sterope.race] grabs a transformative potion from out of a nearby box. Realising that she's about to drink it and transform back into a lesser horse-girl, you wonder whether you should try and convince her to remain in her current form...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				With nothing more to do here now that the two of you have had your fun, all that's left is to head back out into the tavern...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_AFTER_SEX_FERAL_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Despite her earlier amorous behaviour, now that she's got what she wanted out of this evening, Sterope assumes the cold, aloof attitude she has while at work. Ignoring or rejecting all of your attempts to start conversation or begin another session of lewd activities, the mare impatiently stomps her hoofs and trots back and forth as she waits for the feral transformation to end.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Kheiron wasn't happy when I first walked through the tavern in this form,)] she says after some time, [sterope.speech(Something about the customers feeling uncomfortable. So now I have to wait in here like this... Eugh... Getting fucked as a mare is the best, but this part of it sucks.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thankfully, the two of you don't have to wait for much longer, for after a few more minutes you feel your transformation reversing. The process of turning from a quadrupedal animal back into a humanoid is a disorienting blur. A loss of coordination in your limbs is followed by an extreme bout of dizziness, and although you're vaguely aware of your body reshaping as your limbs return to their previous shape, you're mostly oblivious as to what's going on until it's all over.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(You get used to it after the first dozen times,)] you hear Sterope say as your head finally clears. Looking up at her from your position sitting on the floor, you see that she's returned to her horse-girl form, and has already got dressed. Dropping her cold act for a moment, she smirks and teases, [sterope.speech(I had a lot of fun this evening, [pc.name]. We should do this again some time...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she swiftly departs, leaving you to look yourself over and discover that you've been left in the body of [pc.a_fullRace(true)]. Gathering your things, you follow Sterope back out into the tavern and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding not to interfere with her preferences, you watch as Sterope drinks the transformation potion. The fur on her arms, legs, and torso begins to fade away, and as her horse-like head transforms back into her previous, human one, she's left as the same lesser horse-girl you first saw in the Enforcer station.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you [pc.step] over towards the door to leave, Sterope skips in front of you, before turning to flash you a smirk and tease, [sterope.speech(I had a lot of fun this evening, [pc.name]. We should do this again some time...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she swiftly hurries through the door and takes her leave. Following in her footsteps, you [pc.step] back out into the tavern and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE_STAY_TRANSFORMED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You like Sterope in her greater horse-girl form, and so before she can drink the contents of the bottle, you dominantly tell her to stop.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Fun time's over,)] she replies, [sterope.speech(Everyone knows Sterope as a lesser horse-girl, and I don't want them asking too many questions if I suddenly change my appearance.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] towards her, you remind Sterope that she's your horny mare, and you want her to be aware of that fact every moment of every day. This time, she hesitates to reply, allowing you press the issue and order her to discard the potion.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Nobody's ever asked this of me before,)] she submissively pants, [sterope.speech(Staying as a greater horse-girl, knowing that it's because I was ordered to... Fuck, that's so hot...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You order her once again to discard the potion, and this time she obeys. After she's poured the liquid down the shower's drain, you slip your [pc.hand(true)] up the short skirt of her dress, and as you dominantly grope her hot cunt, you ask her what she is. Grinding down against you, she moans, [sterope.speech(I'm a horny, slutty mare... A worthless cunt who gets tied up and fucked <i>hard</i> every night...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've told her that her new body will help her to remember that, Sterope manages to get her lust under control, and after stepping back, she says, [sterope.speech(I had a lot of fun this evening, [pc.name]... We should do this again some time...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she swiftly hurries through the door and takes her leave. Following in her footsteps, you [pc.step] back out into the tavern and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE_NO_TF_OPTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you [pc.step] over towards the door to leave, Sterope skips in front of you, before turning to flash you a smirk and tease, [sterope.speech(I had a lot of fun this evening, [pc.name]. We should do this again some time...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she swiftly hurries through the door and takes her leave. Following in her footsteps, you [pc.step] back out into the tavern and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- STEROPE_FERAL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_FERAL_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to resist the sight of Sterope's feral mare pussy, you eagerly trot forwards and get into position behind her. Looking back over her shoulder once again, she whines, [sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes, mount me and rut me hard!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Centaur threesome content: -->
	
	<!-- STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turned on by the [centaur.race]'s dominant attitude, you find yourself letting out a submissive [pc.moan], before telling [centaur.herHim] that you're a worthless slut. Grinning as [centaur.she] hears this, [centaur.name] grabs hold of you and roughly pulls you into [centaur.her] embrace, before grunting, [centaur.speech(If that's the case, then I'll fuck you alongside this other bitch.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_ATTRACT_TAUR_SUBMIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turned on by the [centaur.race]'s dominant attitude, you find yourself letting out a submissive [pc.moan], before telling [centaur.herHim] that you'll willingly submit to [centaur.herHim]. Grinning as [centaur.she] hears this, [centaur.name] grunts, [centaur.speech(If that's the case, then I'll fuck you alongside this other bitch.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Eager to get started, Sterope desperately pants, [sterope.speech(Come on, I've rented the stable behind this place. Take us there, tie us up, and fuck us hard!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[centaur.Name] lets out a hungry growl as Sterope says this, and after roughly groping the two of you for a moment, [centaur.she] commands, [centaur.speech(Let's get moving then, sluts. I'm going to fuck you worthless bitches all night.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the three of you stand up, the [centaur.race] delivers a sharp slap to both your and Sterope's rear ends, compelling you to hurry forwards towards the far corner of the tavern...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[centaur.Name] takes hold of you and Sterope and roughly pushes you forwards as the three of you head over to the far corner of the tavern.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(I've got the key,)] Sterope declares as you pass by the toilets and come to a halt in front of a locked door. Quickly unlocking it, the [sterope.race] steps into the stable beyond, calling over her shoulder as she does so, [sterope.speech(Here's where the fun happens...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pushing you inside and then following after, [centaur.name] locks the door behind you, giving you a chance to take a good look at your surroundings. The stable appears to be nothing more than what you'd expect, and comes complete with the usual wooden stalls, hay-covered stone floor, and a couple of wooden tables. Beside one of these tables, there's a good deal of rope sitting on top of a wooden chest, and you realise that this is what's to be used to tie both you and Sterope up.
	</p>
	<p>
		As the dominant [centaur.race] finishes locking the door, Sterope quickly slips out of her dress, before kicking off her strappy heels and sliding her thong down her legs. After removing her earrings, she ends up being completely naked, except for the pink leather collar around her neck and the multitude of other piercings over her body. Playfully teasing her fingers over her [sterope.breasts+] and [sterope.pussy+], she winks at [centaur.name] and lets out a playful giggle.
	</p>
	#IF(sterope.getRaceStage()!=RACE_STAGE_GREATER)
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(I'm kind of into transformations,)] she coyly teases as she opens the chest and produces a glass bottle. Excitedly drinking its contents, she giggles, [sterope.speech(It makes it sexier being dominated when I'm turned into more of an animal...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Right before your eyes, you watch [sterope.skinColour] horse-like hair spread all over Sterope's body. Her legs transform into anthropomorphic equine ones, complete with hoofs, and after the her arms and torso have transformed into their horse-like counterparts, her face begins to change. Elongating and transforming into a muzzle, her face takes on the look of an anthropomorphic horse. The transformation is over almost as quickly as it began, and now standing before you is [sterope.a_raceFull(true)].
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_transformed_into_feral) && game.isFeralContentEnabled())
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(Let's transform into mares so that we can get rutted like real animals...)] she breathlessly moans to you as she throws the sheet off of a small boulder in one corner of the stable. As the beast stone is revealed, she reveals to the [centaur.race], [sterope.speech(These used to be super popular years ago, but they fell out of favour and are now pretty taboo. For every ten minutes spent touching it, you get transformed into a feral form for four hours. Fifteen minutes should be enough for the two of us to turn into mares until morning...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(sterope.getRaceStage()!=RACE_STAGE_GREATER)
				Producing a transformative potion,
			#ELSE
				Producing another transformative potion,
			#ENDIF
			 she holds it out to you and says, [sterope.speech(Come on, [pc.name], drink this and join me in touching the stone, then we can spend the night as mares together...)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.getTrueRace()!=RACE_HORSE_MORPH && pc.isAbleToHaveRaceTransformed())
		<p>
			#IF(sterope.getRaceStage()!=RACE_STAGE_GREATER)
				Producing a transformative potion and holding it out to you,
			#ELSE
				Producing another transformative potion and holding it out to you,
			#ENDIF
			 Sterope offers, [sterope.speech(You can join me in becoming a greater horse-girl, [pc.name]. Come on, it'll be hot to get fucked side-by-side while in that form...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Coyly shuffling her hoofs around on the stone floor, Sterope lets out a horny little neigh, before begging, [sterope.speech(Come on, us up and punish us!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_NO_TF"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.getTrueRace()!=RACE_HORSE_MORPH || (flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_transformed_into_feral) && game.isFeralContentEnabled()))
		<p>
			You're really not interested in being transformed into a greater horse-girl, and so you tell Sterope that you don't want the potion. Although she briefly pouts, the horse-girl doesn't seem too bothered by your refusal, and simply puts the bottle back into the chest, before turning to face [centaur.name] and tease, [sterope.speech(So, what are you waiting for?)] 
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Letting out an impatient grunt, [centaur.name] grabs the rope from off of the table and advances upon you and Sterope. After roughly stripping you naked, [centaur.name] pushes the two of you down over the wooden surface and commands, [centaur.speech(Hold still, you dumb sluts!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, the two of you stay in position and allow the [centaur.race] to tie you down to the table. After making sure that [centaur.sheHas] securely bound your limbs so that you're unable to move, [centaur.name] steps back and roughly growls, [centaur.speech(That's better! Now to give you worthless cunts the punishment you deserve!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of transforming into a greater horse-girl, you take the transformative potion from Sterope and drink it all in one long gulp. The [sterope.race] playfully bites her lip and excitedly moans, [sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes, now we can both get fucked like animals...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she finishes saying this, you feel your transformation begin. Horse-like hair quickly grows to cover your entire body, before your feet transform and shift into hoofs. A horse-like tail grows out from just above your ass, while your face pushes out into a long muzzle. Your ears drift up to sit on top of your head and grow up into horse ears, before your head finishes its transformation into becoming that of an anthropomorphised horse.
		#IF(!pc.isFeminine())
			 A high-pitched moan escapes from your lips as you feel your facial features and body shape morphing and becoming more feminine formin appearance.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(!pc.hasBreasts())
			 [centaur.Name] grunts in approval as a pair of breasts swell out from your chest, and before you can react, the [centaur.race] is roughly groping and squeezing them.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.hasPenis())
			 Finally, you can't help but let out a desperate squeal as your cock rapidly shrinks down and
			#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				 disappears, leaving you with just your puffy, horse-like pussy.
			#ELSE
				 disappears, before being replaced by a puffy, horse-like pussy.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(!pc.hasVagina())
			 Finally, you can't help but let out a desperate squeal as a vertical slit in your crotch pulls inwards and forms into a puffy, horse-like pussy.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that your transformation is complete, [centaur.name] lets out an impatient grunt, before grabbing the rope from off of the table and advancing upon you and Sterope. After roughly stripping you naked, [centaur.name] pushes the two of you down over the wooden surface and commands, [centaur.speech(Hold still, you dumb mares!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, the two of you stay in position and allow the [centaur.race] to tie you down to the table. After making sure that [centaur.sheHas] securely bound your limbs so that you're unable to move, [centaur.name] steps back and roughly growls, [centaur.speech(That's better! Now to give you worthless cunts the punishment you deserve!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_FERAL_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of being transformed into a feral mare alongside Sterope, you take the transformative potion from her and drink it all in one long gulp. The [sterope.race] playfully bites her lip and excitedly moans, [sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes, now we can both get fucked as animals...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she finishes saying this, you feel your transformation begin. Horse-like hair quickly grows to cover your entire body, before your feet transform and shift into hoofs. A horse-like tail grows out from just above your ass, while your face pushes out into a long muzzle. Your ears drift up to sit on top of your head and grow up into horse ears, before your head finishes its transformation into becoming that of an anthropomorphised horse.
		#IF(!pc.isFeminine())
			 A high-pitched moan escapes from your lips as you feel your facial features and body shape morphing and becoming more feminine formin appearance.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(!pc.hasBreasts())
			 [centaur.Name] grunts in approval as a pair of breasts swell out from your chest, and before you can react, the [centaur.race] is roughly groping and squeezing them.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.hasPenis())
			 Finally, you can't help but let out a desperate squeal as your cock rapidly shrinks down and
			#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				 disappears, leaving you with just your puffy, horse-like pussy.
			#ELSE
				 disappears, before being replaced by a puffy, horse-like pussy.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(!pc.hasVagina())
			 Finally, you can't help but let out a desperate squeal as a vertical slit in your crotch pulls inwards and forms into a puffy, horse-like pussy.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Eagerly anticipating what's to come, Sterope takes off her leather collar and quickly drops to her knees beside the beast stone, before placing one of her hands on it. A faint purple glow washes over the [sterope.race]'s body, and she excitedly moans, [sterope.speech(Come on, [pc.name]. Join me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she says, you join Sterope in touching the beast stone, and as you place your horse-like hand on its cool surface, you feel a surge of arcane energy wash over you. Along with Sterope, you maintain contact with the beast stone for fifteen minutes, before letting go of it at the same time. The purple glow which was surrounding both of you suddenly shoots into your bodies, and you each let out desperate, shuddering cries as you start to transform.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your transformation starts with a second pair of horse legs growing out of your lower stomach. Accompanying this alarming change, your ass begins to swell and grow in size. Within seconds, your lower body from the waist down has transformed into the form of a full-sized horse. You gasp as your arms then rapidly shrink into your torso, before your upper body shrinks down and transforms into a long, thick neck. Your horse-like face then increases in size, losing its anthropomorphic qualities as it transforms into that of a feral mare. As a slight breeze passes over your fully-feral mare pussy, you find yourself letting out a primal, animalistic neigh, before finding your voice and telling [centaur.name] that you and Sterope are ready to be fucked hard.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Fuck...)] Sterope moans. Looking over to the now-feral mare, you watch her as she stands up on her four, shaking legs. Although she's now in the form of an animal, Sterope, just like you, is clearly still able to speak, and as she turns to face [centaur.name], you notice that there's a distinct look of intelligence in her otherwise horse-like eyes. Letting out a playful whinny, she teases, [sterope.speech(So what are you waiting for? Tie us up, then mount and rut us like the dumb mares we are...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the mare trots around to stand beside you, and together you flick your tails to one side in order to show off your feral horse pussies. Letting out a hungry grunt, [centaur.name] snaps, [centaur.speech(It's about time! I'll tie you up then punish you dumb cunts for making me wait for so long!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_CORE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_PUNISHMENT_SPANKING"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isFeral())
		<p>
			Moving around behind you and Sterope, [centaur.name] begins greedily groping your asses, before suddenly moving [centaur.her] [centaur.hands] down and roughly thrusting [centaur.her] [centaur.fingers] into your puffy, feral cunts. Forcefully fingering the two of you, the [centaur.race] soon has you biting down on your bridles as you let out a stream of horny neighs and whinnies.
		</p>
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(Cum for me, you dumb mares!)] [centaur.name] shouts, before suddenly withdrawing [centaur.her] [centaur.fingers] and delivering a sharp, painful slap to your rear ends.
		</p>
		<p>
			The two of you let out surprised, painful cries, which you repeate when the [centaur.race] slaps your asses for a second time. Showing the two of you no mercy, [centaur.she] continues to forcefully spank your rear ends, sadistically laughing as [centaur.she] does so, [centaur.speech(What are you waiting for, you worthless cunts?! I ordered you to cum!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, [centaur.name] delivers the next slap to your exposed pussies, causing the two of you to let out yet more painful, horny squeals. Madly turned on by this degrading treatment, as soon as the [centaur.race] shoves [centaur.her] [centaur.fingers] back into your sore, quivering cunts, both you and Sterope instantly orgasm. As your dripping, feral pussies spasm and clench down, [centaur.name] stops fingering you yet again, and in the midst of your climax, starts roughly slapping your asses.
		</p>
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(That's it!)] the [centaur.race] gleefully snarls in-between blows, [centaur.speech(Cum to the feeling of being spanked, you filthy, worthless animals!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You and Sterope obediently lift your asses and submit to [centaur.namePos] rough spanking as your orgasms wash over you. Moaning and panting from exertion, the two of you are soon left with sore asses and sloppy cunts as [centaur.name] steps back to decide upon your next punishment...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Moving around behind you and Sterope, [centaur.name] begins greedily groping your asses, before suddenly lifting [centaur.her] [centaur.hands] and roughly swatting them down to strike your exposed rear ends with considerable force.
		</p>
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(Scream for me, you dumb cunts!)] [centaur.name] shouts, before repeating [centaur.her] movements and delivering sharp, painful slaps to your rear ends.
		</p>
		<p>
			The two of you let out surprised, painful cries, which you repeate when the [centaur.race] slaps your asses for a third time. Showing the two of you no mercy, [centaur.she] continues to forcefully spank your rear ends, sadistically laughing as [centaur.she] does so, [centaur.speech(You worthless whores! Lift your asses and submit to me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Loving every moment of this degrading treatment, both you and Sterope obediently lift your asses and submit to [centaur.namePos] rough spanking. After many more blows to your sore asses, and with the two of you left moaning and panting from exertion, [centaur.name] finally steps back to decide upon your next punishment...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_PUNISHMENT_WHIPPING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Bending down over the chest that's situated on one side of the stable, [centaur.name] produces a mean-looking riding crop. After flexing it between [centaur.her] [centaur.hands], [centaur.she] experimentally swats it against a wooden post, which produces a terrifyingly-loud crack. Smirking as [centaur.she] trots up behind the two of you, [centaur.she] teases,
		#IF(pc.isFeral())
			 [centaur.speech(Now, which of you worthless mares should be the first?)]
		#ELSE
			 [centaur.speech(Now, which of you dumb cunts should be the first?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(RND.nextInt(100)<50)
		<p>
			In anticipation of what's about to happen, you can't help but let out a quiet, nervous whine. Seizing upon this, [centaur.name] gently teases the end of the riding crop over your ass, before sharply swinging it down and delivering an excruciating thwack to your rear end. As a painful, horny shriek bursts out from between your [pc.lips], the [centaur.race] laughs in sadistic delight and teases, [centaur.speech(That's it, slut! Scream for me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After delivering a dozen more strikes to your ass, and making you squeal and cry out in masochistic delight in the process, [centaur.name] turns [centaur.her] attention to Sterope. Lifting the riding crop, [centaur.she] whips Sterope's ass with considerable force, causing the [sterope.race] to let out a desperate, high-pitched squeal. Striking her ass again and again, the [centaur.race] soon reduces Sterope to a whimpering, moaning wreck.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			In anticipation of what's about to happen, Sterope can't help but let out a quiet, horny whine. Seizing upon this, [centaur.name] gently teases the end of the riding crop over her ass, before sharply swinging it down and delivering an excruciating thwack to the [sterope.race]'s rear end. As a painful, horny shriek bursts out from between Sterope's [sterope.lips], the [centaur.race] laughs in sadistic delight and teases, [centaur.speech(That's it, slut! Scream for me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After delivering a dozen more strikes to Sterope's ass, and making her squeal and cry out in masochistic delight in the process, [centaur.name] turns [centaur.her] attention to you. Lifting the riding crop, [centaur.she] whips your ass with considerable force, causing you to let out a desperate, high-pitched squeal. Striking your ass again and again, the [centaur.race] soon reduces you to a whimpering, moaning wreck.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		With the two of you now having had a good whipping, [centaur.name] backs off for a moment. As the two of you let out exhausted sighs, the [centaur.name] laughs and cruelly teases,
		#IF(pc.isFeral())
			 [centaur.speech(Oh, did you think I'd finished? You dumb mares! I've only just begun!)]
		#ELSE
			 [centaur.speech(Oh, did you think I'd finished? You worthless bitches! I've only just begun!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [centaur.name] resumes your punishment, alternating between your and Sterope's asses every few strikes or so. Soon enough, your rear ends have been well and truly abused, and with the two of you whimpering and moaning in masochistic glee, [centaur.name] tosses the riding crop away and prepares to move on to the next punishment...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_PUNISHMENT_DEGRADING_TALK"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isFeral())
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(Look at these filthy cunts,)] [centaur.name] sneers as [centaur.she] swats both your and Sterope's tails aside to get a good look at your animalistic genitals. Grabbing hold of your puffy pussies, [centaur.she] roughly forces two of [centaur.her] fingers into your cunts as [centaur.she] spits, [centaur.speech(Disgusting! I can't believe I've got to fuck you worthless mares...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			The combination of [centaur.namePos] degrading words and [centaur.her] fingers in your pussies causes you and Sterope to let out horny, high-pitched whinnies. Continuing [centaur.her] verbal assault as [centaur.she] forces a third finger into your cunts, the [centaur.race] derisively sighs, [centaur.speech(I can't believe you'd want to transform into animals... You two really are filthy degenerates, aren't you?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Submissively agreeing with [centaur.namePos] assessment of you, the two of you push your asses back and moan in desperate, horny delight as [centaur.name] squeezes her fourth digit into your cunts and begins to roughly finger you. As your puffy, animalistic horse-cunts stretch lewdly around [centaur.namePos] intruding digits, the [centaur.race] demands, [centaur.speech(Show me what dirty, horny mares you are... Tell me how worthless you are, then cum for me to prove it!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Unable to resist any longer, you squeal in submissive delight as you feel your pussy begin to involuntarily spasm and squeeze down around [centaur.namePos] fingers. Climaxing at the same moment as you, Sterope declares in a quivering voice, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Yes, I'm a worthless mare! ~Mmm!~ Fuck me! I'm a filthy, dirty animal!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Offering an equally-degrading declaration of your own, you immediately orgasm, and along with Sterope, moan and squeal in ecstasy as [centaur.name] continues to call you degrading names and tell you how worthless you are. Pulling [centaur.her] fingers out of your cunts, [centaur.she] uses your flanks to wipe her fingers clean, before stepping back and deciding upon your next punishment...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(What a pair of worthless cunts,)] [centaur.name] sneers as [centaur.she] swats both your and Sterope's asses. Roughly groping your ass cheeks, [centaur.she] spits, [centaur.speech(Disgusting! I can't believe I've got to fuck you filthy bitches...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[centaur.NamePos] degrading words cause you and Sterope to let out horny, high-pitched whines. Continuing [centaur.her] verbal assault as [centaur.she] continues to molest your rear ends, the [centaur.race] derisively sighs, [centaur.speech(I can't believe you'd want to get tied up and fucked in a stable... You two really are complete degenerates, aren't you?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Submissively agreeing with [centaur.namePos] assessment of you, the two of you push your asses back and moan in desperate, horny delight. Not yet finished with you, the [centaur.race] demands, [centaur.speech(Tell me what dirty, horny cunts you are...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Obediently responding, Sterope declares in a quivering voice, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Yes, I'm a worthless cunt! ~Mmm!~ Fuck me! I'm a filthy, dirty bitch!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Offering an equally-degrading declaration of your own, you moan and pant in horny delight as [centaur.name] continues to call you degrading names and tell you how worthless you are. After continuing this verbal assault for a few minutes, [centaur.she] finally steps back to decide upon your next punishment...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_PUNISHMENT_WAX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turning [centaur.her] attention to the nearby chest, [centaur.name] reaches down and produces two dark red candles. Smirking as [centaur.she] uses a nearby lighter to set them alight, [centaur.name] grunts, [centaur.speech(Let's see how you sluts handle this!)] 
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isFeral())
		<p>
			Grabbing hold of Sterope's tail, the [centaur.race] pulls it to one side and brings the candle down towards her puffy, feral horse-pussy. A drop of the dark red wax soon drips down to splash against the mare's exposed labia, causing her to let out a high-pitched gasp. Neighing and moaning as several more drops of hot wax drip down onto her cunt, Sterope squeals, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Fuck! Yes! Abuse me! ~Ooh!~ I'm your worthless mare!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After spending a few minutes giving the horny mare what she wants, [centaur.name] turns [centaur.her] attention to you. Moving your tail to one side, [centaur.she] allows several drops of wax to fall down onto your exposed mare-pussy. As the hot liquid splashes down onto your private parts you can't help but let out a desperate, shuddering squeal. Neighing and moaning in masochistic delight, you tell [centaur.name] what a submissive slut you are as you're subjected to several minutes of this wax-based punishment.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Grabbing hold of Sterope's tail, the [centaur.race] pulls it to one side and brings the candle down towards her [sterope.pussy+]. A drop of the dark red wax soon drips down to splash against the [sterope.race]'s exposed labia, causing her to let out a high-pitched gasp. Panting and moaning as several more drops of hot wax drip down onto her cunt, Sterope squeals, [sterope.speech(~Aah!~ Fuck! Yes! Abuse me! ~Ooh!~ I'm your worthless slut!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After spending a few minutes giving the horny mare what she wants, [centaur.name] turns [centaur.her] attention to you.
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 After giving your [pc.pussy+] a quick slap, [centaur.name] allows several drops of wax to fall down onto your [pc.labia+]. As the hot liquid splashes down onto your private parts you can't help but let out a desperate, shuddering squeal. Panting and moaning in masochistic delight, you tell [centaur.name] what a submissive slut you are as you're subjected to several minutes of this wax-based punishment.
			#ELSE
				 After giving your [pc.ass+] a quick slap, [centaur.name] allows several drops of wax to fall down onto your rear end. As the hot liquid splashes down onto your ass you can't help but let out a desperate, shuddering squeal. Panting and moaning in masochistic delight, you tell [centaur.name] what a submissive slut you are as you're subjected to several minutes of this wax-based punishment.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Finally, with the two of you covered in a good deal of solidified wax, [centaur.name] blows out the candles and tosses them aside, before stepping back and wondering what to do with the two of you next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_PUNISHMENT_NIPPLES"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isFeral())
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(What fat, lewd teats you sluts have,)] the [centaur.race] grunts, before reaching under you and Sterope to roughly grab and squeeze your feral crotch-boobs. As the two of you let out horny whinnies, [centaur.name] laughs and sneers, [centaur.speech(Now to make you filthy mares really squeal!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the sadistic [centaur.race] forcefully pinches and tugs at your nipples, causing you to let out a surprised, high-pitched neigh. Beside you, Sterope lets out a loud squeal, before moaning, [sterope.speech(Yes! ~Aah!~ Abuse us!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			More than happy to do as Sterope asks, the [centaur.race] continues to cruelly pinch, twist, and tug at your nipples. Only interrupting this process to greedily grope and squeeze your crotch-boobs, [centaur.name] soon reduces you and Sterope to panting, squealing wrecks.
		</p>
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(What a pair of dumb, horny sluts you are!)] the [centaur.race] exclaims. With a final tug on your nipples, [centaur.she] steps back to decide upon how to punish you next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(What fat, lewd nipples you sluts have,)] the [centaur.race] grunts, before reaching under you and Sterope to roughly grab and squeeze your #IF(pc.hasBreasts())breasts#ELSEchests#ENDIF. As the two of you let out horny whines, [centaur.name] laughs and sneers, [centaur.speech(Now to make you filthy cunts really squeal!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the sadistic [centaur.race] forcefully pinches and tugs at your nipples, causing you to let out a surprised, high-pitched cry. Beside you, Sterope lets out a loud squeal, before moaning, [sterope.speech(Yes! ~Aah!~ Abuse us!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			More than happy to do as Sterope asks, the [centaur.race] continues to cruelly pinch, twist, and tug at your nipples. Only interrupting this process to greedily grope and squeeze your #IF(pc.hasBreasts())tits#ELSEbodies#ENDIF, [centaur.name] soon reduces you and Sterope to panting, squealing wrecks.
		</p>
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(What a pair of dumb, horny sluts you are!)] the [centaur.race] exclaims. With a final tug on your nipples, [centaur.she] steps back to decide upon how to punish you next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_PUNISHMENT_SLAPPING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Confidently trotting around in front of you and Sterope, the [centaur.name] sneers down at you and declares, [centaur.speech(I need to put you sluts in your place!)]
	</p>
		<p>
			Before either of you can respond to this, [centaur.name] suddenly slaps you across the face. Ignoring your shocked cry, [centaur.she] repeats this process for Sterope, and after delivering a stinging slap to her, [centaur.name] sneers, [centaur.speech(Show me what dirty, submissive sluts you are! If I don't like your response, you'll be getting another slap!)]
		</p>
	#IF(pc.isFeral())
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ I'm a worthless, filthy mare! Please, fuck me! ~Aah!~)] Sterope eagerly moans, but despite her enthusiastic words, [centaur.name] delivers another slap to her face.
		</p>
		<p>
			Trying to do better than the mare beside you, you eagerly tell [centaur.name] what a dirty slut you are, before submissively claiming that you'll let [centaur.herHim] do anything [centaur.she] wants to you. Just like with Sterope, however, the [centaur.race] doesn't hesitate in delivering a sharp slap to your face.
		</p>
		<p>
			This process continues for a short while, until the two of you realise that all the [centaur.race] will permit is for you to let out submissive whinnies and quiet neighs. Assuming the role of horny mares, you wordlessly moan and bow your heads to [centaur.name].
		</p>
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(That's more like it!)] the [centaur.race] declares, [centaur.speech(You dumb mares need to remember your place!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ I'm a worthless, filthy cunt! Please, fuck me! ~Aah!~)] Sterope eagerly moans, but despite her enthusiastic words, [centaur.name] delivers another slap to her face.
		</p>
		<p>
			Trying to do better than the slut beside you, you eagerly tell [centaur.name] what a dirty bitch you are, before submissively claiming that you'll let [centaur.herHim] do anything [centaur.she] wants to you. Just like with Sterope, however, the [centaur.race] doesn't hesitate in delivering a sharp slap to your face.
		</p>
		<p>
			This process continues for a short while, until the two of you realise that all the [centaur.race] will permit is for you to let out submissive whines and quiet moans. Assuming the role of submissive fuck-toys, you wordlessly pant and bow your heads to [centaur.name].
		</p>
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(That's more like it!)] the [centaur.race] declares, [centaur.speech(You dumb cunts need to remember your place!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		With that, [centaur.name] sadistically slaps each of you one last time, before moving back behind you to decide upon your next punishment...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_PUNISHMENT_END"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isFeral())
		<p>
			Letting out a hungry grunt, [centaur.name] suddenly swats your tails to one side, before roughly forcing [centaur.her] [centaur.fingers] into both your and Sterope's feral mare-pussies. The two of you whinny in unison as the [centaur.race] begins to dominantly finger you, and you can't help but push back into [centaur.herHim] as you feel your puffy cunt quickly getting hot and wet.
		</p>
		<p>
			[centaur.speech(Looks like you dumb mares are ready for a good, hard fucking,)] [centaur.name] suddenly states, before pulling [centaur.her] fingers out of your cunts and sharply swatting your asses.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_centaur_fucks_sterope_first))
				Seeming to prefer the sound of Sterope's masochistic cry to your own, [centaur.name] moves over to the mare beside you, before declaring, [centaur.speech(You'll get it first, you filthy slut!)]
			#ELSE
				Seeming to prefer the sound of your masochistic cry to Sterope's, [centaur.name] moves up behind you, before declaring, [centaur.speech(You'll get it first, you filthy slut!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Letting out a hungry grunt, [centaur.name] suddenly lifts [centaur.her] hands and delivers stinging slaps to both your and Sterope's asses. As the two of you let out synchronised moans, the [centaur.race] declares, [centaur.speech(Looks like you dumb cunts are ready for a good, hard fucking!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Delivering another sharp slap to each of your rear ends, the sadistic [centaur.race] lets out an amused grunt as you both let out a surprised squeal. 
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_centaur_fucks_sterope_first))
				 Seeming to prefer the sound of Sterope's masochistic cry to your own, [centaur.name] moves over to the mare beside you, before declaring, [centaur.speech(You'll get it first, you filthy slut!)]
			#ELSE
				 Seeming to prefer the sound of your masochistic cry to Sterope's, [centaur.name] moves up behind you, before declaring, [centaur.speech(You'll get it first, you filthy slut!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_SEX_START_STEROPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a deep, hungry grunt, [centaur.name] rears up and mounts Sterope in one swift motion. Sliding [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+] up and down over the [sterope.race]'s ass, [centaur.she] [centaur.moans], [centaur.speech(Ready to get rutted, you dumb cunt?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Fuck! ~Ooh!~ Yes, fuck me!)] Sterope squeals in delight as she prepares to receive a good, hard fucking from [centaur.name]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_SEX_START_PLAYER"><![CDATA[
	#IF((!pc.hasVagina() || !pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true)) && (!game.isAnalContentEnabled() || !pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_ANUS, true)))
		<p>
			With a deep, hungry grunt, [centaur.name] trots around in front of you and then quickly rears up to mount your face in one swift motion. Sliding [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+] up and down over the top of your head, [centaur.she] [centaur.moans], [centaur.speech(Ready to get throat-fucked, you dumb cunt?!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out an eager moan and offering the [centaur.race] a suitably submissive response, you prepare to swallow [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+]...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With a deep, hungry grunt, [centaur.name] rears up and mounts you in one swift motion. Sliding [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+] up and down over your ass, [centaur.she] [centaur.moans], [centaur.speech(Ready to get rutted, you dumb cunt?!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out an eager moan and offering the [centaur.race] a suitably submissive response, you prepare to receive a good, hard fucking...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_centaur_fucks_sterope_first))
		#IF((!pc.hasVagina() || !pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true)) && (!game.isAnalContentEnabled() || !pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_ANUS, true)))
			<p>
				With one final thrust of [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+], [centaur.name] pulls back and finishes fucking your face. Letting out a deep grunt as [centaur.she] dismounts you, [centaur.name] delivers a sharp slap to your face and declares, [centaur.speech(You were a good fuck, you filthy slut! Now it's your friend's turn...)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				With one final thrust of [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+], [centaur.name] pulls back and finishes rutting you. Letting out a deep grunt as [centaur.she] dismounts you, [centaur.name] delivers a sharp slap to your ass and declares, [centaur.speech(You were a good fuck, you filthy slut! Now it's your friend's turn...)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With one final thrust of [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+], [centaur.name] pulls back and finishes rutting Sterope. Letting out a deep grunt as [centaur.she] dismounts the well-fucked [sterope.race], [centaur.name] delivers a sharp slap to Sterope's ass and declares, [centaur.speech(You were a good fuck, you filthy slut! Now it's your friend's turn...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_SEX_START_STEROPE_NEXT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a deep, hungry grunt, [centaur.name] rears up and mounts Sterope in one swift motion. Sliding [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+] up and down over the [sterope.race]'s ass, [centaur.she] [centaur.moans], [centaur.speech(Ready for this, you filthy bitch?! Let's see if you're as good of a fuck as your friend was!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Yes! ~Mmm!~ Come on, rut me hard!)] Sterope squeals in delight as she prepares to receive a good, hard fucking from [centaur.name]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_SUBMIT_STABLES_SEX_START_PLAYER_NEXT"><![CDATA[
	#IF((!pc.hasVagina() || !pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true)) && (!game.isAnalContentEnabled() || !pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_ANUS, true)))
		<p>
			With a deep, hungry grunt, [centaur.name] trots around in front of you and then quickly rears up to mount your face in one swift motion. Sliding [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+] up and down over the top of your head, [centaur.she] [centaur.moans], [centaur.speech(Ready to get throat-fucked, you filthy bitch?! Let's see if you're as good of a fuck as your friend was!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out an eager moan and offering the [centaur.race] a suitably submissive response, you prepare to swallow [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+]...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With a deep, hungry grunt, [centaur.name] rears up and mounts you in one swift motion. Sliding [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+] up and down over your ass, [centaur.she] [centaur.moans], [centaur.speech(Ready for this, you filthy bitch?! Let's see if you're as good of a fuck as your friend was!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out an eager moan and offering the [centaur.race] a suitably submissive response, you prepare to receive a good, hard fucking...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_AFTER_SEX_FINAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had [centaur.her] fun, [centaur.name] brings an end to the sex with one final, satisfied [centaur.moan]. Returning to stand behind the two of you, [centaur.she] delivers one final sharp slap to each of your asses.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ That was amazing...)] Sterope moans, before taking on a more authoritative tone as she addresses the [centaur.race], [sterope.speech(We're done here, so untie us.)]
	</p>
	#IF(sterope.hasStatusEffect(SE_PREGNANT_0))
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(Let's find out if you got me pregnant,)] Sterope bluntly states as [centaur.name] removes the ropes which were binding the two of you. Swiftly striding over to a nearby shelf, the [sterope.race] picks up an arcane pregnancy tester, before holding it near her stomach. A second later, the device lets out a short beep, after which Sterope places it down onto a nearby table so that she can take a look at the readout. [pc.Stepping] forwards, you look down to see what the device is displaying.
		</p>
		[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
		#IF(sterope.isPregnant())
			<p>
				[sterope.speech(I lost count of how many times I've been knocked up in this stable a long time ago,)] the [sterope.race] casually reveals, before turning to [centaur.name] and explaining, [sterope.speech(I can't perform all my duties at work if I'm pregnant, so I'll have #IF(sterope.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()==1)this brat#ELSEthese brats#ENDIF pumped out and sent packing before morning. Don't like it? Then you should have pulled out or used a condom.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Leaving the [centaur.race] for a moment to think on [centaur.her] decision to creampie her, Sterope walks down to a stall at the far end of the stable.
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[sterope.speech(Great, getting knocked up's hot in the moment, but it's a pain to deal with afterwards,)] the [sterope.race] casually says, before turning to [centaur.name] and explaining, [sterope.speech(I can't perform all my duties at work if I'm pregnant, so if I get knocked up in one of these sessions, I pump the brat out and send them packing before morning.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Leaving the [centaur.race] for a moment to think on her words, Sterope walks down to a stall at the far end of the stable.
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			After [centaur.nameHasFull] quickly removed the ropes which were binding the two of you, Sterope walks down to a stall at the far end of the stable.
	#ENDIF
		 Following her, you see that this stall has been converted into a crude yet functional shower, and after the [sterope.race] has knocked the tap on with her hips, the four ceiling-mounted shower heads come to life. As the water falls all over and around her, Sterope starts to give herself a thorough clean.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(You joining me or what?)] she asks over the sound of the falling water. Seeing that there's plenty of room in this stall for all of you to get clean, you wonder whether or not to take her up on her offer...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_AFTER_SEX_FINAL_SHOWER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[centaur.speech(I'm out of here,)] [centaur.name] grunts, before trotting off and swiftly exiting the stable.
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that you could do with a clean as well, you [pc.step] into the stall and allow the water to fall over your body. Despite having just shared an intimate experience together, Sterope doesn't seem interested in helping you clean yourself, and so you're left to scrub your body alone.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a few minutes, the two of you are as clean as you're going to get, and so the [sterope.race] turns the tap off with another well-placed swing of her hips. The two of you then use some nearby towels to dry yourselves off.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_AFTER_SEX_FINAL_SHOWER_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[centaur.speech(I'm out of here,)] [centaur.name] grunts, before trotting off and swiftly exiting the stable.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not interested in cleaning yourself off, you tell Sterope that you don't need to use the shower. Shrugging her shoulders in a gesture of indifference, she sets about scrubbing her body clean beneath the falling water, before turning the taps off and drying herself off with a couple of nearby towels.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_AFTER_SEX_FINAL_SHOWER_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping over to the pile of her clothing, Sterope starts to get dressed, and as she does so, she simply says, [sterope.speech(We're done here. If you visit me while at work again, don't you dare mention my private life. If you do, then you'll never get to do this with me again.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you get dressed, you tell Sterope that you'll refrain from mentioning this while she's at work. With nothing more to do here now that the two of you have had your fun, all that's left is to head back out into the tavern...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Readily submitting to [centaur.name], you and Sterope allow [centaur.herHim] to tie your hoofs to rings that have been set into the floor. Immobilised and unable to resist, all you can do is turn your head and look back at the [centaur.race] as [centaur.she] kicks open the nearby chest and exclaims in a wicked tone, [centaur.speech(Looks like I've got the equipment to turn you into real mares!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning down, [centaur.name] produces a set of pink straps and buckles from out of the chest. As [centaur.she] untangles them, you see that these straps are in fact two sets of identical tack equipment. Saddles, reins, bridles, and tail wraps are quickly revealed, and you let out a submissive whinny as [centaur.she] roughly forces them onto you.
	</p>
	<p>
		First the saddle is placed onto your back and secured into place, and as the straps are fastened, you feel the saddles' enchantment making you even more submissive than before. The bridle's bit is then forced into your mouth, and as [centaur.name] secures it into place around your horse's muzzle, another enchantment makes you suddenly feel extremely turned on at being tied up and bound in place. Next your tail is tied up with the wrap so that it's standing up and leaving your puffy asshole and feral mare-cunt completely exposed. Again, an enchantment in this tail wrap makes you love the idea of being an exhibitionist, and you can't help but whinny in excitement as [centaur.name] stops to take a good look at your animalistic genitals. Finally, your hoofs are forced down onto four horse shoes, which attach themselves to you and make you have a sudden craving to be abused and treated like dirt.
	</p>
	<p>
		[centaur.speech(That's better,)] the [centaur.race] sneers as [centaur.she] finishes outfitting Sterope in the exact same gear which you've been forced to wear. Delivering sharp slaps to your asses, [centaur.name] laughs, [centaur.speech(You dumb sluts look like real mares now! Now prepare for your punishments, you dumb cunts!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_SEX_START_STEROPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a deep, hungry grunt, [centaur.name] rears up and mounts Sterope in one swift motion, before grabbing hold of her reins and sharply tugging on them. Sliding [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+] up and down over the [sterope.race]'s ass, [centaur.she] [centaur.moans], [centaur.speech(Ready to get rutted, you dumb mare?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Fuck! ~Ooh!~ Yes, fuck me like an animal!)] Sterope squeals in delight as she prepares to receive a good, hard fucking from [centaur.name]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_SEX_START_PLAYER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a deep, hungry grunt, [centaur.name] rears up and mounts you in one swift motion, before grabbing hold of your reins and sharply tugging on them. Sliding [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+] up and down over your ass, [centaur.she] [centaur.moans], [centaur.speech(Ready to get rutted, you dumb mare?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an excited neigh, you completely submit to the [centaur.race] and prepare to receive a good, hard fucking from [centaur.herHim]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_sterope_centaur_fucks_sterope_first))
		<p>
			With one final thrust of [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+], [centaur.name] pulls back and finishes rutting you. Letting out a deep grunt as [centaur.she] dismounts you, [centaur.name] delivers a sharp slap to your ass and declares, [centaur.speech(You were a good fuck, you filthy mare! Now it's your friend's turn...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With one final thrust of [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+], [centaur.name] pulls back and finishes rutting Sterope. Letting out a deep grunt as [centaur.she] dismounts the well-fucked mare, [centaur.name] delivers a sharp slap to Sterope's ass and declares, [centaur.speech(You were a good fuck, you filthy slut! Now it's your friend's turn...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_SEX_START_STEROPE_NEXT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a deep, hungry grunt, [centaur.name] rears up and mounts Sterope in one swift motion. Sliding [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+] up and down over the mare's ass, [centaur.she] [centaur.moans], [centaur.speech(Ready for this, you filthy cunt?! Let's see if you're as good of a fuck as your friend was!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(Yes! ~Mmm!~ Come on, rut me hard!)] Sterope squeals in delight as she prepares to receive a good, hard fucking from [centaur.name]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_SEX_START_PLAYER_NEXT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a deep, hungry grunt, [centaur.name] rears up and mounts you in one swift motion. Sliding [centaur.her] [centaur.cock+] up and down over your ass, [centaur.she] [centaur.moans], [centaur.speech(Ready for this, you filthy mare?! Let's see if you're as good of a fuck as your friend was!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an eager whinny and offering the [centaur.race] a suitably submissive response, you prepare to receive a good, hard fucking...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_AFTER_SEX_FINAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had [centaur.her] fun, [centaur.name] brings an end to the sex with one final, satisfied [centaur.moan]. Returning to stand behind the two of you, [centaur.she] delivers one final sharp slap to each of your asses.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(~Mmm!~ That was amazing...)] Sterope moans, before taking on a more authoritative tone as she addresses the [centaur.race], [sterope.speech(We're done here, so untie us.)]
	</p>
	#IF(sterope.hasStatusEffect(SE_PREGNANT_0))
		<p>
			[sterope.speech(Let's find out if you got me pregnant,)] Sterope bluntly states as [centaur.name] removes the ropes which were binding the two of you. Swiftly trotting over to a nearby shelf, the [sterope.race] picks up an arcane pregnancy tester in her teeth, before bending her nack back and swiping the device over her stomach. A second later, the device lets out a short beep, after which Sterope places it down onto a nearby table so that she can take a look at the readout. [pc.Stepping] forwards, you look down to see what the device is displaying.
		</p>
		[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
		#IF(sterope.isPregnant())
			<p>
				[sterope.speech(I lost count of how many times I've been knocked up in this stable a long time ago,)] the [sterope.race] casually reveals, before turning to [centaur.name] and explaining, [sterope.speech(I can't perform all my duties at work if I'm pregnant, so I'll have #IF(sterope.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()==1)this brat#ELSEthese brats#ENDIF pumped out and sent packing before morning. Don't like it? Then you should have pulled out or used a condom.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Leaving the [centaur.race] for a moment to think on [centaur.her] decision to creampie her, Sterope trots down to a stall at the far end of the stable.
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[sterope.speech(Great, getting knocked up's hot in the moment, but it's a pain to deal with afterwards,)] the [sterope.race] casually says, before turning to [centaur.name] and explaining, [sterope.speech(I can't perform all my duties at work if I'm pregnant, so if I get knocked up in one of these sessions, I pump the brat out and send them packing before morning.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Leaving the [centaur.race] for a moment to think on her words, Sterope trots down to a stall at the far end of the stable.
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			After [centaur.nameHasFull] quickly removed the ropes which were binding the two of you, Sterope trots down to a stall at the far end of the stable.
	#ENDIF
		 Following her, you see that this stall has been converted into a crude yet functional shower, and after the [sterope.race] has knocked the tap on with a kick of her hoof, the four ceiling-mounted shower heads come to life. As the water falls all over and around her, Sterope starts to give herself a thorough clean.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(We've got to wait for the feral transformation to end, so are you joining me or what?)] she asks over the sound of the falling water. Seeing that there's plenty of room in this stall for all of you to get clean, you wonder whether or not to take her up on her offer...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_AFTER_SEX_FINAL_SHOWER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[centaur.speech(I'm out of here,)] [centaur.name] grunts, before trotting off and swiftly exiting the stable.
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that you could do with a clean as well, you [pc.step] into the stall and allow the water to fall over your body. Despite having just shared an intimate experience together, Sterope doesn't seem interested in helping you clean yourself, and so you're left to scrub your body alone.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a few minutes, the two of you are as clean as you're going to get, and so the [sterope.race] turns the tap off with another well-placed swing of her hoof. You copy her as she rubs her flanks against bales of hay to dry herself off, before [pc.stepping] out of the shower.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're also going to have to wait for your feral transformation to expire before being able to retrieve your clothing and belongings, it looks like you're going to have to spend a little more time with Sterope...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_AFTER_SEX_FINAL_SHOWER_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[centaur.speech(I'm out of here,)] [centaur.name] grunts, before trotting off and swiftly exiting the stable.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not interested in cleaning yourself off, you tell Sterope that you don't need to use the shower. Shrugging her shoulders in a gesture of indifference, she sets about scrubbing her body clean beneath the falling water, before turning the taps off and drying herself off by rubbing her flanks against bales of hay.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're also going to have to wait for your feral transformation to expire before being able to retrieve your clothing and belongings, it looks like you're going to have to spend a little more time with Sterope...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STEROPE_CENTAUR_FERAL_AFTER_SEX_FINAL_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thankfully, the two of you don't have to wait for long before your feral transformation reverts, for after just a couple of minutes you feel your body begin to tingle. The process of turning from a quadrupedal animal back into a humanoid is a disorienting blur. A loss of coordination in your limbs is followed by an extreme bout of dizziness, and although you're vaguely aware of your body reshaping as your limbs return to their previous shape, you're mostly oblivious as to what's going on until it's all over.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sterope.speech(You'll get used to it,)] you hear Sterope say as your head finally clears. Looking up at her from your position sitting on the floor, you see that she's returned to her horse-girl form, and has already got dressed. Dropping her cold act for a moment, she smirks and teases, [sterope.speech(I had a lot of fun this evening, [pc.name]. We should do this again some time...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she swiftly departs, leaving you to look yourself over and discover that you've been left in the body of [pc.a_fullRace(true)]. Gathering your things, you follow Sterope back out into the tavern and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>