<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="HARPY_NEST_DOMINANT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_dominantEncountered))
				Due to the ongoing arcane storm, [harpyDominant.namePos] nest is completely deserted. Her entire flock has retreated into the safety of the upper-floor of the building below, leaving you with no choice but to return at another time if you wanted to speak to her.
			#ELSE
				Due to the ongoing arcane storm, this nest is completely deserted. The entire flock has retreated into the safety of the upper-floor of the building below, leaving you with no choice but to return at another time if you wanted to speak to the matriarch of this particular nest.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(!game.isExtendedWorkTime())
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_dominantEncountered))
				Due to the current hour, [dominantHarpy.namePos] nest is completed deserted; both she and her flock have retired to the comfort of the buildings below in order to get a good night's rest. With the entrances to their night-time residence being securely locked, you're left with no choice but to return at another time if you wanted to speak to her.
			#ELSE
				Due to the current hour, this nest is completed deserted; both the matriarch and her flock have retired to the comfort of the buildings below in order to get a good night's rest. With the entrances to their night-time residence being securely locked, you're left with no choice but to return at another time if you wanted to speak to her.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_dominantEncountered))
			<p>
				You find yourself standing on the outskirts of [harpyDominant.namePos] nest; one of the largest and most populous of all the nests in Dominion. A single, gigantic platform spans the roof-tops of several buildings, with little raised podiums scattered about its surface.
				#IF(!game.isDayTime())
					 A series of bright, arcane-powered lights illuminate the entire area, and from what you can see, the harpies here are just as active at night as they are during daylight hours.
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				Looking closer at the nest's peculiar podiums, you see that there's a red-and-black feathered harpy perched on top of each one. Around the base of each one of these podiums, a crowd of harpies can be seen huddling together, and upon further inspection you notice that they're all bowing down in submission. Curiously, although you can see harpies of almost every colour, the only ones with red or black feathers seem to be those who are sitting on top of those podiums, leading you to believe that those particular colours designate the important members of this particular flock.
			</p>
			<p>
				At the very centre of the platform, you see a podium that's higher than all the rest, and, lounging about on top of it, you see the familiar shape of [harpyDominant.name]. The group surrounding her is unlike all the others, as it's made up solely of the same red-and-black feathered harpies that you can see on top of the other podiums. Despite their somewhat aggressive appearance, the harpies of this flock don't seem to be too bothered by your presence, allowing you to approach [harpyDominant.name] if you had any business with her.
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				You find yourself standing on the outskirts of one of the largest and most populous of all the nests in Dominion. A single, gigantic platform spans the roof-tops of several buildings, with little raised podiums scattered about its surface.
				#IF(!game.isDayTime())
					 A series of bright, arcane-powered lights illuminate the entire area, and from what you can see, the harpies here are just as active at night as they are during daylight hours.
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				Looking closer at the nest's peculiar podiums, you see that there's a red-and-black feathered harpy perched on top of each one. Around the base of each one of these podiums, a crowd of harpies can be seen huddling together, and upon further inspection you notice that they're all bowing down in submission. Curiously, although you can see harpies of almost every colour, the only ones with red or black feathers seem to be those who are sitting on top of those podiums, leading you to believe that those particular colours designate the important members of this particular flock.
			</p>
			<p>
				At the very centre of the platform, you see a podium that's higher than all the rest, and, lounging about on top of it, you see what must be this nest's matriarch. The group surrounding her is unlike all the others, as it's made up solely of the same red-and-black feathered harpies that you can see on top of the other podiums. Despite their somewhat aggressive appearance, the harpies of this flock don't seem to be too bothered by your presence, allowing you to approach their matriarch if you had any business with her.
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="HARPY_NEST_DOMINANT_APPROACH"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_dominantEncountered))
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_dominantPacified))
			<p>
				Deciding to pay [harpyDominant.Name] another visit, you set off towards the centre podium. As you make your way towards the dominant matriarch, you get a good look at the harpies that make up her flock. Just as you've seen before, there's a red-and-black-feathered harpy sitting on top of each of the small podiums that are scattered about the area.
			</p>
			<p>
				The groups that are huddled around each one of these podiums are, unlike their apparent leaders, made up of all sorts of differently coloured harpies. Most of them are on their knees, preening each other's feathers, or talking in hushed tones to one another. Those that aren't on their knees are found at the very base of these podiums, and as you pass, you get yet another look at these unfortunate few.
			</p>
			<p>
				Obviously having displeased their leader in some way, these harpies have been stripped naked and locked into wooden stocks. Some of the flock are taking full advantage of their compromised position, and as you pass each podium, you see all manner of public humiliation taking place. From light spanking and tickling, all the way up to rough group sex, these harpies are being used and abused by rest of their flock.
			</p>
			<p>
				You don't have much time to dwell on any thoughts about this, however, as before you know it, you've reached the centre of the platform. Although larger and made up solely of the red-and-black 'leader' harpies, the group surrounding [harpyDominant.NamePos] podium is similar to all those that you've previously passed. Most are on their knees, talking to one another, but there are several others, not all of them red-and-black, who are locked up in this podium's stocks.
			</p>
			<p>
				As you approach [harpyDominant.Name], your eyes are drawn to the latest of [harpyDominantCompanion.namePos] victims in the stocks in front of you. She's moaning and squealing out loud; the cause of her erotic noises taking the form of a very feminine-looking harpy thrusting away at her exposed rear end. Coming to a halt in front of the podium, you hear [harpyDominantCompanion.name] growling out, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Fucking slut! That's right! Moan for me, whore!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Just as you're about to say something, [harpyDominant.Name], only just noticing your presence, calls out, [harpyDominant.speech([pc.Mistress]! You're back!)]
			</p>
			#IF(harpyDominant.isVisiblyPregnant())
				<p>
					#IF(!harpyDominant.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
						As she jumps down off of her podium, you see that [harpyDominant.name] is sporting a [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and as she gestures towards it, she reveals, [harpyDominant.speech(You got me pregnant, [pc.mistress]...)]
					#ELSE
						Jumping down off of her podium, [harpyDominant.name] gestures towards her [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)] and states, [harpyDominant.speech(I'm still pregnant from when you knocked me up, [pc.mistress]...)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					Noticing what's going on, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] lets out a little squeak, and after quickly pulling out of her fuck-toy, jumps down onto her knees beside her matriarch. Not giving you a moment in which to comment on her pregnancy, [harpyDominant.Name] bows her head and asks, [harpyDominant.speech(What can I do for you [pc.mistress]?)]
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Jumping down off of her podium, [harpyDominant.name] falls to her knees before you. Noticing what's going on, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] lets out a little squeak, and after quickly pulling out of her fuck-toy, jumps down onto her knees beside her matriarch. Shuffling forwards, [harpyDominant.Name] bows her head, before asking, [harpyDominant.speech(What can I do for you [pc.mistress]?)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Deciding to pay [harpyDominant.Name] another visit, you set off towards the centre podium. As you make your way towards the dominant matriarch, you get a good look at the harpies that make up her flock. Just as you've seen before, there's a red-and-black-feathered harpy sitting on top of each of the small podiums that are scattered about the area.
			</p>
			<p>
				The groups that are huddled around each one of these podiums are, unlike their apparent leaders, made up of all sorts of differently coloured harpies. Most of them are on their knees, preening each other's feathers, or talking in hushed tones to one another. Those that aren't on their knees are found at the very base of these podiums, and as you pass, you get yet another look at these unfortunate few.
			</p>
			<p>
				Obviously having displeased their leader in some way, these harpies have been stripped naked and locked into wooden stocks. Some of the flock are taking full advantage of their compromised position, and as you pass each podium, you see all manner of public humiliation taking place. From light spanking and tickling, all the way up to rough group sex, these harpies are being used and abused by rest of their flock.
			</p>
			<p>
				You don't have much time to dwell on any thoughts about this, however, as before you know it, you've reached the centre of the platform. Although larger and made up solely of the red-and-black 'leader' harpies, the group surrounding [harpyDominant.NamePos] podium is similar to all those that you've previously passed. Most are on their knees, talking to one another, but there are several others, not all of them red-and-black, who are locked up in this podium's stocks.
			</p>
			<p>
				As you approach [harpyDominant.Name], your eyes are drawn to the latest of [harpyDominantCompanion.namePos] victims in the stocks in front of you. She's moaning and squealing out loud; the cause of her erotic noises taking the form of a very feminine-looking harpy thrusting away at her exposed rear end. Coming to a halt in front of the podium, you hear [harpyDominantCompanion.name] growling out, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Fucking slut! That's right! Moan for me, whore!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Just as you're about to say something, [harpyDominant.Name], up until now having ignored your presence, calls out,
				#IF(pc.getFemininityValue()>FEMININITY_FEMININE_STRONG.getMinimumFemininity())
					 [harpyDominant.speech([harpyDominantCompanion.Name]! That hungry slut is back for more of our attention!)]
				#ELSE
					 [harpyDominant.speech([harpyDominantCompanion.Name]! That bitch is back for more of our attention!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				[harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Yes, [harpyDominant.name]!)] the harpy calls out, before growling at her victim. [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Once I'm done with this, I'm using your ass next!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Standing up on top of her podium, [harpyDominant.name] growls down at you, 
				#IF(pc.getFemininityValue()>FEMININITY_FEMININE_STRONG.getMinimumFemininity())
					 [harpyDominant.speech(So?! What do you want, whore?!)]
				#ELSE
					 [harpyDominant.speech(So?! What do you want, bitch?!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		 <p>
			Recognising this as one of the nests that you agreed to pacify, you start walking towards the centre podium. As you make your way towards the matriarch, you get a good look at the harpies that reside in this particular nest. Just as you saw from the outskirts, there's a red-feathered harpy sitting on top of each of the small podiums that are scattered about the area. Each one has a plume of jet-black feathers on top of their heads, and the skin that covers their human parts is invariably a light olive colour.
		</p>
		<p>
			The groups that are huddled around each one of these podiums are, unlike their apparent leaders, made up of all sorts of differently coloured harpies. Most of them are on their knees, preening each other's feathers, or talking in hushed tones to one another. Those that aren't on their knees are found at the very base of these podiums, and as you get closer, you find yourself staring, wide-eyed, at these unfortunate few.
		</p>
		<p>
			Obviously having displeased their leader in some way, these harpies have been stripped naked and locked into wooden stocks. Some of the flock are taking full advantage of their compromised position, and as you pass each podium, you see all manner of public humiliation taking place. From light spanking and tickling, all the way up to rough group sex, these harpies are being used and abused by rest of their flock.
		</p>
		<p>
			You don't have much time to dwell on any thoughts about this, however, as before you know it, you've reached the centre of the platform. Although larger and made up solely of the red-and-black 'leader' harpies, the group surrounding the matriarch's podium is similar to all those that you've previously passed. Most are on their knees, talking to one another, but there are several others, not all of them red-and-black, who are locked up in this podium's stocks.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you approach the matriarch, your eyes are drawn to a particular pink-feathered harpy in the stocks in front of you. She's moaning and squealing out loud; the cause of her erotic noises taking the form of a very feminine-looking harpy thrusting away at her exposed rear end. Coming to a halt in front of the podium, you hear the dominant harpy growling out, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(That's right, bitch! I knew you'd end up loving it eventually!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Just as you're about to say something, the matriarch, up until now having ignored your presence, calls out,
			#IF(pc.getFemininityValue()>FEMININITY_FEMININE_STRONG.getMinimumFemininity())
				 [harpyDominant.speech([harpyDominantCompanion.Name]! You can finish with your fuck-toy later! There's another hungry slut right here that needs our attention!)]
			#ELSE
				 [harpyDominant.speech([harpyDominantCompanion.Name]! You can finish with your fuck-toy later! There's some bitch here that needs our attention!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Yes, [harpyDominant.name]!)] the harpy calls out, before growling at her victim. [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Don't think this is over whore! I'm gonna use your ass next time!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As the matriarch, [harpyDominant.Name], stands up on top of her podium, you finally get a good look at her. Just like the other harpy leaders that you've seen, the feathers covering [harpyDominant.NamePos] wings and tail-feathers are bright red, and instead of hair, she's got a long plume of jet-black feathers on top of her head. Her face, one the most beautiful that you've ever seen, is covered in flawless, olive skin, just like the rest of her human body parts. She has average-sized breasts for a harpy, being B-cups, which are covered by her silky black plunge dress.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you're taking in her gorgeous appearance, she growls down at you, 
			#IF(pc.getFemininityValue()>FEMININITY_FEMININE_STRONG.getMinimumFemininity())
				 [harpyDominant.speech(So?! What do you want, whore?!)]
			#ELSE
				 [harpyDominant.speech(So?! What do you want, bitch?!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(!flags.hasFlag(FLAG_dominantPacified) && game.isBadEndsEnabled() && pc.isAbleToHaveRaceTransformed())
		<p style='text-align:center;'><i>
			[style.italicsBadEnd(You get the feeling that you'd be in serious trouble if you were to lose a fight against these harpies...)]
		</i></p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Angry scenes: -->
	
    <htmlContent tag="DOMINANT_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        Deciding that now isn't the best time to be confronting [harpyDominant.name], you turn around and hurry away from the podium. You hear [harpyDominant.name] growling to [harpyDominantCompanion.name] as you leave, [harpyDominant.speechNoEffects(What the fuck was that all about?! Whatever! [harpyDominantCompanion.Name], you can carry on playing with your fuck-toy now...)]
    </p>
    <p>
        Ignoring her words, you continue down the steps and back across the main platform, quickly finding yourself back on the outskirts of the nest.
    </p>
	]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Pacified scenes: -->
	
    <htmlContent tag="PACIFIED_DOMINANT_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        Deciding that you don't want to talk to [harpyDominant.name] right now, you turn around and take your leave. You hear [harpyDominant.name] sighing to [harpyDominantCompanion.name] as you walk away, [harpyDominant.speechNoEffects(Aww! I was hoping for some fun...)]
    </p>
    <p>
        Ignoring her words, you continue down the steps and back across the main platform, quickly finding yourself back on the outskirts of the nest.
    </p>
	]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="PACIFIED_DOMINANT_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        Eager to put [harpyDominant.name] in her place in front of her inner-circle, you reach down and grab her by her wings. Pulling her to her feet, you [pc.step] forwards, before planting a deep kiss on her [harpyDominant.lips+].
    </p>
    <p>
        [harpyDominant.Name] responds to your dominant move by letting out a submissive little whine, and, wrapping her wings around your back, she passionately starts returning your kiss...
    </p>
	]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="PACIFIED_DOMINANT_SEX_START_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        Although you've asserted your superiority over [harpyDominant.name], you find yourself wanting nothing more than to submit to her. Revealing your desire to the harpy matriarch, you ask her to dominate you and put you in your place.
    </p>
    <p>
        A wicked smirk flashes across [harpyDominant.namePos] face as she hears this, and after swiftly stepping forwards and wrapping her wings around your back, she roughly pulls you into a deep, passionate kiss...
    </p>
	]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="DOMINANT_SEX_START_ORAL"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        Eager to put [harpyDominant.name] and [harpyDominantCompanion.name] in their place in front of their nest's inner-circle, you reach down and grab the dominant matriarch's wings. Pulling her to her feet, you [pc.step] forwards and plant a deep kiss on her [harpyDominant.lips+], drawing a series of lustful moans from the surrounding harpies as you do so.
    </p>
	#IF(!harpyDominantCompanion.isAttractedTo(pc))
		<p>
			[harpyDominant.Name] responds to your dominant move by wrapping her wings around your back, grinding herself up against you, and passionately returning your kiss. Letting out an angry tut, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] sneers, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(I can't believe [harpyDominant.name] is submitting to you... There's no way I'd let you kiss me like that...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Breaking off your kiss with [harpyDominant.Name], you tell [harpyDominantCompanion.name] that as you're in charge of this next, she doesn't have any say in the matter. Grabbing the matriarch's subordinate, you pull her into your embrace and give her a taste of your [pc.tongue+]. As the shocked harpy lets out a muffled cry of protest into your mouth, nervous laughter breaks out amongst the surrounding harpies.
		</p>
		<p>
			Wanting the matriarch's and her subordinate's lips to be employed elsewhere, you break off your kiss, before taking hold of both of the harpies' shoulders and pushing them to their knees before you. Realising what it is you want, [harpyDominant.Name] eagerly shuffles forwards towards your groin, pulling [harpyDominantCompanion.name] along beside her as she does so. Gazing up into your eyes, she moans, [harpyDominant.speech(Don't worry about [harpyDominantCompanion.name]. She'll do what I tell her to.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Eugh... Yes, I'll do what you say, Mistress...)] [harpyDominantCompanion.name] groans as her matriarch forces her to join in with performing oral on you...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[harpyDominant.Name] responds to your dominant move by wrapping her wings around your back, grinding herself up against you as she passionately returns your kiss. Letting out a hungry moan, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] eagerly asks, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(You're not going to leave me to stand back and watch, are you?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With [harpyDominant.name] continuing to desperately kiss you, you motion for [harpyDominantCompanion.name] to step forwards and join in. As she happily strides forwards, you pull back from [harpyDominant.namePos] lips, before swiftly grabbing [harpyDominant.namePos] head and giving her a taste of your [pc.tongue+]. As the lustful harpy leans heavily into you, subdued chatter breaks out amongst the surrounding dominant harpies.
		</p>
		<p>
			Wanting the matriarch's and her subordinate's lips to be employed elsewhere, you break off your kiss, before taking hold of both of the harpies' shoulders and pushing them to their knees before you. Realising what it is you want, they both eagerly shuffle forwards towards your groin. Looking up at you, [harpyDominant.name] hungrily moans, [harpyDominant.speech(We'll take good care of you... Isn't that right, [harpyDominantCompanion.name]?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Yes, Mistress...)] [harpyDominantCompanion.name] replies, and you can't help but grin as she and her matriarch eagerly prepare to perform oral on you...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
    </htmlContent>

    <htmlContent tag="DOMINANT_SEX_START_DOGGY"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        Eager to put [harpyDominant.name] and [harpyDominantCompanion.name] in their place in front of their nest's inner-circle, you grab hold of both of them and push them down onto their hands and knees before you. As you drop down behind them, [harpyDominant.name] passionately moans, [harpyDominant.speech(Come on, give the two of us a real good fuck! Use me and [harpyDominantCompanion.name] as much as you want!)]
    </p>
	#IF(!harpyDominantCompanion.isAttractedTo(pc))
		<p>
			Letting out a disgusted groan, the matriarch's subordinate looks back over her shoulder and grunts in disapproval, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Eugh... I'm only doing this because I have no other choice!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Ignoring her words, you lustfully gaze down at [harpyDominantCompanion.name] and her matriarch as you prepare to fuck them side-by-side...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Letting out a hungry moan, the matriarch's subordinate looks back over her shoulder and cries out, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Yes! Please, fuck me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pleased to hear that she's more than happy to be involved in this threesome, you lustfully gaze down at [harpyDominantCompanion.name] and her matriarch as you prepare to fuck them side-by-side...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
    </htmlContent>

    <htmlContent tag="DOMINANT_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(sex.isSatisfiedFromOrgasms(harpyDominant, true))
		<p>
			As you [pc.step] back from [harpyDominant.name], she sinks to the floor, totally worn out from her
			#IF(sex.getNumberOfOrgasms(harpyDominant)>1)
				 orgasms.
			#ELSE
				 orgasm.
			#ENDIF
			 Biting her lip and flashing you a dirty look, she teases, [harpyDominant.speech(I could get used to this, you know...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As you [pc.step] back from [harpyDominant.name], she sinks to the floor, letting out a desperate whine as she realises that you've finished with her. Her feathered hands dart down between her legs, and she frantically starts masturbating as she seeks to finish what you started.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(sex.getAllParticipants(false).contains(harpyDominantCompanion))
		#IF(sex.isSatisfiedFromOrgasms(harpyDominantCompanion, true))
			<p>
				Letting out a deeply satisfied sigh, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] looks to be completely exhausted from the
				#IF(sex.getNumberOfOrgasms(harpyDominantCompanion)>1)
					 orgasms
				#ELSE
					 orgasm
				#ENDIF
				 you gave her. Panting and looking up into your eyes, she moans, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(That was... Wow...)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Not being satisfied from this sexual experience, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] looks over at her matriarch, and as she watches [harpyDominant.namePos] [harpyDominant.breasts+] rise and fall, she starts shamelessly masturbating right there in front of the rest of the surrounding harpies.
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		[harpyDominant.NamePos] inner-circle of harpies, having watched the whole thing, kneel down in submission as you finish with their matriarch. Excitedly chattering amongst themselves, they talk about your performance and wonder aloud how long it will be before you're back for more...
	</p>
	]]>
    </htmlContent>

    <htmlContent tag="DOMINANT_LEAVE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(sex.getAllParticipants(false).contains(harpyDominantCompanion))
		<p>
			Having shown these harpies their place, you set off down the staircase, and after walking back across the lower platform, you quickly find yourself on the outskirts of [harpyDominant.namePos] nest once again.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having shown [harpyDominant.name] her place, you set off down the staircase, and after walking back across the lower platform, you quickly find yourself on the outskirts of [harpyDominant.namePos] nest once again.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- After losing fight: -->
	
    <htmlContent tag="COMBAT_LOST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You fall to the floor, totally beaten. As you collapse, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] jumps down on top of you, pinning you to the floor as she calls out to her matriarch, [harpyDominantCompanion.speechNoEffects([harpyDominant.Name]! The stupid bitch is ready for [pc.her] punishment now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[harpyDominant.speech(Good girl, [harpyDominantCompanion.name]!)] you hear her respond. [harpyDominant.speech(I think it's time to teach this insolent little [pc.race] a lesson!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As [harpyDominantCompanion.name] continues holding you down, [harpyDominant.name] calls out for the rest of the surrounding harpies to help. Rushing to obey their mistress, several of the red-and-black harpies dash forwards and help to pin your [pc.arms] and [pc.legs] to the floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		[harpyDominant.speech(That's right, hold [pc.herHim] still!)] [harpyDominant.name] calls out, stepping down from her podium before strutting over to you. [harpyDominant.speech(Fucking bitch! I know just what you need! Coming into <i>my</i> nest, then trying to act all tough?! You just want to be one of my bitches, don't you?!)]
	</p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="COMBAT_LOST_MATRIARCH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You fall to the floor, totally beaten. As you collapse, [dominantHarpy.name] orders her flock to hold you still, and, rushing to obey their matriarch, you're quickly pinned to the floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dominantHarpy.speech([dominantHarpyCompanion.name], get up!)] you hear [dominantHarpy.name] shouting to her companion. [dominantHarpy.speech(It's time to teach this insolent [pc.race] a lesson!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the members of [dominantHarpy.namePos] inner-circle continue to hold you down, you hear the dominant matriarch and her companion walking towards you. The harpies start laughing as you try to wriggle free, but you're too weak from the fight to offer any real resistance.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dominantHarpy.speech(Time for some revenge, [dominantHarpyCompanion.name]!)] [dominantHarpy.name] shouts out, and as her companion moves to help the other harpies hold you down, she laughs, [harpyDominant.speech(You dumb cunt! I know just what you need! Coming into <i>my</i> nest, then trying to act all tough?! You just want to be one of my bitches, don't you?!)]
	</p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="COMBAT_LOST_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speechNoEffects(Let me go!)] you shout, struggling against the harpies holding you down. You're too weak to shake them off, however, and they easily continue to pin you to the floor, holding you quite still as [harpyDominant.name] sneers down at you.
	</p>
	#IF(game.isBadEndsEnabled())
		<p>
			[harpyDominant.speech([dominantHarpyCompanion.Name], strip this bitch!)] she commands her subordinate, and as she watches you helplessly trying to resist as her harpies strip you out of all your clothing, she teases, [harpyDominant.speech(You're so feisty! I can already see that you're going to turn out to be one of my most interesting pets!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Now completely naked, you're once again forced down onto your back, before [dominantHarpyCompanion.name] sits on your chest. As the sadistic harpy laughs at your fruitless attempts to pull free, her matriarch brings a dark red perfume bottle up to your face. Grinning evilly, she leans in to you, and as she prepares to spray the bottle's contents onto your helpless body, she teases, [harpyDominant.speech(Breathe in deeply! In just a moment you'll be nothing more than one of my angry little bitches!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[harpyDominant.speech(That's the spirit!)] she laughs. [harpyDominant.speech(You're so feisty! It's better to channel all that pent up energy elsewhere though. Don't worry, <i>this</i> will help you with that!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As [dominantHarpyCompanion.name] sits on your chest, laughing at your fruitless attempts to pull free, [harpyDominant.name] brings a dark red perfume bottle up to your face. Grinning evilly, she leans in to you, ready to spray the bottle's contents onto your helpless body...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="COMBAT_LOST_NO_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unwilling to be transformed into one of [harpyDominant.namePos] harpies, you furiously yank your arm free of their grip. In the seconds you have before you're restrained again, you reach up to grab the bottle of perfume from [harpyDominant.namePos] feathered had, before hurling it across the nest to smash into pieces against the hard wooden floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		[harpyDominant.speech(You fucking bitch!)] [harpyDominant.name] screams, grabbing your chin and squeezing cruelly down as she scowls at you. [harpyDominant.speech(You're going to fucking pay for that! [harpyDominantCompanion.Name]! This bitch wants my full attention! How about you help [pc.herHim] entertain me?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Any protests or objections that you might have are muffled as [harpyDominantCompanion.namePos] feathered hand clamps down over your mouth. Leaning down to stare into your eyes, she chuckles, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Let's put on a show!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		For the next few hours, you're forced to act as [harpyDominantCompanion.namePos] play-thing. Tying you up in bondage, publicly spanking you in front of [harpyDominant.name], and being walked around the nest on a leash are amongst the least humiliating things you suffer. Thankfully, the harpies don't show any interest in forcing you to perform any penetrative sexual acts, and they eventually all lose interest.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [harpyDominantCompanion.name] declares that she's bored of playing with you, [harpyDominant.name] finally sets you free. [harpyDominant.speech(Alright bitch! I think you've had enough! Now get the fuck out of my nest!)]
	</p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="COMBAT_LOST_TF_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You stay still, allowing [harpyDominant.name] to spray the bottle's contents onto your face and neck as she taunts you, [harpyDominant.speech(You want to act like an angry, bitchy little harpy? You'd better have the body to match it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You try to make a response, but as you open your mouth, the choking perfume enters your airways, leaving you coughing and spluttering on the floor. Before you know what you're doing, you're breathing in deeply, letting out little whining noises as you find yourself desperate to inhale as much of the sweet-smelling perfume as you possibly can...
	</p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="COMBAT_LOST_TF_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As the perfume's transformative effects come to an end, the harpies' grip on your [pc.arms] and [pc.legs] loosens. Blinking slowly a few times, you let out an exhausted moan, [pc.speech(~Ahh!~ You bitch...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The flock of harpies bursts out into laughter, and the ones who were holding you down finally release you before backing off. Scrambling to your knees, you find yourself looking up at [harpyDominant.Name] as she continues towering over you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[harpyDominant.speech(Good little harpy! Now, after you apologise, you can fuck off and make your own flock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the effects of the perfume still lingering in your mind, you find yourself blurting out, [pc.speech(I'm not apologising to you! Fucking bitch, I'm out of here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[harpyDominant.Name] grins down at you, and, to the background noise of dozens of harpies' laughter, she shouts, [harpyDominant.speech([harpyDominantCompanion.Name]! This bitch wants my full attention! How about you help [pc.herHim] entertain me?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Any protests or objections that you might have are muffled as [harpyDominantCompanion.namePos] feathered hand clamps down over your mouth. Leaning down to stare into your eyes, she chuckles, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Let's put on a show!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		For the next few hours, you're forced to act as [harpyDominantCompanion.namePos] play-thing. Tying you up in bondage, publicly spanking you in front of [harpyDominant.name], and being walked around the nest on a leash are amongst the least humiliating things you suffer. Thankfully, the harpies don't show any interest in forcing you to perform any penetrative sexual acts, and they eventually all lose interest.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [harpyDominantCompanion.name] declares that she's bored of playing with you, [harpyDominant.name] finally sets you free. [harpyDominant.speech(Alright, bitch! I think you've had enough! Now get the fuck out of my nest!)]
	</p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="COMBAT_LOST_THROWN_OUT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finally given an opportunity to leave, you do as [harpyDominant.name] commands. Running away from the harpies' mocking laughter, you dash across the platform, and before you know it, you find yourself back on the outskirts of the nest...
	</p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Bad end: -->
	
    <htmlContent tag="COMBAT_LOST_BAD_END_TF_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Completely overpowered by the aggressive harpies and totally at their mercy, you can't do anything but obey [dominantHarpy.namePos] command. As she starts liberally spraying you with the sweet-smelling perfume, you're unable to prevent the choking vapour from entering your airways, leaving you coughing and spluttering on the floor. Before you know what you're doing, you're breathing in deeply, letting out little whining noises as you find yourself desperate to inhale as much of the sweet-smelling perfume as you possibly can.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dominantHarpy.speechNoEffects(That's right, you pathetic bitch, breathe it all in!)] she mocks, [dominantHarpy.speechNoEffects(Now turn into an angry little harpy bitch for me!)]
	</p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="COMBAT_LOST_BAD_END_TF_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As the perfume's transformative effects come to an end, the harpies' grip on your [pc.arms] and [pc.legs] loosens. Blinking slowly a few times, you let out an exhausted moan, [pc.speech(~Ahh!~ You bitch...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The flock of harpies bursts out into laughter, and the ones who were holding you down finally release you before backing off. Scrambling to your knees, you find yourself looking up at [harpyDominant.Name] as she continues towering over you. With an evil smirk on her face, she demands, [harpyDominant.speech(Apologise to me, you worthless slut! Grovel before me and tell me that you'll serve me!)]
	</p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="COMBAT_LOST_BAD_END_RETORT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With the effects of the perfume still lingering in your mind, you find yourself furiously shouting out, [pc.speech(Fuck you, bitch! I'm not saying sorry!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly having expected this, [harpyDominant.name] continues evilly grinning down at you, and to the background noise of dozens of dominant harpies hurling insults at you, she shouts, [harpyDominant.speech(So, it would seem that I need to put you in your place! You're just one of my worthless harpy bitches now, understand? I'm your matriarch, and I'll do whatever I want with you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can respond to this, the matriarch snaps her fingers and orders her subordinates, [harpyDominant.speech(Restrain this bitch! I know just how to train her!)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasVagina())
		<p>
			Once again, you find yourself being overpowered by [harpyDominant.namePos] harpies, and as they roughly restrain you, the sadistic matriarch sneers, [harpyDominant.speech(Some time in the stocks will make it clear to you what your place is... [harpyDominantCompanion.Name]! Break this bitch!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Although you struggle against them, the harpies manage to manhandle you over to a nearby set of stocks, and after a brief scuffle, you find your [pc.arms] and head securely locked into the wooden device. From the big grin on her face, you can see that [harpyDominantCompanion.name] is delighted to be carrying out her matriarch's orders, and with a skip in her step she swiftly moves around behind you.
		</p>
		<p>
			[harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Please do try to resist for as long as you can. It's no fun otherwise!)] [harpyDominantCompanion.name] laughs, before swinging her hand down as hard as she can to forcefully slap your exposed ass. Moaning in delight in response to the alarmed cry which involuntarily bursts out from between your [pc.lips], [harpyDominantCompanion.name] wastes no time in lifting her hand and slapping your ass once again. Repeating this movement over and over again, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] soon reduces you to a squirming, crying mess.
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(No more! Please!)] you desperately cry out, unable to endure any more of this ruthless punishment.
		</p>
		<p>
			[harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Had enough already?)] [harpyDominantCompanion.name] whines in disappointment, before eagerly moaning, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(It's time to start your training then! You're going to be my bitch!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After a brief moment as she displaces her clothing, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] steps up right behind you, and you can't help but let out a shocked gasp as you feel the head of her cock sliding up and down over your [pc.labia+]...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Once again, you find yourself being overpowered by [harpyDominant.namePos] harpies, and as they roughly restrain you, the sadistic matriarch sneers, [harpyDominant.speech(Giving you your new uniform should show you what your place is... [harpyDominantCompanion.Name]! Dress this bitch!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Although you struggle against them, the harpies prove to be too strong for you, and so after a brief scuffle, you're left with a ballgag firmly fitted into your mouth, a choker fastened around your neck, and a set of revealing, dark purple latex clothing snugly hugging your legs, stomach, and arms. Although your [pc.breasts+] are fully on display, a pair of tape crosses have been stuck over your nipples, and as you reach up to touch them, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] suddenly slaps you and hisses, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(You're not to move unless ordered to, bitch! Now kneel down before your matriarch!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Not giving you any choice in the matter, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] forcefully pushes you down before [harpyDominant.name], who lets out a cruel, mocking laugh and declares, [harpyDominant.speech(That's better! Do you understand your place now, slut? That tag on your choker says 'obedient toy', and that's exactly what you'll be, <i>or else</i>!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With those final, threatening words, the matriarch stoops down to deliver a stinging slap across your face. Unable to respond due to the ballgag in your mouth, you have no other option but to kneel before her and wait to see what it is these harpies will do with you. You're not waiting for long, however, as after straightening up, [harpyDominant.name] calls out, [harpyDominant.speech(Bring that slut, [harpyDominantVictim.name], here! It's time for her punishment!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			A few moments later, a female harpy is led into the area. Blindfolded and bound from head-to-toe in bondage gear, she's forced to crawl forwards on all fours, and as she comes to a halt before [harpyDominant.name], you see that her breasts and groin are exposed in much the same way that yours are. After briefly smirking down at this unfortunate harpy, the matriarch looks over to you and states, [harpyDominant.speech(This worthless bitch is being punished for bringing me the wrong drink that I'd asked for. To remind her of what a dumb cunt she is, she's going to be publicly fucked by an equally-worthless slut. So go on, bitch, mount her! Look, the slut's already wet and ready for it!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking over at [harpyDominantVictim.name], you see that her pussy is indeed already wet, and as she lifts her hips so as to present herself, you realise that you've got very little choice but to do as you're told...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="BAD_END_SEX_VAGINA_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Locked in the stocks and unable to do resist, you're powerless to prevent [harpyDominantCompanion.name] from continuing to tease her cock up and down over your [pc.labia+]. Grabbing your [pc.hips+], she teases, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Come on, bitch, beg for it! Or would you like to go back to the spanking?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your sore ass proving to be a potent reminder of the pain you were just forced to endure, you find yourself opting for the easier choice, and find yourself moaning, [pc.speech(Please, fuck me! No more spankings!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Good bitch!)] [harpyDominantCompanion.name] triumphantly moans, before thrusting forwards and roughly ramming her [harpyDominantCompanion.cock+] deep into your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out a series of dominant groans, she proceeds to rhythmically fuck you in front of all the other harpies...
	</p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="BAD_END_SEX_PENIS_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Before you can make a move, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] aggressively hisses down at you, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Either fuck her, or else I'll spend the rest of today making you wish you'd never even heard of harpies!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a choice between fucking [harpyDominantVictim.name] or being forced to endure some kind of brutal punishment, you decide to go with the easier of the two options. Shuffling forwards, you clamber up over [harpyDominantVictim.namePos] back, and once you've mounted her, you feel your rapidly-hardening cock prod at her [harpyDominantVictim.labia+].
	</p>
	<p>
		[harpyDominant.speech(You can put your tongue to work while my pet fucks you,)] [harpyDominant.name] suddenly states, and after quickly exposing her pussy, she roughly pulls [harpyDominantVictim.namePos] face into her groin. Forcing her victim to eat her out, the sadistic matriarch growls down at you, [harpyDominant.speech(What are you waiting for, bitch? Fuck her worthless cunt!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The matriarch's order, combined with the feeling of [harpyDominantVictim.namePos] wet pussy rubbing against your cock, is too much for you to refuse, and so with a buck of your hips, you thrust your [pc.cock+] into [harpyDominantVictim.namePos] cunt and start fucking her while she eats out [harpyDominant.name]...
	</p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="BAD_END_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasVagina())
		<p>
			Having had her fun, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] pulls her softening cock out of your well-fucked pussy, and after giving your ass one final, stinging slap, she struts off to another part of the nest. A moment later another male harpy approaches you, and without even saying a word, steps around behind you and impatiently shoves her cock into your pussy. As your new partner starts groaning and frantically thrusting her cock in and out of your quivering cunt, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] returns with a very familiar-looking bottle of perfume in her hands.
		</p>
		<p>
			[harpyDominant.speech(The mind-altering effects of this perfume can wear off after a while, but I've been reliably informed that prolonged exposure to it will make the changes permanent,)] [harpyDominant.name] sneers as she steps up beside [harpyDominantCompanion.name]. Giving her subordinate a nod, she commands, [harpyDominant.speech(Keep on spraying her until she sees herself as nothing more than another one of my bitches.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a cruel laugh, [harpyDominant.name] then struts off, leaving [harpyDominantCompanion.name] to carry out her orders. As your pussy continues to stretch and spasm around the cock that's hammering in and out of it, the matriarch's subordinate delights in repeatedly spraying the perfume bottle's contents directly into your face. With each inhalation, you find yourself getting angrier and angrier, while at the same time coming to think of [harpyDominant.name], [harpyDominantCompanion.name], and all of the other harpies as your superiors.
		</p>
		<p>
			Several bottles of perfume, and multiple sexual partners later, and [harpyDominantCompanion.name] finally releases you from the stocks. Although you want to slap her and scream obscenities directly in her face, you don't dare to displease a harpy who's of a higher social standing than you are. Looking to one side, you see your matriarch, [harpyDominant.name], looking at you with an expression of arrogant amusement on her face. Snapping her fingers, she points to the floor and commands, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Kneel down before me, bitch, and tell me who's your matriarch.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having had her fun, [harpyDominant.name] kicks [harpyDominantVictim.name] away from her, before looking at you and commanding, [harpyDominant.speech(Get off her, bitch! Your work is done!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Sliding your cock out of [harpyDominantVictim.namePos] quivering pussy, you decide that the only option for you right now is to play the obedient pet, and so dutifully kneel down and await further orders. You don't have to wait long for your next command, as the matriarch snaps her fingers and exclaims, [harpyDominant.speech(Lie on your back, bitch! [harpyDominantVictim.Name], if you can swallow five of her loads, then your punishment is over.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As you do as you're told and lie on your back, [harpyDominantVictim.name] frantically pounces on you, and within a moment, she's got your cock in her mouth. Doing her best to give you the best blowjob she can, [harpyDominantVictim.name] keeps you pinned to the floor and as you see [harpyDominantCompanion.name] approaching with a very familiar-looking bottle of perfume in her hands.
		</p>
		<p>
			[harpyDominant.speech(The mind-altering effects of this perfume can wear off after a while, but I've been reliably informed that prolonged exposure to it will make the changes permanent,)] [harpyDominant.name] sneers as she steps up beside [harpyDominantCompanion.name]. Giving her subordinate a nod, she commands, [harpyDominant.speech(Keep on spraying her until she sees herself as nothing more than another one of my bitches.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a cruel laugh, [harpyDominant.name] then struts off, leaving [harpyDominantCompanion.name] to carry out her orders. As [harpyDominantVictim.namePos] lips slide up and down around your cock, the matriarch's subordinate delights in repeatedly spraying the perfume bottle's contents directly into your face. With each inhalation, you find yourself getting angrier and angrier, while at the same time coming to think of [harpyDominant.name], [harpyDominantCompanion.name], and all of the other harpies as your superiors.
		</p>
		<p>
			Several bottles of perfume, and multiple orgasms later, and [harpyDominantVictim.name] is finally pulled off of you by [harpyDominantCompanion.name]. Although you want to slap her and scream obscenities directly in her face, you don't dare to displease a harpy who's of a higher social standing than you are. Looking to one side, you see your matriarch, [harpyDominant.name], looking at you with an expression of arrogant amusement on her face. Snapping her fingers, she points to the floor and commands, [harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Kneel down before me, bitch, and tell me who's your matriarch.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
    <htmlContent tag="BAD_END_FINAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Obediently kneeling down before her, you declare, [pc.speech(You're my matriarch, [harpyDominant.name]... I'll do whatever you command...)]
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		...
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasVagina())
		<p>
			Months later, [harpyDominantCompanion.name] is pinning you to the floor as she thrusts her cock in and out of your pussy. Well and truly established as a harpy at the bottom of the nest's female hierarchy, you're often used like this, and more often than not it's [harpyDominantCompanion.name] who's the one to be enjoying your cunt. Soon enough, she's letting out a series of desperate moans, and then a moment later you feel her hot cum filling your pussy.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				[harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Next time I'm using your ass, bitch!)]
			#ELSE
				[harpyDominantCompanion.speech(Next time I'm using your mouth, bitch!)]
			#ENDIF
			 the harpy sneers, before slapping you across the face and strutting off to another part of the nest.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you watch [harpyDominantCompanion.name] depart, you furiously summon a nearby male harpy to your side; she's one of a few who are actually beneath you in the flock's pecking order. Taking out your frustrations on her, you sadistically slap her ass before forcing her to clean your pussy, muttering under your breath that one day you'll be above [harpyDominantCompanion.name], and then she'll pay...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Months later, [harpyDominant.name] is once again using you to punish a disobedient harpy. Well and truly established as a harpy at the bottom of the nest's male hierarchy, you're exclusively used by [harpyDominant.name] to punish those who have displeased her, a job which you've grown to love.
		</p>
		<p>
			You mount the disobedient harpy and pin her to the floor, before roughly forcing your cock into her wet pussy and energetically pounding her cunt. Soon enough, you're finishing inside of her, and after giving her ass a rough slap, you're recalled to your matriarch's side, ready to do it all again to the next harpy unfortunate enough to displease [harpyDominant.name]...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		...
	</p>
	<p><i>
		With your mind having been permanently changed by being subjected to such a huge quantity of transformative perfume, you never once think of trying to escape from [harpyDominant.namePos] nest. Even if you did somehow become aware of what had happened, you're far too angry to listen to reason, and can't see yourself as anything more than one of [harpyDominant.namePos] bitches...
	</i></p>
    ]]>
    </htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
