<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- HELENAS_NEST_EXTERIOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Making your way down one of the the many walkways that criss-cross Dominion's rooftops, you find yourself approaching an exceptionally large Harpy Nest. Spanning several buildings, and with an elaborate system of multi-level platforms built on top of each one, you instantly recognise this as a nest of particular importance.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isDayTime())
			The platforms are covered in countless groups of harpies; lounging around and talking amongst one another, their lazy behaviour is in stark contrast to those flying around in the skies above. Looking up, you see a multitude of colours dashing through the sky as yet more of this nest's residents swoop and dart around in the
			#IF(game.isMorning())
				 morning's cool air
			#ELSE
				 afternoon's warm air
			#ENDIF
			, their energetic dives and spiralling loops threatening to make your head spin if you try to watch them for too long.
		#ELSE
			The platforms are covered in countless groups of harpies; illuminated under soft white lights, you see them lounging around and talking amongst one another, their lazy behaviour in stark contrast to those flying around in the skies above. Looking up, you see a multitude of colours dashing through the sky as yet more of this nest's residents swoop and dart around in the cool night air; their feathers lit up by the arcane-powered lights that are covering this nest.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking back down, you notice that there are little signs dotted around the edges of the platform. Walking up to the nearest one, you read the following words, written in flowing, ornate script;
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
	<i>
		<b>~[helena.name]'s Paradise~</b>
		<br/>Visitors must be accompanied at all times.
		#IF(pc.isQuestProgressGreaterThan(QUEST_LINE_MAIN, QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA))
			<br/>Until further notice, [helena.name] is <b>not receiving any visitors</b>.
		#ELSE
			<br/>Meeting with [helena.name] by appointment only.
		#ENDIF
	</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getQuest(QUEST_LINE_MAIN)==QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA)
			Stepping back, you wonder if you should call over one of the nearby harpies. After all, you do have business with [helena.name], and you're sure that she'd want to hear about Scarlett as soon as possible...
		#ELSE
			Stepping back, you decide against calling over one of the nearby harpies.
			#IF(pc.isQuestFailed(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_HELENA))
				 After all, Helena is so furious with you that she'd never agree to meeting with you...
			#ELSEIF(pc.isQuestProgressGreaterThan(QUEST_LINE_MAIN, QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA))
				 After all, she's not even here at the moment.
			#ELSE
				 After all, you don't have any business with her.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(game.getNonCompanionCharactersPresent().contains(scarlett))
		<p>
			Over in a nearby corner of the nest, you see the familiar figure of Scarlett sitting next to a couple of brightly-coloured harpies.
			#IF(pc.getQuest(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_HELENA) == QUEST_ROMANCE_HELENA_4_SCARLETTS_RETURN)
				 Although you doubt that you'll get an amicable response from her, you need to go over to Scarlett and tell her that Helena wants to see her...
			#ELSE
				 You could always head over and say hello, but you doubt that you'll get an amicable response from her...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_EXTERIOR_STORM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Making your way down one of the the many walkways that criss-cross Dominion's rooftops, you find yourself approaching an exceptionally large Harpy Nest. Spanning several buildings, and with an elaborate system of multi-level platforms built on top of each one, you instantly recognise this as a nest of particular importance.
	</p>
	<p>
		Due to the ongoing arcane storm, the nest is completed deserted; its residents having retreated down into the safety of the buildings below. As yet another flash of arcane lightning illuminates the platforms before you, you notice that there are little signs dotted around the edges of the nest. Walking up to the nearest one, you read, in flowing, ornate script, the following words;
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
	<i>
		<b>~[helena.name]'s Paradise~</b>
		<br/>Visitors must be accompanied at all times.
		#IF(pc.isQuestProgressGreaterThan(QUEST_LINE_MAIN, QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA))
			<br/>Until further notice, [helena.name] is <b>not receiving any visitors</b>.
		#ELSE
			<br/>Meeting with [helena.name] by appointment only.
		#ENDIF
	</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getQuest(QUEST_LINE_MAIN) == QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA)
			You do have business with [helena.name], and you're sure that she'd want to hear about Scarlett as soon as possible, but you'll have to come back after the ongoing storm has passed...
		#ELSEIF(pc.isQuestFailed(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_HELENA))
			There's not much point in waiting around for the storm to pass, as Helena is so furious with you that she'd never agree to meeting with you...
		#ELSEIF(pc.isQuestProgressGreaterThan(QUEST_LINE_MAIN, QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA))
			There's not much point in waiting around for the storm to pass, as [helena.name]'s not even here at the moment...
		#ELSE
			There's not much point in waiting around for the storm to pass, as you don't have any business with [helena.name]...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_EXTERIOR_SLEEPING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Making your way down one of the the many walkways that criss-cross Dominion's rooftops, you find yourself approaching an exceptionally large Harpy Nest. Spanning several buildings, and with an elaborate system of multi-level platforms built on top of each one, you instantly recognise this as a nest of particular importance.
	</p>
	<p>
		Due to the current hour, the nest is completed deserted; its residents having retired to the comfort of the buildings below in order to get a good night's sleep. Taking a look around the deserted platform, you notice that there are little signs dotted around the edges of the nest. Walking up to the nearest one, you read, in flowing, ornate script, the following words;
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
	<i>
		<b>~[helena.name]'s Paradise~</b>
		<br/>Visitors must be accompanied at all times.
		#IF(pc.isQuestProgressGreaterThan(QUEST_LINE_MAIN, QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA))
			<br/>Until further notice, [helena.name] is <b>not receiving any visitors</b>.
		#ELSE
			<br/>Meeting with [helena.name] by appointment only.
		#ENDIF
	</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getQuest(QUEST_LINE_MAIN) == QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA)
			You do have business with [helena.name], and you're sure that she'd want to hear about Scarlett as soon as possible, but you'll have to come back once she's awake, [style.colourMinorBad(between [units.time(6)] and [units.time(22)])]...
		#ELSEIF(pc.isQuestFailed(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_HELENA))
			There's not much point in waiting around for the nests' residents to wake up, as Helena is so furious with you that she'd never agree to meeting with you...
		#ELSEIF(pc.isQuestProgressGreaterThan(QUEST_LINE_MAIN, QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA))
			There's not much point in waiting around for the nests' residents to wake up, as [helena.name]'s not even here at the moment...
		#ELSE
			There's not much point in waiting around for the nests' residents to wake up, as you don't have any business with [helena.name]...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_NEST -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Moving forwards into the nest, you look around for a harpy who can take you to [helena.name]. You don't need to search for long, however, as the moment you pass the sign next to the entrance, a flustered-looking harpy swoops down to land right in front of you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminine(Stop! Wait! Who are you?! You can't come in here!)] she shouts, frantically waving her pink-feathered wings in front of your face. [style.speechFeminine(You need an appointment if you want to see [helena.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(My name's [pc.name], and I really need to talk to [helena.name],)] you reply, standing your ground. [pc.speech(I've got a message for her from Scarlett.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		A few of the surrounding harpies, obviously listening in to your conversation, suddenly start whispering to one another. Caught off-guard at the mention of Scarlett's name, the harpy that you're dealing with trips over her words as she hurries to respond, [style.speechFeminine(S-Scarlett?! What- I mean, who- Wait, no, she's meant to be working down in Slaver Alley! You don't mean <i>that</i> Scarlett, do you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, I mean that Scarlett,)] you reply, [pc.speech(As I said, I need to deliver a message from her to [helena.name].)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminine(Well, I'm not supposed to let people in without an appointment,)] the harpy says, nervously flapping her wings as she struggles to decide what to do, [style.speechFeminine(Helena <i>is</i> in a good mood today, and I'm sure she'd want to know if Scarlett's causing more trouble... Come on then! Follow me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With you hot on her heels, your guide hurries off into the nest, leading you though crowds of inquisitive harpies, over rickety rope bridges, and, finally, up several flights of wooden stairs. After a couple of minutes spent following the pink-feathered harpy in this manner, you eventually arrive at the tallest platform in the nest. Over on the far side, surrounded by a dozen or so other harpies, you see the white-feathered form of Helena sitting on a delicate wooden throne.
	</p>
	<p>
		As your guide bows down to her superiors and starts to explain that you're here to deliver news of Scarlett, you take a good look at these harpies who comprise Helena's inner-circle. Each one of them has a unique colour to their feathers, and they are without exception nothing less than stunningly beautiful. Their flawless features and perfectly-postured bodies leave you with no doubt that they'd each be capable of becoming a matriarch of their own flock, if they so desired. Despite their alluring beauty, your vision doesn't linger on these harpies for too long, as your gaze is irresistibly drawn to the figure of Helena.
	</p>
	<p>
		Sitting upon a white wooden throne, which has been elegantly carved to depict flowing branches and leaves and then inlaid with pure gold, the matriarch of this harpy flock must surely be one of the most beautiful creatures to have ever existed. Your eyes are first drawn to the immaculate feathers which cover [helena.namePos] wings, head, and tail; their pure white brilliance seems almost to radiate a heavenly glow, and there's not a single one on her entire body which isn't perfectly preened and spotlessly clean. Her pale skin, much like her feathers, is absolutely flawless, and there isn't even the slightest hint of a blemish anywhere on her perfect, hourglass-shaped body. The white plunge-dress which she's wearing reveals a large portion of her D-cup cleavage, and you can't help but marvel at not only how perfectly-formed her breasts are, but also how they're significantly larger than those of most harpies. The sharp talons on the end of her bird-like feet are perfectly manicured, and you see them flexing a little as she dismisses your guide with a brief swish of one of her wings. As the matriarch's [helena.eyeColour] eyes lock on to yours, you find yourself gazing upon the inconceivably-beautiful face of Aphrodite reborn, which turns up into a heart-melting smile as she beckons you forwards with one of her feathered fingers.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Welcome to my nest, [pc.name],)] Helena says in a soft, melodic voice which perfectly fits her beautiful appearance, [helena.speech(If I were not so pressed with prior engagements, I would insist upon giving you my full hospitality, but alas, my time is regrettably in very short supply. If you are here to deliver news of my dear Scarlett, then pray do tell without delay.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she retains her regal posture and calm tone of voice, you notice another slight flex of Helena's talons as she mentions the name 'Scarlett', revealing the fact that she's impatient to find out what news you have of her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_NEST_SCARLETT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_SCARLETT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Agreeing with Helena that it would be best not to delay, you set about telling her of Scarlett's failed business, and how she's run out of both money and slaves. As you reveal this information, you see the matriarch's talons digging down into the wooden platform in front of her throne, and before you can get to the part about Scarlett's request that you take her punishment for her, Helena holds up her wing to silence you. With her head-feathers bristling up in a clear display of anger, the beautiful matriarch somehow manages to keep her voice soft and calm as she turns towards one of the nearby harpies and asks, [helena.speech(Is what [pc.name] is saying true, Aello? I do recall giving you the responsibility of watching over Scarlett, and it seems rather perplexing to me that you'd neglect to report a failure of this magnitude.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminineStrong(My queen, please, I thought Scarlett would still have time to fix her mistake. I didn't want to bother you with-)] the harpy tries to explain, but she's cut off mid-sentence as Helena rises up from her throne and sharply sweeps her wings down to either side of her.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Why must I be burdened with such incompetent followers?)] the matriarch asks, starting to losing her noble composure as her voice takes on a distinctly icy tone, [helena.speech(I specifically told you to report any significant news of Scarlett to me at once. Obviously that was too much for your simple little bird-brain to comprehend.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminineStrong(Please, I'm sorry, I'll go and tell Scarlett-)] the harpy starts, but is again quickly silenced, this time by the loud scratching noise of Helena's sharp talons ripping up the floor beneath her.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Oh, that won't be necessary. I'm going to go and personally deal with Scarlett right now. Don't expect me to return any time soon; I need to take a long break away from the ceaseless ineptitude I'm expected to deal with on a daily basis,)] [helena.name] announces in a tone that's by now distinctly hostile. Turning towards the cobalt-blue-feathered harpy sitting closest to her throne, she commands, [helena.speech(Electra, you'll be in charge of the nest until I decide to return. Please do try not to let it turn to ruin in my absence.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		In her current state of anger, it seems as though [helena.name] has completely forgotten about your existence. Ignoring her followers' pleas to stay, she steps over to the edge of the platform and spreads her wings. You only have a moment in which to try and stop her from flying off, and you wonder if you should use this opportunity to offer to take Scarlett's punishment on her behalf...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_NEST_NO_PUNISHMENT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_NO_PUNISHMENT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it would be best to avoid [helena.namePos] wrath, you say nothing as she leaps off the edge of the platform, and simply watch as she wheels around in mid-air and flies off in the direction of Slaver Alley. You're confident that you did the right thing; after all, who knows what horrific punishment [helena.name] would have given you had you said something to stop her.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.NamePos] inner-circle of harpies pay you no heed as their matriarch soars off into the #IF(game.isDayTime())sky#ELSEnight#ENDIF. They're far too concerned with speculating as to what [helena.name] is going to do to Scarlett, and as you overhear some of their more frightful ideas, you suddenly remember that you still need the rude raven-harpy to tell you what happened to Arthur.
	</p>
	<p>
		It doesn't look like anyone's going to prevent you from leaving, so you quickly move to make your exit. You should probably hurry back to Scarlett's shop and find out what [helena.name] had in store for her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_LEAVING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Heading back down the staircase to the nest's main platform, you leave your guide to hurry after you, fretting and flapping her wings as she pleads with you to try and calm [helena.name] down. Going back the same way that you came, it only takes a few moments before you're exiting [helena.name]'s nest, and after telling your worrisome harpy guide that you'll do your best, you leave her behind and head back out into the Harpy Nests once more...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_PUNISHMENT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_PUNISHMENT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Wait!)] you cry out, [pc.speech(There's something else!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.Name] lowers her wings and turns towards you, before asking in an icy tone, [helena.speech(And what, exactly, is so important to tell me that you thought it wise to shout?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Well, Scarlett also asked me to tell you that I should take her punishment for her...)] you explain, your voice trailing off as [helena.name] strides towards you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(There's absolutely no way that Scarlett is going to avoid the punishment which I have planned for her, but seeing as you're so <i>desperate</i> for attention, it's only fair that I give you what you want,)] Helena says, before a deep red glow suddenly starts to pulsate around her wings. Before you get the chance to react to her unexpected ability to harness the arcane, she sweeps her wings down in a sharp, cutting motion. Caught off-guard, the powerful wave of arcane force summoned by this matriarch slams you to the ground. As you then try to stand back up, Helena slams a second wave of force down on top of you, pinning you to the floor as she calls out, [helena.speech(Aello! You have an opportunity to earn some of my forgiveness! Help me to show this insolent [pc.race] how we administer punishments in my nest!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The sound of mocking laughter echoes all around you as you suddenly feel a third wave of force pushing you over right into Aello's welcoming wings.
		#IF(pc.isBipedal())
			 As you're completely thrown off balance, the harpy has no problem at all in bending you down over her knee, and you can't help but let out a surprised gasp as you realise that your exposed ass is pointing up into the air.
		#ELSE
			 As you're completely thrown off balance, the harpy has no problem at all in manipulating your body such that your exposed ass is pointing up into the air.
		#ENDIF
		 Helena continues to demonstrate her arcane mastery, and you feel your [pc.arms] and [pc.legs] bound by an ethereal force as [helena.she] steps forwards and prepares to personally administer your punishment.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Is this the sort of attention you were looking for, [pc.name]?)] the matriarch rhetorically asks, [helena.speech(I think twenty strikes will do nicely for you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [helena.name] raises her right wing high in the air, and with a swift downwards motion, she delivers the first slap down onto your raised ass. Normally, a harpy's touch would be quite weak; their delicate wings are more suited for swift, mid-flight movements rather than for administering forceful blows, but [helena.name]'s strike is anything but light.
		#IF(pc.hasFetish(FETISH_MASOCHIST))
			 A crackle of arcane force accompanies her blow, and you can't help but let out a horny [pc.moan] as an intense, stinging pain shoot into your buttocks. Your masochistic cry
		#ELSE
			 A crackle of arcane force accompanies her blow, and you let out an involuntary cry as you feel a stinging pain shoot into your buttocks. Your exclamation
		#ENDIF
		 is met by a chorus of mocking laughter from [helena.namePos] inner-circle of harpies, and you hear them encouraging their matriarch to show you no mercy as she raises her wing to strike again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_PUNISHMENT_ENDURE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_PUNISHMENT_ENDURE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You scrunch your [pc.eyes] shut and do your best to endure your punishment without complaint. Despite your best efforts to stay quiet, however, [helena.namePos] sharp blows occasionally force a little whimper out from between your [pc.lips], much to the amusement of the harpy onlookers.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although Helena had announced that you'd be receiving only twenty strikes, your public spanking seems to continue on forever. Time and again, the matriarch's wing-like hand relentlessly strikes down at your exposed cheeks, but just as you feel as though you can't possibly stand any more, she decides that you've had enough. Stepping back, she releases the arcane bonds which were restraining your [pc.arms] and [pc.legs], and as you reach back to rub at your tender [pc.ass], Aello pushes you away from her and teases, [style.speechFeminineStrong(That'll teach you to annoy our matriarch!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With her voice once again taking on a softer tone, Helena looks down at you and says, [helena.speech(I must commend you on your resolve. Those who I punish in this fashion often have a tendency to cause quite the scene.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_PUNISHMENT_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With that being said, the matriarch once again walks over to the edge of the platform. Spreading her white-feathered wings, she launches herself into the air, before wheeling around and flying off in the direction of Slaver Alley.
	</p>
	<p>
		With your public humiliation now at an end, [helena.namePos] inner-circle of harpies instantly lose interest in you. Gossiping amongst themselves, they start speculating as to what [helena.name] is going to do to Scarlett, and as you overhear some of their more frightful ideas, you suddenly remember that you still need the rude raven-harpy to tell you what happened to Arthur.
	</p>
	<p>
		It doesn't look like anyone's going to prevent you from leaving, so you quickly move to make your exit. You should probably hurry back to Scarlett's shop and find out what [helena.name] had in store for her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_PUNISHMENT_STRUGGLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_PUNISHMENT_STRUGGLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not at all happy with what Helena's punishment turned out to be, you let out a loud cry as her wing smacks down yet again on your exposed ass. Not giving you a moment's respite, she lifts her wing and delivers a third stinging blow to your [pc.ass+], causing you to squeal once more in pain. Each of her blows draws out a desperate wail from between your [pc.lips], and much to the amusement of the harpy onlookers, you fruitlessly kick and struggle about as Aello firmly holds you in position.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although Helena had announced that you'd be receiving only twenty strikes, your public spanking seems to continue on forever. Time and again, the matriarch's wing-like hand relentlessly strikes down at your exposed cheeks, and although you continue to struggle and shout throughout your whole ordeal, the matriarch only stops once she's decided that you've had enough. Stepping back, she releases the arcane bonds which were restraining your [pc.arms] and [pc.legs], and as you reach back to rub at your tender [pc.ass], Aello pushes you away from her and teases, [style.speechFeminineStrong(That'll teach you to annoy our matriarch!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With her voice once again taking on a softer tone, Helena looks down at you and says, [helena.speech(What a dreadful racket you made... I cannot recall anyone else ever kicking up as much of a fuss as you just did.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_PUNISHMENT_ENJOY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_PUNISHMENT_ENJOY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		More than happy with what Helena's punishment turned out to be, you let out a lewd cry as [helena.namePos] wing smacks down yet again on your exposed ass. Not giving you a moment's respite, she lifts her wing and delivers a third stinging blow to your [pc.ass+], causing you to [pc.moan] in a delightful mixture of pleasure and pain, [pc.speech(Yes! Punish me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking across to one of her followers in confusion, Helana asks, [helena.speech(Is [pc.she]... <i>enjoying</i> this?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminineStrong(I believe so,)] the harpy replies, [style.speechFeminineStrong(perhaps if you were to hit [pc.herHim] harder, [npc.she]'d understand that this is a punishment.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Helena clearly approves of her follower's suggestion, as the next blow that lands on your ass is far more powerful than the ones before, and despite your burning arousal, you can't help but let out a whimpering scream. Encouraged by your painful cry, and seemingly oblivious to the fact that you're still enjoying it, each of [helena.name]'s smacks grow harder and harder, drawing out desperate wails and pleasurable moans from between your [pc.lips].
	</p>
	<p>
		Although Helena had announced that you'd be receiving only twenty strikes, your public spanking seems to be over in a flash. Stepping back, she releases the arcane bonds which were restraining your [pc.arms] and [pc.legs], and as you reach back to rub at your tender [pc.ass], Aello pushes you away from her and teases, [style.speechFeminineStrong(That'll teach you to annoy our matriarch!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_FLIGHT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_TAKE_FLIGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following in [helena.name]'s footsteps, you hurry to edge of the platform. With a flap of your wings, you leap off and take flight, following the speck of white in the distance as [helena.name] leads you back to Scarlett's shop.
	</p>
	<p>
		Somewhere along the way, you lose sight of the harpy matriarch, and it takes you a little while to get your bearings again. Soon enough, however, you spot the familiar pattern of Slaver Alley's passages beneath you, and swoop down to land in front of Scarlett's shop.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_NEST_MEETING_SCARLETT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_MEETING_SCARLETT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to talk to Scarlett, you move forwards onto the nest's wooden platform, before starting to make your way over to where the raven-harpy is sitting. Before you've managed to cover even a quarter of the distance, however, a flustered-looking harpy suddenly dashes forwards and blocks your way. With a stern look on her face, she shouts,
		#IF(game.getNonCompanionCharactersPresent().contains(helena))
			 [style.speechFeminineStrong(Hey! Stop! Nobody's allowed to see Helena without an appointment!)]
		#ELSE
			 [style.speechFeminineStrong(Hey! Stop! Helena's not even here at the moment, so there's no point in trying to get an appointment to see her!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've informed this overzealous harpy that you're actually here to talk to Scarlett, she hesitantly steps to one side, before warning, [style.speechFeminineStrong(You'd better not just be saying this to try and sneak past me! I've got my eye on you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Assuring the harpy that you have no intention of 'sneaking past her', you continue on your way towards Scarlett. As you approach, you can't help but overhear one of the two brightly-coloured harpies sitting next to her loudly suggesting, [style.speechFeminine(You should come too, Scarlett! I'm telling you, she said that if we act as her servants for the day, she'll let us fuck her!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a scowl, Scarlett replies, [scarlett.speech(That bitch isn't worth it; she's a lousy fuck and doesn't even let you use her ass. I'd much rather- Hey! What the fuck are you doing here?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having caught sight of you, Scarlett jumps to her feet and shoots you an angry glare, before continuing,
		#IF(scarlett.isAttractedTo(pc) && game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 [scarlett.speech(Just because you set me free, doesn't mean I owe you anything! Unless you're here to let me fuck your cute ass, then I'm not interested in whatever you're offering!)]
		#ELSE
			 [scarlett.speech(Just because you set me free, doesn't mean I owe you anything! I'm not interested in whatever you're offering, so fuck off already!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_MEETING_SCARLETT_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(scarlett.isAttractedTo(pc) && game.isAnalContentEnabled() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_ANUS, true))
			As it's obvious that Scarlett isn't willing to engage with you in conversation, and not wanting to take her up on her offer of 'fucking your cute ass', you turn around and quickly leave via the same way you arrived...
		#ELSE
			As it's obvious that Scarlett isn't willing to engage with you in conversation, you turn around and quickly leave via the same way you arrived...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="START_SCARLETT_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So, what happens if I <i>am</i> here to let you 'fuck my cute little ass'?)] you tease, stepping up to Scarlett and playfully running your [pc.fingers] down the length of one of her black-feathered wings.
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly not expecting you to actually agree to her suggestion, Scarlett is momentarily thrown off-guard, and blankly stares at you for a couple of seconds before recovering and sneering, [scarlett.speech(Then I'll give you want you want, you dirty little buttslut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling her two friends that she'll catch up with them later, Scarlett roughly grabs you by the [pc.hand], before impatiently leading you over to a nearby downwards staircase. Continuing to pull you along after her, she quickly descends this flight of stairs, which turns out to lead to a small, shaded sub-platform. Now that the two of you are concealed from the prying eyes of the rest of the nest's inhabitants, Scarlett quickly strips naked, presenting you with her tiny boobs and small, pale-skinned cock. Seeing what it is you're looking at, the harpy scowls, [scarlett.speech(You'll be getting a feel of it soon enough! Now get down on all fours and show me your ass, slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you expose your ass and drop down onto all fours, presenting your naked asshole to Scarlett. Dropping down behind you, the impatient harpy instantly thrusts forwards, sinking her hard cock into your rear entrance and moaning, [scarlett.speechNoEffect(~Mmm!~ That's right, slut! Your ass is mine now!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_SCARLETT_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SCARLETT_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had her fun, Scarlett takes a step back, looking down at your ass and sneering, [scarlett.speech(You were a good fuck, you dirty little buttslut! Come back and see me again if you get hungry for my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Quickly getting dressed again, Scarlett waits until you're ready to go, before leading you back up the stairs and pointing to the nest's exit. [scarlett.speech(Go on, get out of here! I've got more stuff to do today than fucking some slut's ass.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With little else to do in Helena's nest, you do as Scarlett orders and quickly take your leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_NEST_MEETING_SCARLETT_TO_SHOP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_MEETING_SCARLETT_TO_SHOP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ignoring Scarlett's rude comments, you tell her that Helena has asked for Scarlett's presence back down at her shop in Slaver Alley. As she hears you say this, the raven-harpy's head and tail feathers droop down, and after letting out an anguished groan, she turns to her two friends and says a half-hearted goodbye. Looking back at you, she asks, [scarlett.speech(She's not planning one nsalving me again, is she?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've reassured her that there's no chance of that, Scarlett steps past you, before running up to the edge of the nest's platform and launching herself into the air. With a flap of her arm-wings, she wheels around and swoops off in the direction of Slave Alley.
		#IF(pc.isPartyAbleToFly())
			 If you wanted to, you could always fly after her and arrive back at Helena's shop moments after she does...
		#ELSE
			 With little else to do up here in the nest, you turn around and quickly leave via the same way you arrived...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_NEST_MEETING_SCARLETT_TO_SHOP_FLY_AFTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it would be a good idea to return to Helena's shop as quickly as possible, you follow Scarlett's lead and launch yourself into the air, before flying after the raven-harpy in the direction of Slaver Alley. After a short while you arrive at your destination, and after swooping down and landing in front of Helena's shop, you see through the window that Scarlett has managed to arrive before you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
