<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="STAIRS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The wide, red-carpeted staircase behind you leads down to the ground floor of Zaranix's house.
		 To either side of you, a corridor leads off into other parts of the building, and you wonder which way you should go...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Much like those found on the ground floor, these corridors are home to numerous fine paintings, cushioned chairs, and well-crafted cabinets.
		 Where once you might have been deeply impressed by the extravagant luxury of this incubus's mansion, you now find yourself thinking that it's not quite as grand as Lilaya's.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="KELLY_PRESENT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you walk down the corridor, an ivory-skinned succubus, wearing a light pink maid's uniform, suddenly stands up from behind a cabinet.
		 She doesn't notice you at first, and continues to swipe her little feather-duster over the top of the wooden furniture, happily humming away as she works.
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you have a chance to say anything, she looks up and catches sight of you.
		 Letting out a little cry, she curtsies as she greets you,
		 [kelly.speech(Ah! [pc.Miss] [pc.name]! Mistress Amber informed me of your visit. I'm Kelly, at your service!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the maid stands up, you see her lustful gaze roaming up and down your body.
		 Biting her lip, she steps towards you, and with more than a little lust in her voice, she moans,
		 [kelly.speech(If there's <i>anything</i> I can do for you, just let me know.
		 Master Zaranix only has time for Amber these days... N-Not that I'm complaining, but... Well... My sister and I get lonely, you understand...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Kelly giggles, and, as she bats her eyelids at you, drops the little feather duster that she's holding.
		 [kelly.speech(Oops!)]
		 she cries, pretending that it was by accident.
		 Bending over right in front of you, she makes a show of flashing her crotchless pink thong in your direction, granting you an unobstructed view of her [kelly.pussy+].
		 Obviously desperate for you to fuck her, you wonder if you should make a move on this horny maid...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KELLY_PRESENT_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Up ahead, you see the ivory-skinned maid, Kelly, busily dusting one of the corridor's picture frames.
		 As you approach, you see that the maid glances at you out of the corner of her eye.
		 Instead of turning and acknowledging your presence, however, Kelly pretends not to have seen you, and suddenly bends over to dust the skirting board.
		 The horny maid makes a show of flashing her crotchless pink thong in your direction, granting you an unobstructed view of her [kelly.pussy+].
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning her head to look back at you, Kelly lets out a little cry as she rather-unconvincingly pretends to have only just noticed you.
		 Standing up to face you, she curtsies and bites her lip to suppress a needy moan.
		 [kelly.speech([pc.Miss] [pc.name]! How pleasant to see you again! If there's <i>anything</i> I can help you with, just let me know!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		 Obviously desperate for you to fuck her, you wonder if you should make a move on this horny maid...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KELLY_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to take up Kelly's transparent offer of sex, you step forwards, grinning as you let your gaze wander up and down over the maid's perfect body.
		 [pc.speech(Well, there is one thing that a horny little succubus like you could do for me.)]
		 
	</p>
	<p>
		Kelly lets out an excited squeal as she gazes into your eyes, and you see them filled with a desperate, burning lust.
		 Bounding forwards, she suddenly wraps her arms around your back, and with a desperate moan, presses her [kelly.lips+] against yours.
		 You reciprocate the gesture, and after spending a few moments sliding your tongues into one another's mouths, you pull back, grinning...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KELLY_SEX_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not willing to take the dominant role, but with a deep desire to have sex with this horny succubus, you smile coyly at her.
		 [pc.speech(Kelly... Erm... If you're feeling a little horny, perhaps you could use me? I mean, I-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Kelly lets out an excited squeal, interrupting your sentence as she bounds forwards and wraps her arms around your back.
		 With a desperate moan, she quickly presses her [kelly.lips+] against yours.
		 You reciprocate the gesture, but only spend a few moments sliding your tongues into one another's mouths before Kelly pulls back, moaning,
		 [kelly.speech(Oh yes! Fuck... I'm so fucking horny! I <i>need</i> you!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KELLY_SEX_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You're not really interested in Kelly's transparent offer of sex right now.
		 [pc.speech(Thank you, Kelly, but there's nothing I need from you at the moment.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[kelly.speech(Aww! Well, if you change your mind, you know where to find me!)]
		 Kelly smiles, before turning away and continuing with her work.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_KELLY_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Kelly lets out a deeply satisfied sigh as you pull away from her,
		 [kelly.speech(~Aaah!~ Fuck... That was great!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you gather your things and prepare to move on, Kelly slumps back against the nearest wall, her hand slipping down between her legs as she slowly strokes herself.
		 [kelly.speech(~Mmm!~ That was so good...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding to leave Kelly to bask in her post-sex afterglow, you turn around and continue down the corridor.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_KELLY_SEX_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Kelly lets out a disappointed whine as you pull away from her,
		 [kelly.speech(Aww! I didn't even get to cum!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you gather your things and prepare to move on, Kelly slumps back against the nearest wall, her hand slipping down between her legs as she seeks to finish herself off.
		 [kelly.speech(Y-You carry on... ~Mmm!~ This won't take me long... ~Aaah!~)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as the unsatisfied maid suggests, you turn around and continue down the corridor.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The door to this room is locked, and there's no sound of anyone within.
		 Knowing that it's sure to just be a dull and uninteresting dead-end, you decide against trying to force the door open, and turn around to continue on your way through Zaranix's home.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_OUTSIDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The door to Zaranix's room is slightly ajar, and from within, you can hear the bubbling of potions and clink of glass vials as the master of the house carries out his experiments.
		 There's nothing stopping you from knocking on the door and stepping inside, but, if you didn't want to speak to Zaranix right now, you could always step back and return another time.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You decide to take your leave, and, smiling at Zaranix, you step back.
		 [pc.speech(I'd better get going now. It was good talking to you again, Zaranix.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(Likewise,)]
		 the imposing incubus states, grinning back at you.
		 [zaranix.speech(Do please visit again! Oh, and if you could, put in a good word with Lilaya about me, hmm?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I will,)]
		 you say, heading towards the door.
		 [pc.speech(Bye!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(Goodbye! Oh, and don't let Amber be too harsh on you, ok?)]
		 Zaranix waves, before turning his back on you and returning to his experiments.
	</p>
	<p>
		Pushing open the bedroom door, you step back outside into the corridor, wondering where to go next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_ENTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to pay Zaranix another visit, you raise your hand and deliver a short rap on the bedroom door.
		 [zaranix.speech(Enter,)]
		 the incubus calls out from within his room, and, following his command, you push open the door and step forwards. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Well-lit by several ceiling-mounted, arcane-powered lights, and with a series of large windows set into the opposite wall, the spacious room that you find yourself stepping into is particularly well-illuminated.
		 Numerous bookcases and shelves line the walls to either side of you, and within the main body of the room itself, a number of long tables are being used to hold piles of books, racks of glass bottles, and boxes full of all sorts of raw alchemical ingredients.
		 As you enter, you find yourself thinking that this room looks very much like a small-scale version of Lilaya's laboratory.
	</p>
	<p>
		There, in the middle of the room, holding a beaker filled with a strange, bubbling green liquid, is the purple-skinned figure of the incubus Zaranix.
		 As he sees that it's you, he places the beaker down on the table beside him and grins.
		 [zaranix.speech(Well, well, well! Look who it is!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Hello again, Zaranix. Amber told me that you'd instructed her to let me in. There's no hard feelings between us then?)]
		 you ask, looking around for any sign of a trap.
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(Not at all!)] Zaranix booms, before stepping forwards, grabbing your [pc.hand], and giving it a firm shake. [zaranix.speech(I couldn't harbour any ill will towards one of Lilaya's relatives! You'll put in a good word of me with her, won't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Making a non-committal response, you smile at the friendly incubus as he finally releases your [pc.hand] and asks, [zaranix.speech(So, what can I do for you this time, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_ENTER_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to pay Zaranix another visit, you raise your hand and deliver a short rap on the bedroom door.
		 [zaranix.speech(Enter,)]
		 the incubus calls out from within his room, and, following his command, you push open the door and step forwards. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Well-lit by several ceiling-mounted, arcane-powered lights, and with a series of large windows set into the opposite wall, the spacious room that you find yourself stepping into is particularly well-illuminated.
		 Numerous bookcases and shelves line the walls to either side of you, and within the main body of the room itself, a number of long tables are being used to hold piles of books, racks of glass bottles, and boxes full of all sorts of raw alchemical ingredients.
		 As you enter, you find yourself thinking that this room looks very much like a small-scale version of Lilaya's laboratory.
	</p>
	<p>
		There, in the middle of the room, holding a beaker filled with a strange, bubbling green liquid, is the purple-skinned figure of the incubus Zaranix.
		 As he sees that it's you, he places the beaker down on the table beside him and grins.
		 [zaranix.speech(Ah! [pc.Name]! Hello again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Hello, Zaranix. How are you?)]
		 you ask, smiling at the friendly incubus as he strides towards you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(I'm very well thank you! Well, apart from my experiments not working... Again! Hah!)]
		 Zaranix booms, grabbing your [pc.hand] and giving it a firm shake.
		 [zaranix.speech(So how's Lilaya's [pc.niece] these days?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'm fine, thank you,)]
		 you say, smiling at the friendly incubus as he finally releases your [pc.hand].
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(So, what can I do for you this time, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_MAIDS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I was wondering how you came by these maids of yours. Kelly and Katherine are sisters, right? And I'm surprised that someone as... dominant... as Amber chooses to work as a maid. What's her story?)]
		 you ask, curious about Zaranix's household.
	</p>
	<p>
		Collapsing down onto a nearby chair, Zaranix grins as he starts to tell you the story,
		 [zaranix.speech(Well, as you know, I haven't been recognised by my Lilin mother, so, unable to rely on her support, I decided early on in my life to focus on making and selling transformative potions.
		 It didn't take me long to find success. After all, it's only us demons who are really able to harness the arcane well enough to make such potions.)]
		 Zaranix smiles as he remembers the events in his past.
		 [zaranix.speech(As demand for my potions increased, so too did the amount of time that I had to spend on making them.
		 The house that I was renting at that time soon fell in to an appalling state of affairs, and I realised that I was going to need to hire a maid.
		 Little did I know that I was going to end up with my little inferno!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You grin as you hear Zaranix's affectionate name for Amber.
		 [pc.speech(So you hired Amber before the sisters?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(That's right!)]
		 Zaranix booms.
		 [zaranix.speech(I went to a local agency, and, not really knowing what I was doing, I signed a contract to hire the first maid that they offered me.
		 Little did I know that I'd just been scammed!
		 I tell you, when I answered the door to Amber the next day, I was sure that there had been some sort of mistake!
		 The very instant that I met her, she started scolding me, insulting me, and forcing me to help her clean the house!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That sounds like her,)]
		 you say, smiling as you imagine that first day's interaction between Amber and Zaranix.
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(Yes, well, I put up with it for that first day, intent on firing her after she left.
		 You can imagine my surprise when Amber informed me, just after making me prepare her some dinner, that she wasn't going home, and that she now lived with me!
		 I immediately ran down to the agency, just in time to catch them before they closed for the evening.
		 That's when I found out that the contract I signed bound me to hire Amber for no less than five years!
		 Defeated, I went back home to suffer a severe scolding from my new maid...)]
		 A deep, booming laugh bursts out of Zaranix's mouth as he recollects his experience.
		 [zaranix.speech(After that, however, things started to get better.
		 Over the next few weeks and months, Amber's fiery temper started to cool, and she eventually began to act like a proper maid, even so far as to start calling me 'master'.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(And Kelly and Katherine?)]
		 you inquire.
		 [pc.speech(When did you hire them?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(Ah, that was after I moved into this house here.
		 Amber told me that this place was too large for her to keep clean alone, so I sent her to hire a couple more maids.
		 Kelly and Katherine were her choices, not mine,)]
		 Zaranix says, smiling.
		 [zaranix.speech(Apparently, they've only ever worked as a pair, and had caused quite a bit of trouble in their previous posts.
		 Thanks to that, they were considerably cheaper than similarly experienced maids, and their troublesome ways were soon dealt with by Amber. Hah!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Coming to the end of his long story, Zaranix stands up, before smiling at you in his friendly manner.
		 [zaranix.speech(So, is there anything else you'd like to talk about?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_EXPERIMENTS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(What are all these experiments that you're running?)]
		 you ask, curious about what the incubus is working on.
		 [pc.speech(You were trying to get Arthur to make a demonic transformative potion, weren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(That's right!)]
		 Zaranix booms, gesturing to the room around you with an open palm.
		 [zaranix.speech(This entire setup was created with that goal in mind.
		 It soon became apparent, however, that such a transformative is impossible to produce.
		 No, the only ways someone becomes a demon is through being born as one, or transformed into one by a Lilin's arcane power.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So what are you working on instead?)]
		 you ask, keen to hear the answer to your first question.
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(Nothing ground-breaking, honestly.)]
		 Zaranix sighs.
		 [zaranix.speech(I'm mainly trying to improve the efficiency of my alchemical processes.
		 I only sell my potions in bulk to suppliers around the city, and one of them, a particularly rough wolf-girl named Vicky, is always demanding more of me.
		 Honestly, it seems as though every female in my life is competing to see which one can be the most dominant...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Shaking his head, Zaranix looks back up at you.
		 [zaranix.speech(Anything else on your mind?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_INCUBUS_FORM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Almost all of the demons that I see are succubi. In fact, you're the only incubus that I've had any significant contact with,)] you say as you lead up to asking Zaranix why he isn't like the vast majority of demons.
	</p>
	<p>
		Sensing the incoming question, Zaranix chuckles as he cuts you short, [zaranix.speech(Why do I choose to stay as an incubus? To tell the truth, I'm not really too attached to one form or another, but I just feel most comfortable in this masculine body.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Do you ever change into your succubus form?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		A sly smirk settles on the incubus's face as he replies, [zaranix.speech(Well, I do agree to change into that form if it's for a partner's preference... Anyway, is there anything else you wanted?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	#IF(zaranix.getSexCount(pc, sex.newSexType(PENETRATION_PENIS, ORIFICE_MOUTH))>0)
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Well, I did come here with something on my mind...)] you say in your most seductive tone. Pointedly looking down at the bulge between Zaranix's legs, you tease him by not-so-subtly suggesting that you could give him another blowjob.
		</p>
		<p>
			[zaranix.speech(Well, I'm not going to say no to that,)] Zaranix replies with a smirk on his face. Taking a step back, he sits down on a nearby chair and teases, [zaranix.speech(You sure do like sucking my cock, huh?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Responding in the affirmative, you [pc.step] forwards and drop down between the imposing incubus's legs. Impatient to get started and have another taste of his big cock, you find yourself quickly going through the familiar motion of undoing Zaranix's trousers, and after pulling both them and his underwear down, you're rewarded by the sight of his rapidly-hardening cock. Letting out a breathless sigh, you immediately lean forwards and start kissing and licking the girthy purple dick. As your [pc.tongue+] slides over the hard, fleshy ribs which encircle his erect length, Zaranix grunts, [zaranix.speech(Don't hold back; I know you like the taste of my balls too...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Moving your head down, you show Zaranix that he's right by spending a couple of minutes licking and kissing his huge, heavy balls. Eventually, however, the two of you are keen to move onto the main event, and so after once again lifting your head up, you part your [pc.lips+] and take the incubus's hot cock into your mouth. Lewd, wet gagging noises are soon filling the room as you bob your head up and down and eagerly give Zaranix a blowjob...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Well, I did come here with something on my mind...)] you say in your most seductive tone. Pointedly looking down at the bulge between Zaranix's legs, you tease him by not-so-subtly suggesting that you could give him a blowjob.
		</p>
		<p>
			[zaranix.speech(Well, I'm not going to say no to that,)] Zaranix replies with a smirk on his face. Taking a step back, he sits down on a nearby chair and reveals, [zaranix.speech(I'll have you know that I'm particularly fond of receiving oral, and those lips of yours sure look good...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Grinning, you [pc.step] forwards and drop down between the imposing incubus's legs. Clearly impatient to get started, Zaranix quickly undoes his trousers, and after pulling both them and his underwear down, he exposes his rapidly-hardening cock to you. Although a hefty [zaranix.cockLengthValues] in length, his girthy, [zaranix.cockColour] shaft is relatively plain for a demon, as its only uncommon attribute is being circled by a series of hard, fleshy ribs. As a bead of slimy precum starts to ooze from his urethra, the incubus teases, [zaranix.speech(Go on, have a taste...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a breathless sigh, you obligingly lean forwards and start kissing and licking his girthy purple cock. As your [pc.tongue+] slides over the hard, fleshy ribs which encircle his erect length, Zaranix grunts, [zaranix.speech(Don't hold back; I know you'll like the taste of my balls too...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Moving your head down, you show Zaranix that he's right by spending a couple of minutes licking and kissing his huge, heavy balls. Eventually, however, the two of you are keen to move onto the main event, and so after once again lifting your head up, you part your [pc.lips+] and take the incubus's hot cock into your mouth. Lewd, wet gagging noises are soon filling the room as you bob your head up and down and eagerly give Zaranix a blowjob...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_BLOWJOB_TF_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF(zaranix.getSexCount(pc, sex.newSexType(PENETRATION_PENIS, ORIFICE_MOUTH))>0)
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Well, I did come here with something on my mind...)] you say in your most seductive tone. Pointedly looking down at the bulge between Zaranix's legs, you tease him by not-so-subtly suggesting that you could give him another blowjob.
		</p>
		<p>
			[zaranix.speech(Well, I'm not going to say no to that,)] Zaranix replies with a smirk on his face. Taking a step back, he sits down on a nearby chair and teases, [zaranix.speech(You sure do like sucking my cock, huh?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Well, I did come here with something on my mind...)] you say in your most seductive tone. Pointedly looking down at the bulge between Zaranix's legs, you tease him by not-so-subtly suggesting that you could give him a blowjob.
		</p>
		<p>
			[zaranix.speech(Well, I'm not going to say no to that,)] Zaranix replies with a smirk on his face. Taking a step back, he sits down on a nearby chair and reveals, [zaranix.speech(I'll have you know that I'm particularly fond of receiving oral, and those lips of yours sure look good... How about we get started then?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Instead of answering Zaranix's question, you inform him that there is one condition to your offer; he'll have to transform into his succubus form before you suck 'her' cock. Letting out an amused huff, the incubus agrees to do as you ask, [zaranix.speech(Fine, I don't particularly object to taking on my succubus form, and if it's so that I can get a blowjob, then I'm more than happy to do it!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_BLOWJOB_TF_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you watch, Zaranix's masculine features start to soften and become distinctly more feminine, and while she retains her muscles and short, black hair, she shrinks down a little and gains more mass around her hips, ass, and chest. Within a few moments, Zaranix has completely transformed into her tomboyish succubus form, and after clearing her throat, she teases, [zaranix.speech(You prefer me like this then? Do these get you turned on too?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus unbuttons her shirt and reveals her breasts to you. While extremely small by succubus standards, they're still about a [zaranix.cupSize]-cup, and sport large, dark-purple nipples on each of their perky tips. Liking Zaranix's new form far more than the one she had before, you find yourself lustfully gazing first at her chest, and then down to her groin, where there's still a large bulge pressing out from beneath her trousers. Seeing what it is you're looking at, the succubus laughs and teases, [zaranix.speech(I've fulfilled my end of the bargain, so let's get started...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ZARANIX_ROOM_BLOWJOB_TF_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After dropping a flirtatious compliment on Zaranix's new appearance, you [pc.step] forwards and drop down between the succubus's legs. Clearly impatient to get started, Zaranix quickly undoes her trousers, and after pulling both them and her underwear down, she exposes her rapidly-hardening cock to you. Although a hefty [zaranix.cockLengthValues] in length, her girthy, [zaranix.cockColour] shaft is relatively plain for a demon, as its only uncommon attribute is being circled by a series of hard, fleshy ribs. As a bead of slimy precum starts to ooze from her urethra, the succubus teases, [zaranix.speech(Go on, have a taste...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a breathless sigh, you obligingly lean forwards and start kissing and licking her girthy purple cock. As your [pc.tongue+] slides over the hard, fleshy ribs which encircle her erect length, Zaranix grunts, [zaranix.speech(Don't hold back; I know you'll like the taste of my balls too...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving your head down, you show Zaranix that she's right by spending a couple of minutes licking and kissing her huge, heavy balls. Eventually, however, the two of you are keen to move onto the main event, and so after once again lifting your head up, you part your [pc.lips+] and take the succubus's hot cock into your mouth. Lewd, wet gagging noises are soon filling the room as you bob your head up and down and eagerly give Zaranix a blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_ZARANIX_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Zaranix pats you on the head, before standing up and getting [zaranix.her] clothes back in order. [zaranix.speech(Thanks, [pc.name]; that was just what I needed! I really should get on with these experiments now, but if you're ever in the neighbourhood again, do drop in and say hello. I'd love to get another feel of those lips wrapped around my cock...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling at Zaranix, you stand up and step back, before telling [zaranix.herHim] that you'll be sure to drop by some again time.
	</p>
	<p>
		[zaranix.speech(Oh, and if you could, put in a good word with Lilaya about me, hmm?)] [zaranix.she] asks.
	</p>
	<p>
		Making a non-committal response, you head to the door and [pc.step] out into the corridor. As you close the door, Zaranix calls out behind you, [zaranix.speech(Oh, and don't let Amber be too harsh on you, ok?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Heading out into the corridor, and with the taste of Zaranix's cock still on your tongue, you wonder where to go next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	

</dialogue>
