<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_APPEARS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking through labyrinthine alleyways, with not a soul in sight. Back-doors and steaming vents line the dark brick walls, and you must often navigate around overflowing bins and stacks of empty crates in order to make any progress. These less-travelled parts of Dominion have a dangerous feel to them, and you can't shake the feeling that you're being followed.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you find yourself walking down yet another narrow passage, you hear a high-pitched tinkling noise coming from somewhere behind you, as though someone's just stepped on broken glass. Quickly turning to face the origin of the sound, you see nothing but a deserted alleyway, with not a soul in sight. Shrugging, you continue on your way.
	</p>
	<p>
		A few moments later, you hear yet another sound coming from behind you, though this time, it's one of quick, barely-audible footsteps. Whoever it is that's making these noises is definitely doing their best to try and remain silent, but, despite their efforts, you're now convinced that someone is stalking you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_APPEARS_EVADE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to stick around to discover who this mysterious stalker could be, you turn and hurry down a particularly narrow passageway. Reaching the far end, you look back to see a little shadowy figure rush past the opening.
	</p>
	<p>
		It looks like you've evaded your pursuer, and you turn around to continue on your way.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_APPEARS_FIRST_ENCOUNTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You aren't going to run from the first hint of danger, and decide that you'll turn the tables on the person who's been tailing you for all this time.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Oh no! It looks like I've got lost again!)]
		 You sigh, trying to lull your pursuer into a sense of false security.
	</p>
	<p>
		Continuing forwards down the narrow alleyway, you soon come to a sharp T-junction; the perfect spot where you'll be able to hide. Striding forwards, you take the turn to your left, and, being certain that your stalker must have lost sight of you, you squat down behind a stack of wooden crates and prepare to spring your ambush.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just as you'd planned, you soon hear the sounds of chinking bottles and scuffed footsteps as your assailant follows your trail. You can't help but grin and gloat at the thought of what you're going to do once you get your [pc.hands] on them. The sound of footsteps suddenly dies away, and you prepare for the mysterious stalker to silently sneak right past your hiding place.
	</p>
	<p>
		Except nobody is coming.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_APPEARS_FIRST_ENCOUNTER_WAITING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.thought(Wait, how long has it been? Why aren't they coming?)]
		 You think to yourself, confused at how easily your perfect plan has been foiled. The only explanation that you're able to think of is that whoever was silently chasing you decided to give up and leave before stumbling upon your ambush.
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a sigh, you stand up and quickly stretch, hopping back and forth a few times on your feet in order to get your limbs back in shape. Looking up and down the length of the alley, you don't see any sign of life, or of any suspicious activity whatsoever.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I've wasted enough time here, I'd better lea-)]
		 You start to say, but you're suddenly cut short by a flash of movement that rushes past you from behind. Your eyes catch up with what looks to be a humanoid with a big, white fluffy tail just as she reaches the end of the alleyway.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MAX_MONEY_STOLEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You reflexively check your belongings, and quickly discover that [style.boldTerrible(you're missing seven-hundred flames!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALL_MONEY_STOLEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You reflexively check your belongings, and quickly discover that [style.boldTerrible(all of your money has been stolen!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_LET_THEM_ESCAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you have better things to do than chasing some thief through the alleyways, you tell yourself that being a few flames lighter won't do you much harm, and, with a shrug, you continue on your way, reminding yourself to stay alert for any possible thieves in the future.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_CHASE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Hey! Come back here, you thief!)]
		 You shout as you start running after the white, fluffy tail.
		 The humanoid thief unsurprisingly ignores your command, and you see them quickly dash off down the right-hand turn at the end of the alley.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF game.isDayTime()
		#THEN
			Running after them, you take the same right-hand turn, and immediately find yourself confronted with one of Dominion's bustling streets. Quickly scanning the crowd, you manage to spot a flash of the fugitive's white furry tail as they dart and weave through the throngs of people with alarming agility. Following in their wake, you end up bumping into numerous people, pushing them aside and excusing yourself while doing your best not to fall behind.
		#ELSE
			Running after them, you take the same right-hand turn, and immediately find yourself confronted with one of Dominion's streets. As it's night-time, the area is far less busy than it would be during the day, and you easily spot the fugitive, lit by the ornate street-lights, running off down the path before you.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		The escapee turns their head in mid-sprint, and, catching sight of you still in full pursuit, their eyes go wide, and they immediately turn back to focus on the way ahead. From what you saw in that moment, the thief has a rather feminine face with a small, pointy nose and puffy jowls, as if they were holding something in their mouth. You suspect that something to be your stolen money, and you're not sure whether to be amused by this animalistic behaviour, or disgusted by the fact that your money is now sure to be covered in saliva.
	</p>
	<p>
		With you hot on their heels, the small figure suddenly darts back into a nearby alleyway, obviously hoping to shake you off their tail. Unfortunately for this opportunistic thief, you're determined to catch them, no matter what it takes, and turn to follow them down the dark passage.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_CHASE_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you enter the alleyway, your eyes quickly settle on the unmistakable figure of the fluffy-tailed thief, desperately trying to climb a twelve-foot-high wall. As you hurry forwards, she loses her grip, and falls back onto her butt. It looks like it's a dead-end for your fluffy fugitive, and a win for you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that you have a moment to take a good look at the thief, you see that she has a small, human body, covered in light skin. The only non-human parts that she has are a fluffy white wolf tail and two perky wolf ears perched on top of her head, which twitch backwards as they hear you approach. Just like her tail and ears, her long, messy hair is a brilliant white colour, and falls all the way down to her small, round butt, which is sure to be well-bruised from the fall she just took. As she jumps to her feet and spins around to face you, you see that she has small, B-cup breasts, and, standing at full height, she can't measure more than five-foot-two.
	</p>
	<p>
		The small [lumi.race] blushes as she realises that she's caught, and, you see that her cheeks are still swollen from the coin purse she's holding in her mouth. Her emerald-green eyes lock onto yours, and, from a mix of shame and anger, tears start to well up in them. You can't help but think how cute she looks, but, reminding yourself that she's a thief, you step forwards and take on a stern tone as you call out to her.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So, the little thief's run has finally come to an end.)] You say, with hands on hips.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(Mmmph mphh mph!)] The girl tries to reply, and blushes even harder from embarrassment as she seems to only just remember that she's got her mouth full. Quickly raising [lumi.her] hands in front of [lumi.her] face, she suddenly spits out a handful of coins, your coins. Now finally able to speak, she replies, [lumi.speech(W-What do you want?!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_COMBAT_PC_OPENING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(What do I want? Well, my money first of all, and then to teach a lesson to a certain naughty wolf-girl.)]
		 You tell her, taking a proper stance to fight.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_COMBAT_LUMI_OPENING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(I knew it! I knew you wanted to hurt me, l-like all the others!)]
		 The wolf-girl replies, before suddenly jumping back down into a squatting position.
		 Not giving you a chance to react, [lumi.she] suddenly pounces forwards, hurling herself at you!
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_PLAYER_LOSS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't carry on fighting any longer, and you feel your legs giving out beneath you as you collapse to the ground, defeated. Taking this chance, the opportunistic wolf-girl shoves the coins back into her mouth, before darting past you and running off down the alleyway. 
	</p>
	<p>
		With seemingly bottomless stamina, the little wolf-girl sprints off at full tilt, and, exhausted from your fight, you know that you have no chance of catching her. You resign yourself to simply resting until you've recovered enough strength to stand back up and carry on your way. As you set off, you try to forget about the money that was stolen from you.
	</p>
	<p>
		After putting up a fight, you can be sure that you won't be bothered by that particular wolf-girl ever again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_PLAYER_WIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Beaten down, the wolf-girl staggers back and leans against the nearest wall. As she sinks down to the ground, breathing heavily, you're left with no doubt in your mind that she's completely unable to continue fighting.
	<p>
	</p>
		With [lumi.her] fall, the stolen money falls from [lumi.her] hands and scatters on the ground. As one of the coins rolls forwards to bump against your [pc.foot], you wonder what you should do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_PLAYER_WIN_RECOVER_MONEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You quietly start to gather up the stolen coins. Most of them were dropped at your feet, but a few are lying beside the defeated wolf-girl. As you step forwards to collect them, you take a glance at the half-unconscious thief to make sure that she's ok.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you do so, she suddenly opens an eye, which flicks over to peek at your bent down form as you reach for another coin. Taking this opportunity, she jumps to her feet with surprising flexibility, and, darting past you, sprints off down the alleyway at full tilt. You suddenly find yourself alone and wondering how she managed to run off that quickly after taking such a beating. Shrugging, you finish collecting the last couple of coins and prepare to leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		After putting up a fight, you can be sure that you won't be bothered by that particular wolf-girl ever again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_PLAYER_WIN_TAKE_ADVANTAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The fight has gotten you riled up, and, looking down at the helpless wolf-girl before you, the thought of using her as sexual relief is foremost on your mind. Stepping forwards, you allow a devilish grin to settle on your face, and prepare to take advantage of the defeated thief.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Oh, this is going to be good!)]
		 You laugh, bending down to grab the wolf-girl's shoulders before pinning her to the ground. Shaken out of her daze by the sudden physical contact, the thief opens her eyes and looks up at you. At first, she simply seems to be surprised, but as she sees the hungry grin on your face, her eyes fill with panic. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(W-What are you doing? Let me go!)] She shouts as she starts to struggle against you. Tears quickly well up in her eyes as she discovers that you've totally immobilised her, and her struggles and cries quickly start to get more frantic and desperate.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Don't worry, I'll make this as enjoyable as possible... For me, that is!)] You sneer as you pin the little wolf-girl to the floor. Unable to hold back any longer, you quickly drop your lips down to hers, intent on putting her whining to an end by forcing her into a kiss.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(Nooo! Let me go! Let me go, let me go, lemmegolemmegolemmego!)] She shouts, struggling more and more and kicking out into mid-air as she tries to wriggle out of your grasp, but to no avail.
	</p>
	<p>
		You lean in and forcibly kiss her, tightening your grip on her arms as you hold her in place. The small [lumi.race] stops struggling and shouting, shocked from having her first kiss stolen. Tears quickly well up in her eyes as she stares at you in fear.
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking this opportunity, you [pc.moanVerb] as you look hungrily into her eyes, [pc.speech(This will be a fitting punishment for you!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you step back from the [lumi.race], she sinks to the floor, tears running down her face. She doesn't say anything, nor does she make any move. She just stays immobile, staring blankly off into space.
	</p>
	<p>
		You gather your belongings and walk away, leaving the traumatized [lumi.race] behind you. After what just happened, you can be sure that you won't be bothered by that particular wolf-girl ever again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_CAUGHT_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Calm down, little pup, I'm not going to hurt you, I just want to talk.)]
		 You say, trying to reassure the frightened wolf-girl.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(R-Really? You won't try to hurt me? You promise?)]
		 She mutters, her [lumi.tail] starting to wag lightly behind [lumi.her] back as her angry expression softens into one of concern.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, I promise.)] You smile, caught off guard by how cute [lumi.she] is.
	</p>
	<p>
		With those words, the wolf-girl lets out a relieved sigh, before suddenly dropping down onto [lumi.her] knees as her adrenaline rush comes to an end. Wanting to spend a moment talking with this unusual thief, you walk towards her and crouch down so as to be on the same level. [pc.speech(Now tell me, why do you steal?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(Because I'm hungry, and people are mean!)] She huffs, [lumi.speech(A-At first I tried stealing food from m-mar... morch...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Merchants?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(Y-Yes, merchants... But those meanies in blue uniforms caught me and scolded me for trying to eat, they said I had to pay with these shiny things...)] She looks at your money in [lumi.her] hands. [lumi.speech(And I need so many...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So many? What do you mean? Food isn't that expensive.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(Uh? I give them all of the shiny things, I take the food and I leave, but then I have no more shiny things, so I have to steal again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.thought(She means she never takes her change when she pays? No wonder she needs to steal all the time,)] you think to yourself, [pc.thought(Those merchants are taking advantage of her...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You know, when you give all your money to the merchants, they should be giving you some of your money back.)] You explain, trying not to sound too condescending. [pc.speech(It only costs about ten or fifteen of these coins to buy a sandwich... Seeing as you don't know all this, I'd guess you're not from Dominion, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Her ears twitch at your question. [lumi.speech(Uh? How do you know that?)] She replies, [lumi.speech(I-I lived in a forest before, but mean fox-ladies drove me out, saying it was their territories, and they threatened me with magic, so I ran as fast as I could and I ended up here...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Were you alone? You're the only person I've seen acting like this in Dominion.)] You ask, thinking about what [lumi.she] just told you. It's certainly not common to see such feral behaviour here in Dominion, and the fact that [lumi.she] doesn't know the basics about money, combined with her limited vocabulary, tells you that she must have come from an isolated, solitary part of this 'forest'.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(Yes, I lived alone, I never really knew my parents, I just barely remember that I was small, then my body grew super fast and then I hugged my mum and left her.)] She explains.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF !pc.getLittersBirthed().isEmpty()
		#THEN
			You know that feeling all too well, to have your children leave before you even have the time to say hello and hold them close to you.
		#ELSE
			You don't really know what to say. You imagine it would be hard as a mother to have your children leave before having the time to take them into your arms.
		#ENDIF
		 Shaking those thought from your head, you sigh, [pc.speech(Anyway, about what you did...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_CAUGHT_TALK_GIVE_MONEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Sensing that the wolf-girl has quickly grown comfortable with your presence, you reach out to give her head a gentle pat, before giving her soft ears a stroke. [pc.speech(You can keep the money.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The little wolf-girl fails to contain a small moan as the pleasure from your petting completely overwhelms her. Quickly realising what she's just done, she clasps her hands over her mouth and pretends as though nothing just happened, although the fact that her fluffy tail is pointing straight up into the air gives her feelings away. From behind her hands, the wolf-girl mutters a barely audible question. [lumi.speech(W-What can I ~mmh~ keep?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving her ears one last stroke, you gently boop [lumi.her] nose. [pc.speech(The money you took from me, silly. You can keep it, but I'll tell you how to use it)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Her big [lumi.eyeColour] eyes light up at what you just said, and [lumi.she] gazes up at you in disbelief. [lumi.speech(Really? You... You'd really give all of this to me? Even if I... I took it from you? You're not kidding?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Playfully laughing at [lumi.her] reaction, you assure her that you mean everything you told her and that your flames are now [lumi.hers] to use how [lumi.she] pleases. You then go on to explain the concept of money and how buying and selling food and other items works. The wolf-girl often tilts [lumi.her] head in confusion as you explain these entirely new concepts to her, but you can tell that [lumi.she]'s absorbing every word, and is completely fascinated by your teachings.
	</p>
	<p>
		Once you've finished, the wolf-girl smiles.
		[lumi.speech(Thank you so much! Uhm...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Call me [pc.Name],)] you tell her, realizing that you haven't exchanged names yet.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech([pc.Name]... [pc.Name], [pc.Name]... I like your name! I'm [lumi.Name]!)] [lumi.She] says with a big smile on [lumi.her] face. Before you can reply, [lumi.she] quickly drops down onto all fours, lowering her torso to the ground and wiggling her butt in the air a few times, before suddenly pouncing forwards, [lumi.her] [lumi.arms] stretched out towards you. Caught off guard, you reflexively try to back off, but the wolf-girl's movement is way too sudden and unexpected, and you suddenly find yourself falling onto your back, with Lumi's arms wrapped tightly around you as she gives you a big hug.
	</p>
	<p>
		Thankfully, the floor in this part of the alleyway seems clean enough, and so you're content to spend the next few minutes lying on the ground, with [lumi.Name] snuggled against you. It's hard to imagine that this cute, trusting wolf-girl is the same thief that just minutes ago was wildly sprinting off with your money.
	</p>
	<p>
		After some time has passed, you reach up to scratch her head to get her attention. [pc.speech(Alright you little pup, I have other things to be getting on with.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.Name] quickly lets you go and you both push yourselves up onto your feet. [lumi.She] looks at you with a gleeful stare, and exclaims, [lumi.speech(I like you, [pc.Name]! You're the first to be really kind to me in a long time! I hope I'll see you again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Lumi puts [lumi.her] coins back into [lumi.her] mouth, stacking them in [lumi.her] jowls like a rodent before running off in the direction of the Shopping Arcade. You wonder if the merchants will raise any objection to be getting paid with coins coated in saliva.
	</p>
	<p>
		You decide that it's also time for you to go. You may have lost some flames, but in exchange, you met a curious, cute little [lumi.race]. As this seems to be the area in which she's made her home, if you ever wanted to meet her again, all you'd have to do would be to wander around through these alleyways...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_CAUGHT_TALK_ASK_FOR_MONEY_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Listen, I can see that you're not a mean girl, but stealing is bad, ok?)] You tell the wolf-girl, putting a hand on [lumi.her] shoulder. [pc.speech(I can't force you not to do it, but you should know that other people won't be as kind or understanding as I am.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The wolf-girl pouts and looks at the ground as she receives her scolding. Putting on a gentler and more reassuring tone, you continue, [pc.speech(Look at me. I will take my money back now, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		She looks at you with sad eyes, her shoulders drooped as she reluctantly hands over your coins. In a barely audible whimper, she mutters, [lumi.speech(H-Here... I'm... I'm sorry...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You feel a prickling sensation in your chest, as you hear the sincerity and sadness in the wolf-girl's voice, you get a twinge of regret about scolding her. Reminding yourself that it was for her own good, you compassionately pat [lumi.her] head, before taking back what is yours. [pc.speech(Thank you, little thief. So, what is your name?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(M-Me? I'm... I'm [lumi.Name].)] [lumi.She] says, hesitantly.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Nice to meet you [lumi.Name], I wish we'd have met in better circumstances... I'm [pc.Name].)] You reply, stopping your head-petting in order to safely put your money back where it belongs. [pc.speech(As you've been so reasonable, how about I treat you to dinner some time?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lumi's eyes instantly brighten and [lumi.her] [lumi.ears] stand fully erect. It looks like the magic keyword to make [lumi.her] feel better is 'dinner'. [lumi.speech(You... You'd really do that? Yes! I'd love to!)] [lumi.She] shouts, [lumi.her] [lumi.tail] wiggling excitingly behind [lumi.her] back as she gazes into your eyes.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Alright, it's settled then! I'll see you around, and stay out of trouble!)] You say, before turning to leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lumi.speech(I like you, [pc.Name]! I hope I'll see you again!)] Lumi shouts, before darting off past you and disappearing down the alleyway. As this seems to be the area in which she's made her home, if you ever wanted to meet this cute wolf-girl again, all you'd have to do would be to wander around through this area...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LUMI_CAUGHT_TALK_THREATEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(This is not acceptable. At all. You're lucky I decided not to give you a beating, but you'd better believe that I won't spare you a second time if you ever do this again. Now, give me my money!)] You shout, scowling in anger as you assertively reach out your hand.
	</p>
	<p>
		The wolf-girl's gaze instantly drops to the ground, and tears start visibly welling in [lumi.her] eyes as she mutters, [lumi.speech(I knew it... I knew you wouldn't be nice to me either...)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		The wolf-girl's voice starts trembling as she realises that you're not the friendly person she took you for. Stepping towards you, she puts your money in your palm, before quickly dashing past you, sobbing uncontrollably and disappearing into the backalleys of Dominion.
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, you're left alone with your money in the alleyway. You tell yourself that it's best not to try and make friends with thieves, and, putting your money safely away, you move to continue on your way. After what just happened, you can be sure that you won't be bothered by that particular wolf-girl ever again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
