<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- Dirty talk -->
	
	<!-- Alleyway beside Helena's shop: -->
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_DIRTY_TALK"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Good slave! Keep on stroking your Mistress's cock!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_DIRTY_TALK"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(That's it! Keep on stroking my cock, slave!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_DIRTY_TALK"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(What a good submissive slave you are! Keep on stroking my cock!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_DIRTY_TALK"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Show your Mistress how much you love her cock!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_DIRTY_TALK"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(That's it, keep on stroking my cock like the good slave you are!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_DIRTY_TALK"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Keep going, slave! Stroke your Mistress's cock!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_DIRTY_TALK"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Remember, slave, you're only to use your [pc.hands]!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_DIRTY_TALK"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(You're forbidden from using anything but your [pc.hands], slave! Keep on stroking!)]]]></htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Receiving blowjob: -->
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Yes, filly! Keep on sucking your Mistress's cock!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(That's it, filly! Suck my cock!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(That's my good little filly slut! Take my cock deep!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Yes! Suck my cock, you dirty little filly!)]]]></htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Receiving rimjob: -->
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Yes, filly! Get your tongue in there!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(That's it, filly! Eat my ass!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(That's my good little filly slut! Worship your Mistress's ass!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Yes! Eat my ass, you dirty little filly!)]]]></htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Giving anal: -->
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_ANAL"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Yes, filly! Take my cock!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_ANAL"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(That's it, filly! Take my cock deep in your slutty ass!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_ANAL"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(That's my good little filly slut! Let your Mistress rut your ass!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_ANAL"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Yes! Your ass feels so good to fuck, you dirty little filly!)]]]></htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Giving blowjob: -->
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(You like having your Mistress giving you a blowjob, filly?)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(I'll make you cum in no time!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(You like the feeling of my lips wrapped around your cock, filly?)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(You'd better appreciate this, you bad little filly!)]]]></htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Giving rimjob: -->
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(You like having your Mistress giving you a rimjob, filly?)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(I'll make you cum in no time!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(You like the feeling of my lips pressing against your ass, filly?)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_GIVING_RIMJOB"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(You'd better appreciate this, you bad little filly!)]]]></htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Receiving anal: -->
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_ANAL"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(You like the feeling of rutting your Mistress's ass, filly?!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_ANAL"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(My ass will make you cum in no time!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_ANAL"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(Go on, filly, get your cock in deep!)]]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="DIRTY_TALK_RECEIVING_ANAL"><![CDATA[[natalya.speech(You'd better appreciate this, you bad little filly!)]]]></htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Orgasm reactions behind Helena's shop -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a lewd moan, Natalya suddenly bucks her hips forwards, thrusting her [natalya.cockGirth], throbbing cock forwards between your [pc.hands]. Wildly pawing at the ground with one of her front hoofs, she desperately squeals, [natalya.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ Slave! Take your Mistress's load!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_ORGASM_FACIAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		At that moment, the [natalya.race]'s [natalya.ballSize] balls tense up, and as the flared head of her horse-like cock swells up, you obediently point it directly towards your face. The last thing you see before instinctively closing your [pc.eyes] is Natalya's urethra opening up as it unleashes a huge gush of musky spunk all over your [pc.face]. Continuing to hold on to your Mistress's throbbing cock, you make sure that each pump of her thick, slimy cum is aimed directly at you, and after just the first couple of spurts, you're absolutely drenched in it.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a few moments, Natalya's heavy balls seem to have emptied themselves, and with a deeply-satisfied sigh, she nimbly sidesteps away from you. Turning back to make sure that you did as she asked, the [natalya.race] arrogantly smirks down at you as she sees her musky cum slowly dripping from your [pc.face]. Pushing up her thick-rimmed glasses from where they'd slipped down her nose a little, she declares, [natalya.speechNoEffects(You show much potential, slave! Being coated in your Mistress's cum is a fitting reward for your service!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Showing absolutely no sign of caring whether or not you're satisfied from this experience, Natalya makes it quite clear from her positioning that she's finished with you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_ALLEYWAY_ORGASM_NO_FACIAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		At that moment, the [natalya.race]'s [natalya.ballSize] balls tense up, and as the flared head of her horse-like cock swells up, you make sure to point it away from your face. With no further warning, Natalya's urethra visibly opens up, before suddenly unleashing a huge gush of musky spunk all over the floor. Continuing to hold on to your Mistress's throbbing cock, you make sure that each pump of her thick, slimy cum is aimed down at the ground, and after just the first couple of spurts, the paving stones are absolutely drenched in it.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a few moments, Natalya's heavy balls seem to have emptied themselves, and with a deeply-satisfied sigh, she nimbly sidesteps away from you. Turning back to make sure that you did as she asked, the [natalya.race] arrogantly scowls down at you as she sees that not a drop of her musky cum has landed on your [pc.face]. Pushing up her thick-rimmed glasses from where they'd slipped down her nose a little, she declares, [natalya.speechNoEffects(I can see that you're in need of much training, slave! It's only fitting that by disobeying me, you've missed out on the reward of feeling my cum drenching your face!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Showing absolutely no sign of caring whether or not you're satisfied from this experience, Natalya makes it quite clear from her scolding that she's finished with you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
</dialogue>
