<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- Orgasm reaction when you cum from Scarlett's anal -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ROUGH_ANAL_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a triumphant chuckle, [scarlett.name] continues to thrust [scarlett.her] [scarlett.cock+] in and out of your [pc.asshole+] as [scarlett.she] asks, [scarlett.speechNoEffects(You like that, bitch?! ~Mmm!~ Tell me what you are!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a deep [pc.moan], you submissively tell the [scarlett.race] what [scarlett.she] wants to hear, [pc.speechNoEffects(~Ooh!~ I'm a dirty buttslut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hilting [scarlett.her] [scarlett.cock+] in your [pc.ass], [scarlett.name] hammers the point home by saying, [scarlett.speechNoEffects(That's right! ~Mmm!~ You came from having my cock pound your ass! ~Aah!~ That makes you my dirty buttslut bitch!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CUSTOMER_INTERRUPTION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CUSTOMER_INTERRUPTION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(scarlett.hasPenis())
		Having spotted a customer heading towards her, Scarlett bucks her hips forwards and slams her [scarlett.cock+] down your throat, effectively silencing you as she calls out, 
	#ELSE
		Having spotted a customer heading towards her, Scarlett bucks her hips forwards and smothers your mouth with her [scarlett.pussy+], effectively silencing you as she calls out,
	#ENDIF
	 [scarlett.speechNoEffects(Ask one of the other harpies for help! I'm fucking busy here!)]
	<br/><br/>
	Scarlett's hostile exclamation effectively dissuades the customer from coming any closer, and after watching them turn around and walk off, the raven harpy draws back a little and hisses down at you,
	#IF(scarlett.hasPenis())
		 [scarlett.speechNoEffects(Keep sucking, bitch!)]
	#ELSE
		 [scarlett.speechNoEffects(Get that tongue working again, bitch!)]
	#ENDIF
	]]></htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CUSTOMER_INTERRUPTION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(scarlett.hasPenis())
		Suddenly thrusting her [scarlett.cock+] down your throat, Scarlett calls out to an approaching customer,
	#ELSE
		Suddenly bucking her hips forwards and smothering your mouth with her [scarlett.pussy+], Scarlett calls out to an approaching customer,
	#ENDIF
	 [scarlett.speechNoEffects(Fuck off and bother one of the other harpies!)]
	<br/><br/>
	Clearly not wanting to argue with such a hostile harpy, the customer scurries off, leaving Scarlett to draw back a little and hiss down at you,
	#IF(scarlett.hasPenis())
		 [scarlett.speechNoEffects(Go on, bitch, keep sucking my cock!)]
	#ELSE
		 [scarlett.speechNoEffects(Go on, bitch, get your tongue in deep!)]
	#ENDIF
	]]></htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENA_INTERRUPTION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENA_INTERRUPTION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(scarlett.hasPenis())
		Letting out a surprised gasp, Scarlett suddenly steps forwards and hilts her cock down your throat, effectively limiting the sounds you can produce to no more than a quiet, gargled splutter.
	#ELSE
		Letting out a surprised gasp, Scarlett suddenly steps forwards and smothers your mouth with her [scarlett.pussy+], effectively limiting the sounds you can produce to no more than a quiet, muffled splutter.
	#ENDIF
	 The reason for this unexpected move is very quickly made clear to you, as from up above, you hear the familiar, soft voice of Helena addressing your sexual partner, [helena.speechNoEffects(Scarlett, my dear, I've just received a complaint from one of our clients. Apparently, you've just been extremely rude to them. What do you have to say for yourself?)]
	<br/><br/>
	[scarlett.speechNoEffects(Ah! S-Sorry, Helena! I didn't mean to be so rude!)] the raven harpy quickly apologises, doing her best to hide the tone of arousal in her voice.
	<br/><br/>
	Thankfully, Helena seems to be oblivious as to what's happening beneath the counter in front of her, and after sharply scolding her subordinate, she lets out an exasperated sigh and asks, [helena.speechNoEffects(So did [pc.name] leave earlier? I thought [pc.she] would have come and said goodbye to me...)]
	<br/><br/>
	[scarlett.speechNoEffects(Yes, but I'm sure [pc.she]'ll be back soon,)] Scarlett says
	#IF(scarlett.hasPenis())
		 as she slowly grinds the base of her cock against your [pc.lips].
	#ELSE
		 as she slowly grinds her wet cunt against your [pc.lips].
	#ENDIF
	 Without saying another word, you hear the beautiful matriarch turn on the spot and head off back into the store, leaving Scarlett to let out a soft laugh and hiss down at you, [scarlett.speechNoEffects(You hear that? Once I've finished with you, Helena'll be wanting to see you. Now hurry up and finish me off!)]
	]]></htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
