<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- WES_QUEST_START -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.isDayTime())
			Although the sun has already set this evening, there are still plenty of people out and about,
		#ELSE
			As you make your way down yet another of Dominion's streets, you can't help but notice how many people are out and about this evening,
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_DEMON)
			 and while they hurry to get out of your way when they see that you're a demon, you still end up having to weave your way around some of the larger of the crowds.
		#ELSE
			 and you have to adjust your path every now and again so as to weave your way around the crowds.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_OBSERVANT))
			 As you're passing a slow-moving group of obnoxiously-loud revellers, you suddenly notice that an orange-furred greater fox-boy, dressed in a grey hoodie and blue jeans, over on the far side of the street keeps on glancing your way. Although his gaze is hidden behind a pair of dark glasses, you can tell that he's got some kind of particular interest in you. As your path around the crowd brings you closer to where he's standing, you see the fox-boy suddenly begin to move towards you, and as he sees that you've noticed his approach, he smiles and asks, [wes.speech(If I'm not mistaken, then you're [pc.name], right?)]
		#ELSE
			 As you're passing a slow-moving group of obnoxiously-loud revellers, you suddenly see that an orange-furred greater fox-boy, dressed in a grey hoodie and blue jeans, is rapidly moving towards you. Although his gaze is hidden behind a pair of dark glasses, you can tell that he's got some kind of particular interest in you, and before you can react to his approach, he smiles and asks, [wes.speech(If I'm not mistaken, then you're [pc.name], right?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		The warm, friendly tone of this mysterious character's voice is not quite what you were expecting, and from his subtle country accent, you get the strong impression that he's not a native city-dweller. Despite his endearing manner of speech, you detect a sense of urgency in the fox-boy's question, and so, seeing no harm in answering him, you quickly reply that you are indeed [pc.name].
	</p>
	<p>
		Retrieving a very official-looking SWORD Enforcer badge from out of his hoodie's pocket, this stranger flashes it at you and reveals, [wes.speech(I know that you're the one who dealt with that sticky situation up in the Harpy Nests, which is why I've come to you for help. I can't talk for too long out in the streets like this, but if you want to help the Enforcers again, then-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Suddenly getting spooked by the sight of something further down the street, the fox-boy interrupts his hasty explanation to ask, [wes.speech(Please, meet me outside the antiques shop in the Shopping Arcade between one and two in the afternoon. I'll be there every day, but it would be best if you were there tomorrow. Look, I have to go. Meet me there, ok?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_AGREE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to do as the fox-boy asks, you agree to meet him at the location and time he's given to you. Letting out a short sigh of relief, he flashes you a warm smile and declares, [wes.speech(I was right to seek your help. I'll see you soon!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hastily striding over to the other side of the street, the fox-boy quickly blends in to one of the crowds that are passing by, and before you know it, you've lost track of him entirely. With nothing else to do here, you set off and continue on your way, wondering what that mysterious SWORD Enforcer could want to discuss with you...
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsMinorGood(The Enforcer will be in the Shopping Arcade, outside of the antiques shop, between [units.time(13)]-[units.time(14)] every day.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_QUESTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know more about what this fox-boy wants before agreeing to meet with him, you ask him what sort of help he's expecting you to give. Sharply exhaling in frustration, he once again glances around and declares, [wes.speech(I don't have time to explain here. Please, just meet me tomorrow and I'll explain everything. I hope to see you soon!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Offering you no further opportunity in which to ask him further questions, the fox-by hastily strides over to the other side of the street, before quickly blending in to one of the crowds that are passing by. Before you know it, you've lost track of him entirely, and so with nothing else to do, you set off and continue on your way, wondering what that mysterious SWORD Enforcer could want to discuss with you...
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsMinorGood(The Enforcer will be in the Shopping Arcade, outside of the antiques shop, between [units.time(13)]-[units.time(14)] every day.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_wesQuestRefused))
		<p>
			Wanting to talk with Wes again, you decide to wait here outside of the antiques shop in the hopes that you'll be able to meet with him. Just like the last time you did this, the fox-boy doesn't show up for a good five minutes, but eventually you see him walking towards you from the same direction as which you arrived.
		</p>
		<p>
			Wearing the same blue jeans and grey hoodie that he was wearing the last time you saw him, the fox-boy steps up to you and asks in a friendly tone, [wes.speech(So, you decided to come back? Have you had a change of mind about helping me?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Still not entirely convinced that you want to help Wes, you ask him once again what exactly it is that he wants you to do. Taking off his dark glasses to once again reveal his bright green eyes, the fox-boy explains, [wes.speech(I'm convinced that my superior officer, Elle, is doing some shady dealings during her long Wednesday lunch breaks. I need you to find out where she's going, and then to collect evidence of her illegal activities. I can't go myself as I have no time in which to follow her, and I can't report this for an internal investigation without solid evidence of Elle's wrongdoing. Please, I need your help.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having been reminded of what it is that Wes wants you to do, you wonder whether to agree to help him, or once again refuse...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to find out more about the mysterious Enforcer who approached you in Dominion's streets, you decide to wait here outside of the antiques shop in the hopes that you'll be able to meet with him again. Unfortunately, despite being in the correct place, at the correct time, you don't see any sign of the fox-boy, and after five minutes spent waiting for him to show up, you start to wonder whether it would be a good idea to come back and try again tomorrow.
		</p>
		<p>
			Just as you're thinking of leaving, however, you suddenly spot the mysterious Enforcer walking towards you from the same direction as which you arrived. Wearing the same blue jeans and grey hoodie that he was wearing the last time you saw him, the fox-boy steps up to you and says in a friendly tone, [wes.speech(Thanks for meeting me here, [pc.name]. Sorry that I left you waiting for a while; I had to make sure that you weren't being followed.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Taking off his dark glasses, the orange-furred fox-boy reveals a pair of bright green eyes, which, unlike the usual shiftiness foxes are stereotyped for, project a disarming, folksy naiveté which perfectly matches his soft county accent. Smiling at you, he finally reveals who he is by saying, [wes.speech(My name's Wesley Wormwood, but everyone just calls me Wes for short. As you've already seen from my badge, I'm one of SWORD's Chief Inspectors, and I work over at the main HQ as a Junior Quartermaster. Sorry for not introducing myself to you earlier, but I was a little pressed for time. The reason I wanted to meet with you is to ask for your help in the investigation of my superior officer.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pausing for a moment, the fox-boy gives you an opportunity in which to respond to what he's just said...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_QUESTION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_QUESTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know more, and thinking that it would be best to start at the beginning, you ask Wes what exactly his superior officer is doing which would warrant them being investigated. After quickly glancing around to make sure that nobody's eavesdropping, the fox-boy explains, [wes.speech(The officer I'm talking about is '[elle.name] [elle.surname]', but everyone just calls her 'Elle'; she's the Senior Quartermaster over at Enforcer HQ. Me and her are the only two who have access to the station's inventory, and I've noticed over the past few weeks that equipment has started to go missing. It started with the odd pistol or a couple of batons, but just two days ago I discovered that even several of the cryoprism guns now only exist on paper. It <i>has</i> to be her who's taking them.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So you want me to find out what she's doing with them?)] you ask, picking up on where Wes is going with his explanation.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(That's right. I'd try to investigate all of this myself, but the problem is that Elle teleports out of her office every Wednesday lunch time, and there's no way for me to follow her. I'm convinced that that's when she's selling these weapons to criminal gangs, but there's nothing I can do to stop her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Why not have this investigated internally?)] you ask, wondering why Wes has sought out your help instead of reporting this to his superiors.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Elle's a half-demon, so internal investigations always get really messy when one of them is involved. Besides, if she were tipped off that she was being investigated, she'd no doubt set me up as the guilty party, and who do you think's going to be believed? Some fox from the sticks, or his half-demon superior officer, who, I'm told, is the child of a direct daughter of Lunette herself?)] Wes sighs, pausing for a moment to collect his thoughts before continuing, [wes.speech(After I heard of your work up in the Harpy Nests, I was hoping that I could ask for your help with all of this...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to hear exactly what is is that Wes is wanting of you before deciding whether to help him or not, you ask the fox-boy what his plan is.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(I'll need you to gather incriminating evidence of Elle selling Enforcer weapons to criminals,)] he states, before producing what looks to be some kind of miniature video recorder from out of his hoodie's spacious front pocket and explaining, [wes.speech(I've requisitioned this arcane recording device, so all you need to do is find out where Elle's teleporting off to, and then to use this to record evidence of her illegal activities.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With one final question left on your mind, you ask Wes how you're supposed to find Elle. After all, if she's teleporting off to somewhere, it could be literally anywhere in all of Lilith's Realm.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(That's going to be the hard part in all of this,)] the fox-boy sighs, [wes.speech(All I can tell you is that she conducts this illegal business during her long lunch breaks every Wednesday, and that she takes a pair of night vision goggles with her. When she returns, her shoes are often wet and sometimes have trace amounts of some kind of glowing residue on them...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having now heard all of the information Wes has to offer you, you wonder whether you should agree to help him by tracking down Elle and collecting evidence of her criminal activities, or tell the fox-boy that you're not interested in getting tangled up in his mess. As you're wondering what to say, Wes holds out the arcane recorder and asks, [wes.speech(Please, [pc.name], can you help me with this? If all goes according to plan, I'll be able to arrange a decent reward for you.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_FAIL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_FAIL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you're certain that you can trust Wes to be telling the truth about the situation with Elle's criminal activities, you really don't like the idea of getting tangled up in the Enforcer's internal affairs. Telling the fox-boy that you're unwilling to do as he asks, you [pc.step] back from him and prepare to leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Well, I don't blame you; it seems to be the common attitude in this city for everyone to look out for themselves and never stick their neck out to help anyone,)] he cynically remarks, before putting the arcane recorder back in his hoodie's pocket and letting out a deep sigh. Putting his dark glasses back on, he turns and starts to walk off into the Shopping Arcade, calling after him as he goes, [wes.speech(If you change your mind, I'll be here at the same time tomorrow...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Wes walks off, leaving you with little else to do except continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_QUESTION_END -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_QUESTION_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling Wes that you'll do as he asks, you take the arcane recorder from him and listen as he instructs you on how to operate it. The device seems simple enough to use, and after you've told the fox-boy that you're confident in your ability at using it, he smiles and says, [wes.speech(Right, once you've tracked down Elle and recorded her illegal activities, you'll need to deposit this recorder in one of our anonymous evidence drop-boxes. Just ask that bimbo at the HQ's front desk where it is, or if you're down in Submission, then all of the Enforcer posts down there have one. After handing the evidence in, wait at least one week for the internal investigation to conclude, and then go back to the HQ's front desk and ask to see me. I'll have a reward for you then.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling Wes that you understand what to do, you watch as he puts his dark glasses back on and flashes you another of his warm smiles. Letting out a happy little chuckle, he says, [wes.speech(I guess not everyone in this city is as selfish as I thought. Thanks for agreeing to help, [pc.name]. Remember, don't come looking for me until at least a week after you've handed in the evidence. Oh, and don't mention any of this to any other Enforcers; they may mean well, but if word of this gets out, you'll be dropping me in pretty hot water...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Wes walks off, leaving you to put the arcane recording device away and wonder to yourself where Elle could be conducting her illegal business. Thinking back on what Wes told you, the main points were:
		<i>
		<br/>She takes [style.colourOrange(unusually long lunch breaks)].
		<br/>She only does this on a [style.colourOrange(Wednesday)].
		<br/>She takes a set of [style.colourOrange(night vision goggles)] with her.
		<br/>Afterwards, her [style.colourOrange(shoes are often wet)] and sometimes have trace amounts of some kind of [style.colourOrange(glowing residue on them)].
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Thinking back on those points, you feel confident that you can figure out where Elle is going, but if not, you realise that you could always go to Lilaya and ask for her help. With that comforting thought in mind, you set off and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_SEARCH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_SEARCH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having figured out that Elle must be conducting her illegal activities in the Bat Caverns, and with it currently being the correct day and time in which to find her down here, you start searching for any clue as to her whereabouts. With these caves being as vast and as dark as they are, you don't hold out much hope of finding Elle on your first try, but by a stroke of particular good fortune, you quickly stumble upon evidence of what appears to be the trail of heavy crates having been dragged through a patch of luminescent fungi.
	</p>
	<p>
		Following this trail down several twists and turns in the maze-like network of caves, you soon find yourself [pc.stepping] out into an underground forest of huge, bioluminescent mushrooms. The carpet of glowing fungi which covers the ground before you has been heavily trodden-down in places, allowing you to continue following the path of whoever has travelled this way before you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the trail for just a little further, you discover that it leads to a small cave, the entrance to which is almost completely concealed by an abnormally-thick patch of tree-like mushrooms. Concerned that Elle might already be inside, you proceed towards the entrance of this cave with caution, but thankfully, as you peer around one of the mushroom's thick trunks, you see that the interior appears to be completely deserted...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Making sure to keep a sharp lookout for any sign of Elle, you squeeze your way around the huge mushrooms which conceal the cave's entrance, before [pc.stepping] inside and starting to take a look around. Immediately, you see that this is definitely the place which you're looking for, as there are numerous piles of both locked and empty crates stacked up against the cave's walls, with more than a couple of them displaying signs of crudely scraped-off SWORD insignias.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you approach these crates to take a closer look, you suddenly hear the sound of feminine, flirty laughter coming from somewhere outside of the cave. Stopping dead in your tracks, you listen as this laughter suddenly cuts off, only to be quickly followed by a slovenly male voice asking, [style.speechMasculineHeavy('Ow much fuckin' further 'ave we gots ta go?! You's better not be settin' us up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Oh, please,)] the flirty voice of the woman replies, [elle.speech(If I wanted to set you up, you'd all be under arrest by now! As it so happens, the weapons I promised you are right inside that cave. Please follow me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that these people intend to enter the cave which you're currently occupying, you quickly look around for a place in which to hide and secretly record evidence of Elle's criminal activity. Thankfully, an empty space behind a particularly large stack of empty crates provides the perfect place in which to conceal yourself, and you manage to duck down into this recess just in time before Elle and several thuggish gang members enter the cave.
	</p>
	<p>
		Peering through a slender gap in the crates, you're able to get a good look of Elle, who turns out to be a greater [elle.race] who looks to be in her early forties. As is the case for most people with demonic blood, Elle's brown-furred anthropomorphic horse-like face is stunningly beautiful, and there's an energetic, excited look in her [elle.eyeColour] demonic eyes. Her SWORD uniform conceals most of her fit body, but you can still quite clearly see that she's got a huge pair of [elle.cupSize]-cup breasts, as well as wide, womanly hips and a large ass.
	</p>
	<p>
		As she turns to one side to beckon the gang members into the cave, you're able to see that Elle's horse-like tail is the same sandy blonde colour as her hair, which is tied up into a smart bun. Growing from her shoulder-blades, you see that she she has a pair of large, lilac-skinned demonic wings, while a long, indigo unicorn horn grows from her upper forehead. Having taken a good look at Elle's appearance, you turn your attention to the group of rat, alligator, and dog-morph gang-members who are roughly pushing their way past the mushrooms and into the cave.
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking out the arcane recorder which Wes gave to you, you point the lens through the gap in the crates and start filming the scene in front of you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE_RECORDING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE_RECORDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With your arcane recorder capturing video and audio footage of all that's happening in the cave, you watch as the rough-looking dog-boy leader of the gang-members steps up to the nearest crate and demands, [style.speechMasculineHeavy(Show us wot ya got then! You's ain't gettin' no flames from me until I sees that you's got the goods ya promised to us!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Teasing the dog-boy by brushing her hand over his arm, Elle laughs, [elle.speech(My, my, you are impatient, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Grunting in amusement at the Enforcer's flirty attitude, the dog-boy hungrily watches as Elle turns her back on him and bends down at the waist to unlock the crate he pointed to. Stepping aside to let the gang-members take a look inside, Elle teases, [elle.speech(Go on then, boys, choose whatever you like! My prices are most reasonable, I can assure you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing weakness in Elle's attitude, one of the rat-boy gang-members pulls a pistol out of the crate, before brazenly waving it at the Enforcer and sneering, [style.speechMasculine('O said anythin' about us payin' fer this? Heh-heh-heh! Now we's got the guns, 'o's ta stop us from 'avin' a little fun with you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Instantly, Elle drops her flirty, light-hearted act, but while her face takes on a grim expression, you can't help but notice the way her eyes light up at the prospect of trouble. Exhibiting an alarming display of speed, the Enforcer darts forwards, and after effortlessly knocking the pistol out of the rat-boy's hands, she grabs hold of him by the neck and violently slams him down onto the floor. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculineHeavy(Woah, woah, woah! We ain't wantin' no trouble!)] the leader of the gang nervously shouts, [style.speechMasculineHeavy('E was only jokin' 'bout not payin'! Look, I's got the flames 'ere, 'ow much do ya-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(I don't give a damn about your money,)] Elle snaps, cutting the gang-member off. Advancing towards him with her wings unfurled, she reveals, [elle.speech(I'm not doing this to get rich! You scum are too soft; do you know how boring it is to be an Enforcer these days?! Oh, what I'd give to go back to the crime waves of the late 70's, or for the fifth human rebellion to still be ongoing. Where's the fun in subduing pathetic, bottom-feeding losers like you lot? Perhaps if these weapons got out onto the streets, however, and a new crime wave started, then I'd get to relive the glory days...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Sensing that they're in very real danger of being on the receiving end of Elle's wroth, the gang-members wisely choose not to interrupt her monologue. Waiting until she's calmed down and folded her wings back into place, the dog-boy leader of the gang holds out a bag of money to Elle, saying, [style.speechMasculineHeavy(A-A deal's a deal, right? We's givin' you's this cash so we can 'ave the weapons, ok? We ain't wantin' no trouble...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After taking a deep breath, Elle assumes her previous, flirty demeanour, and after gently taking the bag of flames from the dog-boy, she teases, [elle.speech(That's a good boy. As I stated before, I don't care much for your money, but I suppose I could use this to fund some other gang activities... Anyway, have fun with all of the guns, and please do try to cause as much trouble as you can.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Elle is suddenly enveloped in a bright flash of purple arcane energy, and after you've blinked away the after-image that's been momentarily burned into your vision, you see that she's vanished. Letting out a deep sigh of relief, the gang's leader steps over to the still-prone form of the rat-boy who threatened Elle, before kicking him and grunting, [style.speechMasculineHeavy(Ya fuckin' idiot! You's almost got us all fuckin' killed there! Now grab as many o' these weapons as ya can carry, then let's get out o' 'ere before that crazy bitch returns.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thankfully, the crates which you're hiding behind have all been emptied by what you assume to be Elle's previous dealings, and so none of the gang-members approach your hiding place. Continuing to film the gang as they encumber themselves with armfuls of pistols, batons, sub-machine guns, and all manner of highly-illegal Enforcer weaponry, you watch and wait until they've exited the cave, before turning the recording device off and putting it away into your inventory. Not wanting to hang around and risk the chance of Elle or the gang suddenly returning, you prepare to follow in their footsteps and head back out into the Bat Caverns...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE_LEAVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With your task complete, having obtained incriminating evidence of Elle selling Enforcer weapons to a criminal gang, you swiftly exit the cave. After quickly looking around to make sure that you're not being watched, you set off into the Bat Caverns, wondering whether you should immediately do as Wes asked and go and anonymously hand in the recorder to either Claire or Candi.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're considering what to do next, a sudden thought enters your head, and you suppose that if you really wanted to, you could seek out Elle and betray Wes's plan to her. If you were to decide to do this, you think that you could probably locate Elle leaving work outside the Enforcer HQ between [units.time(16)]-[units.time(18)].
	</p>
	<p>
		No matter what you decide upon doing with the evidence, you certainly don't want to be discovered here by the now heavily-armed gang if they were to decide to make a sudden return. Wanting to put some distance between you and the cave, you continue on your way through the Bat Caverns, wondering where to go now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CLAIRE_ELLE_EVIDENCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_ELLE_EVIDENCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you're sure that you can trust Claire with the incriminating evidence of Elle, you think that it would be best to follow Wes's instructions, and so you ask the busty cat-girl if there's any way for you to anonymously submit evidence of criminal activity. Raising her eyebrows and flashing you a curious look, the short cat-girl points over to a dark blue box on the other side of the room, saying, [claire.speech(You can deposit stuff like that in there. Is it anything I could help with?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking Claire for her offer, you tell her that it's nothing to worry about, before [pc.walking] over to the anonymous drop-box and depositing the arcane recorder in it. Her curiosity getting the better of her, the busty cat-girl skips over to where you're standing, before flashing you another curious glance and musing out loud, [claire.speech(I wonder what you're up to...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've once again told her not to worry about it, Claire flashes you a big grin and declares, [claire.speech(Oh well, I suppose I shouldn't be asking about anonymous tips anyway! So, is there anything else I can do for you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Recalling what Wes said, you make a mental note to pay him a visit up at the Enforcer HQ after at least a week has passed. Turning your attention back towards Claire, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CANDI_ELLE_EVIDENCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CANDI_ELLE_EVIDENCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to follow Wes's instructions regarding the handling of the arcane recorder's incriminating footage, you ask Candi if there's any way for you to anonymously submit evidence of criminal activity. Blankly staring at you for a moment, the bimbo cat-girl bats her eyelids and asks, [candi.speechNoEffects(Umm, you mean, like, using the blue box thing? Yeah, I think you can, like, submit anonymous tips using that, or something...)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_BUYING_BRAX) && game.getSecondsPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("candi_sex_timer")>60*60*12)
		<p>
			After pointing down at a dark blue box fixed to the front of her counter, Candi bites her lip and lets out a horny moan, before asking, [candi.speechNoEffects(Hey, like, how about you come back here and give me a different kind of anonymous tip? My pussy's, like, all wet and ready for a good fuck, y'know?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Focusing on the task at hand, you [pc.step] over to the anonymous drop-box and deposit the arcane recorder in it. Recalling what Wes said, you make a mental note to pay him a visit here at the Enforcer HQ after at least a week has passed. Finally, you turn back to face Candi wondering whether you should give her what she wants...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			After pointing down at a dark blue box fixed to the front of her counter, Candi instantly loses interest in you, and after producing a nail-file from somewhere beneath her desk, starts focusing all of her attention on giving herself a manicure. Leaving the narcissistic bimbo to focus on her nails, you [pc.step] over to the anonymous drop-box and deposit the arcane recorder in it. Recalling what Wes said, you make a mental note to pay him a visit here at the Enforcer HQ after at least a week has passed. Finally, you turn back to face the reception desk and wonder what to do next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- APPROACH_ELLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="APPROACH_ELLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to betray Wes and side with Elle, you wait outside the Enforcer HQ for the [elle.race] to leave work for the day. Choosing a shaded spot on the opposite side of the street to the imposing building which serves as the Enforcer's Dominion Headquarters, you wait and watch for any sign of her.
	</p>
	<p>
		After forty-five minutes of loitering around in this manner, you start to think that you might have missed her, or that perhaps she didn't come in to work today. Just as you're starting to wonder whether or not it would be too brazen to ask to see Elle at the HQ's front desk, you suddenly catch sight of her stepping out of the front entrance at the side of a cat-boy Enforcer.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to approach her while she's got company, you watch as Elle dominantly steps around in front of the cat-boy and starts correcting his uniform. Although the two of them are too far away to be able to hear, you can tell from their body language that Elle is heavily hitting on the cat-boy. After straightening his tie, the [elle.race] drops her hand down between the Enforcer's legs and gives his groin a firm grope.
	</p>
	<p>
		This seems to be too much for the cat-boy to handle, as he steps back and holds up his hands to try and tell Elle that she's going too far. Clearly not being one to take no for an answer, the [elle.race] steps aside to let the cat-boy pass, but as he does so, she gives his ass a firm slap and calls out after him loud enough for you to hear, [elle.speech(You're to report to my office first thing tomorrow morning! I've got a <i>thorough</i> debriefing planned for you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the cat-boy hurries past you with an apprehensive look on his face, Elle's attention is suddenly drawn to you. Quickly recognising the fact that you're no ordinary member of the public, she fixes her gleaming pink eyes onto you and waits for you to approach. Realising that you're past the point of no return, you make your move and [pc.walk] over to where Elle is waiting for you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(So, who are you?)] she bluntly asks, and you tell both from her tone of voice and from her curious gaze that she's deciding whether to treat you in a seductive or hostile manner.
	</p>
	<p>
		After simply telling her your name, Elle displays her quick-thinking by immediately responding, [elle.speech(So <i>you're</i> [pc.name]. Yes, I know about you. I read the report on the pacification of the Harpy Nests, and, if I may say so, you did a most excellent job up there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding that you're a suitable target to try and seduce, the horny Enforcer steps closer and flashes you a cheeky smile, before asking, [elle.speech(Perhaps you heard something about me from one of the Enforcers up there? Go on, tell me all the naughty things they said about me...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- APPROACH_ELLE_EXPLAIN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="APPROACH_ELLE_EXPLAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get this business with Wes finished as soon as possible, you ignore Elle's teasing and show her the arcane recorder which the fox-boy gave to you. A puzzled look flashes across the [elle.race]'s face as she sees what it is you're holding, and teases, [elle.speech(What's this? You're wanting to record us while we fuck? How kinky... Those arcane recorders aren't cheap, either...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Flipping out the screen that's built into the side of the recorder, you show Elle the footage of her selling weapons to the gang down in the cave in the Bat Caverns. Explaining to her how it was Wes that tried to get her arrested, you look up to see that there's a grim expression on Elle's face. Dropping her seductive tone as she realises how serious this is, she flatly states, [elle.speech(You've done well to bring this to my attention. How careless I was not to search the cave upon entering it... Now hand over that recorder, if you please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As this was your intention all along, you do as Elle asks and give her the arcane recorder. Immediately, she throws it to the ground, and before you have a chance to say anything, she uses her arcane power to cast a spell. Projecting a wave of crushing force down upon the helpless arcane device, Elle instantly obliterates it, sending tiny fragments of metal and plastic all over the street. Ignoring the curious looks which several members of the public cast her way, the [elle.race] looks back up at you and states, [elle.speech(I need to fix this situation before that damn fox-boy reports me. Come back after a week and ask for me at the front desk, and I'll give you a handsome reward for your loyalty.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a dark look in her eyes, Elle turns back towards the Enforcer HQ, before quickly striding across the grounds and heading inside. Finding yourself alone out in the street, you have little else to do but continue on your way, wondering what kind of reward will be given to you when you return to meet Elle next week...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- RECEPTION_DESK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_DESK_WES"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		#IF(game.isWorkTime())
			#IF(game.getMinutesPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_completion_timer")>60*24*7)
				As it's been more than a week since you anonymously handed in the evidence needed to arrest Elle, you could ask Candi to tell Wes that you're here to see him...
			#ELSE
				As it hasn't yet been more than a week since you anonymously handed in the evidence needed to arrest Elle, you shouldn't ask Candi about seeing Wes yet. [style.italicsMinorBad(You should return after [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getMinutesPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_completion_timer")>60*24*7)
				Although it's been more than a week since you anonymously handed in the evidence needed to arrest Elle, Candi is only at work from [style.colourMinorBad([units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)])], so you'll have to return during normal work hours  in order to meet Wes...
			#ELSE
				It hasn't yet been more than a week since you anonymously handed in the evidence needed to arrest Elle, and even it had been, Candi is only at work from [style.colourMinorBad([units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)])], so you'd be unable to meet Wes regardless. [style.italicsMinorBad(You should return after [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_DESK_ELLE"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		#IF(game.isWorkTime())
			#IF(game.getMinutesPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_completion_timer")>60*24*7)
				As it's been more than a week since you contacted Elle, you could tell Candi that you're here to see her...
			#ELSE
				As it hasn't yet been more than a week since you contacted Elle, you shouldn't ask Candi about seeing her yet. [style.italicsMinorBad(You should return after [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getMinutesPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_completion_timer")>60*24*7)
				Although it's been more than a week since you contacted Elle, Candi is only at work from [style.colourMinorBad([units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)])], so you'll have to return during normal work hours in order to meet her...
			#ELSE
				It hasn't yet been more than a week since you contacted Elle, and even it had been, Candi is only at work from [style.colourMinorBad([units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)])], so you'd be unable to meet her regardless. [style.italicsMinorBad(You should return after [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_WES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_WES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As it's been more than a week since you anonymously deposited the arcane recorder in the evidence drop-box, you tell Candi that you're here to meet with a fox-boy SWORD Enforcer called Wesley Wormwood. For a moment, it seems as though the bimbo cat-girl doesn't understand what you're talking about, before suddenly remembering that it's her job to help out visitors and saying, [candi.speechNoEffects(So, you're wanting me to, like, let him know you've arrived? Umm... Hold on a moment...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at the arcane intercom that's built into the top of her desk, she hovers her index finger back and forth between several buttons, speaking out loud to herself as she does so, [candi.speechNoEffects(I know that Wes is, like, at requisitions... I think it's this button that I need...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The dim-witted cat-girl presses the button that's quite clearly marked as 'Requisitions', and after letting out a low-pitched buzzing noise, the arcane intercom's speaker crackles into life, and you hear the familiar voice of Wes asking, [wes.speech(What is it now, Candi? Don't tell me that you've lost your jacket <i>again</i>...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Uh, like, that's kinda rude of you to think that, y'know? I'm actually doing my job for once, thank you very much!)] Candi drawls, [candi.speech(There's, like, [pc.a_race] here at the front desk for you. Are you, like, expecting someone called '[pc.name]'?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Yes, I am,)] Wes replies, [wes.speech(Tell [pc.herHim] to wait right there; I'm on my way.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Even though it's blatantly obvious that you were able to overhear the brief conversation, Candi feels the need to look up at you and explain, [candi.speechNoEffects(Ok, so, like, Wes was kinda rude to me just now, but he's, like, agreed to come and meet you here. You're going to have to wait for him here, y'know? You can, like, use the waiting area.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After pointing over to the collection of sofas on the other side of the room, Candi turns her attention towards the mirror that's sitting on her desk. Leaving the ditzy bimbo behind, you [pc.walk] over to the nearest sofa and wait for Wes arrive...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_WES_ARRIVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_WES_ARRIVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thankfully, you aren't kept waiting long, as less than five minutes after you've entered the waiting area, the familiar figure of Wes appears from out of the guarded door on the far side of the room. Looking around and catching sight of you, he flashes you a warm smile, before calling out, [wes.speech([pc.Name]! Come on through to my office!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding to do as Wes says, you [pc.walk] over to the fox-boy and say hello, before commenting on how smart his uniform looks. Letting out a good-natured laugh, he reveals, [wes.speech(I've been promoted to Superintendent, so I have to keep my uniform in particularly good condition to set an example to the junior ranks. Follow me on through to my new office, and I'll explain all that's happened once we get there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Motioning for the Enforcer who's guarding the inner door to step aside, Wes sets off into the back area of the Enforcer HQ with you at his side...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_WES_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_WES_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Accompanying Wes down the HQ's corridors, you wait as he unlocks an inner-door by brushing his pass over an arcane scanner mounted to the nearby wall, before following him through into the requisitions department. Leading you though a nearby door, you enter the fox-boy's office, which, while being particularly large and extravagantly furnished, seems to look a little <i>too</i> tidy, hinting at the fact that it isn't seeing much use.
	</p>
	<p>
		Sinking down into the executive leather chair positioned behind his desk, Wes lets out a deep, happy sigh and reveals, [wes.speech(Thanks to the evidence you gathered, the internal investigation of Elle all went according to my plan. By taking an active role in the investigation, I managed to secure this promotion to Superintendent which I've been chasing for years. I've received Elle's old title of Senior Quartermaster, and, speaking of her, she ended up being enslaved and given to me as a bonus. Not that I particularly wanted to own her, mind you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Congratulating Wes on his promotion, you comment on the fact that his office looks as though it hasn't seen much use yet. Letting out a short sigh and standing up from behind his desk, he continues, [wes.speech(This is actually only the third or fourth time I've used this office. In an attempt at avoiding a repeat of Elle's siphoning off of equipment, the higher-ups have ordered me to make more regular reports on the inventory's status, which means I'm having to spend all of my time doing my old job of working at the requisitions desk...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving over to the door of his office, the fox-boy sighs, [wes.speech(Speaking of which, I need to get back over there as soon as possible. I've got Elle stationed in there to help me do the work, but I can't trust her to be alone for too long. She might technically be my slave, but she's as free-spirited as ever...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Opening the door and beckoning you to once again follow him, he reveals, [wes.speech(As a way of thanking you for your help, I've arranged for you to be granted a contractor's pass, so you'll not only be granted access to the requisitions area, but I'll also able to sell you surplus Enforcer equipment. Come on, I've got the pass waiting for you over there.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_WES_REQUISITIONS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_WES_REQUISITIONS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Wes out of his office, you accompany him as he walks over to the other side of the corridor and strides through the pair of propped-open doors which lead into the station's requisitions area. Consisting of a large, empty room, the only points of interest in this area are the couple of bare metal tables pushed into each corner, as well as the locked door and waist-high counter set into the wall before you. Telling you to remain here, Wes opens the door, before stepping around to the other side of the counter and starting to rummage around in some of the drawers.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Elle?! What have you done with that contractor pass I told you to put in here?!)] he calls out.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Oh, I didn't realise you were back!)] the familiar voice of Elle replies from somewhere within the maze of shelving units which fill the vast storage area behind the counter. A moment later, the [elle.race] steps into view, and you see that while she looks just as she did the last time you saw her, she's now wearing a metal slave collar and slutty fancy-dress Enforcer uniform. Catching sight of you waiting behind the counter, the horny slave remarks, [elle.speech(What's this, Wes? You've finally brought me someone to fuck other than you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Just tell me where the pass is, Elle,)] the fox-boy sighs in frustration.
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning down and pressing her huge breasts against the back of Wes's head, Elle pulls open the top drawer and sighs, [elle.speech(I told you that I'd put it in here...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Retrieving what looks like a plastic id card attached to a blue lanyard, Wes hands this pass over to you, saying, [wes.speech(This will unlock the doors to this area, and if you show it to an Enforcer patrol, they won't try and confiscate any of the gear you purchase from me here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Noticing your curious glance as you look at Elle's fancy-dress Enforcer uniform, the fox-boy sheepishly admits, [wes.speech(I couldn't have her walking around naked, could I? It felt wrong to have her wearing a real uniform as well, and besides, having her wear that is all part of her punishment.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(You liar,)] Elle teases, leaning into Wes's back and reaching down to stroke his groin. Ignoring the fox-boy's protestations, she looks up at you and says, [elle.speech(He makes me wear this because it turns him on, and he likes reminding me of my place while I'm choking down his yummy, fat knot.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Not now, Elle!)] Wes snaps as he tries, and fails, to push the horny half-demon off of him. Giving up and choosing to simply ignore Elle's sexual harassment, Wes turns his attention back towards you and says, [wes.speech(You can buy gear from me here at any time during my working hours, which are from nine to five. If you'd like to do me a favour again, you could try and help me to calm Elle's libido by taking her over to my office and spending some time with her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As Elle continues trying to get into Wes's pants, you wonder what you should do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_ELLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_ELLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As it's been more than a week since you contacted Elle, you tell Candi that you're here to meet with [elle.a_race] SWORD Enforcer called [elle.name] [elle.surname]. For a moment, it seems as though the bimbo cat-girl doesn't understand what you're talking about, before suddenly remembering that it's her job to help out visitors and saying, [candi.speechNoEffects(So, you're wanting me to, like, let her know you've arrived? Umm... Hold on a moment...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at the arcane intercom that's built into the top of her desk, she hovers her index finger back and forth between several buttons, speaking out loud to herself as she does so, [candi.speechNoEffects(I know that Elle is, like, at requisitions... I think it's this button that I need...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The dim-witted cat-girl presses the button that's quite clearly marked as 'Requisitions', and after letting out a low-pitched buzzing noise, the arcane intercom's speaker crackles into life, and you hear the familiar voice of Elle asking, [elle.speech(What can I help you with, Candi? Don't tell me that you've lost your jacket <i>again</i>...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Uh, like, that's kinda rude of you to think that, y'know? I'm actually doing my job for once, thank you very much!)] Candi drawls, [candi.speech(There's, like, [pc.a_race] here at the front desk for you. Are you, like, expecting someone called '[pc.name]'?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(As a matter of fact, I am,)] Elle replies, [elle.speech(Be a dear and tell [pc.herHim] to wait right there; I'm on my way.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Even though it's blatantly obvious that you were able to overhear the brief conversation, Candi feels the need to look up at you and explain, [candi.speechNoEffects(Ok, so, like, Elle was kinda rude to me just now, but she's, like, agreed to come and meet you here. You're going to have to wait for her here, y'know? You can, like, use the waiting area.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After pointing over to the collection of sofas on the other side of the room, Candi turns her attention towards the mirror that's sitting on her desk. Leaving the ditzy bimbo behind, you [pc.walk] over to the nearest sofa and wait for Elle arrive...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_ELLE_ARRIVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_ELLE_ARRIVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thankfully, you aren't kept waiting long, as less than five minutes after you've entered the waiting area, the familiar figure of Elle appears from out of the guarded door on the far side of the room. Looking around and catching sight of you, she flashes you a cheeky grin, before beckoning you forwards and calling out, [elle.speech(Please, come right this way!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding to do as Elle says, you [pc.walk] over to the [elle.race] and offer her your greetings. Stepping forwards so as to playfully brush up against you, the horny Enforcer reveals, [elle.speech(I've got a lot to thank you for, [pc.name]. Please do follow me on through to my office, and I'll explain all that's happened once we get there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Motioning for the Enforcer who's guarding the inner door to step aside, Elle sets off into the back area of the Enforcer HQ with you at her side...
	</p>
	
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_ELLE_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_ELLE_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Accompanying Elle down the HQ's corridors, you wait as she unlocks an inner-door by brushing her pass over an arcane scanner mounted to the nearby wall, before following her through into the requisitions department. Leading you though a nearby door, you enter the [elle.race]'s office, which turns out to be particularly large and extravagantly furnished.
	</p>
	<p>
		Sitting down on the executive leather chair positioned behind her desk, Elle lets out a happy little sigh and reveals, [elle.speech(Thanks to your tip-off, I took a chance on going to my superiors and placing all of the blame for the missing stock on Wes. Thankfully, everything couldn't have gone smoother, and the poor little fox-boy ended up being enslaved and given to me as a bonus. I'd always considered him to be a little odd, and so wasn't too keen on owning him, but he's turned out to be a great help.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Standing up from behind her desk, she explains, [elle.speech(In an attempt at avoiding a repeat of 'Wes's' siphoning off of equipment, the higher-ups have ordered me to make more regular reports on the inventory's status, which means I'm having to spend all of my time working at the requisitions desk. Thankfully, my little fox-boy slave knows just how to get things done in there, and what's more, he's surprisingly good at keeping me satisfied...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving over to the door of his office, the [elle.race] lets out a soft laugh and runs her hand over your [pc.arm], before teasing, [elle.speech(Perhaps we can talk more about the ways in which I can be satisfied later...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Opening the door and beckoning you to once again follow her, Elle reveals, [elle.speech(As a way of thanking you for your help, I've arranged for you to be granted a contractor's pass, so you'll not only be granted access to the requisitions area, but I'll also able to sell you surplus Enforcer equipment. Come on, I've got the pass waiting for you over there.)]
	
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_ELLE_REQUISITIONS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_ELLE_REQUISITIONS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Elle out of her office, you accompany her as she walks over to the other side of the corridor and strides through the pair of propped-open doors which lead into the station's requisitions area. Consisting of a large, empty room, the only points of interest in this area are the couple of bare metal tables pushed into each corner, as well as the locked door and waist-high counter set into the wall before you. Telling you to remain here, Elle opens the door, before stepping around to the other side of the counter and starting to rummage around in some of the drawers.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Wes, my darling? What have you done with that contractor pass I told you put away?)] she calls out in a flirty, high-pitched tone.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(I told you that I'd put it in the top drawer!)] the familiar voice of Wes calls out from somewhere within the maze of shelving units which fill the vast storage area behind the counter. A moment later, the fox-boy steps into view, and you see that while he looks just as he did the last time you saw him, he's now wearing nothing but a metal slave collar and a pair of black boxers. Catching sight of you waiting behind the counter, Wes flashes you a furious look, before angrily asking, [wes.speech(So, are you happy with what you've done? This criminal keeps her job, and I'm the one who got punished for her crimes!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Now, now, Wes,)] Elle tuts, before stepping over to her slave and fondly pulling him into her ample cleavage. Lovingly stroking the top of his head, she teases, [elle.speech(Being my slave isn't so bad, is it? I can't imagine that many slaves get to have their cocks sucked by their Mistresses all the time... Look, if you're really upset, I'll let you use my pussy tonight. You liked that little 'defeated Elle' roleplay we tried the other night, didn't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly getting extremely embarrassed about Elle saying all of this right in front of you, the fox-boy pushes his owner off of him, before storming over to the counter and retrieving the contractor pass from out of the top drawer. Throwing it over to Elle, he huffs, [wes.speech(I've still got three boxes of assorted uniforms left to catalogue and store away. If there's nothing else you need from me, then I'm getting back to work.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Once I've finished my business with [pc.name] here, I'll come and join you,)] Elle teases, before turning her attention back to you. Handing you the contractor pass, which turns out to be a plastic id card attached to a pink lanyard, Elle says, [elle.speech(This will unlock the doors to this area, and if you show it to an Enforcer patrol, they won't try and confiscate any of the gear you purchase from me here. You can buy gear from me here at any time during my working hours, which are from nine to five. Of course, if you wanted to just chat, or perhaps have a little fun in my office, then I'll always be happy to see you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As Elle flashes you a seductive smile, you wonder what you should do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Post-quest dialogues: -->
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_POST_QUEST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Connected to the adjoining corridor by a pair of wide, propped-open doors, the requisitions area is the place where specialist or replacement equipment can be checked out by the HQ's Enforcers. [pc.Stepping] through the open doors into this area, you find yourself standing in a relatively small room, which, other than a couple of basic metal tables pushed up against one wall, is devoid of any furniture. The only other point of interest is the counter on the far side of the room, which currently appears to be unmanned.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
			Continuing to move forwards into the room, you look past the counter to see a huge storage area filled with all sorts of weapons and protective equipment. Down at the end of one of the aisles formed by the well-stocked shelving units, you see the familiar figure of Elle pinning Wes back against the wall. She's slipped her hand down the fox-boy's boxers, and from the rapid movements of her arm, it's quite obvious that she's giving him a handjob.
		#ELSE
			Continuing to move forwards into the room, you look past the counter to see a huge storage area filled with all sorts of weapons and protective equipment. Down at the end of one of the aisles formed by the well-stocked shelving units, you see the familiar figure of Elle forcing herself on Wes and pinning him back against the wall. She's slipped her hand down the fox-boy's trousers, and from the rapid movements of her arm, it's quite obvious that she's giving him a handjob.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder whether you should ring the bell on the desk's counter to get their attention, or turn around and leave them to it...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_TRADE_DIALOGUE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
		<p>
			Telling Elle that you'd like to buy some Enforcer equipment, you wait as she rummages around in a nearby drawer for a moment, before producing a list of available equipment and placing it down on the counter-top in front of you. Leaning forwards over the counter-top and flashing you a seductive look, she reveals, [npc.speech(Here's what I can sell to you without causing any trouble...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking down at the list, you wonder whether you should buy anything...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Telling Wes that you'd like to buy some Enforcer equipment, you wait as he rummages around in a nearby drawer for a moment, before producing a list of available equipment and placing it down on the counter-top in front of you. Pushing Elle off of him, he lets out a sigh and reveals, [npc.speech(Here's what I can sell to you without causing any trouble...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking down at the list while Elle continues to sexually harass Wes, you wonder whether you should buy anything...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_INTERACTION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_INTERACTION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Elle, you ring the counter's bell, causing her to look over towards the counter and see you standing there. Turning back to whisper something into Wes's ear, she slides her hand out from the fox-boy's boxers, before giving his groin a firm squeeze and then turning to walk over towards you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Stepping up to the counter, the [elle.race] puts on her most seductive look, before teasing, [elle.speech(You caught me in the middle of disciplining my slave... So, what can I do for you thins time, [pc.name]?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Wes, you ring the counter's bell, causing both him and Elle to look over towards the counter and see you standing there. Turning back to whisper something into Wes's ear, Elle slides her hand out from the fox-boy's trousers, before giving his groin a firm squeeze and then stepping back to let Wes walk over towards you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly being a little flustered from the attention Elle was giving to him, the Wes clears his throat and takes a deep breath, before flashing you a warm smile and asking, [wes.speech(What can I do for you today, [pc.name]? Sorry that you had to catch me like that, Elle was just-)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Giving you a quickie,)] the [elle.race] teases, cutting off Wes's sentence as she steps up behind him and lewdly presses her huge breasts into his back. Ignoring Wes's firm request for her to step back, Elle leans in over his shoulder and teases, [elle.speech(Don't worry, babe, I'll finish you off with my mouth once you've dealt with [pc.name].)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a frustrated huff, Wes does his best to ignore Elle's hand as it creeps back down towards his groin, and once again asks, [wes.speech(So, [pc.name], what can I help you with?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_INTERACTION_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
		<p>
			Having got what you wanted from Elle, you tell her that you need to be getting on your way, before saying goodbye and heading towards the exit. As you leave the requisitions area, you take one last look back to see the horny [elle.race] rapidly advancing on Wes and reaching towards his groin...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having got what you wanted from Wes, you tell him that you need to be getting on your way, before saying goodbye and heading towards the exit. As you leave the requisitions area, you take one last look back to see Elle sinking down to her knees in front of the fox-boy and hungrily reaching up towards his groin...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
		<p>
			You ask Elle about her background. (She heavily flirts with the player throughout this scene.)
		</p>
		<p>
			TODO: Display 1 of at least 5 different background scenes. Revealing more about Elle's history with each interaction. (After all 5 have been seen, display repeat variations on each at random.)
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			You ask Wes about his background.
		</p>
		<p>
			TODO: Display 1 of at least 5 different background scenes. Revealing more about Wes's history with each interaction. (After all 5 have been seen, display repeat variations on each at random.)
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_WORK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
		<p>
			You ask Elle about how work is going. (She heavily flirts with the player throughout this scene.)
		</p>
		<p>
			TODO: Display 1 of at least 10 small work dialogue variations. Overall giving the picture of a lot of work to do, and how Wes is handling most of the tedious/physical work. She doesn't get as much done as is expected of her due to the fact that she keeps on sexually harassing Wes.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			You ask Wes about how work is going.
		</p>
		<p>
			TODO: Display 1 of at least 10 small work dialogue variations. Overall giving the picture of a lot of work to do, and how Elle is not much use. He finds learning curve of being master of both the borough's equipment and Elle to be steep and it's taking a toll on on him.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You flirt back with Elle, and she is soon taking things very far.
	</p>
	<p>
		She comes around to the other side of the counter and gets physical with you, before breathlessly suggesting that she gives you a very personal tour of her office...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_DECLINED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You turn down Elle's offer. She is visibly annoyed, and returns to the other side of her desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		Quickly re-assuming her flirty temperament, she asks you if there's anything else you wanted.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You agree to go to Elle's office with her. She tells Wes to watch the place while she's gone.
	</p>
	<p>
		You head into her office. She locks the door behind you and instantly is all over you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_SEX_START_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking charge, you dominantly kiss Elle before telling her that you're going to give her a good fucking.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_SEX_START_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting Elle take charge, you allow her to dominantly kiss you, before she tells you that she's going to add you to her long list of successful sexual conquests. (If already had sex with her, she says something else.)
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_END_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_END_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		If satisfied, Elle is flirty and teases you a little as you both get your things back in order. If not satisfied, she is clearly frustrated, and says she'll get Wes to finish her off.
	</p>
	<p>
		The two of you exit her office, and she heads into the requisitions area, leaving you to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_THREESOME -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You suggest to Elle taht she bring Wes along for the tour. She likes the idea, and tells the fox-boy to join you. Hangs a 'be back soon' sign on the door to the requisitions area.
	</p>
	<p>
		You, Elle, and Wes head into the office. Elle locks the door behind you and instantly is all over you and Wes...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You take charge and tell Wes and Elle that you're going to fuck them...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_JOINT_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You join Elle in taking charge and tell Wes that the two of you are going to fuck him...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_JOINT_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You join Wes in submitting to Elle...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You submit to both Elle and Wes...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_THREESOME_WES_REVENGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You lead Elle into joining you in submitting to Wes...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_END_SEX_THREESOME -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_END_SEX_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		If satisfied, Elle is flirty and teases you a little as the three of you get your things back in order. If not satisfied, she is clearly frustrated, and says to Wes that he's going to finish her off back in the requisitions area.
	</p>
	<p>
		The three of you exit her office, and Elle and Wes head back into the requisitions area, leaving you to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_WES_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_WES_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You ask Elle if you can spend some time with Wes. She agrees and tells you to use her office.
	</p>
	<p>
		You take Wes into Elle's office. All of Elle's flirting and sexual harassment has got Wes worked up, and although he quite clearly hates you for betraying him (vary based on his affection), he seems eager enough to have sex...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_WES_OFFICE_START_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You take charge and prepare to fuck Wes....
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_WES_OFFICE_START_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You let Wes take charge and prepare to be fucked by him....
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_END_SEX_WES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_END_SEX_WES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		If satisfied, Wes is happy enough as the two of you get your things back in order. If not satisfied, he is clearly frustrated, and says that Elle will no doubt enjoy finishing him off back in the requisitions area.
	</p>
	<p>
		You exit Elle's office, and Wes heads back into the requisitions area, leaving you to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You flirt with Wes. From all of Elle's teasing and sexual harassment, he seems quite horny.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a short while of making suggestive remarks to him (with an envious Elle in the background?), you think that you could suggest taking things a step further...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_FINISH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_FINISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You decide not to take things any further, and stop flirting with Wes.
	</p>
	<p>
		The fox-boy asks if he can help you with anything.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You suggest to Wes that he should take a break from work by giving you a tour of his office. He agrees, and tells Elle to watch the place while he's gone.
	</p>
	<p>
		You head into Wes's office. He locks the door behind you and instantly is all over you... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_SEX_START_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You take charge and start having sex with Wes...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_SEX_START_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You let Wes take charge and start having sex with him...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_END_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_END_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		If satisfied, Wes is in good spirits and teases you a little as you both get your things back in order. If not satisfied, he is clearly frustrated, and says he'll have to let Elle finish him off.
	</p>
	<p>
		The two of you exit his office, and he heads into the requisitions area, leaving you to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You suggest to Wes that he should take a break from work by giving you a tour of his office, and to bring Elle along. He agrees, and tells Elle to join you. Hangs a 'be back soon' sign on the door to the requisitions area.
	</p>
	<p>
		You, Elle, and Wes head into the office. Wes locks the door behind you and instantly is all over you and Elle...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You take charge and tell Elle and Wes that you're going to fuck them...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_JOINT_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You join Wes in taking charge and dominantly fuck Elle...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_JOINT_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You join Elle in submitting to Wes and get dominantly fucked by him...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You submit to both Wes and Elle, who both seem more than happy to dominantly fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME_ELLE_REVENGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You convince Wes to join you in submitting to Elle, who seems very happy to be given a chance to get some dominant revenge (or is she just the big horny?) on the two of you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_END_SEX_THREESOME -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_END_SEX_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		If satisfied, Wes is in good spirits and teases you a little as the three of you get your things back in order. If not satisfied, he is clearly frustrated, and says to Elle that she can finish him off back in the requisitions area.
	</p>
	<p>
		The three of you exit the office, and Elle and Wes head back into the requisitions area, leaving you to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_ELLE_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_ELLE_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You ask Wes if you can spend some time with Elle. He is more than happy to be given some relief from the [elle.race]'s constant sexual harassment, and tells you to take her to his office.
	</p>
	<p>
		You take Elle into Wes's office. She doesn't seem too bitter about the fact that you're the cause of her being enslaved, and is very quickly all over you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_ELLE_OFFICE_START_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You take charge and dominantly fuck Elle...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_ELLE_OFFICE_START_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You submit to Elle and let her dominantly fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_END_SEX_ELLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_END_SEX_ELLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		If satisfied, Elle is flirty and teases you a little as you both get your things back in order. If not satisfied, she is clearly frustrated, and says she'll get Wes to finish her off.
	</p>
	<p>
		The two of you exit Wes's office, and Elle heads into the requisitions area, leaving you to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
