<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- WES_QUEST_START -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.isDayTime())
			Although the sun has already set this evening, there are still plenty of people out and about,
		#ELSE
			As you make your way down yet another of Dominion's streets, you can't help but notice how many people are out and about this evening,
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_DEMON)
			 and while they hurry to get out of your way when they see that you're a demon, you still end up having to weave your way around some of the larger of the crowds.
		#ELSE
			 and you have to adjust your path every now and again so as to weave your way around the crowds.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_OBSERVANT))
			 As you're passing a slow-moving group of obnoxiously-loud revellers, you suddenly notice that an orange-furred, greater fox-boy, dressed in a grey hoodie and blue jeans, keeps on glancing your way from over on the other side of the street. Although his gaze is hidden behind a pair of dark glasses, you can tell that he's got some kind of particular interest in you. As your path around the crowd brings you closer to where he's standing, you see the fox-boy suddenly begin to move towards you, and as he sees that you've noticed his approach, he smiles and asks, [wes.speech(If I'm not mistaken, then you're [pc.name], right?)]
		#ELSE
			 As you're passing a slow-moving group of obnoxiously-loud revellers, you suddenly see that an orange-furred, greater fox-boy, dressed in a grey hoodie and blue jeans, is rapidly moving towards you. Although his gaze is hidden behind a pair of dark glasses, you can tell that he's got some kind of particular interest in you, and before you can react to his approach, he smiles and asks, [wes.speech(If I'm not mistaken, then you're [pc.name], right?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		The warm, friendly tone of this mysterious character's voice is not quite what you were expecting, and from his subtle country accent, you get the strong impression that he's not a native city-dweller. Despite his endearing manner of speech, you detect a sense of urgency in this middle-aged fox-boy's question, and so, seeing no harm in answering him, you quickly reply that you are indeed [pc.name].
	</p>
	<p>
		Retrieving a very official-looking SWORD Enforcer badge from out of his hoodie's pocket, this stranger flashes it at you and reveals, [wes.speech(I know that you're the one who dealt with that sticky situation up in the Harpy Nests, which is why I've come to you for help. I can't talk for too long out in the streets like this, but if you want to help the Enforcers again, then-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Suddenly getting spooked by the sight of something further down the street, the fox-boy interrupts his hasty explanation to ask, [wes.speech(Please, meet me outside the antiques shop in the Shopping Arcade between one and two in the afternoon. I'll be there every day, but it would be best if you were there tomorrow. Look, I have to go. Meet me there, ok?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_AGREE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to do as the fox-boy asks, you agree to meet him at the location and time he's given to you. Letting out a short sigh of relief, he flashes you a warm smile and declares, [wes.speech(I was right to seek your help. I'll see you soon!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hastily striding over to the other side of the street, the fox-boy quickly blends in to one of the crowds that are passing by, and before you know it, you've lost track of him entirely. With nothing else to do here, you set off and continue on your way, wondering what that mysterious SWORD Enforcer could want to discuss with you...
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsMinorGood(The Enforcer will be in the Shopping Arcade, outside of the antiques shop, between [units.time(13)]-[units.time(14)] every day.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_QUESTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know more about what this fox-boy wants before agreeing to meet with him, you ask him what sort of help he's expecting you to give. Sharply exhaling in frustration, he once again glances around and declares, [wes.speech(I don't have time to explain here. Please, just meet me tomorrow and I'll explain everything. I hope to see you soon!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Offering you no further opportunity in which to ask him further questions, the fox-boy hastily strides over to the other side of the street, before quickly blending in to one of the crowds that are passing by. Before you know it, you've lost track of him entirely, and so with nothing else to do, you set off and continue on your way, wondering what that mysterious SWORD Enforcer could want to discuss with you...
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsMinorGood(The Enforcer will be in the Shopping Arcade, outside of the antiques shop, between [units.time(13)]-[units.time(14)] every day.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_wesQuestRefused))
		<p>
			Wanting to talk with Wes again, you decide to wait here outside of the antiques shop in the hopes that you'll be able to meet with him. Just like the last time you did this, the fox-boy doesn't show up for a good five minutes, but eventually you see him walking towards you from the same direction as which you arrived.
		</p>
		<p>
			Wearing the same blue jeans and grey hoodie that he was wearing the last time you saw him, the fox-boy steps up to you and asks in a friendly tone, [wes.speech(So, you decided to come back? Have you had a change of mind about helping me?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Still not entirely convinced that you want to help Wes, you ask him once again what exactly it is that he wants you to do. Taking off his dark glasses to once again reveal his bright green eyes, the fox-boy explains, [wes.speech(I'm convinced that my superior officer, Elle, is doing some shady dealings during her long Wednesday lunch breaks. I need you to find out where she's going, and then to collect evidence of her illegal activities. I can't go myself as I have no time in which to follow her, and I can't report this for an internal investigation without solid evidence of Elle's wrongdoing. Please, I need your help.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having been reminded of what it is that Wes wants you to do, you wonder whether to agree to help him, or once again refuse...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to find out more about the mysterious Enforcer who approached you in Dominion's streets, you decide to wait here outside of the antiques shop in the hopes that you'll be able to meet with him again. Unfortunately, despite being in the correct place, at the correct time, you don't see any sign of the fox-boy, and after five minutes spent waiting for him to show up, you start to wonder whether it would be a good idea to come back and try again tomorrow.
		</p>
		<p>
			Just as you're thinking of leaving, however, you suddenly spot the mysterious Enforcer walking towards you from the same direction as which you arrived. Wearing the same blue jeans and grey hoodie that he was wearing the last time you saw him, the fox-boy steps up to you and says in a friendly tone, [wes.speech(Thanks for meeting me here, [pc.name]. Sorry that I left you waiting for a while; I had to make sure that you weren't being followed.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Taking off his dark glasses, the orange-furred fox-boy reveals a pair of bright green eyes, which, unlike the usual shiftiness foxes are stereotyped for, project a disarming, folksy naiveté which perfectly matches his soft county accent. Smiling at you, he finally reveals who he is by saying, [wes.speech(My name's Wesley Wormwood, but everyone just calls me Wes for short. As you've already seen from my badge, I'm one of SWORD's Chief Inspectors, and I work over at the main HQ as a Junior Quartermaster. Sorry for not introducing myself to you earlier, but I was a little pressed for time. The reason I wanted to meet with you is to ask for your help in the investigation of my superior officer.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pausing for a moment, the fox-boy gives you an opportunity in which to respond to what he's just said...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_QUESTION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_QUESTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know more, and thinking that it would be best to start at the beginning, you ask Wes what exactly his superior officer is doing which would warrant them being investigated. After quickly glancing around to make sure that nobody's eavesdropping, the fox-boy explains, [wes.speech(The officer I'm talking about is '[elle.name] [elle.surname]', but everyone just calls her 'Elle'; she's the Senior Quartermaster over at Enforcer HQ. Me and her are the only two who have access to the station's inventory, and I've noticed over the past few weeks that equipment has started to go missing. It started with the odd pistol or a couple of batons, but just two days ago I discovered that even several of the cryoprism guns now only exist on paper. It <i>has</i> to be her who's taking them.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So you want me to find out what she's doing with them?)] you ask, picking up on where Wes is going with his explanation.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(That's right. I'd try to investigate all of this myself, but the problem is that Elle teleports out of her office every Wednesday lunch time, and there's no way for me to follow her. I'm convinced that that's when she's selling these weapons to criminal gangs, but there's nothing I can do to stop her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Why not have this investigated internally?)] you ask, wondering why Wes has sought out your help instead of reporting this to his superiors.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Elle's a half-demon, so internal investigations always get really messy when one of them is involved. Besides, if she were tipped off that she was being investigated, she'd no doubt set me up as the guilty party, and who do you think's going to be believed? Some fox from the sticks, or his half-demon superior officer, who, I'm told, is the child of a direct daughter of Lunette herself?)] Wes sighs, pausing for a moment to collect his thoughts before continuing, [wes.speech(After I heard of your work up in the Harpy Nests, I was hoping that I could ask for your help with all of this...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to hear exactly what it is that Wes is wanting of you before deciding whether to help him or not, you ask the fox-boy what his plan is.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(I'll need you to gather incriminating evidence of Elle selling Enforcer weapons to criminals,)] he states, before producing what looks to be some kind of miniature video recorder from out of his hoodie's spacious front pocket and explaining, [wes.speech(I've requisitioned this arcane recording device, so all you need to do is find out where Elle's teleporting off to, and then to use this to record evidence of her illegal activities.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With one final question left on your mind, you ask Wes how you're supposed to find Elle. After all, if she's teleporting off to somewhere, it could be literally anywhere in all of Lilith's Realm.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(That's going to be the hard part in all of this,)] the fox-boy sighs, [wes.speech(All I can tell you is that she conducts this illegal business during her long lunch breaks every Wednesday, and that she takes a pair of night vision goggles with her. When she returns, her shoes are often wet and sometimes have trace amounts of some kind of glowing residue on them...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having now heard all of the information Wes has to offer you, you wonder whether you should agree to help him by tracking down Elle and collecting evidence of her criminal activities, or tell the fox-boy that you're not interested in getting tangled up in his mess. As you're wondering what to say, Wes holds out the arcane recorder and asks, [wes.speech(Please, [pc.name], can you help me with this? If all goes according to plan, I'll be able to arrange a decent reward for you.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_FAIL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_FAIL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you're certain that you can trust Wes to be telling the truth about the situation with Elle's criminal activities, you really don't like the idea of getting tangled up in the Enforcer's internal affairs. Telling the fox-boy that you're unwilling to do as he asks, you [pc.step] back from him and prepare to leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Well, I don't blame you; it seems to be the common attitude in this city for everyone to look out for themselves and never stick their neck out to help anyone,)] he cynically remarks, before putting the arcane recorder back in his hoodie's pocket and letting out a deep sigh. Putting his dark glasses back on, he turns and starts to walk off into the Shopping Arcade, calling after him as he goes, [wes.speech(If you change your mind, I'll be here at the same time tomorrow...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Wes walks off, leaving you with little else to do except continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_QUESTION_END -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_QUEST_SHOPPING_ARCADE_MEETING_QUESTION_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling Wes that you'll do as he asks, you take the arcane recorder from him and listen as he instructs you on how to operate it. The device seems simple enough to use, and after you've told the fox-boy that you're confident in your ability at using it, he smiles and says, [wes.speech(Right, once you've tracked down Elle and recorded her illegal activities, you'll need to deposit this recorder in one of our anonymous evidence drop-boxes. Just ask that bimbo at the HQ's front desk where it is, or if you're down in Submission, then all of the Enforcer posts down there have one. After handing the evidence in, wait at least one week for the internal investigation to conclude, and then go back to the HQ's front desk and ask to see me. I'll have a reward for you then.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling Wes that you understand what to do, you watch as he puts his dark glasses back on and flashes you another of his warm smiles. Letting out a happy little chuckle, he says, [wes.speech(I guess not everyone in this city is as selfish as I thought. Thanks for agreeing to help, [pc.name]. Remember, don't come looking for me until at least a week after you've handed in the evidence. Oh, and don't mention any of this to any other Enforcers; they may mean well, but if word of this gets out, you'll be dropping me in pretty hot water...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Wes walks off, leaving you to put the arcane recording device away and wonder to yourself where Elle could be conducting her illegal business. Thinking back on what Wes told you, the main points were:
		<i>
		<br/>She takes [style.colourOrange(unusually long lunch breaks)].
		<br/>She only does this on a [style.colourOrange(Wednesday)].
		<br/>She takes a set of [style.colourOrange(night vision goggles)] with her.
		<br/>Afterwards, her [style.colourOrange(shoes are often wet)] and sometimes have trace amounts of some kind of [style.colourOrange(glowing residue on them)].
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Thinking back on those points, you feel confident that you can figure out where Elle is going, but if not, you realise that you could always go to Lilaya and ask for her help. With that comforting thought in mind, you set off and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_SEARCH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_SEARCH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having figured out that Elle must be conducting her illegal activities in the Bat Caverns, and with it currently being the correct day and time in which to find her down here, you start searching for any clue as to her whereabouts. With these caves being as vast and as dark as they are, you don't hold out much hope of finding Elle on your first try, but by a stroke of particular good fortune, you quickly stumble upon evidence of what appears to be the trail of heavy crates having been dragged through a patch of luminescent fungi.
	</p>
	<p>
		Following this trail down several twists and turns in the maze-like network of caves, you soon find yourself [pc.stepping] out into an underground forest of huge, bioluminescent mushrooms. The carpet of glowing fungi which covers the ground before you has been heavily trodden-down in places, allowing you to continue following the path of whoever has travelled this way before you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the trail for just a little further, you discover that it leads to a small cave, the entrance to which is almost completely concealed by an abnormally-thick patch of tree-like mushrooms. Concerned that Elle might already be inside, you proceed towards the entrance of this cave with caution, but thankfully, as you peer around one of the mushroom's thick trunks, you see that the interior appears to be completely deserted...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Making sure to keep a sharp lookout for any sign of Elle, you squeeze your way around the huge mushrooms which conceal the cave's entrance, before [pc.stepping] inside and starting to take a look around. Immediately, you see that this is definitely the place which you're looking for, as there are numerous piles of both locked and empty crates stacked up against the cave's walls, with more than a couple of them displaying signs of crudely scraped-off SWORD insignias.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you approach these crates to take a closer look, you suddenly hear the sound of feminine, flirty laughter coming from somewhere outside of the cave. Stopping dead in your tracks, you listen as this laughter suddenly cuts off, only to be quickly followed by a slovenly male voice asking, [style.speechMasculineHeavy('Ow much fuckin' further 'ave we gots ta go?! You's better not be settin' us up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Oh, please,)] the flirty voice of the woman replies, [elle.speech(If I wanted to set you up, you'd all be under arrest by now! As it so happens, the weapons I promised you are right inside that cave. Please follow me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that these people intend to enter the cave which you're currently occupying, you quickly look around for a place in which to hide and secretly record evidence of Elle's criminal activity. Thankfully, an empty space behind a particularly large stack of empty crates provides the perfect place in which to conceal yourself, and you manage to duck down into this recess just in time before Elle and several thuggish gang members enter the cave.
	</p>
	<p>
		Peering through a slender gap in the crates, you're able to get a good look of Elle, who turns out to be a greater [elle.race] who looks to be in her early forties. As is the case for most people with demonic blood, Elle's brown-furred anthropomorphic horse-like face is stunningly beautiful, and there's an energetic, excited look in her [elle.eyeColour] demonic eyes. Her SWORD uniform conceals most of her fit body, but you can still quite clearly see that she's got a huge pair of [elle.cupSize]-cup breasts, as well as wide, womanly hips and a large ass.
	</p>
	<p>
		As she turns to one side to beckon the gang members into the cave, you're able to see that Elle's horse-like tail is the same sandy blonde colour as her hair, which is tied up into a smart bun. Growing from her shoulder-blades, you see that she has a pair of large, lilac-skinned demonic wings, while a long, indigo unicorn horn grows from her upper forehead. Having taken a good look at Elle's appearance, you turn your attention to the group of rat, alligator, and dog-morph gang-members who are roughly pushing their way past the mushrooms and into the cave.
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking out the arcane recorder which Wes gave to you, you point the lens through the gap in the crates and start filming the scene in front of you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE_RECORDING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE_RECORDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With your arcane recorder capturing video and audio footage of all that's happening in the cave, you watch as the rough-looking dog-boy leader of the gang-members steps up to the nearest crate and demands, [style.speechMasculineHeavy(Show us wot ya got then! You's ain't gettin' no flames from me until I sees that you's got the goods ya promised to us!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Teasing the dog-boy by brushing her hand over his arm, Elle laughs, [elle.speech(My, my, you are impatient, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Grunting in amusement at the Enforcer's flirty attitude, the dog-boy hungrily watches as Elle turns her back on him and bends down at the waist to unlock the crate he pointed to. Stepping aside to let the gang-members take a look inside, Elle teases, [elle.speech(Go on then, boys, choose whatever you like! My prices are most reasonable, I can assure you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing weakness in Elle's attitude, one of the rat-boy gang-members pulls a pistol out of the crate, before brazenly waving it at the Enforcer and sneering, [style.speechMasculine('O said anythin' about us payin' fer this? Heh-heh-heh! Now we's got the guns, 'o's ta stop us from 'avin' a little fun with you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Instantly, Elle drops her flirty, light-hearted act, but while her face takes on a grim expression, you can't help but notice the way her eyes light up at the prospect of trouble. Exhibiting an alarming display of speed, the Enforcer darts forwards, and after effortlessly knocking the pistol out of the rat-boy's hands, she grabs hold of him by the neck and violently slams him down onto the floor. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculineHeavy(Woah, woah, woah! We ain't wantin' no trouble!)] the leader of the gang nervously shouts, [style.speechMasculineHeavy('E was only jokin' 'bout not payin'! Look, I's got the flames 'ere, 'ow much do ya-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(I don't give a damn about your money,)] Elle snaps, cutting the gang-member off. Advancing towards him with her wings unfurled, she reveals, [elle.speech(I'm not doing this to get rich! You scum are too soft; do you know how boring it is to be an Enforcer these days?! Oh, what I'd give to go back to the crime waves of the late 70's, or for the Fifth Human Rebellion to still be ongoing. Where's the fun in subduing pathetic, bottom-feeding losers like you lot? Perhaps if these weapons got out onto the streets, however, and a new crime wave started, then I'd get to relive the glory days...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Sensing that they're in very real danger of being on the receiving end of Elle's wrath, the gang-members wisely choose not to interrupt her monologue. Waiting until she's calmed down and folded her wings back into place, the dog-boy leader of the gang holds out a bag of money to Elle, saying, [style.speechMasculineHeavy(A-A deal's a deal, right? We's givin' you's this cash so we can 'ave the weapons, ok? We ain't wantin' no trouble...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After taking a deep breath, Elle assumes her previous, flirty demeanour, and after gently taking the bag of flames from the dog-boy, she teases, [elle.speech(That's a good boy. As I stated before, I don't care much for your money, but I suppose I could use this to fund some other gang activities... Anyway, have fun with all of the guns, and please do try to cause as much trouble as you can.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Elle is suddenly enveloped in a bright flash of purple arcane energy, and after you've blinked away the after-image that's been momentarily burned into your vision, you see that she's vanished. Letting out a deep sigh of relief, the gang's leader steps over to the still-prone form of the rat-boy who threatened Elle, before kicking him and grunting, [style.speechMasculineHeavy(Ya fuckin' idiot! You's almost got us all fuckin' killed there! Now grab as many o' these weapons as ya can carry, then let's get out o' 'ere before that crazy bitch returns.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thankfully, the crates which you're hiding behind have all been emptied by what you assume to be Elle's previous dealings, and so none of the gang-members approach your hiding place. Continuing to film the gang as they encumber themselves with armfuls of pistols, batons, rifles, and all manner of highly-illegal Enforcer weaponry, you watch and wait until they've exited the cave, before turning the recording device off and putting it away into your inventory. Not wanting to hang around and risk the chance of Elle or the gang suddenly returning, you prepare to follow in their footsteps and head back out into the Bat Caverns...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE_LEAVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_SEARCH_CAVE_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With your task complete, having obtained incriminating evidence of Elle selling Enforcer weapons to a criminal gang, you swiftly exit the cave. After quickly looking around to make sure that you're not being watched, you set off into the Bat Caverns, wondering whether you should immediately do as Wes asked and go and anonymously hand in the recorder to either Claire or Candi.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're considering what to do next, a sudden thought enters your head, and you suppose that if you really wanted to, you could seek out Elle and betray Wes's plan to her. If you were to decide to do this, you think that you could probably locate Elle leaving work outside the Enforcer HQ between [units.time(16)]-[units.time(18)].
	</p>
	<p>
		No matter what you decide upon doing with the evidence, you certainly don't want to be discovered here by the now heavily-armed gang if they were to decide to make a sudden return. Wanting to put some distance between you and the cave, you continue on your way through the Bat Caverns, wondering where to go now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CLAIRE_ELLE_EVIDENCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_ELLE_EVIDENCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you're sure that you can trust Claire with the incriminating evidence of Elle, you think that it would be best to follow Wes's instructions, and so you ask the busty cat-girl if there's any way for you to anonymously submit evidence of criminal activity. Raising her eyebrows and flashing you a curious look, the short cat-girl points over to a dark blue box on the other side of the room, saying, [claire.speech(You can deposit stuff like that in there. Is it anything I could help with?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking Claire for her offer, you tell her that it's nothing to worry about, before [pc.walking] over to the anonymous drop-box and depositing the arcane recorder in it. Her curiosity getting the better of her, the busty cat-girl skips over to where you're standing, before flashing you another curious glance and musing out loud, [claire.speech(I wonder what you're up to...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've once again told her not to worry about it, Claire flashes you a big grin and declares, [claire.speech(Oh well, I suppose I shouldn't be asking about anonymous tips anyway! So, is there anything else I can do for you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Recalling what Wes said, you make a mental note to pay him a visit up at the Enforcer HQ after at least a week has passed. Turning your attention back towards Claire, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CANDI_ELLE_EVIDENCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CANDI_ELLE_EVIDENCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to follow Wes's instructions regarding the handling of the arcane recorder's incriminating footage, you ask Candi if there's any way for you to anonymously submit evidence of criminal activity. Blankly staring at you for a moment, the bimbo cat-girl bats her eyelids and asks, [candi.speechNoEffects(Umm, you mean, like, using the blue box thing? Yeah, I think you can, like, submit anonymous tips using that, or something...)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_BUYING_BRAX) && game.getSecondsPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("candi_sex_timer")>60*60*12)
		<p>
			After pointing down at a dark blue box fixed to the front of her counter, Candi bites her lip and lets out a horny moan, before asking, [candi.speechNoEffects(Hey, like, how about you come back here and give me a different kind of anonymous tip? My pussy's, like, all wet and ready for a good fuck, y'know?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Focusing on the task at hand, you [pc.step] over to the anonymous drop-box and deposit the arcane recorder in it. Recalling what Wes said, you make a mental note to pay him a visit here at the Enforcer HQ after at least a week has passed. Finally, you turn back to face Candi wondering whether you should give her what she wants...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			After pointing down at a dark blue box fixed to the front of her counter, Candi instantly loses interest in you, and after producing a nail-file from somewhere beneath her desk, starts focusing all of her attention on giving herself a manicure. Leaving the narcissistic bimbo to focus on her nails, you [pc.step] over to the anonymous drop-box and deposit the arcane recorder in it. Recalling what Wes said, you make a mental note to pay him a visit here at the Enforcer HQ after at least a week has passed. Finally, you turn back to face the reception desk and wonder what to do next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- APPROACH_ELLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="APPROACH_ELLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to betray Wes and side with Elle, you wait outside the Enforcer HQ for the [elle.race] to leave work for the day. Choosing a shaded spot on the opposite side of the street to the imposing building which serves as the Enforcer's Dominion Headquarters, you wait and watch for any sign of her.
	</p>
	<p>
		After forty-five minutes of loitering around in this manner, you start to think that you might have missed her, or that perhaps she didn't come in to work today. Just as you're starting to wonder whether or not it would be too brazen to ask to see Elle at the HQ's front desk, you suddenly catch sight of her stepping out of the front entrance at the side of a cat-boy Enforcer.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to approach her while she's got company, you watch as Elle dominantly steps around in front of the cat-boy and starts correcting his uniform. Although the two of them are too far away to be able to hear, you can tell from their body language that Elle is heavily hitting on the cat-boy. After straightening his tie, the [elle.race] drops her hand down between the Enforcer's legs and gives his groin a firm grope.
	</p>
	<p>
		This seems to be too much for the cat-boy to handle, as he steps back and holds up his hands to try and tell Elle that she's going too far. Clearly not being one to take no for an answer, the [elle.race] steps aside to let the cat-boy pass, but as he does so, she gives his ass a firm slap and calls out after him loud enough for you to hear, [elle.speech(You're to report to my office first thing tomorrow morning! I've got a <i>thorough</i> debriefing planned for you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the cat-boy hurries past you with an apprehensive look on his face, Elle's attention is suddenly drawn to you.
		#IF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_dsg_set_hlf_regular) || pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_dsg_set_hlf_insurgent))
		 She glances over your salvaged gear and immediately tenses up. Her hands glow with arcane power before her gleaming pink eyes fix themselves on your face. She studies you intently for a brief moment and, apparently deciding that you're more of a curiosity than a threat, relaxes while the spell she was preparing fades. She takes a more casual stance, waiting for you to approach.
		 [##game.getDialogueFlags().setFlag(FLAG_rebelBaseElleCostumeEncountered, true)]
		#ELSE
		 Quickly recognising the fact that you're no ordinary member of the public, she fixes her gleaming pink eyes onto you and waits for you to approach.
		#ENDIF
		 Realising that you're past the point of no return, you make your move and [pc.walk] over to where Elle is waiting for you.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_dsg_set_hlf_regular) || pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_dsg_set_hlf_insurgent))
			#IF(game.getDateNow().getMonthValue()==10)
			[elle.speech(Nice costume,)] she says with a wry smirk on her face, [elle.speech(So, who are you?)]
			#ELSE
			[elle.speech(Nice costume,)] she says with a wry smirk on her face, [elle.speech(But it's a little early, don't you think? So, who are you?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
		[elle.speech(So, who are you?)] she bluntly asks.
		#ENDIF
		 You can tell both from her tone of voice and from her curious gaze that she's deciding whether to treat you in a seductive or hostile manner.
	</p>
	<p>
		After simply telling her your name, Elle displays her quick-thinking by immediately responding, [elle.speech(So <i>you're</i> [pc.name]. Yes, I know about you. I read the report on the pacification of the Harpy Nests, and, if I may say so, you did a most excellent job up there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding that you're a suitable target to try and seduce, the horny Enforcer steps closer and flashes you a cheeky smile, before asking, [elle.speech(Perhaps you heard something about me from one of the Enforcers up there? Go on, tell me all the naughty things they said about me...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- APPROACH_ELLE_EXPLAIN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="APPROACH_ELLE_EXPLAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get this business with Wes finished as soon as possible, you ignore Elle's teasing and show her the arcane recorder which the fox-boy gave to you. A puzzled look flashes across the [elle.race]'s face as she sees what it is you're holding, and teases, [elle.speech(What's this? You're wanting to record us while we fuck? How kinky... Those arcane recorders aren't cheap, either...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Flipping out the screen that's built into the side of the recorder, you show Elle the footage of her selling weapons to the gang down in the cave in the Bat Caverns. Explaining to her how it was Wes that tried to get her arrested, you look up to see that there's a grim expression on Elle's face. Dropping her seductive tone as she realises how serious this is, she flatly states, [elle.speech(You've done well to bring this to my attention. How careless I was not to search the cave upon entering it... Now hand over that recorder, if you please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As this was your intention all along, you do as Elle asks and give her the arcane recorder. Immediately, she throws it to the ground, and before you have a chance to say anything, she uses her arcane power to cast a spell. Projecting a wave of crushing force down upon the helpless arcane device, Elle instantly obliterates it, sending tiny fragments of metal and plastic all over the street. Ignoring the curious looks which several members of the public cast her way, the [elle.race] looks back up at you and states, [elle.speech(I need to fix this situation before that damn fox-boy reports me. Come back after a week and ask for me at the front desk, and I'll give you a handsome reward for your loyalty.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a dark look in her eyes, Elle turns back towards the Enforcer HQ, before quickly striding across the grounds and heading inside. Finding yourself alone out in the street, you have little else to do but continue on your way, wondering what kind of reward will be given to you when you return to meet Elle next week...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- RECEPTION_DESK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_DESK_WES"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		#IF(game.isWorkTime())
			#IF(game.getMinutesPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_completion_timer")>60*24*7)
				As it's been more than a week since you anonymously handed in the evidence needed to arrest Elle, you could ask Candi to tell Wes that you're here to see him...
			#ELSE
				As it hasn't yet been more than a week since you anonymously handed in the evidence needed to arrest Elle, you shouldn't ask Candi about seeing Wes yet. [style.italicsMinorBad(You should return after [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getMinutesPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_completion_timer")>60*24*7)
				Although it's been more than a week since you anonymously handed in the evidence needed to arrest Elle, Candi is only at work from [style.colourMinorBad([units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)])], so you'll have to return during normal work hours  in order to meet Wes...
			#ELSE
				It hasn't yet been more than a week since you anonymously handed in the evidence needed to arrest Elle, and even it had been, Candi is only at work from [style.colourMinorBad([units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)])], so you'd be unable to meet Wes regardless. [style.italicsMinorBad(You should return after [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_DESK_ELLE"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		#IF(game.isWorkTime())
			#IF(game.getMinutesPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_completion_timer")>60*24*7)
				As it's been more than a week since you contacted Elle, you could tell Candi that you're here to see her...
			#ELSE
				As it hasn't yet been more than a week since you contacted Elle, you shouldn't ask Candi about seeing her yet. [style.italicsMinorBad(You should return after [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.getMinutesPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_completion_timer")>60*24*7)
				Although it's been more than a week since you contacted Elle, Candi is only at work from [style.colourMinorBad([units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)])], so you'll have to return during normal work hours in order to meet her...
			#ELSE
				It hasn't yet been more than a week since you contacted Elle, and even it had been, Candi is only at work from [style.colourMinorBad([units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)])], so you'd be unable to meet her regardless. [style.italicsMinorBad(You should return after [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_WES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_WES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As it's been more than a week since you anonymously deposited the arcane recorder in the evidence drop-box, you tell Candi that you're here to meet with a fox-boy SWORD Enforcer called Wesley Wormwood. For a moment, it seems as though the bimbo cat-girl doesn't understand what you're talking about, before suddenly remembering that it's her job to help out visitors and saying, [candi.speechNoEffects(So, you're wanting me to, like, let him know you've arrived? Umm... Hold on a moment...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at the arcane intercom that's built into the top of her desk, she hovers her index finger back and forth between several buttons, speaking out loud to herself as she does so, [candi.speechNoEffects(I know that Wes is, like, at requisitions... I think it's this button that I need...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The dim-witted cat-girl presses the button that's quite clearly marked as 'Requisitions', and after letting out a low-pitched buzzing noise, the arcane intercom's speaker crackles into life, and you hear the familiar voice of Wes asking, [wes.speech(What is it now, Candi? Don't tell me that you've lost your jacket <i>again</i>...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Uh, like, that's kinda rude of you to think that, y'know? I'm actually doing my job for once, thank you very much!)] Candi drawls, [candi.speech(There's, like, [pc.a_race] here at the front desk for you. Are you, like, expecting someone called '[pc.name]'?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Yes, I am,)] Wes replies, [wes.speech(Tell [pc.herHim] to wait right there; I'm on my way.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Even though it's blatantly obvious that you were able to overhear the brief conversation, Candi feels the need to look up at you and explain, [candi.speechNoEffects(Ok, so, like, Wes was kinda rude to me just now, but he's, like, agreed to come and meet you here. You're going to have to wait for him here, y'know? You can, like, use the waiting area.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After pointing over to the collection of sofas on the other side of the room, Candi turns her attention towards the mirror that's sitting on her desk. Leaving the ditzy bimbo behind, you [pc.walk] over to the nearest sofa and wait for Wes arrive...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_WES_ARRIVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_WES_ARRIVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thankfully, you aren't kept waiting long, as less than five minutes after you've entered the waiting area, the familiar figure of Wes appears from out of the guarded door on the far side of the room. Looking around and catching sight of you, he flashes you a warm smile, before calling out, [wes.speech([pc.Name]! Come on through to my office!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding to do as Wes says, you [pc.walk] over to the fox-boy and say hello, before commenting on how smart his uniform looks. Letting out a good-natured laugh, he reveals, [wes.speech(I've been promoted to Superintendent, so I have to keep my uniform in particularly good condition to set an example to the junior ranks. Follow me on through to my new office, and I'll explain all that's happened once we get there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Motioning for the Enforcer who's guarding the inner door to step aside, Wes sets off into the back area of the Enforcer HQ with you at his side...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_WES_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_WES_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Accompanying Wes down the HQ's corridors, you wait as he unlocks an inner-door by brushing his pass over an arcane scanner mounted to the nearby wall, before following him through into the requisitions department. Leading you though a nearby door, you enter the fox-boy's office, which, while being particularly large and extravagantly furnished, seems to look a little <i>too</i> tidy, hinting at the fact that it isn't seeing much use.
	</p>
	<p>
		Sinking down into the executive leather chair positioned behind his desk, Wes lets out a deep, happy sigh and reveals, [wes.speech(Thanks to the evidence you gathered, the internal investigation of Elle all went according to my plan. By taking an active role in the investigation, I managed to secure this promotion to Superintendent which I've been chasing for years. I've received Elle's old title of Senior Quartermaster, and, speaking of her, she ended up being enslaved and given to me as a bonus. Not that I particularly wanted to own her, mind you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Congratulating Wes on his promotion, you comment on the fact that his office looks as though it hasn't seen much use yet. Letting out a short sigh and standing up from behind his desk, he continues, [wes.speech(This is actually only the third or fourth time I've used this office. In an attempt at avoiding a repeat of Elle's siphoning off of equipment, the higher-ups have ordered me to make more regular reports on the inventory's status, which means I'm having to spend all of my time doing my old job of working at the requisitions desk...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving over to the door of his office, the fox-boy sighs, [wes.speech(Speaking of which, I need to get back over there as soon as possible. I've got Elle stationed in there to help me do the work, but I can't trust her to be alone for too long. She might technically be my slave, but she's as free-spirited as ever...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Opening the door and beckoning you to once again follow him, he reveals, [wes.speech(As a way of thanking you for your help, I've arranged for you to be granted a contractor's pass, so you'll not only be granted access to the requisitions area, but I'll also be able to sell you surplus Enforcer equipment. Come on, I've got the pass waiting for you over there.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_WES_REQUISITIONS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_WES_REQUISITIONS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Wes out of his office, you accompany him as he walks over to the other side of the corridor and strides through the pair of propped-open doors which lead into the station's requisitions area. Consisting of a large, empty room, the only points of interest in this area are the couple of bare metal tables pushed into each corner, as well as the locked door and waist-high counter set into the wall before you. Telling you to remain here, Wes opens the door, before stepping around to the other side of the counter and starting to rummage around in some of the drawers.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Elle?! What have you done with that contractor pass I told you to put in here?!)] he calls out.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Oh, I didn't realise you were back!)] the familiar voice of Elle replies from somewhere within the maze of shelving units which fill the vast storage area behind the counter. A moment later, the [elle.race] steps into view, and you see that while she looks just as she did the last time you saw her, she's now wearing a metal slave collar and slutty fancy-dress Enforcer uniform. Catching sight of you waiting behind the counter,
		#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_rebelBaseElleCostumeEncountered) && (pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_dsg_set_hlf_regular) || pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_dsg_set_hlf_insurgent)))
			 her eyes narrow for an instant as she glances over your salvaged gear and arcane power briefly flashes over her hands before she decides you're no threat after all and relaxes. [elle.speech(What's this, Wes?] the horny slave remarks,)]
			#IF(game.getDateNow().getMonthValue()==10)
			 [elle.speech(You've finally brought me someone to fuck other than you? And my, does [pc.she] have a peculiar taste in costumes.)]
			#ELSE
			 [elle.speech(You've finally brought me someone to fuck other than you? And my, does [pc.she] have a peculiar sense of fashion.)]
			#ENDIF
			[##game.getDialogueFlags().setFlag(FLAG_rebelBaseElleCostumeEncountered, true)]
		#ELSE
		  the horny slave remarks, [elle.speech(What's this, Wes? You've finally brought me someone to fuck other than you?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Just tell me where the pass is, Elle,)] the fox-boy sighs in frustration.
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning down and pressing her huge breasts against the back of Wes's head, Elle pulls open the top drawer and sighs, [elle.speech(I told you that I'd put it in here...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Retrieving what looks like a plastic id card attached to a blue lanyard, Wes hands this pass over to you, saying, [wes.speech(This will unlock the doors to this area, and if you show it to an Enforcer patrol, they won't try and confiscate any of the gear you purchase from me here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Noticing your curious glance as you look at Elle's fancy-dress Enforcer uniform, the fox-boy sheepishly admits, [wes.speech(I couldn't have her walking around naked, could I? It felt wrong to have her wearing a real uniform as well, and besides, having her wear that is all part of her punishment.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(You liar,)] Elle teases, leaning into Wes's back and reaching down to stroke his groin. Ignoring the fox-boy's protestations, she looks up at you and says, [elle.speech(He makes me wear this because it turns him on, and he likes reminding me of my place while I'm choking down his yummy, fat knot.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Not now, Elle!)] Wes snaps as he tries, and fails, to push the horny half-demon off of him. Giving up and choosing to simply ignore Elle's sexual harassment, Wes turns his attention back towards you and says, [wes.speech(You can buy gear from me here at any time during my working hours, which are from nine to five. If you'd like to do me a favour again, you could try and help me to calm Elle's libido by taking her over to my office and spending some time with her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As Elle continues trying to get into Wes's pants, you wonder what you should do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_ELLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_ELLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As it's been more than a week since you contacted Elle, you tell Candi that you're here to meet with [elle.a_race] SWORD Enforcer called [elle.name] [elle.surname]. For a moment, it seems as though the bimbo cat-girl doesn't understand what you're talking about, before suddenly remembering that it's her job to help out visitors and saying, [candi.speechNoEffects(So, you're wanting me to, like, let her know you've arrived? Umm... Hold on a moment...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at the arcane intercom that's built into the top of her desk, she hovers her index finger back and forth between several buttons, speaking out loud to herself as she does so, [candi.speechNoEffects(I know that Elle is, like, at requisitions... I think it's this button that I need...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The dim-witted cat-girl presses the button that's quite clearly marked as 'Requisitions', and after letting out a low-pitched buzzing noise, the arcane intercom's speaker crackles into life, and you hear the familiar voice of Elle asking, [elle.speech(What can I help you with, Candi? Don't tell me that you've lost your jacket <i>again</i>...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Uh, like, that's kinda rude of you to think that, y'know? I'm actually doing my job for once, thank you very much!)] Candi drawls, [candi.speech(There's, like, [pc.a_race] here at the front desk for you. Are you, like, expecting someone called '[pc.name]'?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(As a matter of fact, I am,)] Elle replies, [elle.speech(Be a dear and tell [pc.herHim] to wait right there; I'm on my way.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Even though it's blatantly obvious that you were able to overhear the brief conversation, Candi feels the need to look up at you and explain, [candi.speechNoEffects(Ok, so, like, Elle was kinda rude to me just now, but she's, like, agreed to come and meet you here. You're going to have to wait for her here, y'know? You can, like, use the waiting area.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After pointing over to the collection of sofas on the other side of the room, Candi turns her attention towards the mirror that's sitting on her desk. Leaving the ditzy bimbo behind, you [pc.walk] over to the nearest sofa and wait for Elle arrive...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_ELLE_ARRIVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_ELLE_ARRIVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thankfully, you aren't kept waiting long, as less than five minutes after you've entered the waiting area, the familiar figure of Elle appears from out of the guarded door on the far side of the room. Looking around and catching sight of you,
		#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_rebelBaseElleCostumeEncountered) && (pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_dsg_set_hlf_regular) || pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_dsg_set_hlf_insurgent)))
			 her eyes narrow for an instant as she glances over your salvaged gear before she recognises you. She grins wryly at you, before beckoning you forwards and calling out,
			#IF(game.getDateNow().getMonthValue()==10)
			 [elle.speech(Nice costume. Please, come right this way!)]
			#ELSE
			 [elle.speech(Nice costume, but it's a little early for that. Please, come right this way!)]
			#ENDIF
			[##game.getDialogueFlags().setFlag(FLAG_rebelBaseElleCostumeEncountered, true)]
		#ELSE
		 she flashes you a cheeky grin, before beckoning you forwards and calling out, [elle.speech(Please, come right this way!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding to do as Elle says, you [pc.walk] over to the [elle.race] and offer her your greetings. Stepping forwards so as to playfully brush up against you, the horny Enforcer reveals, [elle.speech(I've got a lot to thank you for, [pc.name]. Please do follow me on through to my office, and I'll explain all that's happened once we get there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Motioning for the Enforcer who's guarding the inner door to step aside, Elle sets off into the back area of the Enforcer HQ with you at her side...
	</p>
	
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_ELLE_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_ELLE_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Accompanying Elle down the HQ's corridors, you wait as she unlocks an inner-door by brushing her pass over an arcane scanner mounted to the nearby wall, before following her through into the requisitions department. Leading you though a nearby door, you enter the [elle.race]'s office, which turns out to be particularly large and extravagantly furnished.
	</p>
	<p>
		Sitting down on the executive leather chair positioned behind her desk, Elle lets out a happy little sigh and reveals, [elle.speech(Thanks to your tip-off, I took a chance on going to my superiors and placing all of the blame for the missing stock on Wes. Thankfully, everything couldn't have gone smoother, and the poor little fox-boy ended up being enslaved and given to me as a bonus. I'd always considered him to be a little odd, and so wasn't too keen on owning him, but he's turned out to be a great help.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Standing up from behind her desk, she explains, [elle.speech(In an attempt at avoiding a repeat of 'Wes's' siphoning off of equipment, the higher-ups have ordered me to make more regular reports on the inventory's status, which means I'm having to spend all of my time working at the requisitions desk. Thankfully, my little fox-boy slave knows just how to get things done in there, and what's more, he's surprisingly good at keeping me satisfied...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving over to the door of her office, the [elle.race] lets out a soft laugh and runs her hand over your [pc.arm], before teasing, [elle.speech(Perhaps we can talk more about the ways in which I can be satisfied later...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Opening the door and beckoning you to once again follow her, Elle reveals, [elle.speech(As a way of thanking you for your help, I've arranged for you to be granted a contractor's pass, so you'll not only be granted access to the requisitions area, but I'll also be able to sell you surplus Enforcer equipment. Come on, I've got the pass waiting for you over there.)]
	
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- INTRO_HQ_ELLE_REQUISITIONS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRO_HQ_ELLE_REQUISITIONS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Elle out of her office, you accompany her as she walks over to the other side of the corridor and strides through the pair of propped-open doors which lead into the station's requisitions area. Consisting of a large, empty room, the only points of interest in this area are the couple of bare metal tables pushed into each corner, as well as the locked door and waist-high counter set into the wall before you. Telling you to remain here, Elle opens the door, before stepping around to the other side of the counter and starting to rummage around in some of the drawers.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Wes, my darling? What have you done with that contractor pass I told you to put away?)] she calls out in a flirty, high-pitched tone.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(I told you that I'd put it in the top drawer!)] the familiar voice of Wes calls out from somewhere within the maze of shelving units which fill the vast storage area behind the counter. A moment later, the fox-boy steps into view, and you see that while he looks just as he did the last time you saw him, he's now wearing nothing but a metal slave collar and a pair of black boxers. Catching sight of you waiting behind the counter, Wes flashes you a furious look, before angrily asking, [wes.speech(So, are you happy with what you've done? This criminal keeps her job, and I'm the one who got punished for her crimes!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Now, now, Wes,)] Elle tuts, before stepping over to her slave and fondly pulling him into her ample cleavage. Lovingly stroking the top of his head, she teases, [elle.speech(Being my slave isn't so bad, is it? I can't imagine that many slaves get to have their cocks sucked by their Mistresses all the time... Look, if you're really upset, I'll let you use my pussy tonight. You liked that little 'defeated Elle' roleplay we tried the other night, didn't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly getting extremely embarrassed about Elle saying all of this right in front of you, the fox-boy pushes his owner off of him, before storming over to the counter and retrieving the contractor pass from out of the top drawer. Throwing it over to Elle, he huffs, [wes.speech(I've still got three boxes of assorted uniforms left to catalogue and store away. If there's nothing else you need from me, then I'm getting back to work.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Once I've finished my business with [pc.name] here, I'll come and join you,)] Elle teases, before turning her attention back to you. Handing you the contractor pass, which turns out to be a plastic id card attached to a pink lanyard, Elle says, [elle.speech(This will unlock the doors to this area, and if you show it to an Enforcer patrol, they won't try and confiscate any of the gear you purchase from me here. You can buy gear from me here at any time during my working hours, which are from nine to five. Of course, if you wanted to just chat, or perhaps have a little fun in my office, then I'll always be happy to see you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As Elle flashes you a seductive smile, you wonder what you should do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Post-quest dialogues: -->
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_POST_QUEST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Connected to the adjoining corridor by a pair of wide, propped-open doors, the requisitions area is the place where specialist or replacement equipment can be checked out by the HQ's Enforcers. [pc.Stepping] through the open doors into this area, you find yourself standing in a relatively small room, which, other than a couple of basic metal tables pushed up against one wall, is devoid of any furniture. The only other point of interest is the counter on the far side of the room, which currently appears to be unmanned.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
			Continuing to move forwards into the room, you look past the counter to see a huge storage area filled with all sorts of weapons and protective equipment. Down at the end of one of the aisles formed by the well-stocked shelving units, you see the familiar figure of Elle pinning Wes back against the wall. She's slipped her hand down the fox-boy's boxers, and from the rapid movements of her arm, it's quite obvious that she's giving him a handjob.
		#ELSE
			Continuing to move forwards into the room, you look past the counter to see a huge storage area filled with all sorts of weapons and protective equipment. Down at the end of one of the aisles formed by the well-stocked shelving units, you see the familiar figure of Elle forcing herself on Wes and pinning him back against the wall. She's slipped her hand down the fox-boy's trousers, and from the rapid movements of her arm, it's quite obvious that she's giving him a handjob.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder whether you should ring the bell on the desk's counter to get their attention, or turn around and leave them to it...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_TRADE_DIALOGUE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
		<p>
			Telling Elle that you'd like to buy some Enforcer equipment, you wait as she rummages around in a nearby drawer for a moment, before producing a list of available equipment and placing it down on the counter-top in front of you. Leaning forwards over the counter-top and flashing you a seductive look, she reveals, [elle.speech(Here's what I can sell to you without causing any trouble...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking down at the list, you wonder whether you should buy anything...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Telling Wes that you'd like to buy some Enforcer equipment, you wait as he rummages around in a nearby drawer for a moment, before producing a list of available equipment and placing it down on the counter-top in front of you. Pushing Elle off of him, he lets out a sigh and reveals, [wes.speech(Here's what I can sell to you without causing any trouble...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking down at the list while Elle continues to sexually harass Wes, you wonder whether you should buy anything...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_INTERACTION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_INTERACTION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Elle, you ring the counter's bell, causing her to look over towards the counter and see you standing there. Turning back to whisper something into Wes's ear, she slides her hand out from the fox-boy's boxers, before giving his groin a firm squeeze and then turning to walk over towards you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Stepping up to the counter, the [elle.race] puts on her most seductive look, before teasing,
			#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_rebelBaseElleCostumeEncountered) && (pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_dsg_set_hlf_regular) || pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_dsg_set_hlf_insurgent)))
			 [elle.speech(You caught me in the middle of disciplining my slave...)] Her voice trails off as she notices your salvaged gear and her face shifts into a suspicious expression for an instant shifting right back.
				#IF(game.getDateNow().getMonthValue()==10)
					#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("elle_background_progress")<5)
					 [elle.speech(Nice costume. You really do have the kinkiest roleplaying ideas,)] she says. Before you can ask what she means by that, she changes subject with a giggle, [elle.speech(So, what can I do for you this time, [pc.name]?)]
					#ELSE
					 [elle.speech(Nice costume, did you get that just for me? You really do have the kinkiest roleplaying ideas,)] she says before changing the subject with a giggle, [elle.speech(So, what can I do for you this time, [pc.name]?)] 
					#ENDIF 
				#ELSE
					#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("elle_background_progress")<5)
						 [elle.speech(Nice costume, even if it's a little early. You really do have the kinkiest roleplaying ideas,)] she says. Before you can ask what she means by that, she changes subject with a giggle, [elle.speech(So, what can I do for you this time, [pc.name]?)]
					#ELSE
						  [elle.speech(Nice costume, even if it's a little early. Did you get that just for me? You really do have the kinkiest roleplaying ideas,)] she says before changing the subject with a giggle, [elle.speech(So, what can I do for you this time, [pc.name]?)] 
					#ENDIF 
				#ENDIF
				[##game.getDialogueFlags().setFlag(FLAG_rebelBaseElleCostumeEncountered, true)]
			#ELSE
			 [elle.speech(You caught me in the middle of disciplining my slave... So, what can I do for you this time, [pc.name]?)]
			#ENDIF			
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Wes, you ring the counter's bell, causing both him and Elle to look over towards the counter and see you standing there. Turning back to whisper something into Wes's ear, Elle slides her hand out from the fox-boy's trousers, before giving his groin a firm squeeze and then stepping back to let Wes walk over towards you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly being a little flustered from the attention Elle was giving to him, Wes clears his throat and takes a deep breath, before flashing you a warm smile and asking, [wes.speech(What can I do for you today, [pc.name]? Sorry that you had to catch me like that, Elle was just-)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Giving you a quickie,)] the [elle.race] teases, cutting off Wes's sentence as she steps up behind him and lewdly presses her huge breasts into his back. Ignoring Wes's firm request for her to step back, Elle leans in over his shoulder and teases, [elle.speech(Don't worry, babe, I'll finish you off with my mouth once you've dealt with [pc.name].)]
		</p>
		#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
			#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(wes))
				#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(wes.getId()))
					<p>
						With his back-and-forth with Elle now at an end, Wes is able to finally take a proper look at you, and immediately notices the fact that you're now pregnant. Realising that he must be the father, the fox-boy gulps and asks, [wes.speech(Are you going to be ok, [pc.name]? Is there anything I can do for you? I mean, I know that having kids doesn't seem to be as big a deal here in the city as it is for a lot of country folk, but I'd still like to take responsibility.)]
					</p>
					<p>
						Thanking Wes for his concern, you tell him that you're managing just fine, and won't require any sort of help from him. Warmly smiling at you, he says, [wes.speech(If there's anything I can help you with, [pc.name], please just let me know...)]
					</p>
				#ELSE
					<p>
						With his back-and-forth with Elle now at an end, Wes is able to finally take a proper look at you, and quickly notices the fact that you're still pregnant. Warmly smiling at you, he kindly asks how you are, and after you've replied that you're feeling well, he gets down to business by once again asking, [wes.speech(So, [pc.name], what can I help you with today?)]
					</p>
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				<p>
					With his back-and-forth with Elle now at an end, Wes is able to finally take a proper look at you, and quickly notices the fact that you're still pregnant. Warmly smiling at you, he kindly asks how you are, and after you've replied that you're feeling well, he gets down to business by once again asking, [wes.speech(So, [pc.name], what can I help you with today?)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Letting out a frustrated huff, Wes does his best to ignore Elle's hand as it creeps back down towards his groin, and once again asks, [wes.speech(So, [pc.name], what can I help you with?)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_INTERACTION_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
		<p>
			Having got what you wanted from Elle, you tell her that you need to be getting on your way, before saying goodbye and heading towards the exit. As you leave the requisitions area, you take one last look back to see the horny [elle.race] rapidly advancing on Wes and reaching towards his groin...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having got what you wanted from Wes, you tell him that you need to be getting on your way, before saying goodbye and heading towards the exit. As you leave the requisitions area, you take one last look back to see Elle sinking down to her knees in front of the fox-boy and hungrily reaching up towards his groin...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND_ELLE_1"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("elle_background_progress")<5)
		<p>
			Wanting to get to know Elle a little better, you ask her what she did before becoming an Enforcer, and what made her decide to join Dominion's law enforcement.
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a soft hum as she thinks back to the start of her career, she reveals, [elle.speech(I didn't do much of anything before signing up to become an Enforcer... I suppose that was the main reason why I joined them in the first place; I was simply bored of doing nothing.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pressing her on the issue a little further, you say to Elle that surely she must have been doing <i>something</i> before signing up.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Very well, you've got me to admit it; my mother is a direct daughter of Lunette herself, and what's more, I was her favourite child. I was given absolutely anything I asked for, and so never had to even think about working for a living,)] Elle reveals, before smirking at you and teasing, [elle.speech(I couldn't live that sort of life forever, though; it's far more fun having to work at seducing your next conquest rather than having them simply given to you...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Hungrily looking you up and down, she lowers her voice a little and breathlessly whispers, [elle.speech(Enough talk about my past; surely there are other things you'd like to discus...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Elle about her past again, you ask her if she can tell you anything about her pre-Enforcer days spent living with her mother.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(There's not really much to tell,)] she sighs, before suddenly flashing you a dirty look and revealing, [elle.speech(The sex was the best part about it; I got to fuck a new guy or girl almost every night, and when my mother hosted parties, I'd try to perform oral on as many different guests as I could. I think my record was twenty-seven in one night...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a mischievous giggle, Elle bats her eyelashes at you and teases,
			#IF(pc.hasPenis())
				 [elle.speech(All that practice is why I'm so good at giving head...)]
			#ELSE
				 [elle.speech(All that practice is why I'm so good with my tongue...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND_ELLE_2"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("elle_background_progress")<5)
		<p>
			Having previously discovered from Elle that she joined the Enforcers out of boredom with her privileged life, you ask her what her early experiences as an officer of the law were like.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Mmm... Well, my training at the Academy and my first year as being a member of the Patrol were both pretty boring. I'd slept with everyone worth sleeping with after the first month or so, and I quickly started to realise that being a regular Enforcer wasn't all that fun,)] she sighs, and without any further prompt from you, she quickly continues, [elle.speech(That's when I decided to apply to join SWORD. There were loads of hot guys and girls in their ranks, and I'd heard that they got loads of fun assignments.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Overhearing what it is that Elle is saying, Wes quips in from somewhere behind a nearby shelving unit, [wes.speech(Typical demon... Being allowed to apply for SWORD after just a year of service...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(My instructor said that I was one of the best he'd seen, thank you very much,)] Elle calls out in a light-hearted tone, before biting her lip and teasing, [elle.speech(Of course, that might have had something to do with the fact that I was spreading my legs for him every day in his office...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Hearing no further comment from Wes, Elle smirks and continues, [elle.speech(Anyway, I graduated with above-average grades and then applied for the position of courier, which I was immediately granted. I'd thought that as a courier, I'd be able to have all sorts of fun fucking different people all over Lilith's Realm, but I just so happened to graduate in the July of '88, right before the Fifth Human Rebellion started...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As she says this, the flirty, light-hearted look in Elle's eyes quickly fades away, and she lets out a deep, remorseful sigh. Realising that she's not comfortable talking about this right now, you tell Elle that it wasn't your intention to uncover any unpleasant memories, and perhaps it would be best to drop the subject for now.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Yeah, ask me about this again some other time,)] the [elle.race] sighs, before shaking her head and returning to her flirty attitude as she teases, [elle.speech(It's a lot more fun talking about other stuff, such as the fact that I can easily orgasm just from performing oral on someone...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Elle about her past again, you ask her if she can tell you anything about her early days in the Enforcer Academy or as a Patrol officer.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Oh, you want to know the sorts of things I got up to back then, do you?)] she teases, before seductively biting her lip and recalling, [elle.speech(The actual training at the Academy was really boring, as you'd expect, but I had a lot of fun seducing and fucking the instructors one-by-one... The best memory I've got of my training is the night of our graduation party, when I got three of the instructors to gang-bang me, and the next morning, I woke each of them up in turn by giving them a blowjob! Fun times...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Licking her lips and flashing you a dirty look, she continues, [elle.speech(My days as a Patrol officer were much of the same. It was all boring work while on duty, but getting to fuck my way through all of my superiors sure was fun! But anyway, speaking of fucking, how about we talk more about that...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND_ELLE_3"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("elle_background_progress")<5)
		<p>
			Although Elle seemed to have some unpleasant memories of her early days as a SWORD Enforcer, you're sure that she's prepared to answer your questions about it by now, and so you ask her what her job was like after graduating.
		</p>
		<p>
			Once again, Elle's flirty demeanour vanishes as she recalls her early memories of working as a member of SWORD, but despite the troubled expression which settles on her face, she willingly answers, [elle.speech(Well, as I mentioned before, I'd graduated in the July of '88, less than a month before all the troubles of the Fifth Human Rebellion kicked off. You won't hear many people talking about it these days, but back then, it seemed like the whole world was starting to fall apart...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a deep sigh, she recalls, [elle.speech(I'd been given the job of courier over at SWORD's Fifth Company, which seemed like a cushy assignment for the first couple of weeks. Thanks to my wings, I could fly all over Dominion in no time at all, and if the situation called for it, I could even make the roundabout trip to Elis, Thinis, and even Itza'aak in less than a day. The main thing on my mind back then was who I'd get to seduce and fuck when I arrived at my destination, but that all changed with the violent start of the rebellion; the 'Day of Four Eights'...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(You've never spoken about this before,)] Wes chimes in as he peers around the corner of a nearby shelving unit.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Nobody's ever asked before,)] Elle replies, [elle.speech(And what is there to find out? From my perspective, the rebellion was four years of chaos, uncertainty, and... a hell of a lot of fun!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting a big smirk settle on her after saying this, Elle goes on to reveal, [elle.speech(As my job of courier got a lot more dangerous with the start of the rebellion, I was ordered to get flight combat qualified. I wasn't sure about it at first, but that's where I found my true calling! Swooping and diving... Knowing that the bastards who're after you intend to take you prisoner... The adrenaline! It gets me going just thinking about it! Oh, how I remember the looks on their faces when they realised that I'd out-manoeuvred them! Hahaha!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Caught up in her excitement, Elle suddenly unfurls her large, demonic wings, and with an intense, maniacal look in her bright pink eyes, she gives them a powerful flap and declares, [elle.speech(I was never beaten in the skies, not once! They may have called themselves the 'Human Liberation Front', but those rebel scum had harpies, bats, even dragons attempt to intercept me, and I beat them all!)]  
		</p>
		<p>
			Remembering that those glory days are long gone, Elle folds her wings back down behind her back, before letting out a long sigh and saying, [elle.speech(My early days at SWORD were hell, sure, but I've never felt more alive than I did during those aerial fights... Well, having a good fuck is a decent substitute I suppose, and seeing as I've gone on for long enough about my past, how about we talk more about that sort of thing...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Elle about her past again, you ask her if she's got any stories to tell about her experiences during the Fifth Human Rebellion.
		</p>
		<p>
			A slight smile breaks out across Elle's face as she hears you ask this, and in a wistful tone, she recalls, [elle.speech(Well, if you want a story, then I can tell you about the one rebel who managed to get away from me... Out of all the countless scum who I fought and bested in aerial combat, he was the only one who I'd ever consider to be my equal. He was some kind of greater bird-of-prey harpy, perhaps a falcon, but despite fighting against one another over a dozen times, I could never get a good look at him; he was just too fast.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Elle starts to subconsciously unfurl her wings as she remembers the fights she had with this unidentified harpy, [elle.speech(At the time when I first saw him, I'd already got more than a year's worth of experience in the skies, but despite that, he almost took me out on his first pass. It was just by mere chance that I happened to look behind me as I was flying, and I saw him just a second away from crashing into me. I was able to dodge him, but only just, and before I knew what was happening, he was on me again... I had to drop the package I was carrying, but even then, I was only barely able to keep up with his moves. He pursued me all the way back to HQ, and even had the balls to dive at the Enforcers manning the towers...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With your curiosity piqued, you ask Elle what happened to this rebel harpy, to which she shrugs and replies, [elle.speech(I never found out. There was nothing extraordinary about the last time we fought, and after that ended in a stalemate, I watched him fly off in the direction of the Mountains of the Moon. That was the last I ever saw of him. He was probably caught by a routine ground patrol; I couldn't imagine someone of his fervour ever abandoning his cause.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Taking on a flirty tone once again, she teases, [elle.speech(I would have loved to have found out what he was like to fuck...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND_ELLE_4"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("elle_background_progress")<5)
		<p>
			Curious to hear about Elle's more recent past, you ask her what she did once the Fifth Human Rebellion had ended.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(I continued with my job as a courier,)] she reveals, [elle.speech(Of course, I'd been promoted by that time, so I could delegate the more tedious assignments to those serving under me. Despite taking only the most 'exciting' of assignments, however, I soon grew very bored of my once-exhilarating job. Flying just isn't the same when you don't have to worry about being attacked at any moment by a swooping rebel harpy...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Softly chuckling to herself at the thought, she continues, [elle.speech(Anyway, after several years of working my way up through the ranks, I eventually applied to be transferred to logistics here at Enforcer HQ, hoping that I'd be able to get some excitement from fucking my way through all of my superiors. Well, I did get some excitement doing that, but the higher-ups aren't exactly the best fucks I've ever had, and I soon grew bored again...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			All of her talk about fucking her superiors seems to have got Elle turned on again, for she leans over the counter and suggestively teases, [elle.speech(I'm always up for a good fuck, you know...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Elle about her past again, you ask her if any of her old courier colleagues transferred to logistics, just like she did.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(No, all of the Enforcers I worked with back then have either stayed on as couriers, been promoted to some cushy desk job in other parts of the realm, or retired. I'm the only one from my old Company who's working here at the HQ,)] Elle reveals, before smirking and continuing, [elle.speech(My good little slave, Wes, is actually the one I've known here for the longest.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Seductively biting her lip and leaning forwards over the counter, she teases, [elle.speech(How about we talk about something a little more fun? Like how good it must feel to fuck me...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND_ELLE_5"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("elle_background_progress")<=5)
		<p>
			Having found out almost everything there is to know about Elle's past, you have just one last question to ask her. Wanting to hear her reasons for siphoning off the Enforcer's weapons and selling them to criminal gangs, you ask her why she did it.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Because I was bored!)] she exclaims, as though that's a legitimate reason for breaking the law, [elle.speech(I'm sure that you overheard me saying this to those gang-members back in the cave, but there's really nothing exciting for us Enforcers to do these days. It's all routine patrols, routine equipment checks, routine reports, routine boredom! If the criminals had access to more fire-power, then they could start a serious crime wave, and then I'd finally get to see some action again!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(So much for that,)] Wes snarkily calls out from somewhere behind the shelving units.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Mmm, yes, things didn't quite go as planned, thanks to [pc.name] here,)] Elle replies, before smirking at you and revealing, [elle.speech(Everything worked out well, though. I may not get the excitement of fighting criminals, but Wes has turned out to be surprisingly fun! I always thought he was a little odd, so I never tried to seduce him, but it turns out that he's got a seemingly-endless reserve of stamina, and is ready to fuck at any time! His cock's nice and big as well, and when he shoves his knot into my mouth... Fuck, I can cum just from that!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(It's not like I can say no!)] Wes exclaims.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Just to think that for all of these years, Wes was right under my nose... I could have been having so much fun with him!)] Elle softly laughs, [elle.speech(I let him sleep in my bed at night, and all I have to do is spread my legs and let out a little moan, and he's immediately on top of me, stuffing his big cock into my hungry little pussy...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Getting herself worked up by all this talk of sex, Elle breathlessly pants, [elle.speech(Fuck... I'm getting wet just thinking about it...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having now found out all there is to know about Elle's past, you wonder what to say to her next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Elle about her past again, you ask her what sort of things she got up to while working in logistics here at the Enforcer HQ.
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(There's not really much to tell about all of that,)] Elle sighs, [elle.speech(I transferred here ten years ago, and since then, I got a promotion, fucked over half of all the Enforcers who work here, and ended up gaining Wes as a slave. Other than that, nothing much happened.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Leaning forwards over the counter, she teases, [elle.speech(My little fox-boy slave is proving to be a hell of a lot of fun to fuck, but he's not the only one I've got an interest in...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND_WES_1"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_background_progress")<5)
		<p>
			Wanting to get to know Wes a little better, you ask him about his past life and what he did before joining the Enforcers.
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(Before I joined the Enforcers? Well, that would be before I came to Dominion,)] Wes recalls, and you can't help but notice how his country accent gets a lot stronger as he thinks back to his past, [wes.speech(I spent my early life working on my parents' farm, out on the fringes of the Foloi Fields. Being the youngest of my eight siblings, I realised that I didn't stand much of a chance of inheriting anything, so rather than stay there and find out what ploughing fields would be like with a back bent by age, I decided to travel to the big city.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			At this point in his story, the fox-boy's muzzle turns up into a wry grin, and he scoffs, [wes.speech(I was so naive and foolish back then... I didn't realise how opportunistic and self-serving the majority of city folks are. I went from job to job, always being promised steady work, only to be laid off or replaced by cheaper labour a few weeks after I'd started.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(You poor thing,)] Elle interrupts. Sliding her hand down to rub at Wes's groin, she presses her huge breasts into the fox-boy's back and teases, [elle.speech(I can make you feel better...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(Later, Elle!)] Wes snaps, pushing his horny slave off of him and sighing, [wes.speech(Anyway, where was I... Oh yes, I'd been working odd jobs for a few months, and had finally saved up enough to rent a half-decent apartment. On my way to pay the landlord, I foolishly decided to take a shortcut through some alleyways, and ran straight into a pair of muggers...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Seemingly obsessed with her owner's cock, Elle steps forwards once again and leans heavily into Wes's back, before slipping her hand down to gently tease his groin. Interrupted once again, the fox-boy lets out a sigh and finishes his story by saying, [wes.speech(Anyway, to cut a long story short, I ended up being saved from the muggers by a passing Enforcer patrol. Being the impressionable young fool I was, I saw those kind Enforcers as being representative of all the realm's law enforcement, and quickly convinced myself that I should apply to join them...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Unable to ignore Elle's hand as it slips down into his trousers, Wes apologises, [wes.speech(Sorry, if you're interested in hearing more, ask me about this some other time. Elle here is being particularly difficult today!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As you watch Wes push his horny, unruly slave off of him once again, you wonder what you should say next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Wes about his past again, you ask him what he remembers of his life before becoming an Enforcer. 
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(Well, my early days in Dominion were nothing but bad memories of hopping from one temporary job to another, but my life before that was pretty good,)] he recalls, falling back into his country accent as he remembers his days on his family's farm, [wes.speech(I got on well with my brothers and sisters, but I was the only one out of all of them who wanted more out of life than to be working on the farm or in the local village. The work there wasn't bad, mind you, but I just felt like I was missing out on something being stuck there...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(You mean you wanted to find some hot city girls to fuck?)] Elle teases, before leaning in to playfully nibble on Wes's ear.
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(Not everyone is motivated by sex, you know,)] Wes sharply replies, pulling away from Elle's embrace as he finishes, [wes.speech(I've been back to visit my family several times, but no matter how much time passes, nothing there ever seems to change. My siblings are all still working on the farm or in the village, and none of them have any ambition to ever leave.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having come to the end of his tale, the fox-boy lets out a small sigh, before waiting for you to take the conversation elsewhere...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND_WES_2"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_background_progress")<5)
		<p>
			Having previously heard about Wes's early days on his family's farm and then about his experience of being saved from muggers in Dominion, you ask him if he can tell you more of what happened after that.
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(Well, as I mentioned before, I quickly convinced myself that joining the Enforcers and helping to uphold the law of the land was a just, righteous thing to do with my life,)] Wes says, his cynical tone of voice making it quite clear that he no longer believes this to be the case. Smirking to himself as he recalls his old memories, he continues, [wes.speech(My naive zeal was apparently just what the recruiters were looking for, as I was immediately accepted into the Academy. I didn't really pay it any notice at the time, but thinking back on it, I remember that all of us 'normal' folk had to do a hell of a lot of work to pass the tests, while all the demons and half-demons had to do was mention their demonic lineage to the instructors...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(If it was still anything like it was when I graduated, then that wasn't all we were doing to secure good grades,)] Elle flirtily teases, [elle.speech(I was on my instructor's desk spreading my legs for him practically every afternoon!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out an annoyed grunt as he pushes his horny slave away from him, Wes snaps, [wes.speech(That's exactly what I'm talking about! It's one rule for you, another for us. Anyway, despite the favouritism shown towards demons like Elle here, I ended up graduating from the Academy with better marks than most of them. For the next few years after that I worked as a regular Patrol officer, and despite there being some obvious signs of corruption, I chose to ignore them. I'd take all the unpleasant assignments given to me without complaint. Anything for justice, anything to clean up the streets, anything to uphold the pile of pleasant words I'd been fed at the Academy...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(What a good boy you must have been,)] Elle teases, before sliding her hands down over Wes's hips and reaching around to start stroking his groin. Leaning in over his shoulder, she breathlessly whispers, [elle.speech(Why don't I give you a reward for all of your past hard work...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pushing his unruly slave's hands away from his groin, Wes sighs, [wes.speech(Sorry, [pc.name], but she's getting to be too much again. Let's continue this another time.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Wes about his past again, you ask him what it was like working as a regular Patrol officer. 
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(It was all pretty much as you'd expect it to be,)] he says, [wes.speech(The more 'exciting' parts, such as catching muggers, were pretty few and far between. Most of my time was spent doing more mundane jobs, such as issuing fines, informing the public of the law, writing reports, and just walking around the streets to show criminals that we're never far away.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(What about your first arrest?)] Elle asks, seemingly just as curious as you are to hear more about Wes's early days as an Enforcer.
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(Looking back at it, I found it exciting at the time, sure,)] Wes admits, [wes.speech(It really wasn't anything special though. We'd got reports of a huge, aggressive wolf-boy mugging people in an alleyway close to HQ, and so I was sent with a more experienced partner to track him down and get him enslaved. We found him quickly enough, and instead of running, he actually tried to fight back.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Shaking his head as he recalls the outcome, Wes sighs, [wes.speech(I didn't lose my cool, and hit him straight in the chest with my taser. You know, it really is true what they say; 'The bigger they are, the harder they fall.')]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(So, did you fuck him?)] Elle playfully teases.
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(What?! Of course not!)] the fox-boy angrily replies, [wes.speech(I know a lot of the other Enforcers do that sort of thing, but never on my watch! Besides, you know I don't swing that way.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pushing Elle away from him, Wes turns back towards you and waits to hear what it is you'll ask next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND_WES_3"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_background_progress")<5)
		<p>
			Having heard all about Wes's early days as an Enforcer, you ask him where he went next in his career.
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(After three years of what my superiors described as 'exceptional commitment' to the job, I was approached by a recruiter for SWORD and told that I should apply for their training program,)] Wes reveals, before letting out a deep, remorseful sigh and continuing, [wes.speech(I can't believe that I was still so naive at that point. I actually believed all the crap the recruiter told me about SWORD being the branch that makes the most difference, and how my 'natural talent as an Enforcer' was being wasted in the regular Patrol units.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(You know, it only took me a year of serving before I was asked to join SWORD,)] Elle reveals, [elle.speech(It took you three?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Elle's words clearly strike a nerve in the fox-boy, and you see his eye twitch a little as he hisses through clenched teeth, [wes.speech(That's because you're a demon! Us normal folk usually have to work for at least five years in the Patrol before being considered eligible for SWORD training.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Well, whatever,)] the [elle.race] casually replies, before sliding her hands down to Wes's groin and teasing, [elle.speech(I can tell that you're getting worked up. How about I help you to relieve some stress...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(Not now, Elle!)] the fox-boy sharply replies, before pushing his unruly slave off of him and continuing, [wes.speech(So anyway, I signed up for SWORD, and spent the next several months having all of my naivety, trust, and respect for the Enforcers beaten out of me. To say that the training was brutal is a gross understatement, and despite the fact that you can only ever apply for SWORD once in your life, over half of my fellow recruits had dropped out after the first couple of weeks. Looking back on it, I should have done the same, but some kind of misguided sense of duty kept me going...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(My SWORD training wasn't like that at all,)] Elle reveals, [elle.speech(Sure, parts of it were tough, but all you had to do was ask the instructors to be a little nicer. I guess sucking their cocks helped a bit as well, but still, it really wasn't all that bad.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Whether it's her intention or not, Elle's words seem to infuriate the fox-boy, who closes his eyes and takes a long, deep breath to calm himself down, before saying, [wes.speech(You demons have no idea what the real training was like for us normal folk... None of the demons in my class had to live in the communal dormitory, none of them were publicly punished by the instructors, none of them were threatened with dismissal from the program if they failed even one of the fitness tests...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pushing Elle's hands away from his groin, Wes shakes his head clear of some unpleasant memories, before looking at you and saying, [wes.speech(Let's talk about something else for now. Did you want to buy any gear?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to find out why Wes's SWORD training was such a bad experience, you ask him what it involved. 
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(The vast majority of it was focused on physical training and weapons proficiency,)] he reveals, [wes.speech(The instructors were absolutely merciless; if anyone fell behind during the daily runs, they'd either get physically beaten or be forced to perform pointless, humiliating tasks. The worst one I saw was when a recruit thought it was a good idea to tell one of the instructors to 'fuck off'. By the time the instructors were finished with him, he could barely stand...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(I told an instructor to fuck off once,)] Elle recalls, [elle.speech(All I had to do was another lap around the track.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(Lucky you,)] Wes sighs, [wes.speech(It sure must have been nice, being a demon during training. As for the rest of us, it only got worse at night, when the instructors left us alone in the communal dormitory. The ones seen to have been the weak link during the day's exercises got ganged up on, hard. My naive views on Enforcer comradeship slipped quietly into the dark with each muffled scream I heard...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Come on, don't dwell on stuff like that,)] Elle says as she starts to undo Wes's belt. [elle.speech(You'd rather be fucking my throat, right?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pushing his horny slave's hands away from his groin, Wes sighs and asks you, [wes.speech(Is there anything else you wanted, [pc.name]?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND_WES_4"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_background_progress")<5)
		<p>
			Having heard about Wes's SWORD training, you ask him what he did after graduating.
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(I expected to be able to lead a fireteam,)] he says, [wes.speech(But apparently, foxes aren't considered to be a suitably martial race, and so I was told that I was being assigned to logistics. Instead of breaking down doors and putting an end to criminal gangs, I found myself sorting inventories and doing laundry for Third Company...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Logistics is just as important as the flashy combat roles,)] Elle says, dropping her hands down to start rubbing at Wes's crotch. Letting out a soft giggle, she points out, [elle.speech(It's not as fun as combat, sure, but it's one of the best places to be to get loads of sex!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(That's not on my list of priorities,)] Wes flatly replies as he pushes Elle's hands away from his groin. Letting out a sigh, he continues, [wes.speech(You are right about the importance of logistics, though. Without us, all the ground-pounders running around in the city would stop functioning within a week. Telling myself this day after day, I continued to work my way up the ranks, and even with there being a slower rate of promotion for non-combat personnel, I became Chief Inspector and Junior Quartermaster at the ripe young age of thirty-four.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(That's when I first met you,)] Elle says, teasing her fingers over the fox-boy's bushy tail. [elle.speech(Right from the start, I thought that there was something a little odd about the fact that a country boy had worked his way so high up the ranks in SWORD. I thought it'd be best not to try and seduce you, but oh, was I <i>so</i> wrong not to have done so. You've got so much stamina, and your cock's nice and big as well. When you shove your knot into my mouth... Fuck, I cum every time!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking more and more embarrassed the longer Elle goes on, Wes suddenly snaps, [wes.speech(Elle, please! Can you try to control yourself for just five minutes?!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Mmm,)] the horny [elle.race] hums, [elle.speech(I just want another taste of your cock...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(It was while working here that I finally acknowledged the corruption within the Enforcers,)] Wes continues, ignoring Elle's persistent fondling of his crotch as he reveals, [wes.speech(Half-demons and demons always get promoted over ordinary folk, even when it's obvious that they're ill-suited for the job at hand. Just look at Elle here; all she did on the job was fucking her way around the station, leaving all of the real work for me to do.)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(But fucking is so much fun,)] Elle whines, before pouting at Wes and saying, [elle.speech(You know, nobody else comes close to having your stamina and technique; I just want your big fox-cock stuffed deep into one of my holes... Fuck, I need it <i>now</i>...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Dropping down onto her knees, the horny [elle.race] shuffles underneath the counter and out of sight. By now seeming to have learned to just deal with Elle's horniness instead of repeatedly resisting it, Wes tries to keep a straight face as Elle covertly starts giving him a blowjob, and he grunts, [wes.speech(I can tell you the rest of my story tomorrow; Elle here is being particularly forceful at the moment...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Wes about his experiences working in SWORD logistics, you ask him what sort of duties he was expected to perform. 
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(My old job was exactly the same as what I'm having to do now,)] the fox-boy sighs, [wes.speech(Having to make more regular reports to my superiors means that I don't even get to enjoy the use of my new office.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(You do when you take me in there to fuck me,)] Elle interjects, before leaning in over Wes's shoulder to playfully nibble on his fox-like ear.
		</p>
		<p>
			Shaking himself free of his unruly slave's embrace, Wes sighs, [wes.speech(Sometimes it feels like the universe is out to get me. I spend all of my life working so hard to do the right thing, and then when I finally get the promotion I deserve, what do I get rewarded with? Even more work than I had to do before, only this time, with a horny half-demon interrupting me every five minutes trying to get into my pants.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(You know you love it really,)] Elle giggles, [elle.speech(Especially when I do the 'naughty Enforcer' roleplay for you...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Loudly clearing his throat to interrupt Elle before she says anything else to embarrass him, Wes looks at you and states, [wes.speech(Let's change the subject. Is there anything you wanted to buy from me?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_BACKGROUND_WES_5"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_background_progress")<=5)
		<p>
			Wanting to hear the final part of Wes's story about his background, you ask him what happened after he started working here at the Enforcer HQ and saw clear evidence of demons being promoted over more competent non-demons.
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(What happened? Nothing,)] Wes sighs, [wes.speech(What could I do about it? The people who would end up investigating unfair promotions would likely be demons themselves, and the end result would most likely either be nothing, or, if I was unlucky, I'd be the one being disciplined for 'wasting their time'. Even when I discovered evidence of Elle siphoning off weapons to sell to gangs, I couldn't do anything about it. That is, until I happened to read a report about some kind of vigilante who managed to clear out the Harpy Nests...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Well, everything worked out well thanks to that,)] Elle surprisingly remarks, before pressing her huge breasts into Wes's back and saying to you, [elle.speech(I was only doing that to try and get some more fun into my life, but being Wes's slave is far better than anything I could have asked for! I can't get enough of his cock, and, luckily for me, he loves it when I give him a blowjob or spread my legs for him in his office...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(That's enough, Elle!)] Wes snaps, but his command is ignored by his horny slave, who drops down onto her knees and once again shuffles forwards under the counter.
		</p>
		<p>
			Demonstrating a legendary level of self-control, Wes keeps a straight face as Elle starts sucking his cock beneath the counter and grunts, [wes.speech(Now you know all that there is worth knowing about my past... Is there anything else I can help you with? Do you want to buy some gear, or perhaps you could help me again by taking Elle over to my office and working some of the horniness out of her system...)] 
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to Wes about the corruption in the Enforcer HQ, you ask him whether Elle's arrest has made any sort of impact on the other officers. 
		</p>
		<p>
			[wes.speech(I can't say that it has,)] the fox-boy sighs, [wes.speech(I doubt that anything much is going to change as a result of Elle's enslavement. I suppose that I'll have to be satisfied with just one less corrupt Enforcer...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(I'll make you satisfied, all right,)] Elle teases, before reaching down to grope Wes's groin and breathlessly whisper into his ear, [elle.speech(I want to be choking on your knot again tonight...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pushing his horny slave off of him, Wes clears his throat and asks, [wes.speech(So, [pc.name], is there anything else I can do for you?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_WORK -->
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasQuestInLine(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_WES, QUEST_WES_3_ELLE))
		<p>
			Deciding to try and make some small-talk with Elle, you ask her how her work is going.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Deciding to try and make some small-talk with Wes, you ask him how his work is going.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK_ELLE_1"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Well, I was supposed to have had a report on my superior's desk this morning, but while working on it late last evening, I kind of got distracted and ended up spending all night riding Wes's cock,)] she admits with a big smirk on her face. Leaning forwards over the counter, she bites her lip and reveals, [elle.speech(I was given an extension on the report's deadline, so I've got plenty of time in which to do some more fucking...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Elle doesn't seem interested in talking about her work any further than that, and so you're quickly left wondering what to say to her next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK_ELLE_2"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[elle.speech(It's going pretty well; I've got Wes handling most of the work, but although he does a good job, I can't help but keep on interrupting him to get more of his big cock,)] Elle giggles, before leaning forwards over the counter and suggestively teasing, [elle.speech(I just can't stop myself; I'm so horny all the time...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Elle doesn't seem interested in talking about her work any further than that, and so you're quickly left wondering what to say to her next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK_ELLE_3"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[elle.speech(I need to have a report on the inventory's status ready for tomorrow, but every time I begin work on it, I start daydreaming about Wes's big cock,)] Elle wistfully replies, [elle.speech(I hope that I can resist fucking him all night; I'll be in big trouble if I don't get this report finished on time...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Elle doesn't seem interested in talking about her work any further than that, and so you're quickly left wondering what to say to her next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK_ELLE_4"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[elle.speech(I actually don't really have too much work to do at the moment, as I've got Wes handling it all,)] Elle admits, before smirking and continuing to reveal, [elle.speech(He's not working as fast as he could be, though, as I keep on interrupting him to get another taste of his big cock...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Elle doesn't seem interested in talking about her work any further than that, and so you're quickly left wondering what to say to her next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK_ELLE_5"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Everything's going fine; I had to give a presentation to my superiors earlier, but now that that's out of the way, I can leave the rest of the day's work to Wes,)] she replies, before playfully biting her lip and revealing, [elle.speech(You know, I couldn't stop thinking about Wes's cock during the whole of the presentation, and when I got back here, I rode him for almost an hour without any break...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Elle doesn't seem interested in talking about her work any further than that, and so you're quickly left wondering what to say to her next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK_WES_1"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().getSavedLong("wes_background_progress")<4)
		<p>
			[wes.speech(To tell you the truth, I'm finding the learning curve of being master of both the borough's equipment and Elle to be pretty steep,)] Wes sighs, [wes.speech(It's taking a bit of a toll on me.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Come on, I'm not <i>that</i> demanding, am I?)] Elle asks while continuing to forcefully press her huge breasts into Wes's back.
		</p>
		<p>
			Simply letting out a weary sigh in response, the fox-boy asks, [wes.speech(So, is there anything else I can do for you, [pc.name]?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[wes.speech(Everything's going better now than it was to start with,)] Wes replies, [wes.speech(It took me a while to figure out how best to handle Elle, but it seems best to just let her do her thing and then carry on with work after she's satisfied.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[elle.speech(Mmm, yeah, that works a lot better, doesn't it, babe?)] Elle teases.
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out an amused huff in response, the fox-boy asks, [wes.speech(So, is there anything else I can do for you, [pc.name]?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
		
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK_WES_2"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[wes.speech(I've got a huge amount of inventory management work to get done by the end of today,)] the fox-boy responds, [wes.speech(Elle is mostly proving to be more of a hindrance than a help...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Hey, I help by making sure that your balls are regularly emptied, don't I?)] Elle teases.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(See what I mean?)] Wes sighs, before asking, [wes.speech(So, is there anything else I can do for you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK_WES_3"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Everything's going well today, thanks to Elle,)] the fox-boy responds, [wes.speech(She was able to 'convince' my superior to give me an extra few days to get a report finished. Of course, it was Elle's fault in the first place that the report wasn't done on time...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(I told you that I'd sort it out for you,)] Elle teases, [elle.speech(All I had to do was give him a quick handjob!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Next time, it would be better if you just let me get the report done on time to begin with,)] Wes sighs, before asking, [wes.speech(So, is there anything else I can do for you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK_WES_4"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[wes.speech(I had to give a presentation to my superiors earlier, which went far better than I could have hoped for,)] the fox-boy proudly responds, before letting out a sigh and revealing, [wes.speech(When I got back, however, Elle tricked me into going into my office, before locking the door and refusing to hand over the key until I'd let her ride my cock...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(You make it sound like you didn't enjoy it,)] Elle complains, [elle.speech(You know you love it when I show you my dominant side!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Well, thanks to you 'showing off your dominant side', I've got no real work done all day,)] Wes replies, before looking over at you and asking, [wes.speech(So, is there anything else I can do for you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_WORK_WES_5"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Things are going relatively well, but I'd be much further ahead with my work if Elle didn't keep on interrupting me,)] Wes reveals, [wes.speech(She's absolutely insatiable...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(You know you love it,)] Elle teases in response, [elle.speech(I can't imagine how boring it would be for you if I wasn't here to suck your cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(I suppose I can't argue with that,)] Wes relents, before looking over at you and asking, [wes.speech(So, is there anything else I can do for you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to have a little fun with Elle, you start flirting back with her, and before you know it, she's staring hungrily at your body and dropping multiple graphic hints that she wants to take you to her office and fuck you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not being able to control herself, she's soon unlocking the door to the storage area, before stepping out to the other side of her counter and getting physical with you. Pressing her hot body up against you, she reaches down to give your groin a firm grope, before breathlessly suggesting, [elle.speech(Come on, [pc.name], how about you let me give you a very personal tour of my office?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that a 'tour of Elle's office' will undoubtedly lead into having sex with the horny [elle.race], you wonder what to say in response to her suggestion...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_DECLINED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you were happy enough to flirt with her, you don't really want to have sex with Elle, and so you [pc.step] back and turn down her offer.
	</p>
	<p>
		For a brief moment, you see a furious look flash across the [elle.race]'s bright pink eyes, before she lets out an annoyed tut and declares, [elle.speech(You shouldn't lead me on if you aren't willing to go all the way!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Elle storms over to the nearby door, and after unlocking it, quickly returns to the other side of the counter. Thankfully, the angry expression on her face fades away almost as quickly as it appeared, and after adjusting her uniform, she flashes you a mischievous smirk and light-heartedly declares, [elle.speech(I won't fall for your tricks again, [pc.name]! Not today at least... Anyway, is there anything else I can help you with?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of Elle's suggestion, you tell her that you'd love to have a tour of her office. After flashing you a dirty smirk as she hears you agree to go with her, Elle calls out over the counter, [elle.speech(Wes! I'm heading out for a while; look after the place while I'm gone!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Upon hearing an affirmative reply from her slave, Elle leads you out of the requisitions area and over to the door of her office. Unlocking the door, she steps forwards and beckons you inside.
	</p>
	<p>
		The moment you [pc.step] into her spacious office, the horny [elle.race] immediately shuts and locks the door behind you, before rushing forwards and pulling you into a desperate, passionate kiss. Flapping her wings in excitement, and sending a pile of stacked papers flying across the room in the process, Elle pulls back from kissing you and breathlessly pants, [elle.speech(So, are you going to take the lead, or shall I?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_SEX_START_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Firmly taking hold of Elle's hips, you pull her into your body, before telling her that you're going to be the one in charge. Pulling the hot [elle.race] into a dominant kiss, you reach around and give her [elle.ass+] a good grope, before pulling back and wondering how best to fuck her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_ELLE_OFFICE_SEX_START_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting Elle take charge, you submissively lean in against her and allow her to pull you into another dominant, forceful kiss. Reaching around to give your [pc.ass+] a good grope, the horny [elle.race] pulls back and moans, 
		#IF(elle.getTotalTimesHadSex(pc)>0)
			 [elle.speech(Let's do this a little differently than the last time we were in here...)]
		#ELSE
			 [elle.speech(I'm looking forward to adding you to my list of sexual conquests!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ELLE_END_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ELLE_END_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(elle.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			Letting out a deeply satisfied sigh, Elle steps over to her luxurious leather office chair and sinks down into it. Flashing you a cheeky smirk, she moans, [elle.speech(You were good, [pc.name]... <i>Real</i> good...)]
		#ELSE
			Letting out a frustrated sigh, Elle steps over to her luxurious leather office chair and sinks down into it. Pouting at you in annoyance, she whines, [elle.speech(I'm not satisfied from that, [pc.name]... It's no problem, as I'll just have Wes finish me off, but I was really hoping for more from you...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After quickly getting your things back in order, you and Elle move over to the door of her office, and after she's unlocked it, you [pc.step] back out into the corridor beyond. Saying that she needs to get back to work, the [elle.race] heads back into the requisitions area, leaving you wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to have a little fun with Wes, you start flirting with him and playfully teasing him about the sorts of things he gets up to with Elle. Thanks to his slave's prior teasing and sexual harassment, the fox-boy seems to already be very horny, and after just a few minutes of being subjected to your flirty behaviour, you can tell that he's keen to fuck you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising what's going on, Elle offers Wes her own series of flirtatious remarks in a clear attempt at getting him to fuck her instead of you. Caught between the two of you making advances upon him, Wes soon appears to be on the edge of losing his cool, and you realise that you could easily take advantage of his arousal by asking him to give you a 'personal tour' of his office...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_FINISH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_FINISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding against taking things any further with Wes, you put an end to your flirtatious remarks and stop teasing him. Taking advantage of the fact that you've dropped out of the race, Elle brazenly slips her hand down Wes's trousers and starts giving him a handjob.
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing his absolute best to retain his composure, the fox-boy ignores Elle's happy little moans and grunts, [wes.speech(So, [pc.name]... Can... Can I do anything else for you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Eager to get into Wes's pants, you put on your most seductive voice and ask him if he could give you a private tour of his office.
	</p>
	<p>
		On edge from all of the teasing that you and Elle have subjected him to, the fox-boy quickly replies, [wes.speech(I'd love to, [pc.name]! Elle, watch the place while I'm gone.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Ignoring his slave's disappointed whine, Wes unlocks the door to the storage area, before stepping out to the other side of the counter and hooking one of his arms around your waist. Pressing your body up against him, you allow Wes to lead you out into the corridor and over to the door of his office. Unlocking the door, and with his arm still around your waist, he leads you inside and locks the door after him.
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing exactly what it is that he wants, the fox-boy steps up to you and pulls you into a passionate kiss. Holding you in his tight embrace for a moment, he pulls back, before smirking at you and asking, [wes.speech(Are you happy with me taking the lead?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_SEX_START_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Flashing Wes a smirk of your own, you tell him that you're going to be the one in charge, to which he responds, [wes.speech(That's fine with me, [pc.name].)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eagerly pulling the fox-boy into your dominant embrace, you wonder how best to fuck him...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_SEX_START_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Happy to let Wes act as the dominant partner, you tell him that he can take the lead, and let out a happy little [pc.moan] as he pulls you into his embrace. After planting another passionate kiss on your [pc.lips+], the fox-boy pulls back and prepares to start fucking you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_END_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_END_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(wes.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			Letting out a deeply satisfied sigh, Wes steps over to his luxurious leather office chair and sinks down into it. Flashing you a warm smile, he sighs, [wes.speech(That was just what I needed... Thanks, [pc.name]...)]
		#ELSE
			Letting out a frustrated sigh, Wes steps over to his luxurious leather office chair and sinks down into it. Still sporting a clear erection, he tuts, [wes.speech(That really wasn't enough to satisfy me, [pc.name]... I guess I'll have to let Elle finish me off...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After quickly getting your things back in order, you and Wes move over to the door of his office, and after he's unlocked it, you [pc.step] back out into the corridor beyond. Saying that he needs to get back to work, the fox-boy heads back into the requisitions area, leaving you wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting Elle to miss out on the fun, and knowing that Wes has by now grown accustomed to having sex with his perpetually-horny slave, you ask the fox-boy to give you and Elle a personal tour of his office.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elle.speech(Oooh, I like the sound of that!)] the [elle.race] eagerly exclaims.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(I really could do with taking a break,)] Wes states, before placing a 'be back soon' sign on the counter's surface and declaring, [wes.speech(Come on then, Elle, follow me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With his excited slave beside him, Wes unlocks the door to the storage area, before stepping out to the other side of the counter and hooking one of his arms around your waist. Not wanting to be left out, Elle presses herself up against Wes's free side, letting out a happy giggle as the fox-boy takes hold of her waist with his free hand.
	</p>
	<p>
		With you and Elle now on either side of him, Wes heads out into the corridor and over to the door of his office. Retrieving the keys from out of her owner's pocket, Elle unlocks the door, and joins you in being ushered inside by the horny fox-boy.
	</p>
	<p>
		Shutting and locking the door after him, Wes lets out a surprised cry as you and Elle immediately press yourselves up against him. Jostling against one another in your haste to passionately kiss the fox-boy, you and the [elle.race] start groping Wes's body, causing him to ask, [wes.speech(Hey, hey, who's meant to be the one in charge in here?!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Choosing this moment in which to make your intentions clear, you declare to Elle and Wes that you're the one in charge. Happy enough to let you take the dominant role, the two of them wait to see what it is you'll decide to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_JOINT_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Moving around behind Elle, you reach down to give her [elle.ass+] a good grope, before telling her that it only seems right that the slave should be the one to take the submissive role. Happy enough to let you and Wes take the dominant role, the [elle.race] lets out an excited moan and waits to see how the two of you will decide to use her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_JOINT_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Following Elle's lead in submissively rubbing up against Wes, you tell the fox-boy that he should take charge. Happy enough to take the dominant role, Wes orders the two of you to get down on all fours and present yourselves to him. Doing as you're told, you drop down onto the floor beside Elle, before preparing to be fucked beside her by Wes...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to be dominated by Wes and Elle, you tell them that they should take charge and fuck you.
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 Happy enough to do as you suggest, Elle pushes you down so that you're lying on your animalistic stomach, before moving around in front of you and preparing to use your mouth. Kneeling down behind your feral [pc.legRace]'s body, Wes joins his slave in getting ready to dominantly fuck you...
		#ELSE
			 Happy enough to do as you suggest, Elle pushes you down onto the floor so that you're lying on your back, before kneeling down and planting her groin over your face.
			 #IF(pc.hasLegs())
				 Kneeling down between your legs, Wes joins his slave in getting ready to dominantly fuck you...
			 #ELSE
				 Kneeling down over your groin, Wes joins his slave in getting ready to dominantly fuck you...
			 #ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REQUISITIONS_FLIRT_WES_OFFICE_THREESOME_ELLE_REVENGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be fun for Elle to take charge, you convince Wes to join you in submitting to the horny [elle.race]. Happy to find herself being put in charge, Elle dominantly pushes you and Wes down onto your backs, before straddling you in the cowgirl position and wondering out loud how best to fuck the two of you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_END_SEX_THREESOME -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_END_SEX_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(wes.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			Letting out a deeply satisfied sigh, Wes steps over to his luxurious leather office chair and sinks down into it. Flashing you and Elle a warm smile, he sighs, [wes.speech(That was just what I needed... Thanks, you two...)]
		#ELSE
			Letting out a frustrated sigh, Wes steps over to his luxurious leather office chair and sinks down into it. Still sporting a clear erection, he tuts, [wes.speech(That really wasn't enough to satisfy me... I guess you can finish me off back in the requisitions area, Elle...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After quickly getting your things back in order, the three of you move over to the door of Wes's office, and after he's unlocked it, you [pc.step] back out into the corridor beyond. Saying that he needs to get back to work, the fox-boy leads Elle back into the requisitions area, leaving you wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_ELLE_OFFICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_ELLE_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have some fun with Elle, you tell Wes that you're willing to take him up on his offer of working some of the horniness out of his slave's system. Hearing what it is that you're saying, Elle lets out an excited moan, before telling Wes that she's happy to go and spend some time with you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wes.speech(Great, I should be able to get this work finished in the meantime,)] the fox-boy sighs in relief, before handing a key to his slave and instructing her, [wes.speech(Go and use my office, and come straight back here after you're done.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking the key from Wes, Elle unlocks the door to the storage area, before stepping out to the other side of the counter and getting physical with you. Pressing her hot body up against you, she reaches down to give your groin a firm grope, before breathlessly teasing, [elle.speech(Don't worry, [pc.name], I don't hold anything against you for helping Wes to get me arrested and enslaved... I'm just looking forward to having a good fuck!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she's the one who's got the key, you let Elle take the lead as she heads out of the requisitions area and over to the door of Wes's office. Quickly unlocking it, she steps forwards and beckons you inside.
	</p>
	<p>
		The moment you [pc.step] into Wes's spacious office, the horny [elle.race] immediately shuts and locks the door behind you, before rushing forwards and pulling you into a desperate, passionate kiss. Flapping her wings in excitement, and sending a pile of stacked papers flying across the room in the process, Elle pulls back from kissing you and breathlessly pants, [elle.speech(So, are you going to take the lead, or shall I?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_ELLE_OFFICE_START_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Firmly taking hold of Elle's hips, you pull her into your body, before telling her that you're going to be the one in charge. Pulling the hot [elle.race] into a dominant kiss, you reach around and give her [elle.ass+] a good grope, before pulling back and wondering how best to fuck her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_ELLE_OFFICE_START_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting Elle take charge, you submissively lean in against her and allow her to pull you into a dominant, forceful kiss. Reaching around to give your [pc.ass+] a good grope, the horny [elle.race] pulls back and moans, 
		#IF(elle.getTotalTimesHadSex(pc)>0)
			 [elle.speech(Let's do this a little differently than the last time we were in here...)]
		#ELSE
			 [elle.speech(I'm looking forward to adding you to my list of sexual conquests!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WES_END_SEX_ELLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WES_END_SEX_ELLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(elle.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			Letting out a deeply satisfied sigh, Elle steps over to Wes's luxurious leather office chair and sinks down into it. Flashing you a cheeky smirk, she moans, [elle.speech(You were good, [pc.name]... <i>Real</i> good...)]
		#ELSE
			Letting out a frustrated sigh, Elle steps over to Wes's luxurious leather office chair and sinks down into it. Pouting at you in annoyance, she whines, [elle.speech(I'm not satisfied from that, [pc.name]... It's no problem, as I'll just have Wes finish me off, but I was really hoping for more from you...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After quickly getting your things back in order, you and Elle move over to the door of Wes's office, and after she's unlocked it, you [pc.step] back out into the corridor beyond. Saying that she needs to quickly return to Wes, the [elle.race] heads back into the requisitions area, leaving you wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
