<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The tunnels of Submission have an ominous feel to them at the best of times, but as you make your way down the dirty, deserted passageways, you're filled with a particular sense of dread, as though something terrible is about to happen.
	</p>
	<p>
		At first, the sinister silence that permeates these gloomy catacombs is broken only by the rustling of litter that you disturb underfoot, but as you travel ever onwards, you start hearing faint sounds of movement coming from somewhere far behind you. Realising that you're being followed, and not wanting to be inadvertently shepherded into a trap that might be lying up ahead, you stand your ground and turn to face the direction of your pursuers.
	</p>
	<p>
		After just a moment, you catch sight of the ones that have been following you, as from around the far corner, there appear the forms of four imps. One of these is larger than the others, and, although [npc.her] wings look large enough to sustain flight, [npc.sheIs] choosing to walk upon the ground, while the other three, smaller imps, are fluttering along in the air a short way behind.
	</p>
	<p>
		All four of the imps are dressed in skimpy rags, and, perhaps due to the fact that they appear more comfortable flying around than walking, you notice that the three smaller imps lack any form of footwear. Although all four of the imps have impressive busts, the alpha-imp's breasts are almost comically-huge, and [npc.she] swaggers from side-to-side as [npc.she] leads [npc.her] three companions around the corner.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.she] catches sight of you, the alpha-imp stops in [npc.her] tracks. Obviously being the leader of this gang, [npc.she] steps forwards and sizes you up, before declaring, in a sultry voice, [npc.speech(Ooh! Looks like we've got ourselves a new toy to play with, girls!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The three smaller imps flutter forwards to back their leader up, and [npc3.name] bites [npc3.her] lip as [npc3.she] sighs, [npc3.speech(~Mmm!~ I bet [pc.she] can't wait to taste my pussy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking this opportunity to have [npc4.herself] heard, [npc4.name] giggles, [npc4.speech(I want [pc.herHim] to get a good grope of my tits!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		It's quite clear that these imps are only interested in one thing, and as they start to advance, the third imp, who up until now had been quite content to simply wink and pout at you, puts any doubts as to their intentions to rest, as [npc2.she] calls out, 
		#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
		#THEN
			[npc2.speech(Lucky you! I've still got one of the boss's special potions left! Ooh, I can't wait to turn you into a big manly stud, with a nice thick cock, and big balls ready to pump some yummy cum into my pussy! Oh! And a nice, long tongue for eating us out!)]
		#ELSE
			[npc2.speech(Lucky you! I've still got one of the boss's special potions left! Ooh, I can't wait for you to grow a nice thick cock, with big balls ready to pump some yummy cum into my pussy! Oh! And a nice, long tongue for eating us out!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_BODY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Easily seduced by the imps erotic words, you decide that the best course of action would be to just give the gang what they want. Stepping back, you hold up your [pc.hands] as you submit. [pc.speech(Please, there's no need for violence. You just want sex, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(So, you know your place!)] [npc.name] laughs, before turning [npc.her] head and ordering [npc.her] subordinates to subdue you, [npc.speech(Get [pc.herHim] down, quick!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Two of the smaller imps immediately dart forwards, and, flying up to each side of you, they grab your [pc.arms], before folding their wings behind their backs and using their weight to pull you down onto your knees. As you hit the floor, you look up to see [npc.name] and [npc2.name] stepping forwards, grinning in delight as they see that you're not going to put up a fight.
	</p>
	#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
	#THEN
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Give me the potion,)] [npc.name] commands [npc.her] partner. Quickly producing a bottle of strange liquid, [npc2.name] hands it over to her superior, who immediately pulls the stopper out and steps forwards, before grabbing your chin and squeezing your cheeks. 
			#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
			#THEN
				[npc.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll turn you into our manly stud, with a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll give you a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			With no further warning, and not even giving you time to do as [npc.she] commands, [npc.name] shoves the bottle past your [pc.lips], and you feel the warm, sickly-sweet liquid entering your mouth...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Aww... You've got your mouth blocked! If only the boss was here, she could get rid of that seal enchantment! Eugh!)] [npc.name] tuts. Turning to [npc.her] subordinate, [npc.she] sighs, [npc.speech(Save that potion for the next one we catch. Let's just see what fun we can have with this one as [pc.she] is.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With no further warning, [npc.name] reaches forwards and grabs your shoulders, before pushing you down onto your back. [npc.speech(That's right, lie back and relax! Time to be a good fuck-toy!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_DEFEAT_NO_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Imps do not TF you. This shouldn't be possible, and is a bug! Please report it to Innoxia with the message: 'impAttackDemon COMBAT_DEFEAT_NO_TF is being triggered.'
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to withstand another attack, you collapse to your knees, before desperately trying to catch your breath as you plead, [pc.speech(No more... Please...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not giving you a moment's respite, [npc.name] snaps [npc.her] fingers, before pointing at you and ordering [npc.her] subordinates, [npc.speech(Restrain [pc.herHim]! Go on, get [pc.herHim]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Immediately, two of the smaller imps rush forwards to either side of you, and, grabbing your [pc.arms], they use their body-weight to hold you still. [npc3.Name] lets out a mocking laugh as [npc3.she] reaches around to squeeze your [pc.ass], while [npc4.name] takes this opportunity to 
		#IF pc.hasBreasts()
		#THEN
			reach up and grope your [pc.breasts].
		#ELSE
			rub [npc4.her] groin up against your waist.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
	#THEN
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Give me the potion,)] [npc.name] snaps at [npc.her] partner. Quickly producing a bottle of strange liquid, [npc2.name] hands it over to her superior, who immediately pulls the stopper out and steps forwards, before grabbing your chin and squeezing your cheeks. 
			#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
			#THEN
				 [npc.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll turn you into our manly stud, with a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll give you a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			With no further warning, and not even giving you time to do as [npc.she] commands, [npc.name] shoves the bottle past your [pc.lips], and you feel the warm, sickly-sweet liquid entering your mouth...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[npc.speech(This [pc.insult]'s got [pc.her] mouth blocked! If only the boss was here, she could get rid of that seal enchantment! Eugh!)] [npc.name] tuts. Turning to [npc.her] subordinate, [npc.she] snaps, [npc.speech(Save that potion for the next one we catch! Let's just fuck [pc.herHim] already.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With no further warning, [npc.name] reaches forwards and grabs the back of your head, before pushing you down onto the floor. [npc.speech(Get down, [pc.insult]! Time to be a good fuck-toy for us!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself down on the floor, and at the mercy of the imps' carnal desires, you decide that the best thing for you to do would be to simply go along with whatever they have in store for you. Sensing your willingness to go along with all of this, [npc.name] sneers down at you, [npc.speech(What a submissive bitch you turned out to be! You're just a horny dog who can't wait to fuck us imps, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to cause any trouble by arguing back, you mutter, [pc.speech(Y-Yes... That's right...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you agree with [npc.name], you suddenly feel [npc3.name] start to grope and squeeze your ass, before [npc3.she] calls out, [npc3.speech(I bet you've lost count of the number of us imps you've fucked!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(I want to hear this slut beg to fuck us!)] [npc2.Name] jeers, stepping up beside [npc.name] to smirk down at your submissive form. [npc2.speech(Go on, say it. Say you're nothing more than an imp's sex-toy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'm nothing more than an imp's sex toy...)] You offer, knowing that your words are about to be put to the test.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Louder! And <i>beg</i> for us to let you fuck us!)] [npc2.Name] snaps, clearly not satisfied with your half-hearted answer.
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that you're at the mercy of these evil imps, you decide that it'd be best to do as you're told, and cry out, [pc.speech(I'm nothing more than an imp's sex-toy! Please, I want to fuck imps! Please let me fuck you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc4.speech(That's what we like to hear!)] [npc4.Name] laughs from somewhere off to one side, and you can't help but let out a small [pc.moan] as the imps start moving into position, ready to do as you've just asked and start fucking you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_EAGER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself being pushed to the floor, and at the mercy of the imps' carnal desires, you feel yourself getting immensely turned-on, and can barely contain the [pc.moan+] that drifts out from between your [pc.lips]. Hearing the lewd noise that just came out of your mouth, [npc.name] sneers down at you, [npc.speech(What a submissive bitch you turned out to be! You're just a horny dog who can't wait to fuck us imps, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Your arousal gets the better of you, and before you can think things through, you call out, [pc.speech(Yes! Please, I want to fuck you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you happily respond to [npc.name], you suddenly feel [npc3.name] start to grope and squeeze your ass, before [npc3.she] calls out, [npc3.speech(I bet you've lost count of the number of us imps you've fucked!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(I want to hear this slut beg to fuck us!)] [npc2.Name] jeers, stepping up beside [npc.name] to smirk down at your submissive form. [npc2.speech(Go on, say it. Say you're nothing more than an imp's sex-toy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'm nothing more than an imp's sex-toy! Please, I want to fuck imps! Please let me fuck you!)] You [pc.moan], biting your [pc.lip] as you look up at [npc2.name].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(My, my! How eager you are!)] [npc2.Name] laughs, satisfied with your enthusiastic answer. [npc2.speech(Don't worry, you'll be getting what you crave so badly soon enough!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc4.speech(I love it when they're as desperate as this one!)] [npc4.Name] laughs from somewhere off to one side, and you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] as the imps start moving into position, ready to give you what you're so obviously craving...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_RESIST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself being pushed to the floor, and at the mercy of the imps' carnal desires, you start to panic, and try to stand up again as you cry out, [pc.speech(Stop this! Leave me alone!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you try to push yourself up onto your knees, however, [npc.name] steps forwards and grabs the back of your head, before roughly shoving you back down into your submissive position. [npc.speech(This is what you get for coming into our territory! Don't worry, we'll get you moaning before we're done with you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you start to cry out and protest, you suddenly feel [npc3.namePos] [npc3.hands] groping and squeezing your ass. Before you're able to turn and tell [npc3.herHim] to stop, [npc3.she] calls out, [npc3.speech(I bet you've lost count of the number of us imps you've fucked!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(This [pc.insult] needs to be shown [pc.her] place!)] [npc2.Name] jeers, stepping up beside [npc.name] to smirk down at your defeated form. [npc2.speech(You'll love being an imp's sex-toy! We'll make sure of that!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(No! You can't do this!)] You cry out as you struggle against the imps.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(You'll be begging for it soon enough!)] [npc2.Name] snaps, clearly not having the patience for any more of your protests.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc4.speech(It's fun getting to break in unwilling cunts like you!)] [npc4.Name] laughs from somewhere off to one side, and you can't help but let out a frantic wail as the imps start moving into position, ready to start fucking you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF_REFUSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You have no intention of swallowing the imps' transformative potion, and, jerking your head back, you spit the liquid out all over the floor. Your resistance is immediately met by a sharp slap to the face, accompanied by a loud screech as [npc.name] hurls the bottle to one side. [npc.speech(Fuck! Do you know how much trouble the boss goes through to get these potions for us?! [pc.Insult]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.NamePos] insults are easy to weather, knowing what the alternative was, and you simply cast your gaze to the floor as you wait for [npc.herHim] to calm down. As you do this, however, [npc.she] suddenly reaches forwards, and, grabbing you by the back of the neck, forces you down onto the floor. [npc.speech(Get down, [pc.insult]! If you can't do something so simple as drinking a potion, all you're good for is being a fuck-toy for us to use!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF_ACCEPTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You gulp down the sweet, syrup-like liquid, before opening your mouth to show [npc.name] that you've done as [npc.she] commanded. Your display of submission is met by a devious grin that quickly settles on [npc.namePos] face, and [npc.she] carelessly hurls the now-empty bottle to one side as [npc.she] steps back and looks down at you. [npc.speech(Good dog. You're just a bitch for us imps to command, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes...)] You absent-mindedly reply, concentrating more on the strange feeling that's started to bubble up inside your body than whatever it is that the imp just asked of you. As you feel the curious sensation start to change into a steady warmth that permeates through your entire body, you realise that the potion's transformative effects are about to make themselves known... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF_APPLIED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As the potion's effects come to an end, [npc.name] suddenly steps forwards, and, grabbing you by the back of the neck, forces you down onto the floor. [npc.speech(Good bitch! Now that you're just as we want you, it's time for you to act as our fuck-toy!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_DEFEAT_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had their fun, the imps step back, allowing you to collapse down onto the floor as you pant from exertion.
		#IF (pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc.getId()) || pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc2.getId()) || pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc3.getId()) || pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc4.getId()))
		#THEN
			#IF pc.isVisiblyPregnant()
			#THEN
				Suddenly, you feel [npc.name] sliding [npc.her] fingers into your freshly-creampied pussy, and you let out an exhausted moan as [npc.she] snickers, [npc.speech(Shame you're already knocked up, slut. We could have done with you pumping out some more imps to bolster our gang's numbers.)]
			#ELSE
				Suddenly, you feel [npc.name] sliding [npc.her] fingers into your freshly-creampied pussy, and you let out an exhausted moan as [npc.she] snickers, [npc.speech(Wondering if we got you knocked up, huh slut? Well, if you do end up birthing some more imps, you just send them this way. We could always do with more gang members!)]
			#ENDIF
			#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
			#THEN
				</p>
				<p>
					Before you can respond, [npc.name] steps forwards and shoves [npc.her] cum-coated fingers into your mouth. [npc.speech(Clean me off, bitch.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					With little choice but to do as you're told, you lick the cum from [npc.namePos] fingers
					#IF pc.isVisiblyPregnant()
					#THEN.
					#ELSE, and as you do so, you can't help but wonder if the imp's seed has gotten you pregnant.
					#ENDIF
					 Quickly being forced to swallow down the salty goo that's now in your mouth, you look up as [npc.name] smirks down at you one last time, before gathering [npc.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
				#ELSE
				</p>
				<p>
					Before you can respond, [npc.name] steps forwards and starts wiping [npc.her] cum-coated fingers all over your face. [npc.speech(Hold still, bitch. I don't want this on my hands.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					With little choice but to do as you're told, you hold still as [npc.name] wipes [npc.her] fingers on your face.
					#IF !pc.isVisiblyPregnant()
					#THEN As you feel the slimy spunk being spread over your cheeks, you can't help but wonder if the imp's seed has gotten you pregnant. 
					#ENDIF
					 Once [npc.name] is finished with you, you look up as [npc.she] smirks down at you one last time, before gathering [npc.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 As [npc.sheIs] now finished with you, [npc.name] smirks down at your used form one last time, before gathering [npc.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Left alone to gather your things and get everything in order once more, you spend some time getting your breath back before continuing on your way, making sure to keep a very close watch for any imps that might be lurking around the nearest corner...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
