<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The tunnels of Submission have an ominous feel to them at the best of times, but as you and [npc.name] make your way down the dirty, deserted passageways, you're filled with a particular sense of dread, as though something terrible is about to happen.
	</p>
	<p>
		At first, the sinister silence that permeates these gloomy catacombs is broken only by the rustling of litter that you and your partner disturb underfoot, but as you travel ever onwards, you start hearing faint sounds of movement coming from somewhere far behind you. Realising that you're being followed, and not wanting to be inadvertently shepherded into a trap that might be lying up ahead, you stand your ground and turn to face the direction of your pursuers.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Imps...)] [npc.Name] whispers, and after just a moment, [npc.sheIs] proven right, as from around the far corner, there appear the forms of four imps. One of these is larger than the others, and, although [npc2.her] wings look large enough to sustain flight, [npc2.sheIs] choosing to walk upon the ground, while the other three, smaller imps, are fluttering along in the air a short way behind.
	</p>
	<p>
		All four of the imps are dressed in skimpy rags, and, perhaps due to the fact that they appear more comfortable flying around than walking, you notice that the three smaller imps lack any form of footwear. Although all four of the imps have impressive busts, the alpha-imp's breasts are almost comically-huge, and [npc2.she] swaggers from side-to-side as [npc2.she] leads [npc2.her] three companions around the corner.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc2.she] catches sight of you, the alpha-imp stops in [npc2.her] tracks. Obviously being the leader of this gang, [npc2.she] steps forwards and sizes you up, before declaring, in a sultry voice, [npc2.speech(Ooh! Looks like we've got ourselves a new toy to play with, girls!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The three smaller imps flutter forwards to back their leader up, and [npc4.name] bites [npc4.her] lip as [npc4.she] sighs, [npc4.speech(~Mmm!~ I bet [pc.she] can't wait to taste my pussy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking this opportunity to have [npc5.herself] heard, [npc5.name] giggles, [npc5.speech(I want [pc.herHim] to get a good grope of my tits!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		It's quite clear that these imps are only interested in one thing, and as they start to advance, the third imp, who up until now had been quite content to simply wink and pout at you, puts any doubts as to their intentions to rest, as [npc3.she] calls out, 
		#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
		#THEN
			 [npc3.speech(Lucky you! I've still got one of the boss's special potions left! Ooh, I can't wait to turn you into a big manly stud, with a nice thick cock, and big balls ready to pump some yummy cum into my pussy! Oh! And a nice, long tongue for eating us out!)]
		#ELSE
			 [npc3.speech(Lucky you! I've still got one of the boss's special potions left! Ooh, I can't wait for you to grow a nice thick cock, with big balls ready to pump some yummy cum into my pussy! Oh! And a nice, long tongue for eating us out!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_BODY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Easily seduced by the imps erotic words, you decide that the best course of action would be to just give the gang what they want. Not wanting [npc.name] to have to endure this as well, you tell [npc.herHim] to step back, before holding up your [pc.hands] as you submit to the imps. [pc.speech(Please, there's no need for violence. You just want sex with me, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(So, you know your place!)] [npc2.name] laughs, before turning [npc2.her] head and ordering [npc2.her] subordinates to subdue you, [npc2.speech(Get [pc.herHim] down, quick!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Two of the smaller imps immediately dart forwards, and, flying up to each side of you, they grab your [pc.arms], before folding their wings behind their backs and using their weight to pull you down onto your knees. As you hit the floor, you look up to see [npc2.name] and [npc3.name] stepping forwards, grinning in delight as they see that you're not going to put up a fight.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech([npc.PcName]... Are you sure about this?!)] [npc.Name] calls out from somewhere behind you, but you turn and reassure [npc.herHim] that this is the for the best, before focusing your attention on the imps.
	</p>
	#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
	#THEN
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Give me the potion,)] [npc2.name] commands [npc2.her] partner. Quickly producing a bottle of strange liquid, [npc3.name] hands it over to her superior, who immediately pulls the stopper out and steps forwards, before grabbing your chin and squeezing your cheeks. 
			#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
			#THEN
				 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll turn you into our manly stud, with a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll give you a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			With no further warning, and not even giving you time to do as [npc2.she] commands, [npc2.name] shoves the bottle past your [pc.lips], and you feel the warm, sickly-sweet liquid entering your mouth...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Aww... You've got your mouth blocked! If only the boss was here, she could get rid of that seal enchantment! Eugh!)] [npc2.name] tuts. Turning to [npc2.her] subordinate, [npc2.she] sighs, [npc2.speech(Save that potion for the next one we catch. Let's just see what fun we can have with this one as [pc.she] is.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With no further warning, [npc2.name] reaches forwards and grabs your shoulders, before pushing you down onto your back. [npc2.speech(That's right, lie back and relax! Time to be a good fuck-toy!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Realising that these imps aren't going to be satisfied with anything other than sex, you turn towards your companion, [npc.name], and say, [pc.speech(You're going to have to give the imps what they want. We're not going to get out of this until they're satisfied, so just tell them they can fuck you, and try to have fun, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IFnpc.isAttractedTo(npc2) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
		#THEN[npc.speech(Sure thing, [pc.name],)] [npc.name] replies. [npc.speech(If that's really what you want me to do...)]
		#ELSE[npc.speech([pc.Name]! W-What the hell?!)] [npc.name] replies in alarm. [npc.speech(I-I really don't want to do that!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Having overheard your conversation, [npc2.name] steps forwards, before sneering, [npc2.speech(Hah! Well, that sounds like an acceptable tribute! So long as we can avoid a fight, just one fuck-toy will do!)]
	</p>
	#IFnpc.isAttractedTo(npc2) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
	#THEN
		<p>
			[npc.Name] steps forwards, smiling at the imps as [npc.she] does as you've instructed. [npc.speech(All four of you want me at once, huh? Well, come on then...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(So, you know your place!)] [npc2.name] giggles, before turning [npc2.her] head and ordering [npc2.her] subordinates to subdue [npc.name], [npc2.speech(Get [npc.herHim] down, quick!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[npc.Name] steps back, clearly nervous about what's about to happen. [npc.speech(A-All four of you? At once? I-I don't know...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(So, you still need to be shown your place, huh?!)] [npc2.name] giggles, before turning [npc2.her] head and ordering [npc2.her] subordinates to subdue [npc.name], [npc2.speech(Get [npc.herHim] down, quick, before [npc.she] tries to run!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Two of the smaller imps immediately dart forwards, and, flying up to each side of [npc.name], they grab [npc.her] [npc.arms], before folding their wings behind their backs and using their weight to pull [npc.herHim] down onto [npc.her] knees. As [npc.she] hits the floor, [npc.she] looks up to see the other two imps stepping forwards, grinning in anticipation of what's about to happen.
	</p>
	#IF npc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
	#THEN
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Give me the potion,)] [npc2.name] commands [npc2.her] partner. Quickly producing a bottle of strange liquid, [npc3.name] hands it over to her superior, who immediately pulls the stopper out and steps forwards, before grabbing [npc.namePos] chin and squeezing [npc.her] cheeks. 
			#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
			#THEN
				 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll turn you into our manly stud, with a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll give you a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			With no further warning, and not even giving [npc.name] time to do as [npc2.she] commands, [npc2.name] shoves the bottle past [npc.her] [npc.lips], and you watch as the liquid starts draining out into your companion's mouth...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Aww... You've got your mouth blocked! If only the boss was here, she could get rid of that seal enchantment! Eugh!)] [npc2.name] tuts. Turning to [npc2.her] subordinate, [npc2.she] sighs, [npc2.speech(Save that potion for the next one we catch. Let's just see what fun we can have with this one as [npc.she] is.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With no further warning, [npc2.name] reaches forwards and grabs the back of [npc.namePos] head, before pushing [npc.herHim] down onto the floor. [npc2.speech(Get down, [npc.insult]! Time to be a good fuck-toy for us!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_COMPANION_ORDER_SPIT_COMPANION_SWALLOWS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although happy enough to give [npc.her] body over to the imps, you don't want to see [npc.name] being transformed, so as [npc2.name] shoves the bottle into [npc.her] mouth, you call out, [pc.speech(Don't drink it, [npc.name]! Don't let them change you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Shut up!)] [npc2.Name] shouts, before pinching [npc.namePos] nose and growling, [npc2.speech(Drink it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your dismay, [npc.name] lets out a particularly lewd, muffled moan, before obediently gulping down all of the liquid that's poured out into [npc.her] mouth. Realising that [npc.her] fetish for being transformed has got the better of [npc.herHim], you let out a defeated sigh, and after [npc2.name] hurls the now-empty bottle to one side, you watch as [npc.namePos] body starts to transform...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_COMPANION_ORDER_SPIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although happy enough to give [npc.her] body over to the imps, you don't want to see [npc.name] being transformed, so as [npc2.name] shoves the bottle into [npc.her] mouth, you call out, [pc.speech(Don't drink it, [npc.name]! Don't let them change you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Shut up!)] [npc2.Name] shouts, before pinching [npc.namePos] nose and growling, [npc2.speech(Drink it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your relief, [npc.name] shakes [npc.her] head free of [npc2.namePos] grip, before spitting the transformative liquid out all over the floor. [npc.Her] display of resistance is immediately met by a sharp slap to the face, accompanied by a loud screech as [npc2.name] hurls the now-empty bottle to one side. [npc2.speech(You [npc.insult]! Fuck! Do you know how much trouble the boss goes through to get these potions for us?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing what the alternative was, [npc2.namePos] insults prove easy for [npc.name] to weather, and [npc.she] simply casts [npc.her] gaze to the floor as [npc.she] waits for [npc2.name] to calm down. As [npc.she] does this, however, you see [npc2.name] suddenly reach forwards, and, grabbing your companion by the back of the neck, [npc2.she] forces [npc.herHim] down onto the floor. [npc2.speech(Get down, [npc.insult]! If you can't do something so simple as drinking a potion, all you're good for is being a fuck-toy for us to use!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_COMPANION_ORDER_SWALLOW"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Now that you've given [npc.her] body over to the imps, you find yourself curious to see how [npc.name] will be transformed, so as [npc2.name] shoves the bottle into [npc.her] mouth, you call out, [pc.speech(Drink it all down, [npc.name]! Don't resist!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Listen to your friend over there!)] [npc2.Name] giggles, before pinching [npc.namePos] nose. [npc2.speech(Go on, drink it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your delight, [npc.name] lets out a particularly lewd, muffled moan, before obediently gulping down all of the liquid that's poured out into [npc.her] mouth. Happy that [npc.she] did as you instructed, you let out a happy sigh, and after [npc2.name] hurls the now-empty bottle to one side, you watch as [npc.namePos] body starts to transform...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_COMPANION_ORDER_SWALLOW_COMPANION_SPITS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Now that you've given [npc.her] body over to the imps, you find yourself curious to see how [npc.name] will be transformed, so as [npc2.name] shoves the bottle into [npc.her] mouth, you call out, [pc.speech(Drink it all down, [npc.name]! Don't resist!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Listen to your friend over there!)] [npc2.Name] giggles, before pinching [npc.namePos] nose. [npc2.speech(Go on, drink it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your dismay, [npc.name] shakes [npc.her] head free of [npc2.namePos] grip, before spitting the transformative liquid out all over the floor. [npc.Her] display of resistance is immediately met by a sharp slap to the face, accompanied by a loud screech as [npc2.name] hurls the now-empty bottle to one side. [npc2.speech(You [npc.insult]! Fuck! Do you know how much trouble the boss goes through to get these potions for us?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing what the alternative was, [npc2.namePos] insults prove easy for [npc.name] to weather, and [npc.she] simply casts [npc.her] gaze to the floor as [npc.she] waits for [npc2.name] to calm down. As [npc.she] does this, however, you see [npc2.name] suddenly reach forwards, and, grabbing your companion by the back of the neck, [npc2.she] forces [npc.herHim] down onto the floor. [npc2.speech(Get down, [npc.insult]! If you can't do something so simple as drinking a potion, all you're good for is being a fuck-toy for us to use!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_COMPANION_START_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IFnpc.isAttractedTo(npc2) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
	#THEN
		<p>
			Finding [npc.herself] down on the floor, and at the mercy of the imps' carnal desires, [npc.name] seems willing enough to go along with whatever they have in store for [npc.herHim], and lets out an encouraging [npc.moan] as [npc.she] prepares to get fucked. Hearing the tell-tale sound of [npc.namePos] willingness to go along with all of this, [npc.name] sneers down at [npc.herHim], [npc2.speech(What a submissive bitch you turned out to be! You're just a horny dog who can't wait to fuck us imps, aren't you?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.NamePos] rising arousal gets the better of [npc.herHim], and you can't help but raise your eyebrows as [npc.she] immediately calls out, [npc.speech(Yes! Please, fuck me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As [npc.she] happily responds to [npc2.name], you see [npc4.name] move around and start to grope and squeeze [npc.namePos] ass. Letting out a greedy snarl, [npc4.name] calls out, [npc4.speech(I bet you've lost count of the number of us imps you've fucked!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc3.speech(I want to hear this slut beg to fuck us!)] [npc3.Name] jeers, stepping up beside [npc.name] to smirk down at [npc.her] submissive form. [npc3.speech(Go on, say it. Say you're nothing more than an imp's sex-toy!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(I'm nothing more than an imp's sex-toy! Please, I want to be fucked by imps! Please fuck me!)] [npc.Name] [npc.moansVerb], biting [npc.her] [npc.lip] as [npc.she] looks up at [npc3.name].
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc3.speech(What a slut!)] [npc3.Name] laughs, satisfied with [npc.namePos] enthusiastic answer. [npc3.speech(Don't worry, you'll be getting what you crave so badly soon enough!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc5.speech(I love it when they're as eager as this one!)] [npc5.Name] laughs as [npc5.she] steps around to one side of [npc.name], and your companion can't help but let out [npc.a_moan+] as the imps start moving into position, ready to give [npc.herHim] what [npc.sheIs] so obviously craving...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Finding [npc.herself] down on the floor, and at the mercy of the imps' carnal desires, [npc.name] starts to panic, and tries to stand up as [npc.she] cries out, [npc.speech(Stop this! I don't want to do this!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Before [npc.sheIs] even able to push [npc.herself] up onto [npc.her] knees, however, [npc2.name] steps forwards and grabs the back of [npc.namePos] head, before roughly shoving [npc.herHim] back down into [npc.her] submissive position. [npc2.speech(This is what you get for coming into our territory! Don't worry, we'll get you moaning before we're done with you!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As [npc.name] starts to cry out and protest, you see [npc4.name] step around behind your companion, before starting to grope and squeeze [npc.her] ass. Before [npc.name] able to turn and tell [npc4.herHim] to stop, [npc4.name] calls out, [npc4.speech(I bet you've lost count of the number of us imps you've fucked!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc3.speech(This dumb slut needs to be shown [npc.her] place!)] [npc3.Name] jeers, stepping up beside [npc2.name] to smirk down at [npc.name]. [npc3.speech(You'll love being an imp's sex-toy! We'll make sure of that!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(No! You can't do this!)] [npc.Name] cries out as [npc.she] struggles against the imps.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc3.speech(You'll be begging for it soon enough!)] [npc3.Name] snaps, clearly not having the patience for any more of [npc.her] protests.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc5.speech(It's fun getting to break in unwilling cunts like you!)] [npc5.Name] laughs as [npc5.she] steps around to one side of [npc.name], and your companion can't help but let out a frantic wail as the imps start moving into position, ready to start fucking [npc.herHim]...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Realising that these imps aren't going to be satisfied until they've sated their lust, you turn to your companion, [npc.name], and say, [pc.speech(I don't think fighting them is the best thing to do here... We should just let them have sex with us, it'll be easier this way.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IFnpc.isAttractedTo(npc2) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
		#THEN[npc.speech(Good idea, [pc.name],)] [npc.name] replies. [npc.speech(That'll be easier than having to fight them...)]
		#ELSE[npc.speech([pc.Name]! W-What the hell?!)] [npc.name] replies in alarm. [npc.speech(I-I really don't want to do that!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Having overheard your conversation, [npc2.name] steps forwards, before giggling, [npc2.speech(~Mmm!~ Just can't resist us, huh? Don't worry, that's normal!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That's right. There's no need for violence...)] You say, smiling at the imps as they hungrily look you and [npc.name] up and down.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(So what are you waiting for?)] [npc2.Name] snaps at [npc2.her] subordinates. [npc2.speech(Get them down on their knees!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Two of the smaller imps immediately dart forwards, before flying up beside you and [npc.name]. Reaching out to grab hold of your [pc.arm], [npc4.name] then folds [npc4.her] wings behind [npc4.her] back and uses [npc4.her] weight to pull you down onto your knees. Looking to your side, you see [npc5.name] doing the same to [npc.name]. As the two of you hit the floor, you look up to see the other two imps stepping forwards, grinning in anticipation of what's about to happen.
	</p>
	#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
	#THEN
		#IF npc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
		#THEN
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(Get the potions out!)] [npc2.Name] commands [npc2.her] partner. Quickly producing two bottles of strange liquid, [npc3.name] hands one over to her superior, who immediately pulls the stopper out and steps forwards, before grabbing your chin and squeezing your cheeks. As [npc2.she] does this, [npc3.name] does the same to [npc.name], and as the potions draw ever closer to your open mouths, [npc.name] snickers,
				#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
				#THEN
					 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll turn you into our manly stud, with a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll give you a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				With no further warning, and not even giving you time to do as [npc2.she] commands, [npc2.name] and [npc3.name] start force-feeding the potions to you and your companion, and your eyes open wide as you feel the warm, sickly-sweet liquid entering your mouth...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[npc3.speech(Aww... You've got your mouth blocked! If only the boss was here, she could get rid of that seal enchantment! Eugh!)] [npc3.name] tuts. Turning towards you and [npc2.name], [npc3.she] sighs, [npc3.speech(At least you're gonna get to transform [pc.herHim].)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(Yeah, just save your potion for the next one,)] [npc2.name] replies.#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
				#THEN
					 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll turn you into our manly stud, with a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll give you a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				With no further warning, and not even giving you time to do as [npc2.she] commands, [npc2.name] shoves the bottle past your [pc.lips], and you feel the warm, sickly-sweet liquid entering your mouth...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF npc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
		#THEN
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(Aww... You've got your mouth blocked! If only the boss was here, she could get rid of that seal enchantment! Eugh!)] [npc2.name] tuts, before turning towards [npc2.her] partner. [npc3.she] sighs, [npc3.speech(Just use the other potion we've got on [pc.herHim].)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Quickly producing a bottle of strange liquid, [npc3.name] does as [npc3.her] superior commands, and, pulling the stopper out, [npc3.she] steps forwards, before grabbing [npc.namePos] chin and squeezing [npc.her] cheeks. 
				#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
				#THEN
					 [npc3.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll turn you into our manly stud, with a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc3.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll give you a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				With no further warning, and not even giving [npc.herHim] time to do as [npc3.she] commands, [npc3.name] shoves the bottle past [npc.namePos] [npc.lips], and you see [npc.her] [npc.eyes] open wide as transformative liquid enters [npc.her] mouth...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(Aww... You've both got your mouths blocked! If only the boss was here, she could get rid of those seal enchantments! Eugh!)] [npc2.name] tuts. Turning to [npc2.her] subordinate, [npc2.she] sighs, [npc2.speech(Save the potions for the next ones we catch. Let's just see what fun we can have with these ones as they are.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				With no further warning, [npc2.name] reaches forwards and grabs the back of your head, before pushing you down onto the floor. [npc2.speech(Get down, [pc.insult]! Time to be a good fuck-toy for us!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_THREESOME_COMPANION_SWALLOWS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a loud gulp, [npc.name] swallows down all of the liquid that's in [npc.her] mouth. As [npc3.name] hurls the now-empty bottle to one side, your companion opens [npc.her] mouth to show that [npc.sheHas] swallowed every last drop.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(What an obedient dog!)] [npc3.Name] sneers. [npc3.speech(You like being an imp's plaything, don't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Mmm... Yes...)] [npc.Name] responds, before suddenly letting out a gasp as [npc.she] feels [npc.her] body start to transform...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_THREESOME_COMPANION_SPITS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a firm shake of [npc.her] head, [npc.name] pulls [npc.her] mouth away from [npc3.namePos] bottle, before spitting the liquid that was in [npc.her] mouth all over the floor. [npc3.Name] lets out an angry screech in response to this act of resistance, before slapping your companion across the face. [npc3.speech(You stupid [npc.insult]! We don't get many of these potions, and you just wasted it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before [npc.name] can offer a response, [npc3.name] grabs [npc.herHim] by the back of the neck, before roughly forcing [npc.herHim] down onto the floor. [npc3.speech(Get down, [npc.insult]! You're gonna get a real rough fucking for that!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_THREESOME_BOTH_SPIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Neither you nor [npc.name] have any intention of swallowing the imps' transformative potion, and, almost simultaneously, you each jerk your heads back, before spitting the liquid out all over the floor. Your displays of resistance are immediately met by sharp slaps to the face, accompanied by furious screeching as [npc2.name] and [npc3.name] hurl their now-empty bottles to one side. [npc2.speech(You [pc.insultPlural]! Fuck! Do you know how much trouble the boss goes through to get these potions for us?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing what the alternative was, [npc2.namePos] insults are easy for the two of you to weather, and you both cast your gazes to the floor as you wait for [npc2.herHim] to calm down. As you do this, however, the two imps suddenly reach forwards, and, grabbing you each by the back of the neck, they force the two of you down onto the floor. [npc2.speech(Get down, you [pc.insultPlural]! If you can't do something so simple as drinking a potion, all you're good for is being fuck-toys for us to use!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_THREESOME_REFUSES_ORDER_TO_SPIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting your companion to be transformed by these evil imps, you call out, [pc.speech(Don't drink it, [npc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your dismay, your words seem to fall on deaf ears, and as you glance across at [npc.name], you see [npc.herHim] submissively looking up into [npc3.namePos] [npc3.eyes] as [npc.she] prepares to drink the transformative potion.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_THREESOME_BOTH_SPIT_WITH_ORDER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting neither you nor your companion to be transformed, you jerk your head back, spitting the liquid that was in your mouth all over the floor before shouting, [pc.speech(Don't drink it, [npc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your relief, [npc.name] seems willing to do as you say, and as you glance across at [npc.herHim], you see [npc.herHim] turn [npc.her] head to one side, before spitting [npc3.namePos] potion onto the floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your displays of resistance are immediately met by sharp slaps to the face, accompanied by furious screeching as [npc2.name] and [npc3.name] hurl their now-empty bottles to one side. [npc2.speech(You fucking [pc.insultPlural]! Fuck! Do you know how much trouble the boss goes through to get these potions for us?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing what the alternative was, [npc2.namePos] insults are easy for the two of you to weather, and you both cast your gazes to the floor as you wait for [npc2.herHim] to calm down. As you do this, however, the two imps suddenly reach forwards, and, grabbing you each by the back of the neck, they force the two of you down onto the floor. [npc2.speech(Get down, you [pc.insultPlural]! If you can't do something so simple as drinking a potion, all you're good for is being fuck-toys for us to use!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_THREESOME_OBEYS_ORDER_TO_SWALLOW"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting your companion to be transformed, you call out, [pc.speech(Drink it, [npc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your delight, [npc.name] does as you command, and as you glance across at [npc.herHim], you see [npc.herHim] submissively looking up into [npc3.namePos] [npc3.eyes] as [npc.she] prepares to drink the transformative potion.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_THREESOME_REFUSES_ORDER_TO_SWALLOW"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting your companion to be transformed, you call out, [pc.speech(Drink it, [npc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Ignoring your command, [npc.name] firmly shakes [npc.her] head, before pulling away from [npc3.namePos] bottle and spitting the liquid all over the floor. [npc3.Name] lets out an angry screech in response to this act of resistance, before slapping your companion across the face. [npc3.speech(You stupid [npc.insult]! We don't get many of these potions, and you just wasted it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before [npc.name] can offer a response, [npc3.name] grabs [npc.herHim] by the back of the neck, before roughly forcing [npc.herHim] down onto the floor. [npc3.speech(Get down, [npc.insult]! You're gonna get a real rough fucking for that!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_ATTACK_OFFER_THREESOME_SPIT_WITH_ORDER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting your companion to be transformed by these evil imps, you call out, [pc.speech(Don't drink it, [npc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Obeying your command, [npc.name] firmly shakes [npc.her] head, before pulling away from [npc3.namePos] bottle and spitting the liquid all over the floor. [npc3.Name] lets out an angry screech in response to this act of resistance, before slapping your companion across the face. [npc3.speech(You stupid [npc.insult]! We don't get many of these potions, and you just wasted it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before [npc.name] can offer a response, [npc3.name] grabs [npc.herHim] by the back of the neck, before roughly forcing [npc.herHim] down onto the floor. [npc3.speech(Get down, [npc.insult]! You're gonna get a real rough fucking for that!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to withstand another attack, both you and [npc.name] collapse to your knees. Desperately trying to catch your breath, you plead, [pc.speech(No more... Please...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not giving you a moment's respite, [npc2.name] snaps [npc2.her] fingers, before pointing at the two of you and ordering [npc.her] subordinates, [npc.speech(Restrain them! Go on, get them, quick!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Two of the smaller imps immediately dart forwards, before flying up beside you and [npc.name]. Reaching out to grab hold of your [pc.arm], [npc4.name] then folds [npc4.her] wings behind [npc4.her] back and uses [npc4.her] weight to pull you down onto the floor. Looking to your side, you see [npc5.name] doing the same to [npc.name]. As the two of you hit the floor, you look up to see the other two imps stepping forwards, grinning in anticipation of what's about to happen.
	</p>
	#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
	#THEN
		#IF npc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
		#THEN
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(Get the potions out!)] [npc2.Name] snaps at [npc2.her] partner. Quickly producing two bottles of strange liquid, [npc3.name] hands one over to her superior, who immediately pulls the stopper out and steps forwards, before grabbing your chin and squeezing your cheeks. As [npc2.she] does this, [npc3.name] does the same to [npc.name], and as the potions draw ever closer to your open mouths, [npc.name] snickers,
				#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
				#THEN
					 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll turn you into our manly stud, with a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll give you a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				With no further warning, and not even giving you time to do as [npc2.she] commands, [npc2.name] and [npc3.name] start force-feeding the potions to you and your companion, and your eyes open wide as you feel the warm, sickly-sweet liquid entering your mouth...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[npc3.speech(Aww... You've got your mouth blocked! If only the boss was here, she could get rid of that seal enchantment! Eugh!)] [npc3.name] tuts. Turning towards you and [npc2.name], [npc3.she] sighs, [npc3.speech(At least you're gonna get to transform [pc.herHim].)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(Yeah, just save yer potion for the next cunt we find,)] [npc2.name] snaps.
				#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
				#THEN
					 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll turn you into our manly stud, with a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc2.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll give you a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				With no further warning, and not even giving you time to do as [npc2.she] commands, [npc2.name] shoves the bottle past your [pc.lips], and you feel the warm, sickly-sweet liquid entering your mouth...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF npc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
		#THEN
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(Aww... You've got your mouth blocked! If only the boss was here, she could get rid of that seal enchantment! Eugh!)] [npc3.name] tuts, before turning towards [npc2.her] partner. [npc3.speech(At least you're gonna get to transform [npc.herHim].)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Quickly producing a bottle of strange liquid, [npc3.name] does as [npc3.her] superior commands, and, pulling the stopper out, [npc3.she] steps forwards, before grabbing [npc.namePos] chin and squeezing [npc.her] cheeks. 
				#IF properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE || properties.getForcedTFTendency()==FORCED_TF_MASCULINE_HEAVY
				#THEN
					 [npc3.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll turn you into our manly stud, with a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc3.speech(Open wide, hun! This'll give you a big, thick cock! It'll also give you nice, big balls, so that you have lots of yummy cum to pump into my pussy! Oh, and I almost forgot! It'll make your tongue real nice and long, so you can get it in deep when you're eating us out!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				With no further warning, and not even giving [npc.herHim] time to do as [npc3.she] commands, [npc3.name] shoves the bottle past [npc.namePos] [npc.lips], and you see [npc.her] [npc.eyes] open wide as transformative liquid enters [npc.her] mouth...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(Aww... You've both got your mouths blocked! If only the boss was here, she could get rid of those seal enchantments! Eugh!)] [npc2.name] tuts. Turning to [npc2.her] subordinate, [npc2.she] sighs, [npc2.speech(Save the potions for the next ones we catch. Let's just see what fun we can have with these ones as they are.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				With no further warning, [npc2.name] reaches forwards and grabs your chin, before forcing you to look [npc2.herHim] in the eye as [npc2.she] snarls, [npc2.speech(Stupid [pc.insultPlural]! You're gonna love being our fuck-toys!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself down on the floor, and at the mercy of the imps' carnal desires, you decide that the best thing for you to do would be to simply go along with whatever they have in store for you. Sensing your willingness to go along with all of this, [npc2.name] sneers down at you, [npc2.speech(What a submissive bitch you turned out to be! You're just a pair of horny dogs who can't wait to fuck us imps, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to cause any trouble by arguing back, you mutter, [pc.speech(Y-Yes... That's right...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you agree with [npc2.name], you suddenly feel [npc4.name] start to grope and squeeze your ass, before [npc4.she] calls out to you and [npc.name], [npc4.speech(I bet you two have taken miles of dick already, haven't you?! How many imps have you fucked?! I bet you've lost count!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(I want to hear these sluts beg to have sex with us!)] [npc3.Name] jeers, stepping up beside [npc2.name] to smirk down at your submissive form. [npc3.speech(Go on, say it. Say you're nothing more than a sex-toy for us imps!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'm a sex-toy for you imps...)] You offer, knowing that your words are about to be put to the test.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(Louder! And <i>beg</i> for us to fuck you!)] [npc3.Name] snaps, clearly not satisfied with your half-hearted answer.
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that you're at the mercy of these evil imps, you decide that it'd be best to do as you're told, and cry out, [pc.speech(I'm an imp's sex-toy! Please, I want you to use me! Please fuck me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc5.speech(That's what we like to hear!)] [npc5.Name] laughs from somewhere off to one side, and you can't help but let out a small [pc.moan] as the imps start moving into position, ready to do as you've just asked and start fucking you and [npc.name]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_EAGER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself being pushed to the floor, and at the mercy of the imps' carnal desires, you feel yourself getting immensely turned-on, and can barely contain the [pc.moan+] that drifts out from between your [pc.lips]. Hearing the lewd noise that just came out of your mouth, [npc2.name] sneers down at you, [npc2.speech(What a submissive bitch you turned out to be! You're just a pair of horny dogs who can't wait to fuck us imps, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Your arousal gets the better of you, and before you can think things through, you call out, [pc.speech(Yes! Please, I want to fuck you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you happily respond to [npc2.name], you suddenly feel [npc4.name] start to grope and squeeze your ass, before [npc4.she] calls out, [npc4.speech(I bet you've lost count of the number of us imps you've fucked!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(I want to hear this slut beg to fuck us!)] [npc3.Name] jeers, stepping up beside [npc2.name] to smirk down at your submissive form. [npc3.speech(Go on, say it. Say you're nothing more than an imp's sex-toy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'm nothing more than an imp's sex-toy! Please, I want to fuck imps! Please let me fuck you!)] You [pc.moan], biting your [pc.lip] as you look up at [npc3.name].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(My, my! How eager you are!)] [npc3.Name] laughs, satisfied with your enthusiastic answer. [npc3.speech(Don't worry, you'll be getting what you crave so badly soon enough!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc5.speech(I love it when they're as eager as this one!)] [npc5.Name] laughs from somewhere off to one side, and you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] as the imps start moving into position, ready to give you and [npc.name] the fucking that you're so obviously craving...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_RESIST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself being pushed to the floor, and at the mercy of the imps' carnal desires, you start to panic, and try to stand up again as you cry out, [pc.speech(Stop this! Leave me alone!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you try to push yourself up onto your knees, however, [npc2.name] steps forwards and grabs the back of your head, before roughly shoving you back down into your submissive position. [npc2.speech(This is what you get for coming into our territory! Don't worry, we'll get you moaning before we're done with you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you start to cry out and protest, you suddenly feel [npc4.namePos] [npc4.hands] groping and squeezing your ass. Before you're able to turn and tell [npc4.herHim] to stop, [npc4.she] calls out, [npc4.speech(I bet you've lost count of the number of us imps you've fucked!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(This [pc.insult] needs to be shown [pc.her] place!)] [npc3.Name] jeers, stepping up beside [npc2.name] to smirk down at your defeated form. [npc3.speech(You'll love being an imp's sex-toy! We'll make sure of that!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(No! You can't do this!)] You cry out as you struggle against the imps.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(You'll be begging for it soon enough!)] [npc3.Name] snaps, clearly not having the patience for any more of your protests.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc5.speech(It's fun getting to break in unwilling cunts like you!)] [npc5.Name] laughs from somewhere off to one side, and you can't help but let out a frantic wail as the imps start moving into position, ready to start fucking you and [npc.name]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF_REFUSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You have no intention of swallowing the imps' transformative potion, and, jerking your head back, you spit the liquid out all over the floor. Your resistance is immediately met by a sharp slap to the face, accompanied by a loud screech as [npc2.name] hurls the bottle to one side. [npc2.speech(You fucking [pc.insult]! Fuck! Do you know how much trouble the boss goes through to get these potions for us?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.NamePos] insults are easy to weather, knowing what the alternative was, and you simply cast your gaze to the floor as you wait for [npc2.herHim] to calm down. As you do this, however, [npc2.she] suddenly reaches forwards, and, grabbing you by the back of the neck, forces you down onto the floor. [npc2.speech(Get down, [pc.insult]! If you can't do something so simple as drinking a potion, all you're good for is being a fuck-toy for us to use!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF_ACCEPTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You gulp down the sweet, syrup-like liquid, before opening your mouth to show [npc.name] that you've done as [npc.she] commanded. Your display of submission is met by a devious grin that quickly settles on [npc.namePos] face, and [npc.she] carelessly hurls the now-empty bottle to one side as [npc.she] steps back and looks down at you. [npc.speech(Good dog. You're just a bitch for us imps to command, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes...)] You absent-mindedly reply, concentrating more on the strange feeling that's started to bubble up inside your body than whatever it is that the imp just asked of you. As you feel the curious sensation start to change into a steady warmth that permeates through your entire body, you realise that the potion's transformative effects are about to make themselves known... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_DEFEAT_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had their fun, the imps step back, allowing you to collapse down onto the floor as you pant from exertion.
		#IF (pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc2.getId()) || pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc3.getId()) || pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc4.getId()) || pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc5.getId()))
		#THEN
			#IF pc.isVisiblyPregnant()
			#THEN
				Suddenly, you feel [npc2.name] sliding [npc2.her] fingers into your freshly-creampied pussy, and you let out an exhausted moan as [npc2.she] snickers, [npc2.speech(Shame yer already knocked up, slut. We could have done with you pumpin' out some more imps to join our gang.)]
			#ELSE
				Suddenly, you feel [npc2.name] sliding [npc2.her] fingers into your freshly-creampied pussy, and you let out an exhausted moan as [npc2.she] snickers, [npc2.speech(Wonderin' if we got you knocked up, huh, slut? Well, if you get pregnant from this, just send them imp kids of yours this way. We could always do with more gang members!)]
			#ENDIF
			#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
			#THEN
				</p>
				<p>
					Before you can respond, [npc2.name] steps forwards and shoves [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers into your mouth. [npc2.speech(Clean me off, bitch.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					With little choice but to do as you're told, you lick the cum from [npc2.namePos] fingers
					#IF pc.isVisiblyPregnant()
					#THEN.
					#ELSE, and as you do so, you can't help but wonder if the imp's seed has gotten you pregnant.
					#ENDIF
					 Quickly being forced to swallow down the salty goo that's now in your mouth, you look up as [npc2.name] smirks down at you one last time, before gathering [npc2.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
				#ELSE
				</p>
				<p>
					Before you can respond, [npc2.name] steps forwards and starts wiping [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers all over your face. [npc2.speech(Hold still, bitch. I don't want this on my hands.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					With little choice but to do as you're told, you hold still as [npc2.name] wipes [npc2.her] fingers on your face.
					#IF !pc.isVisiblyPregnant()
					#THEN As you feel the slimy spunk being spread over your cheeks, you can't help but wonder if the imp's seed has gotten you pregnant. 
					#ENDIF
					 Once [npc2.name] is finished with you, you look up as [npc2.she] smirks down at you one last time, before gathering [npc2.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 As [npc2.sheIs] now finished with you, [npc2.name] smirks down at your used form one last time, before gathering [npc2.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Are you ok, [npc.pcName]?)] [npc.Name] asks, stepping out from the shadows to return to your side once more.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah... Don't worry about me...)] You respond, before gathering your things and getting everything in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		You and [npc.name] then spend some time resting, waiting until you've fully recovered from the imp gang-bang before continuing on your way. As you set off, the two of you make sure to keep a very close watch for any more troublesome imps that might be lurking around the nearest corner...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_DEFEAT_SEX_WITH_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had their fun, the imps step back, allowing you and [npc.name] to collapse down onto the floor as the two of you pant from exertion.
		#IF (pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc2.getId()) || pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc3.getId()) || pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc4.getId()) || pc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc5.getId()))
		#THEN
			#IF (npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc2.getId()) || npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc3.getId()) || npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc4.getId()) || npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc5.getId()))
			#THEN
				 Suddenly, you feel [npc2.name] thrusting [npc2.her] fingers into your freshly-creampied pussy, and from [npc.namePos] sudden yelp, you realise that [npc2.name] has just done the same to [npc.herHim].
				#IF npc.isVisiblyPregnant()
				#THEN
					#IF pc.isVisiblyPregnant()
					#THEN
						 [npc2.speech(Shame you two sluts were already knocked up! We could 'ave done with you two pumping out more imps for our gang!)]
					#ELSE
						 Addressing [npc.name], [npc2.name] snarls, [npc2.speech(Shame you're already knocked up, [npc.insult], but your boss here's got an empty womb. Here's hopin' [pc.sheIs] gonna get knocked up from this!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					#IF pc.isVisiblyPregnant()
					#THEN
						 Addressing you, [npc2.name] snarls,  [npc2.speech(Shame you're already knocked up, [pc.insult], but your friend here's got an empty womb. Here's hopin' [npc.sheIs] gonna get knocked up from this!)]
					#ELSE
						 [npc2.speech(Here's hopin' you two sluts are gonna get knocked up from this! We can always do with more imps comin' to join our gang!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					Before either of you can respond, [npc2.name] withdraws [npc2.her] fingers, which, much to the amusement of the other three imps, causes you and [npc.name] to let out synchronised [pc.moans]. As you turn your head to look back at [npc2.herHim], [npc2.name] quickly steps forwards,
					#IF npc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
					#THEN
						#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
						#THEN
							 before shoving [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers into your and [npc.namePos] mouths. [npc2.speech(Clean me off, [pc.insultPlural]!)]
						#ELSE
							 before shoving [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers into [npc.namePos] mouth, and starting to wipe [npc2.her] other hand over your face. [npc2.speech(Hold still, [pc.insultPlural]!)]
						#ENDIF
					#ELSE
						#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
						#THEN
							 before shoving [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers into your mouth, and starting to wipe [npc2.her] other hand over [npc.namePos] face. [npc2.speech(Hold still, [pc.insultPlural]!)]
						#ELSE
							 before starting to wipe [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers over your and [npc.namePos] faces. [npc2.speech(Hold still, [pc.insultPlural]!)]
						#ENDIF
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					Not having any other option, you do as [npc2.name] says, and hold still until [npc2.sheHas] uses the two of you to clean [npc2.her] fingers. Once [npc2.sheHas] finished, you look up as [npc2.name] smirks down at you one last time, before gathering [npc2.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
				</p>
			#ELSE
				#IF pc.isVisiblyPregnant()
				#THEN
					Suddenly, you feel [npc2.name] sliding [npc2.her] fingers into your freshly-creampied pussy, and you let out an exhausted moan as [npc2.she] snickers, [npc2.speech(Shame yer already knocked up, slut. We could have done with you pumpin' out some more imps to join our gang.)]
				#ELSE
					Suddenly, you feel [npc2.name] sliding [npc2.her] fingers into your freshly-creampied pussy, and you let out an exhausted moan as [npc2.she] snickers, [npc2.speech(Wonderin' if we got you knocked up, huh, slut? Well, if you get pregnant from this, just send them imp kids of yours this way. We could always do with more gang members!)]
				#ENDIF
				#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
				#THEN
					</p>
					<p>
						Before you can respond, [npc2.name] steps forwards and shoves [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers into your mouth. [npc2.speech(Clean me off, bitch.)]
					</p>
					#ELSE
					</p>
					<p>
						Before you can respond, [npc2.name] steps forwards and starts wiping [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers all over your face. [npc2.speech(Hold still, bitch. I don't want this on my hands.)]
					</p>
				#ENDIF
				<p>
					Not having any other option, you do as [npc2.name] says, and hold still until [npc2.sheHas] uses you to clean [npc2.her] fingers. Once [npc2.sheHas] finished, you look up as [npc2.name] smirks down at you one last time, before gathering [npc2.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF (npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc2.getId()) || npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc3.getId()) || npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc4.getId()) || npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc5.getId()))
			#THEN
				#IF npc.isVisiblyPregnant()
				#THEN
					Suddenly, you see [npc2.name] step around behind your companion, before sliding [npc2.her] fingers into [npc.her] freshly-creampied pussy. [npc.Name] lets out an exhausted moan as [npc.she] feels the sudden penetration, and [npc2.name] leans forwards to snicker, [npc2.speech(Shame yer already knocked up, slut. We could have done with you pumpin' out some more imps to join our gang.)]
				#ELSE
					Suddenly, you see [npc2.name] step around behind your companion, before sliding [npc2.her] fingers into [npc.her] freshly-creampied pussy. [npc.Name] lets out an exhausted moan as [npc.she] feels the sudden penetration, and [npc2.name] leans forwards to snicker, [npc2.speech(Wonderin' if we got you knocked up, huh, slut? Well, if you get pregnant from this, just send them imp kids of yours this way. We could always do with more gang members!)]
				#ENDIF
				#IF npc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
				#THEN
					</p>
					<p>
						Before [npc.name] can respond, [npc2.name] steps forwards, and you watch as [npc2.she] forcefully shoves [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers into your companion's mouth. [npc2.speech(Clean me off, bitch.)]
					</p>
					#ELSE
					</p>
					<p>
						Before [npc.name] can respond, [npc2.name] steps forwards, and you watch as [npc2.she] starts wiping [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers all over your companion's face. [npc2.speech(Hold still, bitch. I don't want this on my hands.)]
					</p>
				#ENDIF
				<p>
					Not having any other option, [npc.name] does as [npc2.name] says, and holds still until [npc2.sheHas] uses [npc.herHim] to clean [npc2.her] fingers. Once [npc2.sheHas] finished, the two of you look up as [npc2.name] smirks down at you one last time, before gathering [npc2.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
				</p>
			#ELSE
			 As [npc2.sheIs] now finished with the two of you, [npc2.name] smirks down at your used forms one last time, before gathering [npc2.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Are you ok, [npc.pcName]?)] [npc.Name] asks, pushing [npc.herself] up onto [npc.her] knees.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah... Don't worry about me...)] You respond as you follow suit, standing up on trembling [pc.legs].
	</p>
	<p>
		You and [npc.name] then spend some time gathering your things and catching your breath, waiting until you've both fully recovered from the imp gang-bang before continuing on your way. As you set off, the two of you make sure to keep a very close watch for any more troublesome imps that might be lurking around the nearest corner...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_WATCHING_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had their fun, the imps step back, allowing [npc.name] to collapse down onto the floor as [npc.she] pants from exertion.
		#IF (npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc2.getId()) || npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc3.getId()) || npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc4.getId()) || npc.isCharactersCumInOrifice(ORIFICE_VAGINA, npc5.getId()))
		#THEN
			#IF npc.isVisiblyPregnant()
			#THEN
				Suddenly, you see [npc2.name] step around behind your companion, before sliding [npc2.her] fingers into [npc.her] freshly-creampied pussy. [npc.Name] lets out an exhausted moan as [npc.she] feels the sudden penetration, and [npc2.name] leans forwards to snicker, [npc2.speech(Shame yer already knocked up, slut. We could have done with you pumpin' out some more imps to join our gang.)]
			#ELSE
				Suddenly, you see [npc2.name] step around behind your companion, before sliding [npc2.her] fingers into [npc.her] freshly-creampied pussy. [npc.Name] lets out an exhausted moan as [npc.she] feels the sudden penetration, and [npc2.name] leans forwards to snicker, [npc2.speech(Wonderin' if we got you knocked up, huh, slut? Well, if you get pregnant from this, just send them imp kids of yours this way. We could always do with more gang members!)]
			#ENDIF
			#IF npc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true)
			#THEN
				</p>
				<p>
					Before [npc.name] can respond, [npc2.name] steps forwards, and you watch as [npc2.she] forcefully shoves [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers into your companion's mouth. [npc2.speech(Clean me off, bitch.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					With little choice but to do as [npc.sheIs] told, [npc.name] licks the cum from [npc2.namePos] fingers
					#IF npc.isVisiblyPregnant()
					#THEN.
					#ELSE, and as [npc.she] do so, you glance down at the imp's seed oozing out of [npc.her] pussy, wondering if it's gotten [npc.herHim] pregnant.
					#ENDIF
					 Quickly being forced to swallow down the salty goo that's now in [npc.her] mouth, [npc.name] looks up as [npc2.name] smirks down at [npc.herHim] one last time, before gathering [npc2.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
				#ELSE
				</p>
				<p>
					Before [npc.name] can respond, [npc2.name] steps forwards, and you watch as [npc2.she] starts wiping [npc2.her] cum-coated fingers all over your companion's face. [npc2.speech(Hold still, bitch. I don't want this on my hands.)]
				</p>
				<p>
					With little choice but to do as [npc.sheIs] told, [npc.name] holds still as [npc2.name] wipes [npc2.her] fingers on [npc.her] face.
					#IF !npc.isVisiblyPregnant()
					#THEN As the slimy spunk is being spread over [npc.her] cheeks, you glance down at the imp's seed oozing out of [npc.namePos] pussy, and you can't help but wonder if it's gotten [npc.herHim] pregnant.
					#ENDIF
					 Once [npc.her] tormentor is finished, [npc.name] looks up as [npc2.name] smirks down at [npc.herHim] one last time, before gathering [npc2.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 Realising that the imps are now finished with [npc.herHim], [npc.name] looks up at the smirking figure of [npc2.name], who then quickly turns away, before gathering [npc2.her] gang and disappearing off into the dark tunnels of Submission.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Are you ok, [npc.name]?)] you ask, stepping out from the shadows to return to your companion's side once more.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IFnpc.isAttractedTo(npc2) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
		#THEN
			[npc.speech(Yeah, it was actually kind of fun!)] [npc.She] happily responds.
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(I guess... I can't believe you made me do that though...)] [npc.Name] responds in a sombre tone.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You and [npc.name] then spend some time resting, waiting until your companion has fully recovered from the imp gang-bang before continuing on your way. As you set off, the two of you make sure to keep a very close watch for any more troublesome imps that might be lurking around the nearest corner...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
