<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="STAIRCASE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		This area of the bat caverns is home to the staircase that leads back up to Submission. A wooden sign next to the staircase warns any traveller against consuming the mushrooms found in certain parts of the caverns. A picture of some glowing blue mushrooms is displayed next to this warning, and beneath that, there's some information that identifies this particular fungi to be an exception. Apparently, it's the only edible type of mushroom that grows down here, and is highly sought-after by the slimes which inhabit these caverns. Apparently, eating these mushrooms has caused the slimes down here to glow, and also causes them to experience psychedelic effects, which makes their behaviour highly unpredictable.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking up towards the top of the staircase, you see the relatively bright lighting of Submission's tunnels shining down to illuminate the top dozen or so steps. Perhaps because of that ever-present source of light, this area seems entirely deserted...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_DARK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The oppressive, inky blackness of the bat caverns is kept at bay by the softly glowing moss beneath your feet. With every step, a new pool of the low light blooms outward as the previous one fades, allowing you to see out to roughly [unit.lSizes(1500)] all around you. Above your head, the cavern's roof is so high that all you can see is a blanket of completely impenetrable darkness. Occasionally you think you hear a sound, a high-pitched keening, from somewhere up there, but you try not to think too hard about it.
	</p>
	<p>
		There's an ever-present dripping sound that echoes from everywhere and nowhere, giving the caverns its own ambient, if unfocused, melody. The air is also surprisingly fresh, clean and cool; not at all what you'd expect from a typical cave. Indeed, the fresh air down here is certainly chilly enough to raise goosebumps on any exposed skin and harden nipples beneath clothing. 
	</p>
	<p>
		You weave through clusters of stalagmites as you proceed forwards through the darkness, reaching out to use the smooth, cool stone for support as you step over little streams and narrow cracks in the floor.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_LIGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Compared to the majority of the bat caverns, the area you find yourself standing in is lit up like a beacon. The moss carpet beneath your feet thrives in amongst bioluminescent fungi of all shapes, sizes, and colours, and forms trailing paths which wind through the area. While some of these mushroom-like plants approach the height of trees, the vast majority are no more than twenty-or-so [unit.sizes] tall. Pools of still, shallow water are to be found scattered throughout the floor of this underground forest, and by reflecting the many hues of light from the surrounding flora, they give this place an unearthly, almost ethereal ambiance.
	</p>
	<p>
		The luminescence given off by the fungi is bright enough to reveal just how colossal these caves are. The tips of stalactites, illuminated by the taller of the tree-sized mushrooms, look to be almost [unit.lSizes(10000)] above your head, while the base where they connect to the ceiling, still shrouded in darkness, is significantly higher even than that. Some of the largest of these spires have points of light shining out from them, and you realise that you're looking upon the carved-out windows of bat-morphs' roosts.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like the dark parts of the caverns, there's an ever-present dripping sound that echoes from everywhere and nowhere, producing an ambient, if unfocused, melody. The air is also surprisingly fresh, clean and cool; not at all what you'd expect from a typical cave. Indeed, the fresh air down here is certainly chilly enough to raise goosebumps on any exposed skin and harden nipples beneath clothing. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite the fact that this area is well illuminated, there are enough of the tree-sized mushrooms present to provide any would-be attacker with a convenient hiding place...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RIVER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A slow-moving underground river carves its way through the bat caverns, and it's beside this body of water that you find yourself travelling. While the river's surface is illuminated by the bioluminescent lichen, the light is too dim to penetrate the cool, dark depths, and you wonder what sort of creatures, if any, would call such an inhospitable place home.
	</p>
	<p>
		The air in this part of the caverns is particularly fresh and cool, and you feel a slight breeze blowing over the exposed parts of your body. Perhaps due to the immediate proximity of such a large body of water, the dripping sounds that are found all throughout the caverns are particularly loud here, and you often find yourself turning around to check that nobody's using the noise to mask their approach...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RIVER_BRIDGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A slow-moving underground river carves its way through the bat caverns, and it's beside this body of water that you find yourself travelling. While the river's surface is illuminated by the bioluminescent lichen, the light is too dim to penetrate the cool, dark depths, and you wonder what sort of creatures, if any, would call such an inhospitable place home.
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you, small patches of glowing turquoise fungi grow along both sides of the river's sheer banks. A pair of tree-sized bioluminescent mushrooms grow out from the middle of these patches, and have been shaped into a horizontal, weaving pattern by the residents of these caverns in order to form a living bridge across the water's dark depths.
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping up to this fascinating structure, you see that planks of wood have been tied to the mushrooms' stalks in order to provide sturdy footing. Rope-netting has also been cunningly erected to either side, making this bridge a very safe way to get to the path on the other side.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RIVER_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A slow-moving underground river carves its way through the bat caverns, and it's beside this body of water that you find yourself travelling. While the river's surface is illuminated by the bioluminescent lichen, the light is too dim to penetrate the cool, dark depths, and you wonder what sort of creatures, if any, would call such an inhospitable place home.
	</p>
	<p>
		The cavern's roof slopes down before you, and the path that you were walking on suddenly comes to an abrupt halt as it meets a solid wall of stone. The river to your side drops away into a pitch-black abyss, and by the light of the lichen underfoot, you see that a finely meshed metal grate has been built to save anyone from being swept down into the bottomless depths below.
	</p>
	<p>
		With no way forwards, you'll have to turn around and double-back on yourself...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLIME_LAKE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The underground river before you widens out into a huge, still body of water. You can't help but stop in your tracks as you find yourself looking upon a gigantic underground lake, it's still, black waters illuminated by the countless mushrooms of the bioluminescent fungi forests that line its banks.  
	</p>
	<p>
		Out in the middle of the lake, you see a small island, covered in glowing lichens, mosses, and mushrooms. On the island's highest point, you can see that someone's built a stout stone tower, complete with medieval-style crenellations. Although it's quite some distance away, you can see light shining out from the arrow slits in the tower's walls, and at the base, a large wooden door appears to be firmly closed and barred. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLIME_LAKE_QUEEN_UNKNOWN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From this distance, it looks like there's no possible way to gain entry to such a well-fortified structure. You have no reason to visit the tower at the moment, but if ever you had business with a reclusive individual who might lock themselves away somewhere in the Bat Caverns, you now know where to look.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLIME_LAKE_QUEEN_GUESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You have a strong feeling that this is the place where the elusive 'Slime Queen' is hiding. Looking around for a way to cross the wide expanse of water, you soon find a small jetty, which has been built behind several particularly large mushroom-trees in order to try and keep it hidden from passersby. There are several little wooden boats tied up beside it, each one complete with a pair of oars. You suppose that this is how the Queen's visitors travel back and forth from her tower, and wonder if you should use one of these boats to pay her a visit.
		#IFpc.isAbleToFly()#THEN
		 Then again, you could always just fly over there...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLIME_LAKE_QUEEN_KNOWLEDGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You now know that this is the place where the elusive 'Slime Queen' lives. Walking over to the place where the jetty is concealed, you see that there are several little wooden boats still tied up beside it. You suppose that this is how the Queen's visitors travel back and forth from her tower, and wonder if you should use one of the boats to pay her a visit.
		#IFpc.isAbleToFly()#THEN
		 Then again, you could always just fly over there...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLIME_LAKE_BOAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You step down into the nearest wooden boat, before quickly sitting down and grabbing hold of the sides in order to stop it from rocking. Sliding the oars through the oarlocks, you push off from the jetty and start rowing towards the island.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your journey across the lake is uneventful, and before you know it, you've reached your destination. Built into the lake's shore, you see a jetty which is very similar to the one from which you departed. Mooring your boat alongside this jetty, you start to walk up the island's gentle incline towards the stout stone tower.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLIME_LAKE_FLY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seeing no need to use one of boats, you take a small run up towards the lake's shore, and#IF(!pc.isAbleToFlyFromExtraParts()), with a flap of your wings,#ENDIF launch yourself into the air. Circling around a couple of times to gain altitude, you glide over the lake's calm, still surface, speedily making your way towards the island.
	</p>
	<p>
		It only takes a minute or so to reach your destination, and#IF(!pc.isAbleToFlyFromExtraParts()), with a final flap of your wings,#ENDIF you land on the island's shore, right beside a wooden jetty that's the mirror image of the one on the lake's far side. Smiling to yourself as you think about those poor people who aren't able to fly, you begin to walk up the island's gentle incline towards the stout stone tower.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLIME_LAKE_PACIFIED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach, you see that the front door is slightly ajar, and from within, a thin beam of golden light shines out onto the island's mossy knoll. Although there's no sign of life outside the tower, you know that [slimeIce.name] and [slimeFire.name] are standing guard just inside the entrance. As you've already come to an arrangement with the Slime Queen, you're free to come and go from her tower without having to worry about fighting her guards.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLIME_LAKE_READY_FIGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach, you see that the front door is slightly ajar, and from within, a thin beam of golden light shines out onto the island's mossy knoll. Although there's no sign of life outside the tower, you're certain that there must be guards just inside the entrance, and ready yourself for a fight.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLIME_LAKE_BOAT_RETURN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Walking down to the lake's shore, you soon find the island's wooden jetty. Deciding upon the nearest boat, you quickly lower yourself into it and grab hold of the sides in order to stop it from rocking. Sliding the oars through the oarlocks, you push off from the jetty and start rowing towards the far shore.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your journey across the lake is uneventful, and before you know it, you've reached your destination. Tying the boat up at the jetty, you step out onto solid ground once more.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLIME_LAKE_FLY_RETURN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seeing no need to use the little wooden boat, you take a small run up towards the lake's shore, and#IF(!pc.isAbleToFlyFromExtraParts()), with a flap of your wings,#ENDIF launch yourself into the air. Circling around a couple of times to gain altitude, you glide over the lake's calm, still surface, speedily making your way towards the far shore.
	</p>
	<p>
		It only takes a minute or so to reach your destination, and so#IF(!pc.isAbleToFlyFromExtraParts()), with a final flap of your wings,#ENDIF you quickly land on the edge of the underground mushroom forest. Smiling to yourself as you think about those poor people who aren't able to fly, you set off to continue on your journey.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FIND_MUSHROOMS_LIGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although there's no shortage of bioluminescent fungi in this area, you can tell that the vast majority of it is poisonous, and is clearly unsuitable for consumption. As you walk past a particularly large mushroom-tree, however, you see a little cluster of glowing blue mushrooms that look to be quite different from all the rest. Crouching down, you take a look at this peculiar fungi, and, comparing it to the mushrooms on the sign at the entrance to the Bat Caverns, you're certain that these are the ones that are edible.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FIND_MUSHROOMS_DARK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			With the weight of each of your footsteps
		#ELSE
			With the weight of your [pc.legs]
		#ENDIF
		 causing the carpet of bioluminescent lichen to light up and just about illuminate your way, you continue [pc.walking] through the otherwise dark caverns. As you continue to make forwards progress, you suddenly see a faint glimmer of light on the floor up ahead. Approaching this irregularity, you discover that this light source is in fact a small cluster of glowing blue mushrooms. Crouching down, you take a look at this peculiar fungi, and after mentally comparing it to the mushrooms on the sign at the entrance to the Bat Caverns, you're certain that these are the ones which are edible.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FIND_ITEM_LIGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you travel through the underground mushroom forest, you see a splash of bright purple slime sprayed up the side of a nearby mushroom-tree. First glancing around to check that the slime who left this mark is long gone, you then take a step towards this purple goo in order to investigate further.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you approach, you see that there's a similar patch of glowing slime on the floor at the base of the tree, but unlike the goo splashed up the trunk, this slime is a bright orange. Beside this pool of orange goo, you see that one of the participants of what you assume to have been a sexual encounter has dropped some sort of a package.
	</p>
	<p>
		Opening this package reveals:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FIND_ITEM_DARK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			With the weight of each of your footsteps
		#ELSE
			With the weight of your [pc.legs]
		#ENDIF
		 causing the carpet of bioluminescent lichen to light up and just about illuminate your way, you continue [pc.walking] through the otherwise dark caverns. As you continue to move forwards, you suddenly see a splash of bright pink slime sprayed up the side of the wall up ahead. First glancing around to check that the slime who left this mark is long gone, you take a step towards this pink goo in order to investigate further.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you approach, you see that there's a similar patch of glowing slime on the floor at the base of the wall, but unlike the goo which first drew your attention, this slime is a bright green. Beside this pool of green goo, you see that one of the participants of what you assume to have been a sexual encounter has dropped some sort of a package.
	</p>
	<p>
		Opening this package reveals:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- In the BatCavernsEncounterDialogue.java class -->
	
	<!-- REBEL_BASE_DISCOVERED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_DISCOVERED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			With the weight of each of your footsteps
		#ELSE
			With the weight of your [pc.legs]
		#ENDIF
		 causing the carpet of bioluminescent lichen to light up and just about illuminate your way, you continue [pc.walking] through the otherwise dark caverns. By a stroke of exceptional luck, as you pass by what at first appears to be yet another featureless cave wall, you just so happen to notice a sliver of a shadow that's being cast onto it by the dim light of the surrounding bioluminescent fungi. While a shadow ordinarily wouldn't be enough to catch your interest, this one has a suspiciously straight edge to it. With your curiosity piqued, you take a moment to investigate, and after approaching it you can see that this shadow is being cast by a well-hidden door handle that's just barely jutting out from the rock.
	</p>
	<p>
		Between the dim light and the thick layer of dust on it, you can't tell how old this handle is or how long it's been here. Briefly glancing around, you can see no obvious seams or hinges that might suggest the presence of a door.
		#IF(pc.isCowardly())
			 Your cowardly mind immediately jumps to the conclusion that this handle might activate some sort of trap. Nervously gulping, you fret to yourself about whether or not to try pulling it...
		#ELSEIF(pc.isBrave())
			 Although a part of you recognises the fact that this handle might activate some sort of trap, you're far too brave to let such a possibility deter you from pulling it, aren't you?
		#ELSE
			 Although this handle might activate some sort of trap, you're not sure whether you can leave such an extraordinary find behind without at least trying to pull it... 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REBEL_BASE_DOOR_NO_PASS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_DOOR_NO_PASS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your chances, you grab the handle. To your surprise, the moment in which you make contact with what turns out to be cold metal, a series of glowing, light-blue letters materialise across the cavern wall before you, spelling out the question [style.glowBlueLight('Fiat Justitia?')]
	</p>
	<p>
		Steeling yourself for whatever might happen next, you proceed to give the handle an experimental tug, but much to your disappointment it remains fixed in place. It looks like the wall wants an answer to its question, and since you're not sure what the correct response would be there's nothing more that you can do at the moment. Letting go of the handle, you watch as the glowing letters rapidly fade away and return to their invisible, dormant state.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] away from the handle, you think to yourself that surely by carrying out a thorough search of the vicinity will reveal some clues...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REBEL_BASE_DOOR_PASS_ONE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_DOOR_PASS_DARK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you carefully navigate the myriad obstacles offered by the twisting passages of the cavern, you suddenly almost slip on something beneath your feet.
		#IF(pc.isFeminine())
			 Sighing
		#ELSE
			 Grumbling
		#ENDIF
		 to yourself about the responsible disposal of slippery objects in a damp cave, you find the cause of your near-faceplant to be a piece of laminated paper.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_DOOR_PASS_LIGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Walking] through the bioluminescent forest, you find yourself passing by an absolutely gigantic specimen of mushroom-tree, as you do so, you just so happen to see something glinting by its base. Taking a closer look, you push a small patch of mushrooms aside to see that the source of the reflected light is a piece of laminated paper.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_DOOR_PASS_ONE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Picking up the paper to take a closer look, you see that it appears be a page from a journal of some sort that someone laminated after it had already been torn out. Even more strangely, someone tore it in half after going through all the trouble of laminating it. Water has gotten inside the seal and rendered most of the page unreadable but you can still make out an entry:
	</p>
	<p align=right>
		<i>
			1st July 1990
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>
			Under Astrea's command, we have successfully broken through into the Bat Caverns. At last, a way into the wretched heart of Dominion! And not a moment too soon, if news from the other fronts is to be believed. A small hideout hidden in the cave wall will provide us a staging area for the operations to come, and in any case, the cool damp is a welcome relief from the sweltering heat above. The door has been enchanted to only open for those who know the password:</br><center>RUAT C</center>
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Annoyingly, the rest of the password has been torn away. You'll have to find the half of the page which matches up with this one in order to complete the password.
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_rebelBaseDarkPassFound))
			 You get the feeling that this missing half won't be found in these dark tunnels. Perhaps you should head into another part of the Bat Caverns and look in a place that's a little brighter?
		#ELSE
			 You get the feeling that this missing half won't be found in this bioluminescent forest. Perhaps you should head into another part of the Bat Caverns and look in a place that's a little darker?
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REBEL_BASE_DOOR_PASS_TWO -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_DOOR_PASS_TWO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Immediately recognising it as the other half of the torn journal page, you thank your lucky stars for this miraculously good stroke of fortune and quickly pick it up. Like its counterpart, this laminated sheet has been heavily damaged and is also barely legible, yet after brushing off the layer of muck which was obscuring most of the text, you breathe a sigh of relief as you see that the second part of the password can still be read:
	</p>
	<p align=center>
		<i>
			AELUM
		</i>
	</p>
	<p align=right>
		<i>
			3rd July 1990
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>
			Damn Enforcers were waiting for us in the canals! And we've lost one of our lead fighters. She didn't know the password or the exact location of the hideout but it's obvious she broke under interrogation. We found footprints that weren't ours outside this morning. This is going to be much harder than we imagined.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Putting together the two pages, you see that the password is <b>RUAT CAELUM</b>.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- REBEL_BASE_DOOR_PASS_SEARCH_FAIL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_DOOR_PASS_SEARCH_FAIL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You carefully examine every nook and cranny of the area around you. Despite your best efforts, your search turns up nothing.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- REBEL_BASE_DOOR_PASS_SILLY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_DOOR_PASS_SILLY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You rage at having been given yet another pointless side quest. [pc.speech(Can't they see I have things to see and people to do?)] you rant at nobody in particular, [pc.speech(I bet there's not even anybody to fuck behind that stupid door!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As if in reply to your humble cry of anguish, a gust of wind howls through the caverns. You suddenly feel more accomplished but also terribly unsatisfied.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- In the BatCaverns.java dialogue class -->
	
	<!-- REBEL_BASE_ENTRANCE_EXTERIOR (CAVERN_DARK.getContent() is appended before these) -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_ENTRANCE_EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again you find yourself passing by the entrance to the once-hidden cave. Nobody seems to have passed by this way since you were last here, or if they did then they decided not to explore the cave, as by looking through the still-open doorway you can just about see a layer of completely undisturbed glowing mushrooms inside, but nothing else.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_ENTRANCE_EXTERIOR_COLLAPSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again you find yourself passing by the caved-in entrance to the once-hidden cave. As there's no way back inside without digging through several hundred tonnes of rock, this section of the Bat Caverns is no longer any more interesting than any other.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REBEL_BASE_ENTRANCE_HANDLE (CAVERN_DARK.getContent() is appended before this) -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_ENTRANCE_HANDLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again you find yourself passing by the wall onto which the strange door handle is attached. If you didn't already know it was there, it'd be almost impossible to find, as it's only given away by its barely visible lichen-lit shadow.
		#IF(pc.isQuestProgressLessThan(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_REBEL_BASE, QUEST_REBEL_BASE_PASSWORD_COMPLETE))
			 As you're not yet in possession of the required password, trying to pull the handle again will undoubtedly prove to be a fruitless endeavour...
		#ELSE
			 As you're now in possession of the password, you could try pulling the handle again...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- REBEL_BASE_DOOR_OPENED -->
    
    <htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_DOOR_OPENED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Armed with the complete password, you [pc.step] forwards and grab the handle once more. Just as before, the series of glowing letters light up across the wall in front of you, spelling out, [style.glowBlueLight('Fiat Justitia?')]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isMute())
			Being unable to talk, you trace one of your [pc.fingers] over the wall so as to spell out the words 'Ruat Caelum'.
		#ELSE
			[pc.speech(Ruat Caelum,)] you answer
			#IF(pc.isConfident() || pc.isBrave())
				 in your supremely-confident voice.
			#ELSEIF(pc.isCowardly())
				 in a cowardly tone.
			#ELSE
				 in the most confident voice you can muster.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		 The handle suddenly loosens and you pull it with all your might. The ground starts to vibrate as you pull, and before you know it a section of the cavern wall has swung open, revealing the entrance to another cave! You can just about see some clusters of glowing mushrooms inside, but nothing else.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
</dialogue>
