<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	
	<!-- COURTYARD -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="COURTYARD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Separating the gateway from the fortress's wooden keep, there's a deserted courtyard, which has a very militarised feel to it. Numerous straw dummies are lined up in front of the far-side wall, with all but one missing a limb or two. 
		#IF pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_OBSERVANT)
		#THEN
		 Thanks to your observant nature, you're able to pick up on the fact that the damage they've sustained looks to have been caused by a bladed weapon, and, lacking any obvious burn, freeze, or corrosive marks, you deduce that the one practising their sword-work has a blade that deals physical damage.
		#ELSE
		 You assume that the one who set up, and subsequently destroyed, these dummies must be the leader of this keep, who obviously is in possession of a bladed weapon.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Over in one corner of the courtyard, a row of archery targets have been set up; their bright rings add a splash of colour to the otherwise drab and grey surroundings. Although there are no stray arrows in sight, the conspicuous burn marks scarring their surface inform you that they must, at one time, have seen regular use as a focal point for arcane archery practice.
	</p>
	<p>
		In the opposite corner to these targets, sits the main keep. Being of significantly better construction than the perimeter wall, you find yourself thinking that the leader of this fortress must have put all of their construction efforts into making this structure as presentable as possible. With the framework made primarily out of dark wooden boards, and the areas in-between covered with very oriental-looking paper sheeting, this solitary building strongly reminds you of Japanese architecture. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_FORTRESS_FLY_EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While the perimeter wall's hazardous construction prohibits anyone from climbing over it, there's nothing stopping you from utilising your ability to fly in order to get to the other side. Breaking out into a short sprint, you quickly launch yourself into the air, before flying over the defensive barrier and swooping back down to land on the floor of the cavern beyond.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thanks to the builders' liberal use of translucent paper in place of solid walls, the keep's arcane lighting is able to shine out to cast a pale golden glow on the floor and walls of the fortress's courtyard.
	</p>
	<p>
		Illumination isn't the only thing that's escaping through the building's thin walls, for as you approach the sliding doors before you, gasps and short rounds of applause can be heard coming from within the keep. Although these voices are higher-pitched and clearly belonging to imps, a fourth, deep [npc.masculine] voice occasionally cuts their praise short, and you find yourself thinking that [npc.she] sounds a lot more ominous than [npc.her] companions.
	</p>
	<p>
		If you were to enter this keep, the occupants would undoubtedly notice you almost immediately. You should be prepared for the worst, and expect to not only have to fight three imps, but also the leader of the gangs which roam the surrounding tunnels...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_DEFEATED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having defeated [impMaleLeader.name], the [impMaleLeader.race] who led the imp gangs roaming the surrounding tunnels, [impMaleLeader.her] keep is now completely deserted. The sliding doors before you have been left wide open, and, taking a cursory glance inside, you see that there's absolutely nothing within that would be of interest to you. There's nothing more to do here except turn around and go back the way you came...
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF pc.isQuestProgressGreaterThan(QUEST_LINE_MAIN, QUEST_MAIN_2_B_SIRENS_CALL)
		#THEN
			[style.italicsMinorBad(You get the feeling that [impMaleLeader.name] will return to reclaim [impMaleLeader.her] fortress sooner or later!)]
		#ELSE
			[style.italicsBad(You get the feeling that [impMaleLeader.name] will not be back until you've dealt with the Dark Siren!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_PACIFIED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thanks to the builders' liberal use of translucent paper in place of solid walls, the keep's arcane lighting is able to shine out to cast a pale golden glow on the floor and walls of the fortress's courtyard.
	</p>
	<p>
		Illumination isn't the only thing that's escaping through the building's thin walls, for as you approach the sliding doors before you, gasps and short rounds of applause can be heard coming from within the keep. You can hear the distinctive, deep voice of [impMaleLeader.name] as [impMaleLeader.she] occasionally cuts [impMaleLeader.her] three alpha-imp guards' praise short.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [impMaleLeader.name] no longer considers you a threat, you could enter the keep without risking a fight...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP_ENTRY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping up to the keep's paper doors, you're pleased to discover that there's no way to lock them, and, sliding them aside, you step forwards into the building. You see that the interior of the structure is one big open hall, with the polished, perfectly-level wooden flooring broken only by a series of dark, carved wooden beams which run around the edge of the room and hold up the ceiling. Numerous arcane-powered lanterns are fixed to these pillars, which cast a light golden glow over the curious display in the middle of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		In the very centre of the hall, the four occupants of this fortress are gathered around a series of thick, upright bamboo poles, several of which have been sliced to pieces. While the three masculine alpha-imps are much the same as the guards at the gate, their leader is a muscular red-skinned incubus, who, apart from the white cloth wrapping around his hands and torso, is clad only in very oriental-looking, black, skirt-like leggings. Two red horns point out from his forehead, and as he turns to see who's entered his home, you see that his messy, black, shoulder-length hair is framing a very rugged, handsome face. As his yellow eyes lock on to yours, he swipes the dangerous-looking arcane katana in his hands to one side, before sheathing it in the decorative scabbard at his waist. Placing his hands on his hips, the incubus's huge pecs rise and fall as he booms, [npc.speech(What have we here, hmm?! A new challenger come to test [npc.namePos] mettle?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the incubus, who you now know is called [npc.name], says this, you notice that he has an additional, smaller sword fastened at his waist, and you realise that the sounds you heard while outside the keep were of this swordsman testing the power of his two blades on the unfortunate poles of bamboo standing behind him. Impatient to hear who you might be, [npc.name] doesn't give you enough time to answer, and quickly continues, [npc.speech(None who enter my dojo uninvited may be permitted to leave without being duly punished. Fifteen years have I spent training with the youko of the Shinrin Highlands. You stand no chance against my katana and I. Submit to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As he says this, the incubus places one hand on the grip of the larger of his two swords, and readies himself for a fight. The three alpha-imps rush to back their leader up, and you realise that you only have a moment in which to either defuse the situation, or ready yourself for combat...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_ENTRY_RETURN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again sliding the keep's paper doors aside, you step forwards into the building. The hall beyond appears much as it did the last time you were here, with the many pillar-mounted arcane lanterns casting a soft golden glow over both the polished, perfectly-level wooden flooring, as well as the bamboo 'test cutting' setup in the middle of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		In the very centre of the hall, you spot the familiar occupants of [npc.namePos] dojo gathered around the bamboo poles. The [npc.race] [npc.himself] is the first to notice your arrival, and, sheathing his sword and placing his hands on his hips, he booms, [npc.speech(Back again, hmm?! You stand no chance against me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As he says this, the [npc.race] places one hand on the grip of the larger of his two swords, and readies himself for a fight. The three alpha-imps rush to back their leader up, and you realise that you only have a moment in which to either defuse the situation, or ready yourself for combat...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_ENTRY_PACIFIED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again sliding the keep's paper doors aside, you step forwards into the building. The hall beyond appears much as it did the last time you were here, with the many pillar-mounted arcane lanterns casting a soft golden glow over both the polished, perfectly-level wooden flooring, as well as the familiar bamboo setup in the middle of the room.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_ENTRY_PACIFIED_DEMAND_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In the very centre of the hall, you spot the familiar occupants of [npc.namePos] dojo gathered around the bamboo poles. The [npc.race] [npc.himself] is the first to notice your arrival, and, sheathing his sword and placing his hands on his hips, he booms, [npc.speech(Back again, hmm?! And with a flat stomach! Good! I was just thinking that I need a break, so come over here and let me put some imps in that belly of yours!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_ENTRY_PACIFIED_DEMAND_IMPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In the very centre of the hall, you spot the familiar occupants of [npc.namePos] dojo gathered around the bamboo poles. The [npc.race] [npc.himself] is the first to notice your arrival, and, sheathing his sword and placing his hands on his hips, he booms, [npc.speech(Back again, hmm?! But it looks like you're not one to be bred... Damn! Well, I was just thinking that I need a break anyway, so come over here and entertain my imps while I rest!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_PACIFIED_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to have sex right now, you quickly blurt out, [pc.speech(Ah, sorry, [npc.name], I was just checking everything was ok. I've got to go now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Ignoring the booming admonishment that's shouted after you in response, you quickly turn your back on [npc.name] and [npc.her] imps, and make haste as you exit [npc.her] dojo...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_PACIFIED_REPEAT_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Obediently doing as you're told, you hurry over to where [npc.name] is standing, and drop down onto your knees before [npc.herHim]. Smirking down at you, the [npc.race] raises [npc.her] voice so that [npc.she] can be heard over the gleeful chatter coming from [npc.her] imp guards, and commands, [npc.speech(So, you know your place! Good! Now, on your back. Let's get you bred.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to please [npc.name], you once more do as you're commanded, and, lying back, you #IF(pc.hasLegs())spread your [pc.legs]#ELSEpresent yourself#ENDIF and beg, [pc.speech(Please, give me your strong seed!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Kneeling down #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your [pc.legs]#ELSEbefore you#ENDIF, the [npc.race] shuffles forwards to bump the rapidly-hardening bulge in [npc.her] crotch against your groin, and bellows, [npc.speech(Oh, you'll be getting it alright!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a happy [pc.moan], you prepare to get bred by [npc.namePos] [npc.cockSize] cock...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_PACIFIED_REPEAT_SEX_IMPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Obediently doing as you're told, you hurry over to where [npc.name] is standing, and drop down onto your knees before [npc.herHim]. Smirking down at you, the [npc.race] raises [npc.her] voice so that [npc.she] can be heard over the gleeful chatter coming from [npc.her] imp guards, and commands, [npc.speech(So, you know your place! Good! Now, on your back, and do your best to satisfy my guards.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to please [npc.name], you once more do as you're commanded, and, lying back to present yourself to the imps, you look over at them and whine, [pc.speech(Come on, fuck me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Quickly moving forwards to surround you, the three alpha-imps start groping and squeezing your body, with the one#IF(pc.hasLegs()) between your [pc.legs]#ELSEat your groin#ENDIF sneering, [npc2.speech(Mmm, yeah, you're gonna love my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Making a submissive noise in agreement, you prepare to get fucked by [npc.namePos] guards...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_ENTRY_OFFER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The prospect of having to fight such a fearsome opponent is too much for you to handle, and you hold up your [pc.hands] as you cry out, [pc.speech(W-Wait! There's no need for violence!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] releases [npc.her] grip on [npc.her] katana as [npc.she] realises that you're not willing to face [npc.herHim] in combat. Striding forwards and coming to a halt right in front of you, [npc.she] reaches out to grab you by the shoulders, and, before you can react, [npc.she] pushes you down onto your knees, before booming, [npc.speech(How dishonourable! The only way you're getting out of here now is by surrendering your womb to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're now in such a submissive position, all you can do is look up into the [npc.race]'s [npc.eyeColour] eyes, before stuttering, [pc.speech(M-My womb?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That's right!)] [npc.Name] bellows, before dropping to [npc.her] knees before you and firmly pushing you down onto your back. [npc.speech(For one such as you, the only suitable punishment is having your belly filled with imps!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking hold of your [pc.legs]#IF(pc.hasLegs()), [npc.name] starts to push them apart, getting#ELSE[npc.name] gets#ENDIF ready to fuck you in the missionary position...  
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_ENTRY_OFFER_SEX_IMPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The prospect of having to fight such a fearsome opponent is too much for you to handle, and you hold up your [pc.hands] as you cry out, [pc.speech(W-Wait! There's no need for violence!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] releases [npc.her] grip on [npc.her] katana as [npc.she] realises that you're not willing to face [npc.herHim] in combat. Striding forwards and coming to a halt right in front of you, [npc.she] reaches out to grab you by the shoulders, and, before you can react, [npc.she] pushes you down onto your knees, before booming, [npc.speech(How dishonourable! The only way you're getting out of here now is by using your body to satisfy my guards!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're now in such a submissive position, all you can do is look up into the [npc.race]'s [npc.eyeColour] eyes, before stuttering, [pc.speech(W-What?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That's right!)] [npc.Name] bellows, before beckoning [npc.her] imps forwards. [npc.speech(I prefer to breed insolent trespassers, but as that's not possible with you, I'll just let my guards have some fun!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.she] says this, the three alpha-imps quickly surround you, before starting to grope and squeeze your body. [npc.Name] lets out a booming laugh, before stepping back and making sure that [npc.her] horny imps are enough to handle you. Before you can react to what's going on, two of the imps suddenly push you down onto your back, with the third stepping up #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your [pc.legs]#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and chuckling, [npc2.speech(Mmm, yeah, you're gonna love my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Making a submissive noise in agreement, you prepare to get fucked by [npc.namePos] guards...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP_MALES_TAMESHIGIRI -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_MALES_TAMESHIGIRI_MAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Sensing an opportunity to intimidate this [npc.race] into submission, you grip your weapon as you step forwards and issue your challenge, [pc.speech(Your blades are no match for my [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0], and it would be a disgrace for me to have to fight someone with such puny swords. Stand aside, and I'll demonstrate this on those bamboo poles for you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hah! How ridiculous! None can match my katana!)] [npc.name] booms, but, despite [npc.her] words, [npc.she] stands aside. [npc.speech(So, you consider yourself a competent practitioner of tameshigiri, do you? Oh, that'd be 'test cutting' to someone not familiar with the youko's tongue.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Not particularly, but anything you and your flimsy swords can do, my [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] can do better,)] you reply, stepping up to the bamboo poles. [pc.speech(Which one's the hardest?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The [npc.race] points to a blackened bamboo pole at the far end of the dojo. Its sides have been scored with countless cuts and gashes, and you realise that [npc.name] has repeatedly tried, and failed, to slice through it with [npc.her] katana. [npc.speech(Your pathetic [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] is likely to shatter if you try cutting it! One of the eight-tailed youko themselves enchanted it to be resistant to bladed weapons! If you even manage to make a mark, I'd be impressed! Not that it'd be enough to escape without a punishment! Hah!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Walking up to the enchanted target, you notice a faint purple shimmer rippling across the blackened surface. Determined to show this [npc.race] how powerful you are, you raise your [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] and slice it down with full force into the bamboo pole. [pc.speech(Hyah!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At first, [npc.name] seems to think that you've missed the target completely, for [npc.she] starts to let out a booming laugh as [npc.she] sees that your blade seemed to encounter no resistance, and is now on the other side of the pole. [npc.Her] mocking roar is suddenly cut short, however, as the top half of the blackened pole slides to one side, before falling to the floor with a heavy thud.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_MALES_TAMESHIGIRI_KEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(I-Impossible...)] [npc.name] stutters, [npc.her] voice lowering to the volume of a regular person for the first time since you entered [npc.her] dojo. Shaking [npc.her] head, [npc.she] clears [npc.her] throat and scowls angrily at you, before shouting, [npc.speech(That was some kind of trick! It won't work on my blade, fool!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a furious shout, [npc.she] draws [npc.her] sword and slashes it directly at your body. Raising your weapon to block [npc.her] strike, you see the [npc.race]'s eyes open wide in shock as your enchanted arcane blade causes [npc.her] katana to visibly bend at the point of impact. Jumping back, [npc.she] holds [npc.her] weapon in trembling [npc.hand] and starts to wearily back away from you. [npc.speech(That's not possible! W-Who are you?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That doesn't matter. Suffice it to say that you'd be no challenge for one as powerful as I am. Now, tell me why your imp gangs are attacking people in Submission.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(S-She told us to...)] [npc.name] stammers, before trying to regain some of [npc.her] lost confidence. [npc.speech(Our leader, the Dark Siren, that is. She told the other two leaders and I to assert our dominance, so that's what we do. I'm sure you've probably already seen it, seeing as you're here, but she's the one who occupies that citadel in the middle of Submission's tunnels.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I see. So you're just following orders, huh?)] you ask, the tone of your voice making it clear that you don't approve of such an excuse.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Well, I was, until now. If I give you one of the keys needed to get inside that place, you'll agree to let me leave with my honour intact. Deal?)] [npc.name] offers, reaching into a hidden pocket of [npc.her] hakama and producing a thick steel key, which, despite its considerable girth, is no more than five inches in length. Throwing it to you, [npc.name] continues, [npc.speech(There's no need for us to fight. You've already proven you're a foe beyond my level.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You don't believe for one moment that [npc.name] intends to leave and never return, but you're also sure that beating [npc.herHim] in combat wouldn't achieve anything...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_MALES_TAMESHIGIRI_DEFEATED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having once again proven yourself to [npc.name], you ask [npc.herHim], [pc.speech(Why did you come back? I told you to stay away from here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(The Dark Siren... )] [npc.name] stutters, [npc.her] voice lowering to the volume of a regular person for the first time since you entered [npc.her] dojo. [npc.speech(She said I had to...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Still blindly following her orders, huh?)] you ask, the tone of your voice making it clear that you don't approve of such an excuse.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Yes,)] [npc.name] agrees, [npc.speech(but this is the last time. I won't come back here again. Just let me go, and we can avoid a fight.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You don't believe for one moment that [npc.name] intends to leave and never return, and you doubt that even beating [npc.herHim] in combat would change that...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_MALES_TAMESHIGIRI_DEFEATED_DS_DEALT_WITH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having once again proven yourself to [npc.name], you ask [npc.herHim], [pc.speech(Why did you come back? I've already dealt with your leader, and I told you to stay away from here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(The Dark Siren will return... )] [npc.name] stutters, [npc.her] voice lowering to the volume of a regular person for the first time since you entered [npc.her] dojo. [npc.speech(S-So I need to carry out her last orders!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You do realise that she's under lock and key in Lyssieth's palace, right?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That doesn't matter. She'll find a way to escape,)] [npc.name] says. [npc.speech(But until [siren.she] does, I'll leave this place. Just let me go, and we can avoid a fight.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You don't believe for one moment that [npc.name] intends to wait until [npc.her] leader is released before returning, and you doubt that even beating [npc.herHim] in combat would change that...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_MALES_TAMESHIGIRI_ALLOW_TO_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seeing no reason to fight [npc.name], you lower your weapon and command, [pc.speech(Go on then, get out of here! And don't come back!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a dismissive grunt, [npc.name] beckons for [npc.her] imps to follow [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] retreats out through the sliding doors and disappears off into Submission.
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite its impressive construction, you quickly realise that [npc.namePos] dojo has absolutely nothing of value in it, so, with nothing more to do, you prepare to move off and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP_TALK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AUDIENCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Wait, there's no need for violence,)] you say, holding up your [pc.hands]. [pc.speech(I just have some questions about the demon calling herself 'The Dark Siren'.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		That name causes [npc.name] to halt in [npc.her] tracks, and [npc.she] narrows [npc.her] [npc.eyes] as [npc.she] asks, still at maximum volume, [npc.speech(Oh, you want to know something about our leader?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Well, I was hoping to get an opportunity to meet with her,)] you explain, [pc.speech(and was wondering if you could help me with that.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AUDIENCE_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A grin breaks out across [npc.namePos] face as [npc.she] hears what it is you're after. With [npc.her] gaze hungrily roaming up and down over your body, [npc.she] offers [npc.her] terms, [npc.speech(Well, I haven't had the opportunity to breed [pc.a_race] as fine as you in a good long while, so you let me knock you up, and then I'll give you my help in getting to meet with our boss.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Rubbing the bulge in [npc.her] hakama, [npc.she] continues, [npc.speech(Of course, you can say no, but then I'll be forced to punish you for barging in here uninvited. So, either way, I'm going to be painting the insides of your womb with my cum, so you might as well get something out of it, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The three alpha-imps laugh at you as their leader says this, and you wonder whether to do this the easy way, or the hard way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AUDIENCE_IMPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A grin breaks out across [npc.namePos] face as [npc.she] hears what it is you're after. Dismissively tutting as [npc.she] sizes you up, [npc.she] offers [npc.her] terms, [npc.speech(Well, I would have liked to have fathered more imps with you, but as that's not possible, I think surrendering your body to satisfy my guards would be a suitable offer. You let them fuck you, and I'll give you my help in getting to meet with our boss.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Gripping [npc.her] katana, [npc.she] continues, [npc.speech(Of course, you can say no, but then I'll be forced to punish you for barging in here uninvited. So, either way, you're going to be servicing imp cock, so you might as well get something out of it, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The three alpha-imps laugh at you as their leader says this, and you wonder whether to do this the easy way, or the hard way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AUDIENCE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to do as [npc.name] asks, you sigh, [pc.speech(Ok, I'll do it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] releases [npc.her] grip on [npc.her] katana as [npc.she] hears your reply. Striding forwards and coming to a halt right in front of you, [npc.she] reaches out to grab you by the shoulders, and, before you can react, [npc.she] pushes you down onto your knees, before booming, [npc.speech(Excellent! Now surrender your womb to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're now in such a submissive position, all you can do is look up into the [npc.race]'s [npc.eyeColour] eyes, before answering, [pc.speech(Yes... Make me a mother...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That's what I like to hear!)] [npc.Name] bellows, before dropping to [npc.her] knees before you and firmly pushing you down onto your back. [npc.speech(Now, let's get started!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking hold of your [pc.legs]#IF(pc.hasLegs()), [npc.name] starts to push them apart, getting#ELSE[npc.name] gets#ENDIF ready to fuck you in the missionary position...  
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AUDIENCE_SEX_IMPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to do as [npc.name] asks, you sigh, [pc.speech(Ok, I'll do it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] releases [npc.her] grip on [npc.her] katana as [npc.she] hears your reply. Striding forwards and coming to a halt right in front of you, [npc.she] reaches out to grab you by the shoulders, and, before you can react, [npc.she] pushes you down onto your knees, before booming, [npc.speech(Excellent! Now make sure to satisfy all three of them!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're now in such a submissive position, all you can do is look up into the [npc.race]'s [npc.eyeColour] eyes, before sighing, [pc.speech(I will...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That's what I like to hear!)] [npc.Name] bellows, before beckoning [npc.her] imps forwards. [npc.speech(Come on, it's not every day I let you three have fun like this!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as their leader commands, the three alpha-imps quickly surround you, before starting to grope and squeeze your body. Before you can react to what's going on, two of the imps suddenly push you down onto your back, with the third stepping up #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your [pc.legs]#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and chuckling, [npc2.speech(Mmm, yeah, you're gonna love my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Making a submissive noise in agreement, you prepare to get fucked by [npc.namePos] guards...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP_AFTER_SEX_AUDIENCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_SEX_AUDIENCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Good enough, I suppose,)] [npc.name] says, smirking down at you as you pant and sigh on the floor. [npc.speech(A deal's a deal, and I'm sure our boss won't mind meeting someone as submissive as you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pushing yourself back up onto your [pc.feet], you start to get your things in order as [npc.name] continues, [npc.speech(This key is one of three that you need in order to gain access to the stone citadel in the middle of Submission's tunnels. That's where our 'Dark Siren' rules from, if you hadn't already figured it out. The other keys you should be able to get from our other fortresses. Oh, and pay her the proper respect when you meet her. She's a recognised daughter of Lyssieth herself, and if you step out of line, she'll have you locked up and being fucked by her imps before you know what's happening.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having finally got your belongings sorted out, you look up to see [npc.name] holding out a thick steel key, which, despite its considerable girth, is no more than five inches in length.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP_AFTER_JOINING_GAIN_KEY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_SEX_AUDIENCE_KEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking the key, you thank [npc.name] and turn to leave. As you're heading towards the sliding doors, the [npc.race] calls after you, [npc.speech(Come back when you're ready to be knocked up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		To the sounds of impish laughter and lewd taunts, you step out of [npc.namePos] dojo and into the courtyard beyond. Clutching the small key in your hand, you wonder where you should head to next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_KEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You let out a relieved sigh as [npc.name] and [npc.her] guards slump down onto the floor before you, defeated. Stepping forwards, you look down at the [npc.race] and ask, [pc.speech(Why do you do this? Getting all those imps to attack people in Submission, I mean.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(She told us to...)] [npc.name] pants. [npc.speech(Our leader, the Dark Siren... She said we need to assert dominance... You've probably already seen it, seeing as you're here... That citadel in the middle of Submission's tunnels. That's where she is...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I see. So you're just following orders, huh?)] you ask, the tone of your voice making it clear that you don't approve of such an excuse.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Yes... Just... Please, let me go... I-I can give you one of the keys needed to get inside that place in exchange,)] [npc.name] offers, reaching into a hidden pocket of [npc.her] hakama and producing a thick steel key, which, despite its considerable girth, is no more than five inches in length. Giving it to you, [npc.name] continues, still panting, [npc.speech(You'll need keys from the other two gang leaders if you want to confront her... Now just... Please let me go!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You let out a relieved sigh as [npc.name] and [npc.her] guards slump down onto the floor before you, defeated. Stepping forwards, you look down at the [npc.race] and ask, [pc.speech(Why did you come back? I told you to stay away from here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(The Dark Siren... )] [npc.name] pants. [npc.speech(She said I had to...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Still blindly following her orders, huh?)] you ask, the tone of your voice making it clear that you don't approve of such an excuse.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Yes... Just... Please, let me go...)] [npc.name] begs. [npc.speech(I won't cause any more trouble!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_DS_DEFEATED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You let out a relieved sigh as [npc.name] and [npc.her] guards slump down onto the floor before you, defeated. Stepping forwards, you look down at the [npc.race] and ask, [pc.speech(Why did you come back? I told you to stay away from here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(The Dark Siren will return... )] [npc.name] pants. [npc.speech(So I need to carry out her last orders...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You do realise that she's under lock and key in Lyssieth's palace, right?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That doesn't matter... She'll find a way to escape... Now please, let me go...)] [npc.name] begs. [npc.speech(I won't cause any more trouble!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_SCARE_OFF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having dealt with [npc.name], and not wanting to go any further, you stand before [npc.herHim] and [npc.her] imps and declare, [pc.speech(Go on then, get out of here, all of you! And don't come back!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(W-We won't!)] [npc.name] stutters as [npc.she] stands up. Not even giving you another backwards glance, [npc.she] runs off down the length of the dojo, with [npc.her] imp guards close behind. Dashing out through the open doors, the gang disappear off into Submission, leaving you alone in the now-empty room.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking around, you see that there's absolutely nothing of value in here, so, with nothing more to do, you prepare to move off and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have a little fun with [npc.name] and [npc.her] imps before you let them go, you reach down and start moving them into position. As you do this, the [npc.race] lets out a surprisingly erotic groan, before thrusting [npc.her] [npc.hips] towards you. [npc.speech(Come on then, ride my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'll do whatever I feel like,)] you respond, giving [npc.her] [npc.ass] a quick smack to remind [npc.herHim] who's in charge.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your disciplinary action causes [npc.name] to let out a frustrated cry, and you smirk as you reflect upon how proud [npc.she] was when you first entered [npc.her] dojo...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have a little fun with [npc.name] and [npc.her] imps before you let them go, you reach down and start gently moving them into position. As you do this, the [npc.race] lets out a surprisingly erotic groan, before thrusting [npc.her] [npc.hips] towards you. [npc.speech(Come on then, ride my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'll do as I please,)] you respond, giving [npc.her] [npc.ass] a soft smack to remind [npc.herHim] who's in charge.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your disciplinary action causes [npc.name] to let out a frustrated cry, and you smirk as you reflect upon how proud [npc.she] was when you first entered [npc.her] dojo...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_ROUGH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have a little fun with [npc.name] and [npc.her] imps before you let them go, you reach down and start roughly forcing them into position. As you do this, the [npc.race] lets out a surprisingly erotic groan, before thrusting [npc.her] [npc.hips] towards you. [npc.speech(Come on then, ride my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Don't you <i>dare</i> try and tell me what to do!)] you angrily respond, giving [npc.her] [npc.ass] a sharp slap to remind [npc.herHim] who's in charge.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your disciplinary action causes [npc.name] to let out a frustrated cry, and you smirk as you reflect upon how proud [npc.she] was when you first entered [npc.her] dojo...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_SUBMIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling sorry for [npc.name] and [npc.her] imps, you bend down next to [npc.herHim] and ask, [pc.speech(Are you ok? Sorry, I think I went a little too far...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.NamePos] defeated expression quickly shifts into a hungry grin as [npc.she] realises that you're going to be easy to take advantage of. Grabbing hold of your wrists, [npc.she] booms, [npc.speech(No, I'm not ok! Now help me up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Submissively doing as you're told, you assist [npc.name] as [npc.she] pushes [npc.herself] to [npc.her] feet. Refusing to let go of your wrists, [npc.she] suddenly yanks you forwards, pressing you tightly against [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] growls, [npc.speech(So, how are you going to apologise for what you did?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Being held so close to [npc.her] body, you're able to suddenly feel something hard pressing against your [pc.leg], and you glance down to see the distinctive bulge of a fat cock pressing out against the folds of [npc.namePos] hakama. Gulping at the sight of it, you look back up into the [npc.race]'s [npc.eyeColour] eyes, before offering, [pc.speech(I-I could take care of that for you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Now that's what I like to hear!)] [npc.Name] bellows, before reaching out to grab you by the shoulders. Before you can react, [npc.she] pushes you down onto your knees, before booming, [npc.speech(The only way to earn my forgiveness is by surrendering your womb to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're now in such a submissive position, all you can do is look up into the [npc.race]'s [npc.eyeColour] eyes, before stuttering, [pc.speech(M-My womb?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That's right!)] [npc.Name] bellows, before dropping to [npc.her] knees before you and firmly pushing you down onto your back. [npc.speech(For one such as you, the only suitable punishment for what you've done is to have your belly filled with imps!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking hold of your [pc.legs]#IF(pc.hasLegs()), [npc.name] starts to push them apart, getting#ELSE[npc.name] gets#ENDIF ready to fuck you in the missionary position...  
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_SUBMIT_IMPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling sorry for [npc.name] and [npc.her] imps, you bend down next to [npc.herHim] and ask, [pc.speech(Are you ok? Sorry, I think I went a little too far...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.NamePos] defeated expression quickly shifts into a hungry grin as [npc.she] realises that you're going to be easy to take advantage of. Grabbing hold of your wrists, [npc.she] booms, [npc.speech(No, I'm not ok! Now help me up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Submissively doing as you're told, you assist [npc.name] as [npc.she] pushes [npc.herself] to [npc.her] feet. Refusing to let go of your wrists, [npc.she] suddenly yanks you forwards, pressing you tightly against [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] growls, [npc.speech(So, how are you going to apologise for what you did?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Being held so close to [npc.her] body, you're able to suddenly feel something hard pressing against your [pc.leg], and you glance down to see the distinctive bulge of a fat cock pressing out against the folds of [npc.namePos] hakama. Gulping at the sight of it, you look back up into the [npc.race]'s [npc.eyeColour] eyes, before offering, [pc.speech(I-I could take care of that for you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(I'm only interested in those I can impregnate!)] [npc.Name] bellows, before roughly shoving you down onto your back in front of [npc.herHim]. [npc.speech(No, if I can't breed you, then I'm not interested. My guards, on the other hand...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.she] says this, the three alpha-imps quickly surround you, before starting to grope and squeeze your body. [npc.Name] lets out a booming laugh, before stepping back and making sure that [npc.her] horny imps are enough to handle you. Before you can react to what's going on, two of the imps suddenly push you down onto your back, with the third stepping up #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your [pc.legs]#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and chuckling, [npc2.speech(Mmm, yeah, you're gonna love my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Making a submissive noise in agreement, you prepare to get fucked by [npc.namePos] guards...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc2.Name] lets out a triumphant bellow as [npc2.she] watches you fall to the floor, defeated. With a hungry tone in [npc.her] voice, [npc.she] steps forwards and booms, [npc.speech(I think it's time for your punishment!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking up and letting out a startled groan, you see the [npc.race] rubbing the thick bulge in [npc.her] hakama. As your eyes open wide, [npc.she] drops to [npc.her] knees before you and firmly pushes you down onto your back. [npc.speech(I'll make you a mother soon enough!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking hold of your [pc.legs]#IF(pc.hasLegs()), [npc.name] starts to push them apart, getting#ELSE[npc.name] gets#ENDIF ready to breed you in the missionary position...  
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_IMPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] lets out a triumphant bellow as [npc.she] watches you fall to the floor, defeated. [npc.Her] attitude soon changes, however, and [npc.she] dismissively tuts as [npc.she] sizes you up, before sighing, [npc.speech(Well, I would have liked to have fathered more imps with you as your punishment, but that's not possible. I think having my guards use your body is a suitable substitute. So go on, you three, have your fun with [pc.herHim]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking up and letting out a groan, you see the three imps rushing forwards to take advantage of you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Submissively allowing [npc.name] to #IF(pc.hasLegs())spread your [pc.legs]#ELSEtake hold of your hips#ENDIF, you can't help but let out a small [pc.moan] as you realise that you're about to be bred by this strong, dominant [npc.race].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Eager to get knocked up, are you?)] [npc.name] laughs, before shuffling forwards and bumping [npc.her] bulge against your groin. [npc.speech(I'll have you know that my seed's extra virile, so you're all but guaranteed to get pregnant from this!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out yet another [pc.moan] as you hear [npc.herHim] say that, you prepare to be made into a mother by [npc.name]...  
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_EAGER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Submissively #IF(pc.hasLegs())spreading your [pc.legs] for [npc.name]#ELSEpresenting yourself to [npc.name]#ENDIF, you can't help but let out a desperate [pc.moan] as you realise that you're about to be bred by this strong, dominant [npc.race]. [pc.speech(Oh, yes! Come on, breed me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(My, my, so eager to get knocked up!)] [npc.name] laughs, before shuffling forwards and bumping [npc.her] bulge against your groin. [npc.speech(In that case, I'm sure you'll be pleased to hear that my seed's extra virile, so you're all but guaranteed to get pregnant from this!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out yet another lustful [pc.moan] as you hear [npc.herHim] say that, you eagerly anticipate being made into a mother by [npc.name]...  
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_RESIST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You frantically try to
		 #IF(pc.hasLegs())
		 	 close your [pc.legs], but [npc.name] is far too strong, and easily manages to force them open.
		 #ELSE
		 	 pull away, but [npc.name] is far too strong, and easily holds you in position.
		 #ENDIF
		  Realising that you're about to be bred by this strong, dominant [npc.race], you let out a frantic scream, before trying to shuffle away from [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Not liking the idea of being knocked up, eh?)] [npc.name] laughs, before shuffling forwards and bumping [npc.her] bulge against your groin. [npc.speech(Well, you should have thought about that before barging in here uninvited! I'll have you know that my seed's extra virile, so you're all but guaranteed to get pregnant from this!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out yet another desperate wail as you hear [npc.herHim] say that, you do your best to resist being made into a mother by [npc.name]...  
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_IMPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The three alpha-imps move forwards, before quickly surrounding you and starting to grope and squeeze your body. [npc.Name] lets out a booming laugh, before stepping back and making sure that [npc.her] horny imps are enough to handle you. Before you can react to what's going on, two of the imps suddenly push you down onto your back, with the third stepping up #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your [pc.legs]#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and chuckling, [npc2.speech(Mmm, yeah, you're gonna love my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Making a submissive noise in agreement, you prepare to get fucked by [npc.namePos] guards...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_IMPS_EAGER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The three alpha-imps move forwards, before quickly surrounding you and starting to grope and squeeze your body. [npc.Name] lets out a booming laugh, before stepping back and making sure that [npc.her] horny imps are enough to handle you. Before you can react to what's going on, two of the imps suddenly push you down onto your back, with the third stepping up #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your [pc.legs]#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and chuckling, [npc2.speech(Mmm, yeah, you're gonna love my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Making a submissive noise in agreement, you eagerly prepare to get fucked by [npc.namePos] guards...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_IMPS_RESIST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The three alpha-imps move forwards, before quickly surrounding you and starting to grope and squeeze your body. [npc.Name] lets out a booming laugh, before stepping back and making sure that [npc.her] horny imps are enough to handle you. Before you can react to what's going on, two of the imps suddenly push you down onto your back, with the third stepping up #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your [pc.legs]#ELSEto your groin#ENDIF and chuckling, [npc2.speech(Mmm, yeah, you're gonna love my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a frantic scream, you do your best to resist as [npc.namePos] guards prepare to fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP_AFTER_SEX_PACIFIED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_SEX_PACIFIED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You collapse to the floor, and with a satisfied [pc.moan], you look up to see [npc.name] smiling down at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Not bad,)] [npc.she] says. [npc.speech(You can come back any time, if this is what you're after! For now though, I need to get back to my work. Come back when you're ready to be knocked up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		To the sound of [npc.namePos] impatient foot tapping on the polished wooden floor, you set about getting your things in order. Once done, you let out one last submissive whine, before heading over to the dojo's doors and preparing to take your leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP_AFTER_SEX_VICTORY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_SEX_VICTORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] and [npc.her] imps collapse to the floor, utterly exhausted. Quickly getting your things in order, you can't help but smile as you hear the [npc.race] panting, [npc.speech(Oh... Fuck...)]
	</p>	
	<p>
		Grinning down at the worn out gang, you wonder if you should tell them to get out of here right away, or perhaps you could first take this opportunity to confiscate their belongs...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_SEX_VICTORY_SCARE_OFF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Get out of here, all of you! And don't come back!)] you order, smirking down at the gang.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(W-We won't!)] [npc.name] stutters as [npc.she] stands up. Not even giving you another backwards glance, [npc.she] runs off down the length of the dojo, with [npc.her] imp guards close behind. Dashing out through the open doors, the gang disappear off into Submission, leaving you alone in the now-empty room.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking around, you see that there's absolutely nothing of value in here, so, with nothing more to do, you prepare to move off and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- KEEP_AFTER_SEX_DEFEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KEEP_AFTER_SEX_DEFEAT"><![CDATA[
	#IF impMaleLeader.isAbleToEquipDildo(pc)
	#THEN
		<p>
			You lie back on the floor of [npc.namePos] dojo, and with an exhausted [pc.moan], you close your eyes and feel the [npc.race]'s huge amount of cum drooling out of your pussy. Suddenly, something hard rubs against your [pc.labia+], and you open your eyes and look down just in time to see the potential father of your imp offspring thrust an insertable dildo all the way into your well-used cunt. Although the demonic cum acts as ample lubrication for the sudden insertion, it still takes you by surprise, and you cry out, [pc.speech(Aaah! What are you doing?!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Well, we wouldn't want all my seed leaking out and going to waste now, would we?)] [npc.name] replies, letting out a laugh as [npc.she] firmly presses [npc.her] palm up against the dildo's flat end to make sure that it's in as far as it will go. [npc.speech(It's not that I don't trust you, but it's got a sealing enchantment on it as well, so my seed will have had ample time to take root in your womb before you can get it washed out.)]
		</p>
		#IF impMaleLeader.isAbleToEquipThong(pc)
		#THEN
			<p>
				You start to let out a protesting whine, but before you can offer any real objection to [npc.namePos] treatment of you, [npc.she] quickly produces a dark red crotchless thong, before firmly forcing it first over your [pc.feet], and then up your thighs. [pc.speech(Hey! W-What's this?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Sliding the thong all the way up to rest in place around your [pc.hips+], the [npc.race] lets out a delighted laugh as [npc.she] then steps back to admire [npc.her] handiwork. [npc.speech(So, how does that feel? Are you desperately wishing to get pregnant from my seed yet?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				As [npc.name] says this, you can't help but let out a frantic moan at the thought of new life being born in your womb. Reaching down#IF(pc.hasLegs()) between your [pc.legs]#ENDIF, you make sure that the dildo is securely in place, letting out a relieved sigh as you feel that it's firmly plugging your vagina and keeping all that precious cum locked deep inside your uterus.
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.speech(Hah! I see the enchantment's having an effect already!)] [npc.she] laughs. [npc.speech(It'll also make sure your hips are nice and wide to help you carry, and later birth, our demonic offspring. Oh, and yes, before you ask, it's sealed too, although with a stronger enchantment than the dildo. You won't be taking it off any time soon!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				You feel your cheeks flush as [npc.name] talks about the imps that you might be pregnant with, and you find yourself desperately wishing that you're soon going to be showing signs of being a mother.
			</p>
			<p>
				Having finally finished with you, [npc.name] stands up, before dismissively shooing you away with one hand. [npc.speech(Come back once your pregnancy is over, and I'll knock you up all over again. That special thong you're wearing will make sure you stay eager to be knocked up, so I'm sure I'll see you again.)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Having finished with you, [npc.name] then stands up, before dismissively shooing you away with one hand. [npc.speech(Come back once your pregnancy is over, and I'll knock you up all over again. Don't get that dildo removed too soon, ok?!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF impMaleLeader.isAbleToEquipThong(pc)
		#THEN
			<p>
				You lie back on the floor of [npc.namePos] dojo, and with an exhausted [pc.moan], you close your eyes and feel the [npc.race]'s huge amount of cum drooling out of your pussy. Suddenly, something soft rubs over your [pc.feet+], and you open your eyes and look down just in time to see the potential father of your imp offspring sliding a dark red crotchless thong up your thighs. [pc.speech(Hey! W-What's this?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Sliding the thong all the way up to rest in place around your [pc.hips+], the [npc.race] lets out a delighted laugh as [npc.she] then steps back to admire [npc.her] handiwork. [npc.speech(So, how does that feel? Are you desperately wishing to get pregnant from my seed yet?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				As [npc.name] says this, you can't help but let out a frantic moan at the thought of new life being born in your womb. Reaching down#IF(pc.hasLegs()) between your [pc.legs]#ENDIF, you push your [pc.fingers] into your cum-stuffed cunt, before desperately trying to push as much of the precious seed deep into your uterus as you possibly can.
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.speech(Hah! I see the enchantment's having an effect already!)] [npc.she] laughs. [npc.speech(It'll also make sure your hips are nice and wide to help you carry, and later birth, our demonic offspring. Oh, and yes, before you ask, it's got a strong sealing enchantment on it. You won't be taking it off any time soon!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				You feel your cheeks flush as [npc.name] talks about the imps that you might be pregnant with, and you find yourself desperately wishing that you're soon going to be showing signs of being a mother.
			</p>
			<p>
				Having finally finished with you, [npc.name] stands up, before dismissively shooing you away with one hand. [npc.speech(Come back once your pregnancy is over, and I'll knock you up all over again. That special thong you're wearing will make sure you stay eager to be knocked up, so I'm sure I'll see you again.)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				You collapse to the floor, and with an exhausted [pc.moan], you look up to see [npc.name] grinning down at you. [npc.speech(Come back when you're desperate to become a mother, and I'll get you knocked up!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		To the sound of their cackling laughter, the imps then unceremoniously drag you out of the dojo and through the fortress's front gate. Before you know it, you've been dragged far away from [npc.namePos] base, and are being carelessly hurled to the floor. Threatening you never to return, the imps head back the way they came, leaving you alone to catch your breath...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
