<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		This area joins the hidden cave with the Bat Caverns outside. The air is heavy but not unpleasant. The way back was once hidden by a tight fitting stone panel and a clever arcane password lock, but you have since defeated these measures. The remaining light from outside and the dim glow from the inside are just enough for you to find your way.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although made of the same stone and afflicted with the same damp as the Bat Caverns, the wooden supports along the walls are clear signs that this cave is artificial. Although you see what look like hooks for placing lanterns or torches nailed into each support, the sodden wood has been more or less taken over by bioluminescent mushrooms and wood ears, conveniently lighting the way.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLEEPING_AREA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From the bunkbeds scattered about the room, you guess that it was once used as a sleeping area. Some of the beds have been knocked over and all are unusable rotting husks covered in bioluminescent mushrooms. Piled high in the middle of the room are mysteriously stained pieces of fabric that might have been clothing at one point but are now home to yet more mushrooms.
	</p>
	<p>
		You notice several waterproof footlockers next to some of the beds. They're pretty beaten up, but they might still be sealed. There is also what remains of someone's journal lying on one of the beds.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLEEPING_AREA_CACHE_OPEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You rummage through the footlockers and find sets of uniforms, boots, and armbands of some sort that you don't recognize.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLEEPING_AREA_JOURNAL_OPEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You try to gingerly open the journal, but as you'd expect for paper that's spent who knows how long in a damp cave, most of the pages immediately crumble into illegible pieces. There's no way you can remove this journal from its resting place without destroying it. The light provided by the surrounding mushrooms is just enough for you to read some of the intact pages:
	</p>
	<p align=right>
		<i>
			8th August 1988
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>
			The day of reckoning is here! At last the demons and their running dogs will answer for millennia of injustice. Already we're driving the Enforcers back into their holes, and they'll never emerge from them if we can help it. The adjutant would prefer that humans supplant the demons at the top, but that kind of thinking won't get us any allies among the non-humans. The hearts and minds of the people are what we need to win. We'll all crawl out from under the corpse of this corrupt society and then the Realm will be free!
		</i>
	</p>
	<p align=right>
		<i>
			4th November 1989
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>
			We've kept Dominion under siege since our liberation began and have taken the outer boroughs, but the inner boroughs are a tough nut to crack even with our numbers advantage. Command issued these collars imbued with angelic magic for interrogating prisoners as part of our initial assault kits and they've proven useful, but the adjutant has started taking advantage of how docile and compliant they make the wearer. He's using some of the prisoners to relieve himself, or as he puts it, "recreational procreation". I don't agree with his methods, but I can't argue with the results. More of his children swell our ranks every day, human and non-human. They're definitely the most gung-ho of any of us, I guess because they know only what we've told them, and well... neither they nor anyone else needs to know who their parents are or how they came to be.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p align=right>
		<i>
			20th December 1989
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>
			I always knew that our cause was just, but today a literal angel has returned to aid us! Of course I'd heard the rumors from the old guard that they helped get this whole rebellion started, but I never ever thought I'd see one. Astrea is her name and I admit, she's more than just a pretty face. She's just the shot in the arm that we needed and under her we've broken the Thinis salient at last! I am a little bit concerned though. She and the adjutant agree on more things than I'd like, namely what our post-Lilith society should look like. I think non-humans have earned their place at the table, why can't they see that? Haven't they fought just as hard against the demons as us? Haven't we all had enough of races stepping on each other? And, another thing. A lot of the officers are starting to copy the adjutant's treatment of prisoners, to let off steam or so they say. This is going to come back to bite us when we win.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p align=right>
		<i>
			15th March 1991
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>
			It... is not easy for me to put down on paper what I am thinking right now. Last night during the block meeting, Astrea accused me and those who share my opinion on non-humans of being demon sympathizers. And of course the loudest accuser was the adjutant, just because I don't participate in his...recruitment activities. Well, it's true. I don't slap and choke and rape prisoners even if almost all of the other officers do. The collars do the work well enough. There is something wrong with these "angels". Every night that Astrea and the adjutant spend together, he gets more animalistic in his hate for non-humans and in his lust for rape. She is not an angel, she can't be. And if she is, I want nothing to do with them. We are being sent away from here to train insurgents, but I am not going. The other accused and I have agreed, we're leaving this rebellion to start our own. To what end, I don't know, but I can't be a part of this one, not anymore.
		</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLEEPING_AREA_SEARCHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From the bunk-beds scattered about the room, you guess that it was once used as a sleeping area. Some of the beds have been knocked over and all are unusable rotting husks covered in bioluminescent mushrooms. Piled high in the middle of the room are mysteriously stained pieces of fabric that might have been clothing at one point but are now home to yet more mushrooms.
	</p>
	<p>
		The waterproof footlockers now sit empty and what's left would give even Rose a real challenge. There is also what remains of someone's journal lying on one of the beds.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMMON_AREA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		This room appears to have been some kind of common area, although the single table and a few chairs would have made for spartan accommodations even if they weren't covered in glowing lichen. The table has been split in two, right down the middle, either intentionally or from too much weight.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking over to the far corner of the room, you see a heavy metal cabinet. The paint is flaking off and there's a huge dent in it, but it might still contain something of worth.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMMON_AREA_CACHE_OPEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Walking] over to the cabinet, and by having to apply more than a little force, you manage to pull the door open and find within:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COMMON_AREA_SEARCHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		This room appears to have been some kind of common area, although the single table and a few chairs would have made for spartan accommodations even if they weren't covered in glowing lichen. The table has been split in two, right down the middle either intentionally or from too much weight.
	</p>
	<p>
		The cabinet in the far corner is now empty and there isn't anything left worth taking.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARMORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't be sure what this room was used for, given that half of it has caved in. Poking out from rubble, there are two large metal containers. The containers have burst open from the pressure exerted by the rubble but you see glimpses of plastic bags inside.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARMORY_CACHE_OPEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Approaching the rubble-entombed metal containers, you're able to shift aside some of the rocks and pull several plastic bags free from the debris. Tearing these bags open, you find:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARMORY_CACHE_OPEN_FIREBOMBS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getOccupation() == OCCUPATION_SOLDIER)
			Having seen quite a few in improvised weapons training,
		#ELSE
			 Having seen them in use during riots on the news,
		#ENDIF
		 you instantly recognise the disposable firebombs as being an arcane parody of Molotov cocktails. You don't have a way to get more and you doubt any honest shop would want to carry something so obviously illegal, but perhaps a shopkeep with less scruples has the means to provide you with a supply of them...	
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_axelExplainedVengar))
	<p>
		[roxy.NamePos] shop would probably be a good place to start.
	</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARMORY_SEARCHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't be sure what this room was used for, given that half of it has caved in.
	</p>
	<p>
		The metal containers and plastic bags are now empty, leaving nothing else but rubble in this room.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_CAVED_IN_ROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		It's impossible to even hazard a guess as to what this room was once used for, as it's completely buried beneath hundreds of tonnes of rubble. There's no sign of anything buried beneath the rock which almost completely fills this room, and so there's really little else to do but turn around and continue your search elsewhere...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_COLLAPSE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you make your way back out, you hear an ominous cracking sound from deep within the hidden cave. The rotting supports have finally given way! The cave's unsupported ceiling starts to collapse, bringing down a hundred thousand tonnes of rock with it.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="REBEL_BASE_ESCAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You run as fast as your [pc.legs] will carry you and manage to reach safety just in time. A thunderous boom echoes throughout the Bat Caverns, and you thankfully manage to dart to one side just in time to avoid the cloud of dust and debris which is expelled from out of the collapsing cave's entrance.
	</p>
	<p>
		The sudden cave-in thankfully doesn't show any sign of spreading out into the Bat Caverns, and after a few moments have passed both the noise and vibrations have completely faded away. All that's left to remind you of the cave's existence is the metal handle, which is lodged half-way up the huge pile of rubble which spews out of the place where the hidden door once sat.
	</p>
	<p>
		By some sort of a miracle you've managed to escape completely unharmed, although there's now no way back into the hidden cave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
