<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FIND_ITEM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you walk through the gloomy tunnels of Submission, keeping an eye out for any sign of danger, you suddenly spot what appears to be an unopened cardboard box, dropped to one side of a rubbish pile. Stepping over towards it, you don't see any sign of a trap or ambush, so, curious as to what could be inside, you tear off the sealing tape and open the lid.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just as you'd hoped, the package doesn't appear to have been opened before, and with no sign of its intended recipient in sight, you decide that there'd be no harm in taking the contents. Inside, you find...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEWER_ENTRANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A large stone building, spanning the entire width of the tunnel, has been erected here. A sign reading 'Official Enforcer Post' is clearly displayed beside the main entrance, and within, a dozen or so Enforcers are manning desks or standing guard beside internal doorways. None of them seem to pay you much attention, allowing you to come and go as you please.
	</p>
	<p>
		As usual, you see the short, busty form of the cat-girl Enforcer, Claire, hurrying around as she fetches and delivers all sorts of miscellaneous paperwork. If you wanted to, you could approach her and ask for some more information about Submission.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEWER_ENTRANCE_CLAIRE_MILKERS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A large stone building, spanning the entire width of the tunnel, has been erected here. A sign reading 'Official Enforcer Post' is clearly displayed beside the main entrance, and within, a dozen or so Enforcers are manning desks or standing guard beside internal doorways. None of them seem to pay you much attention, allowing you to come and go as you please.
	</p>
	<p>
		As usual, you see the short, busty form of the cat-girl Enforcer, Claire, hurrying around as she fetches and delivers all sorts of miscellaneous paperwork. As she catches sight of you, she lets out a little cry and waves her arms to get your attention, causing her massive breasts to bounce up and down in a hypnotic rhythm.  Skipping over to where you're standing, and causing her tits to jiggle up and down in the process, the busty cat-girl bluntly asks, [claire.speech(Hey, [pc.name], you know that business you got mixed up in down at the Rat Warrens? Did you meet a nasty little rat-boy called 'Murk' while you were in there?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_murkIntroduced))
			Having met Murk while in there, you reply to Claire's question in the positive, before asking her what this is all about.
		#ELSE
			Not having met anyone called 'Murk' while in there, you reply to Claire's question in the negative, before asking her what this is all about.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Well, as we discovered as we cleared out the place, that nasty little rat had kidnapped four humans from Dominion. We'd had them on our missing persons list for so long that we'd given up ever finding them,)] she reveals, before letting out a sigh and allowing an uncharacteristically sad look to settle on her face. As you state that surely it's a good thing that these people were found, the cat-girl shakes her head and reveals, [claire.speech(That rat really messed their heads up. All they keep asking for is to be put back into chains and milked while being treated as sex slaves. We've had one of our demon Enforcers who specialises in psychological damage take a look at them, but she said that there's nothing we can do with the limited budget that our department has.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to know what the point is that Claire's getting to, you ask the cat-girl what's going to become of these captives, and what she wants you to do about it.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Well, the four of them kept on demanding to be made slaves and sold to someone who'd give them the sort of degrading life they've grown to love,)] Claire sighs, the frustration in her voice making it clear that she doesn't approve of this. Throwing her hands up in the air, she reveals, [claire.speech(My superior said that we don't have the time or resources to do anything else with them, so they've been enslaved, transferred to slaver alley, and are due to be auctioned off at the end of the day. Look, I know that I don't owe them anything, and neither do you, but I don't want them being sold to someone who's going to abuse them. I know that you'd treat them right, so I can arrange it for you to take ownership of them instead. It won't cost you anything, either!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the busty cat-girl gives you a pleading expression, and you wonder whether to agree to take on these four slaves, or to instead decline and let them be sold off to the highest bidder...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEWER_ENTRANCE_CLAIRE_MILKERS_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to take on these four ex-captives, you tell Claire that you're not able to take ownership of them.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(That's too bad...)] Claire laments, before forcing herself to smile and declare, [claire.speech(Well, I'd better get back on with work! If you need anything, just let me know!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the busty cat-girl skips off, leaving you to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEWER_ENTRANCE_CLAIRE_MILKERS_ACCEPTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of what it is that Claire's suggesting, you tell the cat-girl that you'd be happy to take ownership of the humans who were rescued from the Rat Warrens.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Great! I knew I could rely on you, [pc.name],)] Claire happily replies, before stating, [claire.speech(All I need is to see your slaver license, then I can get the paperwork signed right away!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Producing the piece of paper which she's asking for, you allow Claire to inspect your license, and after she's satisfied, she quickly fills in the paperwork and declares, [claire.speech(That's that all sorted then! Your new slaves will be waiting for you in the administration building in slaver alley.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking Claire for the opportunity and for the new slaves, you tell her that the four humans are going to be safe in your hands. Flashing you a big smile, the busty cat-girl bounces up and down, causing her massive breasts to sway as she exclaims, [claire.speech(Thanks again for helping out, [pc.name]; I really didn't want such vulnerable people auctioned off to the public. Anyway, I'd better get back on with work! If you need anything, just let me know!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the busty cat-girl skips off, leaving you to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CLAIRE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to talk with Claire, you approach the short cat-girl messenger and call out a greeting in order to get her attention.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(claire.isVisiblyPregnant())
			#IF(!claire.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
					[claire.speech(Oh, [pc.name], look!)] Claire excitedly exclaims as she sees that it's you who's calling out to her. Pointing down to her swollen belly, she continues, [claire.speech(You got me pregnant! Isn't that so exciting?! We're gonna have a kid together!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Responding in the positive, you let the happy cat-girl take your [pc.hands] in hers, and you can't help but smile as she gets you to feel her pregnant bump. Concerned with the sort of work she's being asked to perform while pregnant, you ask, [pc.speech(Is there anything I can do to help? They're not making you work too hard here, are they?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[claire.speech(Oh, no, don't worry about me!)] she happily replies, [claire.speech(I can always switch over to a desk job for a few days if all the running around gets too much for me. So, anyway, what can I do for you?)]
			#ELSE
				[claire.speech(Oh, hello again, [pc.name]!)] Claire cheerfully exclaims as she sees that it's you who's calling out to her. Pointing down to her still-swollen belly, she insists on getting you to run your hands over it as she purrs, [claire.speech(I'm still pregnant with our kid, isn't that so exciting?! So, anyway, what can I do for you this time?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
				[claire.speech(Oh, hello again, [pc.name]!)] Claire cheerfully exclaims as she sees that it's you who's calling out to her, [claire.speech(What can I do for you this time?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_claireAskedWarehouseEscape))
	<p>
		Before you can answer, the busty cat-girl suddenly steps up closer to you, and, batting her eyelids, she seductively whispers, [claire.speech(You know, that storeroom behind me would be the perfect place to go and have a quick fuck... We'd <i>probably</i> not be discovered in there...)]
	</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- CLAIRE_INFO_SUBMISSION_SOCIETY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_INFO_SUBMISSION_SOCIETY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I was wondering if you could tell me a little more about Submission, and the people who live down here,)] you say.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Of course!)] Claire happily replies, [claire.speech(You know, not many people really ask about that sort of thing, but I so happen to be an expert on Submission history and customs!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You can't help but smile as the small cat-girl proudly pushes her huge breasts out and places her hands on her absurdly wide hips, before starting, [claire.speech(There are five main types of residents down here; rat-morphs, alligator-morphs, slimes, imps, and bat-morphs. That's not to say those are the only races down here, however. You can find all the same races as you would up in Dominion, but it's those five who make up the vast majority of the population. Out of all of those, it's only the imps who are invariably troublesome. You get good and bad in all the other groups of Submission society, but I've yet to hear of an imp who cares about something other than causing mischief or having sex.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You can tell from the shift in tone of her voice that even the mention of imps is getting Claire annoyed, and you can only imagine how much trouble they must cause for the Enforcers down here. Before you can say anything to steer the conversation in a different direction, however, she quickly moves on, [claire.speech(Anyway, the imps stick to the tunnels, which are also filled with muggers, aggressive slimes, and all sorts of other unsavoury folk. You should always stick to the main walkways, where the majority of rat and alligator-morphs make their home. The alligators prefer to use the water ways to travel throughout Submission, while the rat-morphs, just like all the other races, stick to the walkways.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(What about bat-morphs?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Ah, yes, it's very rare for us to have to deal with any bat-morphs, as almost all of them stay down in the Bat Caverns. Thanks to their echolocation ability, they're not bothered by the dark, and have tunnelled out roosts up in the high ceilings of the caves down there,)] Claire replies, proudly smiling as she reels off all of this information. [claire.speech(About half of Submission's slime population lives down there as well. Apparently, they love the taste of the bioluminescent plants that thrive in some areas, and a lot of those slimes have eaten so much that their bodies have ended up glowing as well!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having heard enough about Submission society, you thank Claire for the information.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(You're welcome! Is there anything else you needed?)] she cheerily asks.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CLAIRE_INFO_LYSSIETH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_INFO_LYSSIETH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I wanted to ask you what you know about Lyssieth,)] you reply, noting how Claire's cheerful expression shifts into one of concern as she hears that name.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Well, as you might already know, Lyssieth is the Elder Lilin who's in charge of all of Submission. We Enforcers work to uphold the general laws of Lilith's domain, but it's Lyssieth who's in charge of giving us any special rules to enforce,)] Claire explains, uncomfortably shifting about a little as she finishes talking. Her small movements cause her huge breasts to start swaying from side to side in a pendulous manner, and you can't help but glance at them as she continues, [claire.speech(You should keep away from her palace. Her guards operate outside of our authority, and won't hesitate to attack if they suspect you of anything.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'll be careful of them,)] you reply, before continuing, [pc.speech(but you mentioned Lyssieth setting special rules; what are those?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Claire starts fidgeting even more as you ask that question, but despite her discomfort, she answers you, [claire.speech(Well, please don't go around telling anyone about this, but we've been told to ignore the anti-human laws that have been set in Dominion. You know, things like stopping and searching humans at random, and detaining them without reason for as long as we like.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I see,)] you respond, [pc.speech(So Lyssieth's only special rule is not to discriminate against humans?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Yes, but there aren't many humans living down here, so not many people know about this. Oh, and please don't go spreading this information. Everybody knows how much Lilith hates humans, and if she were to hear about this, I'm sure it'd be us, not Lyssieth, who gets punished,)] Claire mutters, before dropping back into her cheerful tone once again and asking, [claire.speech(Is there anything else I can help you with?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CLAIRE_INFO_TELEPORTATION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_INFO_TELEPORTATION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I was wondering if you could tell me any more about those 'teleportation pads' you mentioned before? I've never seen anything like that up in Dominion.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Claire grins in delight as you mention the thing that she's most proud of, and immediately thrusts her disproportionately-large breasts out towards you as she proudly puffs up her chest and says, [claire.speech(I can tell you a little more, I suppose. I'm not really meant to talk too much about them, but it'd do some good to show a member of the public that we Enforcers aren't all bad! Basically, these teleportation pads allow me to instantly travel between the Enforcer posts down here in Submission in order to quickly relay messages. Being under-staffed down here, we don't have many demons who can use telepathy, so the higher-ups managed to get SWORD to give us some of their unused teleportation pads for long-range communications instead. You know, it's super rare for us Frontline Patrol units to get access to these kind of arcane devices; it's normally just SWORD or ORICL who get to use this kind of stuff.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You must have worked hard in order to be chosen as the one to be using them then,)] you reply, hoping to encourage the proud cat-girl to reveal some more information about teleportation.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_SLIME_QUEEN))
		<p>
			[claire.speech(Thank you, yes I did!)] she replies, letting out a happy, contented little sigh as she hears you recognising her hard work, [claire.speech(I really put everything I've got into this job, and it all paid off when I was the one chosen to have such an important assignment! Hey, you know what, how about I show you the pads some time? I can tell you're really interested in them, and seeing as you've helped us out with that slime queen problem, my superior is sure to give you special permission to see them!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After telling her that you'd be happy to take a look at the teleportation pads some time when she's free, Claire smiles happily at you and exclaims, [claire.speech(Great! Just tell me whenever you're ready!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[claire.speech(Thank you, yes I did!)] she replies, letting out a happy, contented little sigh as she hears you recognising her hard work, [claire.speech(I really put everything I've got into this job, and it all paid off when I was the one chosen to have such an important assignment! I'd love to show you the teleportation pads some time, but I really don't think my superior will give you permission...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Coming to the end of her explanation about teleportation, Claire smiles happily at you and asks, [claire.speech(So, is there anything else you wanted, [pc.name]?)]
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
			[style.italicsMinorBad(You will be unable to visit the teleportation pads until you've completed the 'Slime Queen' side quest.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CLAIRE_INFO_SWORD_ORICL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_INFO_SWORD_ORICL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You mentioned 'SWORD' and 'ORICL' when talking about the teleportation pads before,)] you say, [pc.speech(Could you tell me more about them?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_TELEPORTATION))
			[claire.speech(Well, after that business in their warehouse, I think you already know enough about SWORD,)] Claire replies with sigh, [claire.speech(But just to give you a rundown again, the 'Special Weapons and Operations Response Department' are the ones who get all the heavy weapons and dangerous assignments. They're the guys who deal with stuff like hostage rescue, tracking down serious criminals, and conducting raids on criminal hideouts. They've got a pretty well-earned reputation for being trigger-happy, and it's us Frontline Patrol units who end up getting all the flak from members of the public when we have to go in and clean up after they've finished their operations...)]
		#ELSE
			[claire.speech(Yeah, of course,)] Claire replies, [claire.speech(The 'Special Weapons and Operations Response Department', just as their name suggests, are the ones who get all the heavy weapons and dangerous assignments. They're the guys who deal with stuff like hostage rescue, tracking down serious criminals, and conducting raids on criminal hideouts. They've got a pretty well-earned reputation for being trigger-happy, and it's us Frontline Patrol units who end up getting all the flak from members of the public when we have to go in and clean up after they've finished their operations...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(And ORICL?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Hmm, yeah, the 'Office of Realm Intelligence, Counter-Espionage, and Logistics'... Best not to ask too many questions about them,)] Claire replies, putting her hands on her hips and letting out a little huff, [claire.speech(An all-demon branch of the Enforcers, they're the guys who pay you a visit in the middle of the night, and then you're never seen again. As long as you don't start going around questioning Lilith's rule, or doing anything subversive against her rule, then you don't really need to worry about them.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking Claire for the information, you wonder what to ask her next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CLAIRE_INFO_REPORT_BACK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_INFO_REPORT_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With the thought of the five-thousand flame reward on your mind, you report, [pc.speech(I've got some information on the slimes that are transforming people out in Submission's tunnels.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(I knew you'd ignore my warnings and go into there!)] Claire replies as she angrily wags her finger at you, before dropping her hands back down to her hips and sighing, [claire.speech(But if you managed to get some useful information out of it, then please do tell! That reward is still available.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Well, when I encountered one of those slimes, they mentioned that they were transforming people due to following orders from a 'Slime Queen'. They even mentioned something about a quota of having to transform five people a day,)] you explain, recollecting what the slime said when you first encountered them.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Hmm... A Slime Queen...)] Claire mutters, before starting to pace back and forth. You can't help but notice the way her massive hips and huge breasts rhythmically sway from side to side as she struts back and forth, and look on in amusement as you notice that the other Enforcers are all giving her a wide berth. [claire.speech(You know, we'd heard rumours of a slime calling herself a Queen before, but we've scoured every last [unit.size] of the tunnels, and haven't found any trace of her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Perhaps she isn't in the tunnels?)] you offer.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Well, that's no good for us then,)] Claire sighs, stopping in front of you and placing her hands on her hips once more. [claire.speech(We're only authorised to patrol the tunnels and walkways. The only place where a Slime Queen could be hiding - if one even exists, that is - would be down in the Bat Caverns. We simply don't have the manpower to patrol down there, so who knows what could be hiding away down there in the dark...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So you want me to go down there and find evidence of the Slime Queen?)] you ask, guessing where this conversation is headed.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(What? No! It's far too dangerous!)] Claire quickly replies, flustered by your response. [claire.speech(There are bat-morphs which can swoop down on you at any moment, aggressive slimes who'd just love to attack you, and the whole place is completely pitch-black! Well, there are patches of bioluminescent fungi, but it's still really dark and scary down there!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Well, if I were to go down there and find a Slime Queen, that'd help you out, right?)] you ask, ignoring Claire's warnings.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Well, I suppose so, yes... I don't like to tell anyone, as I don't want to encourage people to seek out danger, but we do have a twenty-thousand flame reward for anyone who's able to put an end to this slime transformation problem.)] Claire says, wringing her hands with worry. [claire.speech(So if you're able to find and convince this Queen to stop, you'll have earned that reward. But please don't go looking for danger down there! I need to get back on with work now, but promise me you'll be careful before I go!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Don't worry so much,)] you reply, [pc.speech(I'm always careful.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a sigh of relief, Claire turns and rushes off to fetch your five-thousand flame reward, leaving you wondering whether it'd be worth risking a visit to the Bat Caverns. After all, if you were able to find and subdue this 'Slime Queen', you'd earn twenty-thousand flames. before you're able to decide what to do about this new information, Claire returns to deliver your reward, and after handing the flames over to you, she asks, [claire.speech(So, is there anything else I can help you with?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_INFO_SLIME_QUEEN_REPORT_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to report on your success with dealing with the Slime Queen, you say, [pc.speech(I should probably let you know that I've recently been down into the Bat Caverns, and I was able to find the Slime Queen down there...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Y-You what?!)] Claire shouts, puffing up her chest and wagging a finger at you. [claire.speech(I told you that was too dangerous!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Well, dangerous or not, I did as you asked,)] you reply, holding up the Slime Queen's crown for Claire to see. [pc.speech(I put an end to her plans of transforming everyone in Submission to slimes, and I brought her crown back as proof.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Really? She actually existed? And you managed to stop her?)] Claire asks, returning her hands to her hips once more. [claire.speech(That's amazing... Where did you find her?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(She's living in a tower, built on an island in the middle of an underground lake,)] you reply. [pc.speech(She said that she doesn't have any way to contact the people who claim to be her subjects, so she can't ask them to stop. She did, however, promise to stop producing those transformative 'Biojuice Canisters'.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(You've been such a huge help,)] Claire sighs, [claire.speech(With the sheer number of new cases of forced slime transformations, we were close to breaking point. You've no idea how much this is going to help us out. Let me get that reward I promised!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You watch as Claire hurries off into one of the back rooms, and, just a moment later, returns with a bag of coins in her hand. [claire.speech(Here you are!)] she squeaks, [claire.speech(Thank you so much, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You're welcome,)] you reply, smiling at the little cat-girl.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_claireAskedTeleportation))
			[claire.speech(Hey, now that you've helped us Enforcers out with this, I'm sure that I could get permission from my superior to let you see the teleportation pads!)] Claire happily exclaims, before asking, [claire.speech(So, would you like to see them now, or is there anything else I can help you with?)]
		#ELSE
			[claire.speech(So, is there anything else I can help you with?)] Claire happily asks.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_INFO_SLIME_QUEEN_REPORT_BACK_LIE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to make your fictitious report that the Slime Queen has been dealt with, you say, [pc.speech(I should probably let you know that I've recently been down into the Bat Caverns, and I was able to find the Slime Queen down there...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Y-You what?!)] Claire shouts, puffing up her chest and wagging a finger at you. [claire.speech(I told you that was too dangerous!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Well, dangerous or not, I did as you asked,)] you reply, holding up the Slime Queen's crown for Claire to see. [pc.speech(I put an end to her plans of transforming everyone in Submission to slimes, and I brought her crown back as proof.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Really? She actually existed? And you managed to stop her?)] Claire asks, returning her hands to her hips once more. [claire.speech(That's amazing... Where did you find her?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(She was hiding in one of those bioluminescent mushroom caverns,)] you lie, not wanting the Enforcers to find Catherine. [pc.speech(She said that she doesn't have any way to contact the people who claim to be her subjects, so she can't ask them to stop. She did, however, promise to stop producing those transformative 'Biojuice Canisters'.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(You've been such a huge help,)] Claire sighs, [claire.speech(With the sheer number of new cases of forced slime transformations, we were close to breaking point. You've no idea how much this is going to help us out. Let me get that reward I promised!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You watch as Claire hurries off into one of the back rooms, and, just a moment later, returns with a bag of coins in her hand. [claire.speech(Here you are!)] she squeaks. [claire.speech(Thank you so much, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You're welcome,)] you reply, smiling at the little cat-girl.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_claireAskedTeleportation))
			[claire.speech(Hey, now that you've helped us Enforcers out with this, I'm sure that I could get permission from my superior to let you see the teleportation pads!)] Claire happily exclaims, before asking, [claire.speech(So, would you like to see them now, or is there anything else I can help you with?)]
		#ELSE
			[claire.speech(So, is there anything else I can help you with?)] Claire happily asks.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- CLAIRE_VENGAR_HELP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_VENGAR_HELP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be a good idea to hear Claire's opinion of Vengar, you ask her if she's aware of the fact that he's leading a criminal gang, and if there's anything the Enforcers are doing to stop him. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Yes, of course I'm aware of Vengar,)] the busty cat-girl sighs, [claire.speech(And no, there's nothing we can do to stop him; frontline patrol units aren't equipped to directly confront gangs like his, and we don't have the manpower to guard the premises he's extorting for protection money. There's really nothing we can do about him.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So I wouldn't get any help if I were to go into his hideout and confront him?)] you ask, revealing your intentions.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Excuse me?!)] Claire exclaims, puffing up her chest and wagging a finger as she scolds you, [claire.speech(You'd better not be serious about that! Do you realise how dangerous Vengar is?! There's no way you're actually thinking about trying to confront him, right?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Replying that you are in fact serious about wanting to put a stop to Vengar's criminal activities, you watch as Claire pouts and places her hands on her hips, before letting out a weary sigh and revealing, [claire.speech(If you're really, truly serious about all this, then there is something that I can do to help. I'll need to run it by the Inspector first, though, so just wait here, ok?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_VENGAR_HELP_WAIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Agreeing to wait for her return, you watch Claire hurry off to a door marked 'Inspector Powell', before knocking on it and stepping inside. After an uneventful five minutes, she eventually steps back out of the office, and with her huge breasts bouncing up and down, she rushes back over towards you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Ok, I got permission to give you some help,)] she reveals, [claire.speech(but under the condition that this is all off the record, ok? If we manage to capture Vengar, we can't offer you a reward or anything...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Curious to hear what kind of help Claire is willing to offer, you tell her that you're ok with not getting any official recognition, before asking what she has in mind.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(This is meant to be classified information, but seeing as you might be able to provide us with a unique opportunity, and also due to the fact that I vouched for you, the Inspector is allowing me to tell you this,)] Claire reveals, before stepping closer to you and lowering her voice, [claire.speech(There's been a SWORD unit waiting to launch a raid on the Rat Warrens for a couple of weeks now, but they're only interested in capturing Vengar himself, and so they're waiting for confirmation that he's inside before assaulting the place. If they were to raid the place and fail to find Vengar, he'd be sure to take precautions against ever being found again...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So you want me to find out if he's in there for you?)] you ask, picking up on what it is Claire is about to ask you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(That's right,)] she confirms, before reaching into a pouch on her vest and producing a small, dark-purple sphere. Handing it towards you, she says, [claire.speech(This is a basic resonance stone, calibrated to send a signal to the one in the SWORD unit's possession. These are normally illegal for citizens to possess, let alone use, but you have special permission from the Inspector. Just twist the two halves in opposite directions to activate it. Oh, and obviously only use it once you're in the Rat Warrens and have confirmed that Vengar is inside, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking the resonance stone from Claire, you see that there's a shallow groove running the entire way around its circumference, effectively splitting the sphere into two halves. Telling the busty cat-girl that you understand how it works, you put it away into your inventory.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(The Inspector told me that the response time for the SWORD squad is going to be about five to ten minutes, so just buy some time after activating the stone, and they'll come to help you deal with Vengar as soon as they can,)] Claire further explains, [claire.speech(Oh, and show them the stone when they arrive, so that they don't arrest you by mistake...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking Claire, and with nothing more on the matter to discuss, you wonder what to do next... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CLAIRE_TELEPORTATION_PADS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_TELEPORTATION_PADS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to take a look at the teleportation pads, you say, [pc.speech(I was hoping to take you up on your offer of showing me those teleportation pads,)] you explain.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Oh, of course!)] the happy Enforcer replies, proudly puffing up her chest and placing her hands on her absurdly-wide hips as she continues, [claire.speech(I've got permission from the higher-ups to show you them, but on one condition!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(What's that?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(That you let your friends know that we Enforcers aren't all bad,)] Claire reveals, letting out a playful giggle. Even her armoured vest isn't enough to contain the heaving of her huge, [claire.cupSize]-cup breasts as she lets out this burst of mirthful laughter, and more than a couple of heads turn your way to witness the show that the busty cat-girl is inadvertently putting on. Seemingly oblivious to the people staring at her chest, she turns on the spot and starts walking towards a nearby door, calling over her shoulder as she goes, [claire.speech(Come on, [pc.name]. They're through here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as she asks, you follow in Claire's footsteps and head through the nearby door, which you notice is marked as 'Enforcers Only'. Instead of housing the teleportation pads, as you'd expected, the room beyond turns out to be a normal old office. A very bored-looking wolf-girl Enforcer is sitting behind a desk on the right-hand side of the room, and as the two of you enter, she sighs, [genericFemale.speech(Hey, Claire. Is that the visitor here to see the pads?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Hey Karen! That's right, I got permission from Inspector Powell and everything,)] Claire replies, leading you over to yet another wooden door just past Karen's desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[genericFemale.speech(Yeah, yeah, I know you've got permission,)] the wolf-girl replies, stifling a yawn before continuing, [genericFemale.speech(I'm getting off shift in two minutes, and Lucy's always five minutes late, so after you're done, could you cover for me until she shows up?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Sure thing!)] Claire happily replies, opening the door and leading you through as she calls out, [claire.speech(See you tomorrow, Karen!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Yet another tired yawn follows the two of you through into the high-ceilinged room beyond, where you finally get your first look at these 'teleportation pads'. Devoid of any other furnishings, this room houses two of them, with each one taking the form of a bulky, circular metal pad, around [unit.lSize(300)] in diameter. Fixed to each one is a simple control panel, which sits atop a waist-high metal tube that connects to the pad below.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(So, here they are!)] Claire excitedly exclaims, [claire.speech(I wish I could demonstrate them to you, but teleportation is some seriously restricted stuff; even getting to see these pads is kind of a big deal. It's just fortunate for you that the Deputy Commissioner is as concerned with public relations as I am!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can give Claire your thoughts on the devices before you, she continues, [claire.speech(The one on the right is our backup pad, and is totally deactivated right now, so you can even stand on it if you want! Go on!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking the opportunity to get a closer look at the device, you do as Claire suggests and step forwards onto the smooth metal surface. Sure enough, the control panel looks to be completely dead, and for all intents and purposes, it's as though you're just standing on a big sheet of ordinary metal.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(These things were designed to teleport up to four people at once, you know, which is why they're so big!)] Claire reveals, stepping up onto the pad beside you. [claire.speech(See? There's plenty of room! W-Wait, why is that lighting up?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following Claire's suddenly-worried gaze, you look back across to the control panel just in time to see the half-dozen buttons and dials lighting up. The last thing you see before a blinding flash of purple light surrounds you are the words on the control panel's display screen:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
	[style.italicsArcane(
		Group Teleportation Detected...<br/>
		Destination set: <b>SWORD_P_GTP_0047</b><br/>
		<b>Warning, destination pad's essence storage is depleted!</b><br/>
		Teleport activated...
	)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	

	<!-- ENFORCER_WARHOUSE_APPEARANCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENFORCER_WARHOUSE_APPEARANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The purple flash of light almost instantly dissipates, but instead of the scene before you returning to that of the room you were just in, you find yourself looking directly down at a concrete floor. Suddenly being at a right-angle to the direction of gravity momentarily disorients you, and you only just manage to brace your short fall at the last moment. Almost immediately as you hit the floor, the full weight of Claire's body suddenly crashes down on your back.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getSexualOrientation().isAttractedToFeminine())
			[claire.speech(Eek!)] she cries out in alarm. Quickly realising that it was you who just broke her fall, she starts to frantically apologise, [claire.speech(Oh, sorry, [pc.name]! I-I don't know what happened! Just let me get up- Eek!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Claire attempts to stand up, she slips and collapses back down on top of you; her massive breasts cushion her fall as you feel them suddenly press down into your upper back. Apologising once again, the busty cat-girl manges to successfully stand up on her second attempt, before leaning down to help you get to your feet. As you stand up beside her, she looks around and worriedly asks, [claire.speech(Oh no, where <i>are</i> we?)]
		#ELSE
			[claire.speech(Eek!)] she cries out in alarm. Quickly realising that it was you who just broke her fall, she starts to frantically apologise, [claire.speech(Oh, sorry, [pc.name]! I-I don't know what happened! Just let me move over, hang on!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Continuing to apologise, Claire quickly stands up, before leaning down to help you get to your feet. As you stand up beside her, she looks around and worriedly asks, [claire.speech(Oh no, where <i>are</i> we?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENFORCER_WARHOUSE_APPEARANCE_SOLO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have that question answered yourself, you take a look around to see what sort of place you've ended up in. It's immediately apparent that you're in a warehouse of some sort, as you're surrounded on all four sides by towering stacks of wooden crates, while high above you, long rows of arcane lights hang from a corrugated steel roof.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENFORCER_WARHOUSE_APPEARANCE_COMPANIONS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Looking around, the first thing you notice is that it's just the two of you who are present. Your companion was obviously left behind when you and Claire accidentally teleported here, but you're confident that they'll be able to find their way home without issue. The next thing which is immediately apparent to you is that you're in a warehouse of some sort, as you're surrounded on all four sides by towering stacks of wooden crates, while high above you, long rows of arcane lights hang from a corrugated steel roof.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENFORCER_WARHOUSE_APPEARANCE_ELEMENTAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Looking around, the first thing you notice is that it's just the two of you who are present. Your elemental was obviously dispelled when you and Claire accidentally teleported here, but you're confident that you'll be able to summon them again without issue. The next thing which is immediately apparent to you is that you're in a warehouse of some sort, as you're surrounded on all four sides by towering stacks of wooden crates, while high above you, long rows of arcane lights hang from a corrugated steel roof.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENFORCER_WARHOUSE_APPEARANCE_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Looking back down, you see that the teleportation pad which you just arrived on has been tipped up onto its side and then leant against the closest stack of crates, which would explain why you and Claire appeared horizontally. There doesn't seem to be anyone nearby, nor, rather worryingly, any way to get out of the four-sided enclave the two of you are currently standing in.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPerkAnywhereInTree(PERK_OBSERVANT))
				[pc.speech(What are these markings?)] you ask, noticing that each of the wooden crates have a black-inked serial number and accompanying stamp on their side, [pc.speech(Is that 'SWORD'?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[claire.speech(SWORD?! Oh no!)] Claire replies, clearly distressed by the mention of that name, [claire.speech(We need to get out of here, <i>now</i>! Help me with this!)]
		#ELSE
			[claire.speech(What are these markings?)] Claire asks, drawing your attention to the fact that each of the wooden crates have a black-inked serial number and accompanying stamp on their side, [claire.speech(Is that 'SWORD'?! Oh no! We need to get out of here, <i>now</i>! Help me with this!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		The small cat-girl starts tugging at the teleportation pad, clearly intending to reposition it so that it's lying flat on the ground. Doing as she asks, you move forwards and help her to steadily lay it down, and after you've done so, she continues in a frantic, worried tone, [claire.speech(This is a different design to the ones I'm used to! How did this even happen?! There must be an essence port somewhere on it... Please, help me look for a small round hatch!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	

	<!-- CLAIRE_WAREHOUSE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CLAIRE_WAREHOUSE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you didn't get much time to talk about it immediately after your escape, you ask Claire what she thought about your experience in the SWORD warehouse.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(N-Not so loud!)] the cat-girl hisses, [claire.speech(Look, I had to tell my boss about it, but nobody else needs to know, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Don't worry, I've kept it a secret,)] you reply, [pc.speech(and there's nobody nearby who's going to overhear us.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Y-Yes, well, you never know,)] Claire responds, and you notice that for some odd reason she's starting to blush. Before you can ask her what's wrong, she continues, [claire.speech(The truth is, I kind of found that whole experience to be... well.. pretty exciting...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I suppose it was,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(No, not like that,)] the busty cat-girl hisses, before stepping up close to you and explaining, in an alarmingly-sensual tone, [claire.speech(I mean that I keep on fantasising about it... Just imagine if we'd been caught! Those SWORD guys could have done whatever they wanted with us... The thought of being caught doing something naughty... It's just so... hot!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getSexualOrientation().isAttractedToFeminine())
				Before you offer a response to this revelation, Claire suddenly leans in against you, crushing her huge, [claire.cupSize]-cup breasts into your torso. Craning her neck forwards, she presses her [claire.lips+] firmly against yours, and right in the middle of the busy Enforcer post, she passionately kisses you.
			</p>
			<p>
				Almost immediately as she's started, the horny cat-girl breaks off the kiss. Quickly straightening back up, she glances around to make sure that nobody noticed what she just did. Sure enough, by some sort of miracle, none of the the dozen-or-so Enforcers around you noticed your brief kiss. Biting her lip and giggling in delight, Claire moans, [claire.speech(Fun, isn't it? You know, this room behind me is only used for storage. We could always sneak into there if you wanted to get another taste of me... We <i>probably</i> won't be discovered...)] 
		#ELSE
			Before you offer a response to this revelation, Claire continues, [claire.speech(You know, this room behind me is only used for storage... We could always sneak into there and have some fun if you wanted to re-enact that sense of danger... We <i>probably</i> won't be discovered...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech('Probably'?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Yes, well, the door doesn't have a lock, and people do sometimes use it... But that all adds to the thrill, doesn't it?)] Claire giggles, before continuing, [claire.speech(We don't have to do it right now; just let me know if you're ever feeling... naughty...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Claire's experience in the SWORD warehouse has obviously awoken some kind of fetish for risky sex, and you wonder whether you should play along with it or not...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- START_CLAIRE_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="START_CLAIRE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the idea of having some risky sex with your cat-girl friend, you suggest to her that two of you could step inside the Enforcer storage room and get intimate with one another. As soon as you say this, Claire's eyes light up, and, stepping forwards to press her huge boobs against you, she responds, [claire.speech(~Ooh!~ Yes, let's just wait until nobody is watching, then we can sneak inside... Come on!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting her lead the way, you follow Claire over to a nearby door, beside which the two of you wait and pretend to talk to one another. When it looks like nobody's watching, the little cat-girl pulls opens the door, and after the two of you have rushed inside, she quickly shuts it. Remaining motionless as the two of you wait to see if anyone follows you inside, the only sound in the dimly-lit stockroom is yours and Claire's excited, heavy breathing.
	</p>
	<p>
		Thirty seconds pass in silence like this, and then another minute more. Eventually, once it's clear that nobody saw you sneak inside, Claire suddenly throws herself at you, pressing her lips against yours and moaning, [claire.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Come on, let's fuck and get out of here before anyone turns up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Just as Claire mentioned, there's no lock on the door, and so, with the threat of someone entering and catching the two of you at any moment, you and the busty cat-girl prepare to have some incredibly risky sex...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- AFTER_CLAIRE_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_CLAIRE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(!claire.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			With the prospect of someone catching the two of you being too much for you to bear, you tell Claire that you should stop. Letting out an annoyed whine, the cat-girl moans, [claire.speech(~Aww!~ But I didn't even get to cum... This sucks...)]
		#ELSE
			Having managed not to be caught in the middle of fucking one another, you and Claire each let out a deeply-satisfied sigh, and, quickly gathering the discarded clothing on the floor, you get dressed and prepare to leave.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Slowly opening the door to the storeroom, Claire peeks out to make sure that the coast is clear. Whispering under her breath, she counts, [claire.speech(Get ready... Three... Two... One... Go!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		On her mark, the two of you hastily exit the storeroom, and, quickly shutting the door behind you, you both glance around to make sure that nobody's looking your way. Thankfully, the Enforcers all seem to busy with their work, and it appears as though your intimate storeroom antics have gone completely unnoticed.
	</p>
	<p>
		[claire.speech(Fuck... That was such a thrill!)] Claire excitedly squeals, before biting her lip at you and asking, [claire.speech(We're going to have to do that again some time, but until then, do you need anything else from me?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- WALKWAYS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WALKWAYS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The main tunnels of Submission are surprisingly spacious, clean and full of life.
		 A deep channel of opaque, greenish water flows at a steady pace down the centre of each passage, and to either side, well-maintained wooden walkways have been built up against the grey stone walls.
		 Numerous bridges cross the watery divide at regular intervals, and every [unit.lSizes(10000)] or so, a series of stone steps trails down into the murky river to provide easy access for Submission's aquatic inhabitants.
	</p>
	<p>
		The damp atmosphere holds just enough chill to gently caress any exposed skin, but, thanks to the wide iron grates built into the ceiling, the air doesn't feel stagnant down here.
		 Looking up trough the iron bars, you're granted an unobstructed view of the sky, and, every now and then, up the occasional skirt.
		 The dizzying network of pipes and valves that run along the upper-half of the walls makes you feel sorry for whoever has to map and maintain them.
	</p>
	<p>
		Houses and shops of all kinds have been tunnelled out and built into the walls, and, while not as busy as Dominion, there are enough people ambling by to fill the tunnels with a continuous background drone of chatter and laughter.
		 There seems to be a heavy presence of Enforcers down here, and you can't go more than five minutes without seeing a patrol marching by.
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite Submission being their home, you only see the occasional imp in this area;
		 evidence that they're so much of a nuisance that the vast majority of them are banished to the dark tunnels that branch off on either side of this main passage.
		 The vast majority of people that you pass are slimes, alligator-morphs, and rat-morphs, but there are also plenty of regular morphs eking out a living down here.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WALKWAYS_EXTRA"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		Did that wave just wink at you? No, it must have been your imagination...
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="WALKWAYS_EXTRA"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		Looking over the edge of the walkway, you see an alligator-girl slowly lowering herself down into the water beneath you. Catching your eye, she winks and disappears beneath the surface...
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="WALKWAYS_EXTRA"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		Looking over the edge of the walkway, you see an alligator-boy slowly lowering himself down into the water beneath you. Catching your eye, he winks and disappears beneath the surface...
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="WALKWAYS_EXTRA"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		In his haste, a passing rat-boy almost bumps into you. He scowls and lets out a muffled curse before quickly scurrying away...
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="WALKWAYS_EXTRA"><![CDATA[
	<p><i>
		In her haste, a passing rat-girl almost bumps into you. She scowls and lets out a muffled curse before quickly scurrying away...
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TUNNEL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unlike the main passages of Submission, the shaded alcoves and wide pipe openings make these dark, claustrophobic tunnels the perfect place for an ambush. Filmy perspiration drips from the walls, and you flinch every time a drop touches you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Kicking up rubbish and random debris as you quickly move through the dilapidated area, each of your steps sounds as loud as a thunder-clap to your ears. You can't help but shake the feeling that someone's lying in wait around each corner, waiting for their chance to lunge out of the shadows and attack...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TUNNEL_IMP_CONTROL"><![CDATA[
	<p style='color:[#pc.getLocationPlace().getPlaceType().getColour().toWebHexString()];'>
		<i>This tunnel is part of a network that's currently being controlled by an imp fortress! Until the fortress is cleared, anyone who calls these tunnels home is sure to remain in hiding...</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAT_CAVERNS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The tunnel before you comes to an abrupt halt, but instead of a brick wall or iron grate to block your way, the passageway instead opens out into a pitch-black void.
		 Cautiously stepping forwards, you see that a sign has been placed just before the end of the walkway, and you read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'><i>
		<b>Bat Caverns</b><br/>
		In order to avoid exciting the resident bat-morphs, travellers are advised to extinguish all personal light sources.
		 The luminescent lichen will provide you with enough illumination.
	</i></p>
	<p>
		Moving forwards past the sign, you peer down into the darkness.
		 The light from the passage behind you manages to illuminate the first dozen steep stone steps that are carved into the rock below, letting you know that there's a way down into these caverns even for people who are incapable of flight.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAT_CAVERNS_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to travel down into the bat caverns, you step towards the edge of the precipice before you.
		 Looking down at the steep, stone staircase that disappears into the inky blackness of the caverns' depths, you move forwards and take the first step.
	</p>
	<p>
		Instantly, the dark grey hue of the staircase beneath your [pc.feet] is replaced by a soft, turquoise glow.
		 Looking down, you see that the stone steps are coated in a blanket of bioluminescent lichens and mosses, which, when pressure is applied to them, light up to illuminate their the area around them.
		 Although bright enough to allow you to see your immediate surroundings, the lichen's light drops off at a distance of about [unit.lSizes(1500)] or so, and you can't help but feel like it's painting you as a target to anyone lurking in the darkness beyond.
	</p>
	<p>
		Determined to continue on your downwards journey, you proceed to the bottom of the staircase, and find yourself stepping forwards into pitch-black cavern.
		 Thankfully, the same bioluminescent carpet that coats the stairs seems to grow all throughout this area as well, and as you begin your exploration, your footsteps illuminate the way ahead.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- RAT_WARREN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAT_WARREN_CLOSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		This side tunnel looks just like all of the others that you've travelled through so far, but with one exception. Built into the wall nearest to where you're standing, a large stone archway has been constructed, which houses a pair of heavy oaken doors.
	</p>
	<p>
		Having been cleared out by the SWORD raid, the Rat Warrens are now completely deserted, and to prevent any new gang from moving in and setting up shop, several iron bars have been bolted onto the doors in front of you, preventing them from being opened. Several identical pieces of paper have been plastered over the stonework to either side of the entrance, and, taking a closer look at one of them, you read:
	</p>
	<h6 style='text-align:center;'>Submission Enforcer Department</h6>
	<h5 style='text-align:center;'>NOTICE OF ASSET SEIZURE</h5>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		Having been identified as being used, or suspected of being used, by criminal(s), this property has been seized by the Submission Enforcer Department.<br/>
		Any unauthorised entry beyond this point is in violation of the law.
		<br/><br/>
		Officer in charge of investigation: <i>Inspector Powell</i>
		<br/><br/>
		Any complaints or inquiries should be made in person at the nearest Submission Enforcer Outpost. Thank you for your understanding.
	</p>
	<p>
		With nothing more to be gained from loitering in this area, you step back from the doors and prepare to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAT_WARREN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		This side tunnel looks just like all of the others that you've travelled through so far, but with one exception. Built into the wall nearest to where you're standing, a large stone archway has been constructed, which houses a pair of heavy oaken doors. Shut tight and bolted from within, these doors block access to whatever is on the other side.
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping forwards to take a closer look, you see that the words <i>'Vengar's Rat Warrens'</i> have been carved into the stone to the right of the doors. You wonder if you should give the doors a knock, or simply carry on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- RAT_WARREN_KNOCK_ON_DOOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAT_WARREN_KNOCK_ON_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to see if you can gain access to the Rat Warrens, you step up to the heavy oaken doors, before reaching out and giving them a sharp knock.
	</p>
	<p>
		After just a few moments, you hear sounds of movement coming from beyond, followed by the noise of a heavy metal bolt sliding to one side. With a deafening creak of rusted hinges, the weathered doors slowly open inwards to reveal a small hallway, with yet another pair of wooden doors built into the far wall. Set into the stone on either side of this interior pair of doors, you see a couple of small, open hatches, and as you step forwards, cocked crossbows suddenly poke out from them, aiming in your general direction.
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensEntryWhore))
		<p>
			[npc.speech('Ey, you's that whore wot was here ta get fucked by Vengar!)] the rough voice of [npc.name] calls out from one of the hatches, [npc.speech(Ya back ta get some more o' 'is cock? Come on in!)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensEntry))
		<p>
			[npc.speech('Ey, you's that person wot was here doin' business with Vengar!)] the rough voice of [npc.name] calls out from one of the hatches, [npc.speech(Ya back ta see 'im again? Come on in!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Wot you wantin'?!)] a rough voice calls out from one of the hatches, [npc.speech(Speak up quick, or else yer gonna see wot these things can do!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(That's right!)] a second voice chimes in, [npc2.speech(If ya ain't got any business 'ere, then fuck off!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAT_WARREN_ENTRY_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding against entering the Rat Warrens right now, you shout out to the guards that you've changed your mind, before stepping back into the tunnel.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Wot a fuckin' waste o' our time!)] [npc.name] shouts out, [npc.speech(Don't bother fuckin' comin' back unless ya wantin' ta come in!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seemingly powered by an internal mechanism, the exterior doors slowly start grinding shut, and after just a moment, you find yourself once again locked out in the tunnels of Submission.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAT_WARREN_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Without any reason to be here, you've go no choice but to shout out to the guards that you've changed your mind about wanting to enter, before stepping back into the tunnel.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Wot a fuckin' waste o' our time!)] the rough voice shouts out, [npc.speech(Don't bother fuckin' comin' back unless ya got business ta be here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seemingly powered by an internal mechanism, the exterior doors slowly start grinding shut, and after just a moment, you find yourself once again locked out in the tunnels of Submission.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- GAMBLING_DEN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GAMBLING_DEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Over the past several minutes, you've noticed that the walkways that you're travelling down have steadily been getting busier and busier.
		 Up in the wide streets of Dominion, this volume of traffic wouldn't be a problem, but down here, there's not much room on the narrow pathways in which to manoeuvre, and you soon find yourself having to physically push your way through the bustling crowds.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just as you're thinking about turning back in order to find another way past this area, the tunnel that you're travelling through starts to widen out, and, mercifully, so do the walkways.
		 Afforded a little space at last, you're able to quickly weave through the crowds, and soon find yourself in a particularly large and spacious area of Submission, being at least double the height and four-times the width of all the other tunnels you've travelled through.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you step forwards onto the wide, well-maintained walkways, you quickly discover the reason behind the abnormal amount of people that are in this area.
		 All around you, brightly coloured canvas stalls have been erected, and as you pass, you see that they're selling all sorts of different goods.
		 This area is obviously Submission's main marketplace, and although the wares for sale aren't of any interest to you, they're enough to attract crowds of shoppers from all over Submission.
	</p>
	<p>
		A huge, two-story building, reaching up to the tunnel's ceiling, has been built into the wall on one side of this area.
		 A sign above the entrance declares it to be the 'Gambling Den'.
		 While the market stalls aren't worth your time, this building looks as though it contains something of interest.
		 Walking up to the open doorway, you see a little sign fixed onto the wall, which bears the words 'Open 24/7'.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_CAVERN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking down a stone pathway, which has been cut out of the rock floor of a colossal underground cavern.
		 The waterway that runs through Submission's tunnels continues on to one side of the path, flowing down the gently sloping floor to eventually fall away into a wide chasm that cuts across the far side of the cavern.
	</p>
	<p>
		This chasm serves as a protective moat for a massive, Gothic-styled palace that has been half-built, half-carved into the far stone wall.
		 A huge wooden drawbridge links the stone path that you're walking on to the palace's front gate.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_CAVERN_NOT_MET_ELIZABETH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While you appear to be the only person making use of the path, you're not alone in this area. Up ahead, standing guard beside the drawbridge, are the figures of at least twenty demons. Each one appears to be wearing an olive uniform and has some kind of weapon holstered by their side, but from this distance, it's hard to see them clearly.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_CAVERN_MET_ELIZABETH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While you appear to be the only person making use of the path, you're not alone in this area. Up ahead, standing to attention beside the drawbridge, are the familiar figures of at least twenty of Lyssieth's royal guards. Although it's hard to see her clearly from this distance, you're still able to recognise Elizabeth at the head of them.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having crossed the huge cavern, you find yourself approaching the massive Gothic palace that has been carved into the dark stone wall. In front of you, separating the huge front gates from the path that you're standing on, is a vast, seemingly bottomless ravine. A heavy wooden drawbridge crosses the pitch-black depths of the chasm, which appears to be the only means of entry to the palace.
	</p>
	<p>
		A group of twenty-or-so half-succubi are standing on this side of the ravine, and are preventing any unwelcome visitors from proceeding across the drawbridge. The majority of them appear to be half-demons, and, much like Lilaya, they have human faces and bodies, with demonic wings, horns, tails, and ears. Rather curiously, they're all wearing drab olive uniforms, with matching hats, skirts, and shoes. At each guards' side, they appear to have a holstered revolver, although, with the nature of this world being as it is, you know that they're likely to fire condensed arcane essences rather than actual bullets. These weapons, in combination with their uniforms, makes them look very much like mid-twentieth century British soldiers.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_ENTRY_GRANTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Walking up to the drawbridge, you smile at Elizabeth as she calls out, [elizabeth.speech(Well, hello again, [pc.name]. I can escort you into the palace, if you wish.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The demons around you step aside, allowing you to continue onwards over the drawbridge to Lyssieth's palace.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_ENTRY_BLOCKED_QUEST_COMPLETED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Walking up to the drawbridge, you smile at Elizabeth as she calls out, [elizabeth.speech(Well, if it isn't the [pc.hero] of the hour [pc.herself]. Her Highness has already sent word that her daughter is safely locked in her room, awaiting her punishment. Now, as a formality, I'll need to take a statement of how you defeated her before I can allow you to enter the palace.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		It looks as though Elizabeth really wants you to deliver the report right at this moment, and, thinking that it would be best to stay on her good side, you decide to do just that...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_ENTRY_BLOCKED_QUEST_GAINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach, you see the familiar figure of Elizabeth standing at the head of her group of guards. Catching sight of you, she narrows her eyes, before stating, [elizabeth.speech(We've had no news of the capture of Her Highness's daughter. Until you're able to deal with her, I'm afraid that you're not going to be getting past us.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You see that the demons around you are alert and ready to fight, and, realising that you stand no chance at gaining entry through force, there's nothing more for you to do here but turn around and leave. Then again, if you had anything else to ask of Elizabeth, you could do that first...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_ENTRY_BLOCKED_INTRODUCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach, the leader of the group, a light-skinned half-demon succubus, with crimson-skinned demonic parts, steps forwards to bar your passage. [elizabeth.speech(That's far enough, [pc.name]. Her Highness still isn't receiving visitors, so there really isn't anything for you here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You see that the demons around you are alert and ready to fight, and, realising that you stand no chance at gaining entry through force, there's nothing more for you to do here but turn around and leave. Then again, if you had anything else to ask of Elizabeth, you could do that first...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_ENTRY_BLOCKED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach, a light-skinned half-succubus, with crimson-skinned demonic parts, steps forwards to bar your passage. [elizabeth.speech(Stop right there#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_HUMAN)!#ELSE, [pc.race].#ENDIF Her Highness, Lyssieth, isn't receiving visitors at the moment, and it's quite out of the ordinary for someone to just waltz up to us like this. Identify yourself!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You notice that the small army of demons around you are alert and ready for a fight, and, realising that it would be best to cooperate, you decide to do as the half-succubus asks.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_INTRODUCTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(My name is [pc.nameFull],)] you say, seeing no reason to conceal your identity.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech([pc.Name]... I'll remember you,)] the half-succubus replies, with a suspicious tone in her voice. [elizabeth.speech(My name is Elizabeth, and I'm the captain of Lyssieth's royal guard. If you have any business with Her Highness, then you may let me know, although, as I said before, she isn't receiving visitors at the moment.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With introductions out of the way, Lyssieth's royal guard seem to relax a little, and you suppose that you could turn around and leave without being detained. Then again, if you had anything to ask of Elizabeth, you could do that first...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_AUDIENCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Is there any way I could get to see Lyssieth? It's quite urgent,)] you say to Elizabeth, hoping that there might be some exceptions to the 'no visitors' rule that appears to be effect.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Unless you're here on official business from another Lilin, then no. And before you say something you'll regret, any official messenger would have supporting paperwork,)] she flatly states.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Not even if I'm Lilaya's [pc.niece], who has something very important to discuss?)] you ask, invoking your aunt's name in an attempt to convince the stoic half-succubus.
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your delight, as you reveal that you're somewhat related to Lyssieth herself, Elizabeth raises her eyebrows. [elizabeth.speech(Hmm, you <i>do</i> fit the description of the one who's living with her...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Does <i>everybody</i> know about my living arrangements?!)] you groan, thinking back to the way Zaranix also recognised you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Well, I can't speak for anyone else, but we of the royal guard always keep ourselves well-informed of who Lyssieth's recognised children are mingling with. As a final confirmation, may I ask the name of the gentleman who also recently moved in with Lilaya?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That'd be Arthur,)] You quickly reply, eager to get this over and done with so that you can finally meet Lyssieth.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Yes, that checks out,)] the half-succubus smirks, allowing her stony expression to be broken. [elizabeth.speech(From what we understand, [pc.name], you're quite the expert at resolving difficult situations. Business with the Enforcers, regular trips to Demon Home, and, from what I hear, well-acquainted with both the Harpy Nests and Slaver Alley. You have been busy...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You make a mental note to keep a closer look-out for anyone following you when you return to Dominion, before trying to encourage Elizabeth to move on to the business at hand, [pc.speech(Well, now that you know who exactly I am, can I please be allowed to see Lyssieth?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Ordinarily, no. When Her Highness says no visitors, she means it. As it turns out, however, we're in need of someone with your particular skills. You help us out, and we'll allow you to enter the palace,)] Elizabeth says, before continuing, [elizabeth.speech(Another of Her Highness's recognised daughters has been causing nothing but trouble for the local Enforcers ever since she was allowed to leave the palace. Perhaps you've seen the gangs of imps roaming parts of Submission? Those are all her doing.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising where this is going, and used to having to sort out other people's problems by now, you sigh as you respond, [pc.speech(You want me to put an end to the trouble she's causing?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(That's right. Even if Her Highness did have the freedo- ~Ahem!~ That is, even if Her Highness did have the time to leave her palace, it would be a major scandal if she was heard to be having to discipline one of her recognised daughters. The amount of royal guards it would take to drag her kicking and screaming back to Her Highness's side is also simply unacceptable, and would leave the palace too vulnerable. No, we need someone like you to sort out this situation for us.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Fine. If that's what it's going to take,)] you say, resigning yourself to your fate.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Excellent. The demon you're after is going by the title 'the dark siren', and can be found somewhere in the tunnels in the very centre of Submission,)] Elizabeth explains, before reaching into one of her pockets and producing a rather curious-looking ring. Handing it over to you, she continues, [elizabeth.speech(This is one of Her Highness's signet rings, which normally carry some impressive enchantments. We've had this particular one altered, however, to enslave the person who puts it on. We've also registered Her Highness's daughter as a slave of special interest, so instead of being teleported to Slaver Alley, she'll be sent straight to Her Highness's room. I'm sure you can find some way to trick her into putting it on.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ok, I'll get this sorted out,)] you reply, placing the ring in your inventory.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Excellent. We hope to hear of your success soon,)] Elizabeth says in return, before taking a step back and waiting for you to take your leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_AUDIENCE_SKIP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Is there any way I could get to see Lyssieth? It's quite urgent,)] you say to Elizabeth, hoping that there might be some exceptions to the 'no visitors' rule that appears to be effect.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Unless you're here on official business from another Lilin, then no. And before you say something you'll regret, any official messenger would have supporting paperwork,)] she flatly states.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Not even if I'm Lilaya's [pc.niece], who has something very important to discuss?)] you ask, invoking your aunt's name in an attempt to convince the stoic half-succubus.
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your delight, as you reveal that you're somewhat related to Lyssieth herself, Elizabeth raises her eyebrows. [elizabeth.speech(Hmm, you <i>do</i> fit the description of the one who's living with her...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Does <i>everybody</i> know about my living arrangements?!)] you groan, thinking back to the way Zaranix also recognised you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Well, I can't speak for anyone else, but we of the royal guard always keep ourselves well-informed of who Lyssieth's recognised children are mingling with. As a final confirmation, may I ask the name of the gentleman who also recently moved in with Lilaya?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That'd be Arthur,)] You quickly reply, eager to get this over and done with so that you can finally meet Lyssieth.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Yes, that checks out,)] the half-succubus smirks, allowing her stony expression to be broken. [elizabeth.speech(From what we understand, [pc.name], you're quite the expert at resolving difficult situations. Business with the Enforcers, regular trips to Demon Home, and, from what I hear, well-acquainted with both the Harpy Nests and Slaver Alley. You have been busy...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You missed out the part where I defeated the 'dark siren'. Pretty sure your spies should have picked up on that one,)] you say, a little frustrated at how these guards have been spying on you. [pc.speech(So anyway, now that you know who I am, can I please be allowed to see Lyssieth?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you reveal the fact that it was you who defeated Lyssieth's daughter, Elizabeth raises her eyebrows and gazes at you in disbelief. [elizabeth.speech(Wait, that was <i>you</i> who beat her in a fight?! There's no way... T-Tell me how it happened! Her Highness has already informed us of her daughter's version of events, so we'll see if your stories match up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You spend the next fifteen minutes or so explaining your methods, starting at how you got an arcane key from one of the surrounding imp fortress, and finishing with a description of how you bested Lyssieth's daughter in combat. As you finish recounting the battle you had in the stone keep, Elizabeth stammers and trips over her words as she realises that you were actually telling the truth. [elizabeth.speech(Wow... But Lyssieth herself taught her how to use the arcane... I-I mean, everyone in the palace knows about how she over-estimates her abilities, but she... I mean... Who <i>are</i> you?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(As I told you at the start of all this, I'm Lilaya's [pc.niece]. Well, sort of, anyway. That's why I need to speak with Lyssieth so badly; I have a lot of questions that I need answered.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Well, after dealing with Lyssieth's daughter for us, you've earned the right to do just that,)] Elizabeth replies, before producing a curious signet ring from one of the pouches hanging at her waist. She then holds this ring out to you, and as you take it, she explains, [elizabeth.speech(Her Highness instructed us to give this as a reward to whoever dealt with her daughter.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've thanked her, Elizabeth suddenly shouts out a sharp order for her troops to stand to one side. As one, they do as commanded, granting you access to the drawbridge that they've been tasked to defend. Turning towards you once more, Elizabeth smiles and says, [elizabeth.speech(You're now free to come and go as you please. That being said, I will have to escort you through the palace. We can't just let people wander around in there unsupervised. I'm sure you understand.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_COMPLETED_QUEST_WITH_COMBAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ok, I can deliver that report now,)] you say to Elizabeth, who nods and produces a small notepad and pen.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(So, how did you do it?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You spend the next fifteen minutes or so explaining your methods, starting at how you got an arcane key from one of the surrounding imp fortress, and finishing with a description of how you bested Lyssieth's daughter in combat. As you recount the battle you had in the stone keep, Elizabeth raises her eyebrows and gazes at you in disbelief. [elizabeth.speech(You actually beat her in a fight?! There's no way... But that would mean you still have the ring I gave you! Show it to me, and prove that you're not lying.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Producing Lyssieth's signet ring, you hand it over to Elizabeth, who stammers and trips over her words as she realises that you were actually telling the truth, [elizabeth.speech(Wow... But Lyssieth herself taught her how to use the arcane... I-I mean, everyone in the palace knows about how she over-estimates her abilities, but she... I mean... Who <i>are</i> you?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(As I told you before, I'm Lilaya's [pc.niece]. Well, sort of, anyway. That's why I need to speak with Lyssieth so badly; I have a lot of questions that I need answered.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Well, as promised, you've earned the right to do just that,)] Elizabeth replies, before handing the ring to one of her subordinates, and then producing an identical ring from her pocket. She then holds out this ring to you, and as you take it, she explains, [elizabeth.speech(Don't worry, this one doesn't carry an enslavement enchantment. Her Highness instructed us to give this to you as a reward if you managed to deal with her daughter.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've thanked her, Elizabeth suddenly shouts out a sharp order for her troops to stand to one side. As one, they do as they're commanded, granting you access to the drawbridge that they've been tasked to defend. Turning towards you once more, Elizabeth smiles and says, [elizabeth.speech(You're now free to come and go as you please. That being said, I will have to escort you through the palace. We can't just let people wander around in there unsupervised, I'm sure you understand.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_COMPLETED_QUEST_WITH_TRICKERY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ok, I can deliver that report now,)] you say to Elizabeth, who nods and produces a small notepad and pen.
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(So, how did you do it?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You spend the next fifteen minutes or so explaining your methods, starting at how you got an arcane key from one of the surrounding imp fortress, and finishing with a description of how you tricked Lyssieth's daughter into wearing the enslavement ring.
		#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_CHUUNI))
		 As you recount the conversation the two of you had in the stone keep, Elizabeth rolls her eyes and starts impatiently tapping her foot on the ground. As your story comes to an end, she sighs, [elizabeth.speech(I can't imagine what it must be like to be in the presence of the two of you at once...)]
		#ELSE
		 As your story comes to an end, Elizabeth raises an eyebrow and says, [elizabeth.speech(I can't believe she actually fell for that...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_CHUUNI))
			Taking that as a compliment, you smirk as you reply, [pc.speech(I suppose that it must be rather hard for you to picture such a cataclysmic encounter between two of the greatest arcane-wielders to ever have lived! But anyway, enough of that! I have a lot of questions that I need Lyssieth to answer. Can I please enter the palace now?)]
		#ELSE
			[pc.speech(It <i>was</i> easier than I expected,)] you reply, [pc.speech(Anyway, as I said before, I have a lot of questions that I need Lyssieth to answer. Can I please enter the palace now?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Well, as promised, you've earned the right to do just that,)] Elizabeth replies, before producing a very familiar-looking signet ring from her pocket. She then holds out this ring to you, and as you take it, she explains, [elizabeth.speech(Don't worry, this one doesn't carry an enslavement enchantment. Her Highness instructed us to give this to you as a reward if you managed to deal with her daughter.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've thanked her, Elizabeth suddenly shouts out a sharp order for her troops to stand to one side. As one, they do as they're commanded, granting you access to the drawbridge that they've been tasked to defend. Turning towards you once more, Elizabeth smiles and says, [elizabeth.speech(You're now free to come and go as you please. That being said, I will have to escort you through the palace. We can't just let people wander around in there unsupervised, I'm sure you understand.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_UNIFORMS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious about the royal guard's uniform and weaponry, you ask Elizabeth, [pc.speech(Why are you all wearing these uniforms? And where did you get those revolvers from? I haven't seen anyone else carrying guns in the city...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The half-succubus lets out a little sigh as you ask your question, before answering, [elizabeth.speech(Well, if you must know, these uniforms and weapons were given to each one of us by Her Highness herself. It is not for us, nor <i>you</i> for that matter, to question her decisions. We proudly wear these uniforms, knowing that it makes Lyssieth happy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With your curiosity now sated, you wonder what you should do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_GATE_SURNAME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Why did you introduce yourself by your first name?)] you ask of Elizabeth. [pc.speech(I would have expected a captain of the royal guard to be addressed by their surname.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Yes, well, ordinarily, that would indeed be the case. As all of us royal guard share the same surname, however, that would get extremely confusing, so we use our first names instead,)] Elizabeth replies, raising her eyebrows a little as she anticipates your follow-up question.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You all share the same surname? So you're all sisters?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(That is correct, we are all Lyssieth's daughters, and so all have the surname of '[elizabeth.surname]',)] Elizabeth replies.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Wait, you're all Lyssieth's daughters?!)] you exclaim. [pc.speech(So Lilaya is your sister as well?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(Well, technically, yes,)] the half-succubus awkwardly replies. [elizabeth.speech(However, none of us are recognised daughters, you see, so we can't really call her that. Lyssieth can't recognise too many of us... Lilin politics, and all that...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having got your answer, you wonder what you should do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The sheer obsidian walls of Lyssieth's palace drop away into the inky blankness of the ravine below you, and with the sole exception of the massive wooden gates before you, there's not a single weak point to be seen in the entire face of the carved structure. The few windows that break up the smooth, glass-like surface take the form of narrow arrow-slits, and all but the very smallest of these are covered with what look to be iron bars.
	</p>
	<p>
		A pair of masterfully-carved stone gargoyles, each one standing at well over [units.size(250)] in height, snarl down at anyone crossing the drawbridge. Every time you glance up at one of them, they seem to be wearing a slightly different expression, but whether this is some arcane-enchantment, or just your imagination, you can't tell. As you've come to expect from this world, the two sculptures are completely naked, and while each of the masculine figures are sporting balls large enough to put a horse to shame, it's what their cocks are buried in that catches your attention the most. Appearing to be carved out of the same jet-black obsidian, a rat-girl and succubus are being restrained in full-nelson holds; their legs lifted from the floor as the gargoyles' cocks slam deep into their exposed pussies.
	</p>
	<p>
		Casting your gaze back down from the lewd expressions on each of the girls' faces, you turn your attention to the huge wooden gates before you. Set into the wall of the palace by about two or three feet, the only observable entrance boasts an extra line of defence, in the form of a thick metal portcullis. Thankfully, this has been raised, allowing Elizabeth to freely approach the doors before you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_ELIZABETH_LEADS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(So, shall we enter?)] the half-succubus asks. [elizabeth.speech(Once inside, I'll escort you directly to see Her Highness.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You could take Elizabeth up on her offer, or turn around and head back out into Submission...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_ELIZABETH_LEADS_COMPANIONS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(So, shall we enter?)] the half-succubus asks, before glancing over at [npc.name]. [elizabeth.speech(I'm afraid that for security reasons, we can't allow your companion here to come with you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You could enter Lyssieth's palace now, or turn around and head back out into Submission. If you choose to enter, [npc.name] will be sent home...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILIN_PALACE_ELIZABETH_ESCORT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[elizabeth.speech(As Her Highness has given you permission to come and go as you please, I will unlock the doors for you, should you wish to enter,)] Elizabeth states.
	</p>
	<p>
		You could take Elizabeth up on her offer, or turn around and head back out into Submission...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_FORTRESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you turn a corner in the tunnel that you're travelling down, you find yourself stepping out into a huge, underground cave. Several holes in the high roof, which you see are covered in iron bars, let a generous amount of light into the cavern.
	</p>
	<p>
		In the very centre of the cavern's huge floor, a considerable amount of earth and rock has been dug out and piled up to form a large mound. On the top of this hill, a crude fence, made out of all sorts of old planks and bits of rubbish, has been erected. Within this circular enclosure, a squat wooden keep has been constructed - looking every bit as crude as its protective fence.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_FORTRESS_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Glancing over at the rudimentary gate that's set in to one side of the wall, you see two alpha-imps standing guard. They seem more interested in talking to one another rather than keeping a close watch, and so haven't spotted you yet. If you were feeling brave enough to try and gain entry to this imp stronghold, you could approach them and see if you can either talk or fight your way through
		#IF(pc.isPartyAbleToFly())
			. Then again, you could simply just fly over the stronghold's outer fence...
		#ELSE
			...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_FORTRESS_ENTRY_PACIFIED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Glancing over at the rudimentary gate that's set in to one side of the wall, you see two alpha-imps standing guard. They seem more interested in talking to one another rather than keeping a close watch, and so haven't spotted you yet. As you're on friendly terms with the leader of this imp fortress, you're able to pass the guards and enter the fortress without any risk of a fight.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_FORTRESS_ENTRY_DEFEATED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Glancing over at the rudimentary gate that's set in to one side of the wall, you see that it's been left wide open, and there's no sign of life within the courtyard beyond. The imps that once ruled over the surrounding tunnels are obviously still too frightened to return, but you can be sure that's it's just a matter of time before they gather their courage and lay claim to this fortress once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_FORTRESS_FLY_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking a short run-up, you launch into the air, and, after quickly gaining some height, fly over the fortress's outer wall and swoop down into the courtyard beyond.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_FORTRESS_ALPHA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From the very top of this makeshift fortress flies a black flag, bearing a white icon of a clenched fist in the very middle of it.
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_FORTRESS_FEMALES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From the very top of this makeshift fortress flies a white flag, bearing an icon of a pair of round, pink breasts.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_FORTRESS_MALES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From the very top of this makeshift fortress flies a white flag, bearing a red symbol of what looks to be a sheathed katana.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_CITADEL_BASE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		For some time, you've been feeling that the tunnels in this part of Submission have been sloping down towards something, and as the passage suddenly opens up in front of you, you discover that this 'something' is a huge, dark cavern. Unlike the rest of Submission, there are no iron grates set into the ceiling, so, due to the absence of light from sun or moon, numerous arcane-powered lanterns have been hung from long chains fixed to the high ceiling, which cast a dim golden glow over the huge subterranean space before you.
	</p>
	<p>
		The most remarkable feature of this area, and the one that instantly catches your eye, is that a huge stone citadel, reaching from floor to ceiling, has been built up against the far wall. Although there are slender arrow-slits set into the walls of the adjoining towers, they all appear to be firmly shuttered and bolted from within.
	</p>
	<p>
		A worn path leads up to the entrance, and, walking down it, you discover that the citadel's gates are carved from dark black stone. Three small keyholes have been drilled into the very middle of them, and, looking up, you see that there's an inscription on the stonework above, which reads:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center'><i>
		In this mighty citadel, resides the Dark Siren; Daughter of Lyssieth, Empress of the arcane, Bearer of cataclysmic terror, She who rends worlds; Those who seek her favour must first prove themselves, and with three keys, then enter.
	</i></p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_CITADEL_DEFEATED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again, you find yourself stepping forwards into the huge underground cavern that houses the ruins of [siren.namePos] citadel. Despite the fact that the one-time residence of the 'Dark Siren' is now destroyed and abandoned, the numerous arcane-powered lanterns hanging from the cave's high ceiling are still active, and they cast a dim golden glow over the huge subterranean space before you.  
	</p>
	<p>
		Walking over to where the citadel's ruins now lie, you take note of the fact that over half of the outer wall has crumbled into an impassable pile of loose rocks and shattered masonry. Thankfully, the citadel's main gates seem to have avoided taking significant damage, and have been left wide open. The surrounding structure hasn't been so lucky, however, and a significant amount of the inscribed stonework above the gates has been smashed to pieces, so that it now reads:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center'><i>
		In ... citadel, ... Dark Siren; Daughter ... Lyssieth, Empress ... cataclysmic terror, She who ... favour ... first ... three keys, ... enter.
	</i></p>
	<p>
		The ruins look dangerously unstable, which is obviously the reason why no imps have chosen to return to this place. If you were careful, however, you think that you could pass through the gates and explore the ruins without risking injury.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_CITADEL_NO_KEYS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From a brief inspection of the citadel's walls, you can see no other way to gain entry. Without these 'three keys' that the inscription refers to, it doesn't look like you're going to be able to get inside...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_CITADEL_KEYS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From a brief inspection of the citadel's walls, you can see no other way to gain entry. However, as you have the 'three keys' that the inscription refers to, it looks like opening the gates won't be a problem...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_CITADEL_KEY_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You decide that the time has come to use the three keys required to open the gates to the dark siren's citadel. As you insert the first of them into its corresponding hole, it suddenly disappears from sight in a bright purple flash. Around the keyhole, a glowing pentagram appears, and, encouraged that this is the right thing to do, you quickly insert the other two keys into their respective locks, each of which produces much the same effect.
	</p>
	<p>
		As the third key vanishes, a vertical purple line splits the stone gates down the very middle, and, with a loud grinding noise, they slowly start to swing open before you. At that moment, yet another bright purple flash is emitted by each of the three keyholes, causing you to blink and turn your head to one side. As you rub your [pc.eyes] to clear the lingering afterimage, you see that the three keys have reappeared in the keyholes before you, and have been linked by a thin silver chain. Grabbing this key-chain necklace from out of the gates, you wait as they fully swing open before you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping forwards into the citadel, you find yourself looking out across the inner courtyard, and you see that the material used in the construction of the outer walls and gateway has been obtained by mining out a large portion of the far wall. Carved into this recess, there's a huge stone archway, which houses a pair of massive, iron-reinforced wooden doors. Off to your left, you see a well in one corner of the courtyard, and beside that, there sits a squat, stone tower. On the opposite side of the courtyard to this tower, the cave's wall curves inwards, and into this, a small doorway has been carved.
	</p>
	<p>
		The most alarming thing about the scene before you is that there are at least twenty imps and alpha-imps scattered around the courtyard. A few of them are simply loitering about, but most are engaged in simple tasks such as cleaning and mending clothes, sparring with one another, or preparing and eating food. You also notice that there are a few who are openly having sex over in one corner.
	</p>
	<p>
		None of these imps seem bothered about your sudden arrival, and you assume that it's because only expected guests would be in possession of the three keys required to gain entry. As you move forwards into the courtyard, the nearest of the imp guards calls out, [genericMale.speech(The siren's in 'er throne room, if yer were lookin' fer 'er!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_CITADEL_KEY_ENTRY_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again, you find yourself wanting to enter the dark siren's citadel. Unlike the first time, when you insert each of the three keys into their respective holes, they produce a glowing pentagram around their locks without first disappearing.
	</p>
	<p>
		As the third key is inserted, a vertical purple line splits the stone gates down the very middle, and, with a loud grinding noise, they slowly start to swing open before you. Grabbing your key-chain necklace from out of the gates, you wait as they fully swing open before you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping forwards into the citadel, you find yourself looking out across the inner courtyard, and you see that the material used in the construction of the outer walls and gateway has been obtained by mining out a large portion of the far wall. Carved into this recess, there's a huge stone archway, which houses a pair of massive, iron-reinforced wooden doors. Off to your left, you see a well in one corner of the courtyard, and beside that, there sits a squat, stone tower. On the opposite side of the courtyard to this tower, the cave's wall curves inwards, and into this, a small doorway has been carved.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_CITADEL_KEY_ENTRY_REPEAT_IMPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Just as before, there are at least twenty imps and alpha-imps scattered around the courtyard. A few of them are simply loitering about, but most are engaged in simple tasks such as cleaning and mending clothes, sparring with one another, or preparing and eating food. You also notice that there are a few who are openly having sex over in one corner.
	</p>
	<p>
		None of these imps seem bothered about your sudden arrival, and you assume that it's because only expected guests would be in possession of the three keys required to gain entry. As you move forwards into the courtyard, the nearest of the imp guards calls out, [genericMale.speech(The siren's in 'er throne room, if yer were lookin' fer 'er!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_CITADEL_KEY_ENTRY_REPEAT_NO_IMPS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You're surprised to see that none of the imps have returned, and that the courtyard before you is completely deserted. Although there's no sign of anyone being inside the laboratory tower or cell block, you can see slivers of light shining out from the cracks around the keep's huge wooden doors, letting you know that the siren is still at home...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="IMP_CITADEL_RUINS_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although the dark siren's citadel now lies in ruin, you find yourself wanting to head back inside and explore. You don't need to use your key-chain necklace to gain entry, as the stone gates have been permanently jammed open. Taking care as you step around the piles of smashed rock piled up against the gates, you walk forwards through the entranceway.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking over the cracked, rubble-strewn courtyard, you find yourself gazing at the huge, ruined archway of the main keep. One of the huge wooden doors has completely splintered into pieces, while the other looks to be straining under the weight of the crumbling masonry above. Off to your left, the citadel's well looks to have been completely crushed beneath the collapsed left-side wall of the laboratory tower. On the opposite side of the courtyard, you see rubble and smashed rock blocking the small doorway of the cell block.
	</p>
	<p>
		All in all, the citadel looks to be in a dangerously unstable condition, which would explain why there's absolutely no sign of life anywhere before you. Exploring these ruins will be slow going, as you need to carefully navigate around gaping fissures and piles of precariously stacked rocks.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
</dialogue>
