<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BEE_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Bee-morphs are commonly found in the grasslands and forests that make up the Foloi region, although the odd individual may sometimes wander through the streets of Dominion. Antenae, translucent wings, and their distinctive stinger is usually enough to identify a person as a bee-morph.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<htmlContent tag="BEE_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldBee(Bees)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Bee-morphs are inhabitants of the forests of Foloi. While it's not unheard of to see one living alone, they for the most part tend to stick to their hives. Occasionally swarms may venture beyond their usual homes to gather resources or sell produce.
	</p>
	<p>
		Bees living in a hive are part of a matriarchal society under the rule of the queen. Besides the queen and other royals, there are the drones and, below them, the workers. The main duties of the drones are to breed and serve the queen and bear her eggs as she sees fit. As a result, they rarely leave the hive. The stronger, larger workers, on the other hand, are tasked with gathering resources, transporting honey, and protecting the hive.
	</p>
	<p>
		It is a common misconception that all drones are male. In reality, having a penis is the only requirement. Because of this, hermaphroditic drones are not unheard of in hives, including a few favoured former workers.
	</p>
	<p>
		Like most morphs, arcane storms induce a breeding frenzy in bees, and they, will aggressively seek out a partner. Since most hives are scattered and a decent distance from the storms' epicentre in Dominion, one rarely has to worry about falling victim to a swarm's lust.
	</p>
	<p>
		Like most morphs, a bee's offspring will be a mix of bees and the partner's race. However, due to the near infertility among most female bees, hives are largely dependent on royals to populate the hive.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldBee(Royal Bees)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At the top of the bee hierarchy stands the Queen and the royals. Despite the name, royals are not born with the title. Rather, normal bee-morphs are elevated to the role through arcane transformation. Most do not stray far from the hives in the Foloi woodlands.
	</p>
	<p>
		Queens and royals often tower over other bee-morphs, though their build varies depending on their lifestyle and former role. Royals have significantly more freedom than others in the hive. They can choose to assist their family in anyway they can or to simply live off the hive's work in luxury. Though they always had the option to leave regardless of class, female royals could now set out to make their own hives.
	</p>
	<p>
		Though not as strong as demons or even half-demons, royal bee-morphs possess an innate grasp on the arcane. As such, royal bees are able to resist the influence of arcane storms
	</p>
	<p>
		A royal bee's offspring will be a mix of normal bee-morphs and the partner's race.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</bookText>
