<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONKEY_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Monkey-morphs tend to stay anywhere there is lush vegetation and towering trees, and will mainly be found in the jungle, woodland, and forest, though some subspecies make their homes in the mountains or may be found in the savannah in the south of Lilith's Realm. While uncommon, some tend to find their way to Dominion, often becoming lost and finding their way to areas of interest such as gambling dens and nightclubs. Rounded, furry ears, large round eyes, lithe muscular bodies, and long prehensile tails distinguish most monkey-morphs from other morphs.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="MONKEY_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While the individual personalities of monkey-morphs vary greatly from one individual to another, monkey-morphs in general have a well-earned reputation for being overly curious bordering on endless naivety; and a passion for causing mischief only outweighed by a powerfully uncontrolled libido. In the wild, monkey-morphs live in troops, fornicating in the trees above visitors and gleefully sending their spunk down atop the heads of errant travelers. In the resulting chaos, others of their troop often times steal from the target while they are distracted. The few known subspecies of monkey-morphs who thrive both in the mountains and savannah tend to maintain the same general personality traits as their tree loving cousins.
	</p>
	<p>
		Monkey-morphs are split into a few distinct subspecies, the most common of which tends to have short, coarse solid or ombre-coloured fur and powerful prehensile tails; these tend to be seen all throughout the jungles and woodlands. Other subspecies whom live in the savannah regions are known for their more dog-like muzzles, time spent on the ground, and non-prehensile tails. Another subspecies has adapted to the cold of the mountains, with softer, usually golden fur. Legends tell of an even more rare subspecies with large wings; these stories have yet to be proven true. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Like most other races, monkey-morphs are greatly affected by arcane storms. However, due to the fact that many of them live far away from Dominion's epicentre of such storms, they typically only experience mild effects. Monkey-morphs caught near enough to arcane lightning become extremely aggressive while their innate curiosity and mischievousness each become extremely deviant; often they will force themselves upon much larger victims, their uncanny strength and nimble form used to great effect. Many a survivor has told stories of being ravaged by an entire troop of horny monkey-morphs during a storm. More than one has told the same story twice with a smile on their face.
	</p>
	<p>
		A monkey-morph's offspring will be a mixture of monkey-morphs and offspring of their partner's race.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</bookText>
