<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- CAVERN_ATTACK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that this is a dangerous area, you make sure to stay alert as you navigate your way through the caves. Thanks to your awareness, you catch sight of a figure sneaking towards you in your peripheral vision. Turning towards them, you see that the figure is [npc.a_fullRace(true)], and, expecting the worst, you jump back into a fighting stance.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Well, well, well!)] [npc.she] states, placing [npc.her] [npc.hands] on [npc.her] [npc.hips+] and striking a confident pose. [npc.speech(What do we have here? Someone who's walking through my territory without my permission?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply to [npc.name], [npc.she] continues, [npc.speech(You can't just be walking around in my territory for free, you understand? Either you hand over some cash, right now, or else I'll make you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
			Your powerful arcane aura is clearly turning [npc.herHim] on, and from [npc.her] hungry gaze that lingers on your body, you're able to get a good idea of what [npc.she] wants to do with you.
			#IF(game.isNonConEnabled())
				 Knowing that defeat will result in being raped by this horny [npc.race], you ready yourself for a fight.
			#ELSE
				 Knowing that defeat will result in this horny [npc.race] wanting to have sex with you, you ready yourself for a fight.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Although your powerful arcane aura is turning [npc.herHim] on a little, it doesn't look as though [npc.sheIs] really all that interested in your body, and will most likely only rob you if you were to lose this fight.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_PAY_OFF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isCowardly())
			Wanting to avoid a fight if at all possible, you take a step backwards, fumbling about to grab a handful of flames to offer to [npc.name]. [pc.speech(I don't want to fight! Please, just take my money and leave me alone!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF(pc.isConfident())
				Not wanting to waste your time dealing with this pathetic [npc.race], you produce a handful of flames, before confidently stepping forwards and holding them out to the mugger. [pc.speech(Count yourself lucky that I've got far more important things to do than waste my time on a miserable wretch like yourself!)]
			#ELSE
				Not wanting to get caught up in a fight with this [npc.race], you decide to take the safer route, and offer [npc.herHim] a handful of your flames. [pc.speech(Here's your money. Now step aside and let me pass.)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Give that to me!)] [npc.name] snaps, [npc.her] desire to rob you of your money obviously the motivating factor behind [npc.her] assault. Before you can reply, [npc.she] quickly steps forwards, before snatching the flames out of your [pc.hand]. With a mocking laugh, [npc.she] stands aside and sneers, [npc.speech(Now get out of my sight!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isBrave())
			With the conflict now resolved, you continue on your way, making sure to keep an eye on [npc.name] in case [npc.she] tries following you. Thankfully for [npc.herHim], it looks like [npc.sheIs] more concerned with counting out [npc.her] ill-gotten gains than attempting to make any sort of threatening move, and you soon turn a corner and leave the [npc.race] behind.
		#ELSEIF(pc.isCowardly())
			With the conflict now resolved, you hurry on your way, hoping that [npc.name] doesn't pursue you and demand more money. Quickly retreating around a corner, you thankfully leave the [npc.race] behind, breathing a sigh of relief as you reflect on the fact that you just came close to having a violent confrontation.
		#ELSE
			With the conflict now resolved, you continue on your way, giving [npc.name] one last backwards glance to make sure [npc.she] isn't going to follow you. Thankfully, it looks like [npc.sheIs] more concerned with counting out [npc.her] ill-gotten gains than attempting to make any sort of threatening move, and after just a moment, you turn a corner and leave the [npc.race] behind.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_OFFER_BODY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight, and unwilling to hand over any of your money, you decide to do the only other thing you can think of, and flash a seductive smile at [npc.name]. [pc.speech(There's no need to fight. If you're looking for a bit of fun, all you have to do is ask...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Oh really?)] [npc.name] replies, stepping forwards in an intimidating manner. You remain in place, biting your [pc.lip] and trying to make yourself as small as possible as you attempt to entice [npc.name] into using you for some sexual relief.
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your delight, your would-be attacker reaches up and grabs you by the [pc.arms], before pulling you forwards into a tight embrace. Pressing [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours, [npc.she] thrusts [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth, aggressively kissing you for a moment before pulling back, growling, [npc.speech(You're going to be a good [pc.girl] now, aren't you bitch?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Whimpering in the affirmative, you surrender yourself to [npc.namePos] dominant touch, allowing yourself to be used as payment for trespassing on [npc.her] territory...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_REPEAT_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that [npc.name(a)] is prowling around this area, you make sure to stay on high alert, carefully checking each and every dark corner and recess as you navigate your way through the caves. Just as you suspected, you suddenly see a figure sneaking towards you in your peripheral vision. Turning towards them, you instantly recognise the [npc.fullRace(true)] from your previous encounter, and you jump back into a fighting stance as you ready yourself for the worst.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_REPEAT_PREGNANCY_REVEAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As [npc.she] stands before you, you notice that there's definitely something different about [npc.herHim] this time. The consequence of ejaculating inside of [npc.herHim] is staring you right in the face, and you gulp as you see [npc.herHim] pointing down at [npc.her] [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)].
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(pc.getId()))
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
				[npc.speech(That's right, you got me knocked up!)] [npc.name] shouts, the excitement in [npc.her] voice clearly giving away the fact that [npc.sheHasFull] a fetish for being pregnant.
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(Just 'cause I love being a mommy, don't think I'm letting you off the hook! I'm so fucking horny all the time, and you're gonna take responsibility for that!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(Just 'cause I love being a mommy, don't think I'm letting you off the hook! I could do with some cash, so just give up and let me rob you already!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE [npc.speech(That's right, you got me pregnant...)] [npc.name] mumbles, before clearing [npc.her] throat and glaring at you.
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(Even though I'm pregnant, I'm still so fucking horny all the time, s-so you're gonna take responsibility for that, understand?!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(You're going to take responsibility for this! I need some cash for food, so just hand it over already!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
				[npc.speech(That's right, [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()] got me knocked up!)] [npc.name] shouts, the excitement in [npc.her] voice clearly giving away the fact that [npc.sheHasFull] a fetish for being pregnant.
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(Just 'cause I love being a mommy, don't think I'm letting you off the hook! I'm so fucking horny all the time, and you're gonna take responsibility for that!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(Just 'cause I love being a mommy, don't think I'm letting you off the hook! I could do with some cash, so just give up and let me rob you already!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(That's right, [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()] got me pregnant...)] [npc.name] mumbles, before clearing [npc.her] throat and glaring at you.
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					[npc.speech(Even though I'm pregnant, I'm still so fucking horny all the time, s-so you're gonna take responsibility for that, understand?!)]
				#ELSE
					[npc.speech(You're going to take responsibility for this! I need some cash for food, so just hand it over already!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_REPEAT_STILL_PREGNANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(npc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(pc.getId()))
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
				You see that [npc.sheIs] still sporting a round, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she] laughs, [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant, all thanks to you!)]
			#ELSE
				You see that [npc.sheIs] still sporting a round, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she] scowls, [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant, and it's all your fault!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
				You see that [npc.sheIs] still sporting a round, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she] laughs, [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant, all thanks to [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()]!)]
			#ELSE
				You see that [npc.sheIs] still sporting a round, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she] scowls, [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant, and it's all your and [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()]'s fault!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_REPEAT_PLAYER_PREGNANCY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(npc.getId()))
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_IMPREGNATION))
				[npc.speech(Well, well, well,)] [npc.name] sneers, looking down at your swollen belly. [npc.speech(Looks like I got you knocked up, slut! Seeing as you've been put in your place, you should just submit for another good fuck!)]
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Wait, I got you pregnant?!)] [npc.name] exclaims, staring down at your swollen belly. [npc.speech(Fuck... Don't think that I'm going to be helping out or anything! I've barely got enough money to buy food for myself!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_IMPREGNATION))
				[npc.speech(Well, well, well,)] [npc.name] sneers, looking down at your swollen belly. [npc.speech(Looks like someone got you knocked up, huh, slut?! Been going around town submitting to anyone who wants to pump a load in you, I'll bet!)]
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Heh, you've got yourself knocked up, huh?)] [npc.name] asks, grinning as [npc.she] looks down at your swollen belly. [npc.speech(Don't think that'll make me go easy on you! I'm still gonna need your cash!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_REPEAT_CONTINUED_PLAYER_PREGNANCY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(npc.getId()))
			[npc.speech(Hah!)] [npc.name] laughs, looking down at your swollen belly. [npc.speech(Looks like you're still carrying my kids around, slut! Seeing as you like being bred so much, you should just submit for another good fuck!)]
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Hah!)] [npc.name] laughs, looking down at your swollen belly. [npc.speech(Looks like you're still knocked up, huh slut?! Seeing as you like being bred so much, you should just submit for a good fuck!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You again?!)] [npc.she] shouts. [npc.speech(This'll be a lot easier if you just give up right now!)] 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_REPEAT_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
			Your powerful arcane aura is clearly turning [npc.herHim] on, and from [npc.her] hungry gaze that lingers on your body, you're able to get a good idea of what [npc.she] wants to do with you.
			#IF(game.isNonConEnabled())
				 Knowing that defeat will result in being raped by this horny [npc.race], you ready yourself for a fight.
			#ELSE
				 Knowing that defeat will result in this horny [npc.race] wanting to have sex with you, you ready yourself for a fight.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Although your powerful arcane aura is turning [npc.herHim] on a little, it doesn't look as though [npc.sheIs] really all that interested in your body, and will most likely only rob you if you were to lose this fight.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_SUBMITTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that [npc.name] calls this particular part of the bat caverns [npc.her] home, you look out for any sign of [npc.herHim] as you proceed through the network of caves. Just as you were expecting, you suddenly catch sight of movement a short way up ahead. Catching sight of you at the same moment, this figure [npc.steps] forwards to block your passage, allowing you to see that it's the [npc.race] you were looking out for.
	</p>
	#IF(npc.isVisiblyPregnant() && npc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(pc.getId()))
		#IF(!npc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
			<p>
				As [npc.she] steps out from the shadows, you notice that there's something different about [npc.herHim] this time. The consequence of cumming inside of [npc.herHim] is staring you right in the face, and you gulp as you see [npc.herHim] pointing down at [npc.her] [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)].
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(npc.isMute())
					Although unable to talk, [npc.name] gives you a smug smirk and a condescending glare which makes it very clear that [npc.she] still sees you as nothing more than [npc.her] submissive bitch.
					#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
						 Casting a hungry gaze up and down over your body, [npc.she] licks [npc.her] [npc.lips] and gestures for you to come closer.
					#ELSE
						 Allowing a smirk to settle on [npc.her] face, [npc.name] strikes an intimidating pose and gestures for you to come closer.
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
						[npc.speech(Yeah, [pc.name], you were the one who did this!)] [npc.name] shouts, the excitement in [npc.her] voice clearly giving away the fact that [npc.sheHasFull] a fetish for being pregnant. [npc.speech(Just because I love being a mommy, don't think that I'm going to start treating you as my equal! Now get over here, [pc.name], I've got plans for you.)]
					#ELSE
						[npc.speech(That's right, you got me pregnant, [pc.name]...)] [npc.name] mumbles, before clearing [npc.her] throat and glaring at you. [npc.speech(Even though you knocked me up, don't think that I'm going to start treating you as my equal! Now get over here, [pc.name], I've got plans for you.)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				As [npc.she] steps out from the shadows, you see that [npc.sheIs] still sporting a round, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she]
				#IF(npc.isMute())
					 gives you a smug smirk and a condescending glare.
					#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
						 Casting a hungry gaze up and down over your body, [npc.she] licks [npc.her] [npc.lips] and gestures for you to come closer.
					#ELSE
						 Allowing a smirk to settle on [npc.her] face, [npc.name] strikes an intimidating pose and gestures for you to come closer.
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
						 laughs,
					#ELSE
						 scowls,
					#ENDIF
					 [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant. Now get over here, [pc.name], I've got plans for you.)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
		<p>
			#IF(npc.isMute())
				Although unable to talk, [npc.name] pointedly looks down at your swollen belly and sneers, before giving you a 
				#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(npc.getId()))
					 triumphant smirk which seems to say 'I did that to you'.
				#ELSE
					 degrading smirk which seems to say 'I'm better than you, slut'.
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(npc))
					#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(npc.getId()))
						[npc.speech(Looks like I got you knocked up, huh, [pc.name]?!)] [npc.name] sneers, looking down at your swollen belly. [npc.speech(Now hurry up and get over here!)]
					#ELSE
						[npc.speech(Looks like someone got you knocked up, huh, [pc.name]?!)] [npc.name] sneers, looking down at your swollen belly. [npc.speech(Been going around town submitting to anyone who wants to pump a load in you, I'll bet! Now hurry up and get over here!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					[npc.speech(Hah! Looks like you're still pregnant, huh, slut?!)] [npc.name] laughs, looking down at your swollen belly. [npc.speech(Now hurry up and get over here!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(!npc.isVisiblyPregnant() && !pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
		<p>
			#IF(npc.isMute())
				Apparently either not willing or not able to talk, [npc.name] flashes you a smug smirk and a condescending glare which makes it very clear that [npc.she] still sees you as nothing more than [npc.her] submissive bitch. Snapping [npc.her] [npc.fingers], [npc.she] points at the floor before [npc.herHim] in a clear command for you to approach.
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Back again, [pc.name]?)] [npc.she] sneers, [npc.speech(I've got plans for you. Get over here like the good, submissive bitch that you are!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(npc.isApplyingPostCombatTransformations())
		<p>
			Hurrying to obey, you swiftly approach [npc.name] and wait to
			#IF(npc.isMute())
				 find out
			#ELSE
				 hear
			#ENDIF
			 what it is that [npc.sheHas] got planned for you.
			#IF(npc.isUsingForcedTransform(pc) && npc.getPostCombatPotion()!=null)
				#IF(npc.isUsingForcedFetish(pc) && npc.getPostCombatFetishPotion()!=null)
					 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] produces a couple of curious little bottles from somewhere out of sight, and shakes them from side to side
					#IF(!npc.isMute())
						 as [npc.she] taunts, [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]! Now open wide, [pc.name]!)]
					#ELSE
						 before your face, allowing you to see that on the side of one of them there's a label which reads '[npc.preferredBody(b)]'. Motioning for you to open wide and prepare to drink the transformative potions, [npc.name] begins to advance upon you.
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] produces a curious little bottle from somewhere out of sight, and shakes it from side to side
					#IF(!npc.isMute())
						 as [npc.she] taunts, [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]! Now open wide, [pc.name]!)]
					#ELSE
						 before your face, allowing you to see that on the side there's a label which reads '[npc.preferredBody(b)]'. Motioning for you to open wide and prepare to drink the transformative potion, [npc.name] begins to advance upon you.
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] produces a curious little bottle from somewhere out of sight, and shakes it from side to side
				#IF(!npc.isMute())
					 as [npc.she] taunts, [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! You're going to end up being my perfect partner; this potion will fix your fetishes and make sure of that! Now open wide, [pc.name]!)]
				#ELSE
					 before your face, allowing you to see that on the side there's a warning label which says something about permanent fetish alterations. Motioning for you to open wide and prepare to drink the transformative potion, [npc.name] begins to advance upon you.
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Flashing you a brief, menacing glare, [npc.name] makes it quite clear that [npc.she] expects instant obedience from you. With only a moment in which to make your decision, you wonder whether to go obey [npc.name] and be transformed to [npc.her] liking or to refuse and prepare to fight for your freedom...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Hurrying to obey, you swiftly approach [npc.name] and wait to
			#IF(npc.isMute())
				 find out
			#ELSE
				 hear
			#ENDIF
			 what it is that [npc.sheHas] got planned for you.
			#IF(npc.isMute())
				#IF(flags.getSavedLong('randomResponseIndex')<=3)
					 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] flashes you a sneer and makes a gesture to signify that you need to pay [npc.herHim]. Impatiently tapping [npc.her] [npc.foot(true)] on the hard ground, she uses [npc.her] [npc.fingers] to imply that you need to pay [npc.herHim] [style.intToString([#flags.getMuggerDemand3()])] flames. As you start to offer a response, [npc.name] smacks [npc.her] fist into [npc.her] other [npc.hand(true)], before making a few hand gesture to imply that if you can't pay, then you're to tag along and help [npc.herHim] mug someone. Pausing to look you up and down as if appraising your body, [npc.she] thinks for a moment before making yet another lengthy series of convoluted and erratic hand-signs, implying that if you don't want to fight, then [npc.she] could always pimp you out and sell your body to a friend of [npc.hers].
				#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('randomResponseIndex')==4)
					 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] suddenly [npc.steps] forwards and dominantly gropes your
					#IF(pc.hasBreasts())
						 [pc.breasts+],
					#ELSE
						 [pc.ass+],
					#ENDIF
					 flashing you a hungry glare as [npc.she] does so.
					#IF(npc.hasStatusEffect(SE_WEATHER_STORM_VULNERABLE))
						 With [npc.name] clearly being uncontrollably turned on by the arcane storm raging overhead, you find yourself just moments away from being fucked by the horny, mute [npc.race].
					#ELSE
						 With [npc.her] intentions clear, you find yourself just moments away from being fucked by the horny, mute [npc.race].
					#ENDIF
				#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('randomResponseIndex')==5)
					 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] gives you wicked smirk, before pointing at the floor and motioning for you to crawl after [npc.herHim]. As you start to ask where it is that you'll be going with [npc.herHim], [npc.name] lets out an angry tutting noise, before using hand signals to imply that [npc.sheIs] going to find somewhere to get some food, and that you're to embarrass yourself by crawling along beside [npc.herHim] like a dumb bitch.
				#ELSE
					 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] flashes you an evil smirk and motions for you to follow [npc.herHim]. As you start to ask what it is that you'll be doing with [npc.herHim], [npc.name] lets out an angry huff, and through a lengthy series of convoluted and erratic hand-signs, implies that a friend of [npc.hers] is going to tattoo you to mark you as [npc.her] bitch, after which this friend is to fuck you as means of payment.
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(flags.getSavedLong('randomResponseIndex')<=3)
					 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] flashes you a sneer and snaps, [npc.speech(I've run out of cash and owe some people some money, so pay up, [pc.name]. Let's see... I think [style.intToString([#flags.getMuggerDemand3()])] flames ought to do it. If you can't pay, then you'll help me earn some cash another way. You can either tag along and help me mug someone, or I can pimp you out to a friend of mine. So, what'll it be, [pc.name]? You going to pay, fight, or fuck to get me my money?)]
				#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('randomResponseIndex')==4)
					 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] suddenly [npc.steps] forwards and dominantly gropes your
					#IF(pc.hasBreasts())
						 [pc.breasts+],
					#ELSE
						 [pc.ass+],
					#ENDIF
					 sneering as [npc.she] does so,
					#IF(npc.hasStatusEffect(SE_WEATHER_STORM_VULNERABLE))
						 [npc.speech(This damn arcane storm's got me so turned on I can't think straight! All I need right now is to give you a good, hard fuck, [pc.name]!)]
					#ELSE
						 [npc.speech(I'm feeling pretty horny at the moment, [pc.name]. I think I'll give you a good fuck.)]
					#ENDIF
				#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('randomResponseIndex')==5)
					 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] gives you wicked smirk, before pointing at the floor and sneering, [npc.speech(Get down, [pc.name]. I was just about to go and get some food, and it'd be fun to have you crawling along beside me like the dumb bitch you are.)]
				#ELSE
					 As you come to a halt in front of [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] flashes you an evil smirk and reveals, [npc.speech(I've made arrangements with an old friend of mine. They're going to tattoo you to mark you as my bitch, and as payment I said I'd let them screw you once the job's done. So come on, [pc.name], let's go get you inked and fucked.)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Flashing you a brief, menacing glare, [npc.name] makes it quite clear that [npc.she] expects instant obedience from you. With only a moment in which to make your decision, you wonder whether to go along with what [npc.she] orders or to refuse and prepare to fight for your freedom...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_DEMAND_SUBMIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that [npc.name] calls this particular part of the bat caverns [npc.her] home, you look out for any sign of [npc.herHim] as you proceed through the network of caves. Just as you were expecting, you suddenly catch sight of movement a short way up ahead. Catching sight of you at the same moment, this figure [npc.steps] forwards to block your passage, allowing you to see that it's the [npc.race] you were looking out for.
	</p>
	#IF(npc.isVisiblyPregnant() && npc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(pc.getId()))
		#IF(!npc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
			<p>
				As [npc.she] steps out from the shadows, you notice that there's something different about [npc.herHim] this time. The consequence of cumming inside of [npc.herHim] is staring you right in the face, and you gulp as you see [npc.herHim] pointing down at [npc.her] [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)].
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(npc.isMute())
					Although unable to talk, [npc.name] gives you a menacing glare which makes it very clear that [npc.her] pregnancy isn't going to stop [npc.herHim] from carrying out [npc.her] criminal activities. Unlike your previous encounters with [npc.herHim], [npc.name] doesn't seem interested in your money, and instead strikes an intimidating pose and prepares to demand something else.
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
						[npc.speech(Yeah, you were the one who did this!)] [npc.name] shouts, the excitement in [npc.her] voice clearly giving away the fact that [npc.sheHasFull] a fetish for being pregnant. [npc.speech(Just because I love being a mommy, don't think I'm letting you off the hook! I've got something special in mind for you!)]
					#ELSE
						[npc.speech(That's right, you got me pregnant...)] [npc.name] mumbles, before clearing [npc.her] throat and glaring at you. [npc.speech(I'm not letting my pregnancy get in the way! I've got something special in mind for you!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				You see that [npc.sheIs] still sporting a round, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she]
				#IF(npc.isMute())
					 gives you a menacing glare. Unlike your previous encounters with [npc.herHim], [npc.name] doesn't seem interested in your money, and instead strikes an intimidating pose and prepares to demand something else.
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
						 laughs,
					#ELSE
						 scowls,
					#ENDIF
					 [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant, but I'm not letting it get in the way! I've got something special in mind for you!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
			#IF(npc.isMute())
				Although unable to talk, [npc.name] pointedly looks down at your swollen belly and sneers, before giving you a 
			#ELSE
				Looking down at your swollen belly, [npc.name] sneers and gives you a
			#ENDIF
			#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(npc.getId()))
				 triumphant smirk which seems to say 'I did that to you'.
			#ELSE
				 degrading smirk which seems to say 'I'm better than you, slut'.
			#ENDIF
			 With that, [npc.she] [npc.steps] forwards in a threatening manner, before
		#ELSE
			With a wicked glint in [npc.her] [npc.eyeColour] [npc.eyes], [npc.name] [npc.steps] forwards in a threatening manner, before
		#ENDIF
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			#IF(game.isFootContentEnabled() && npc.getFetishDesire(FETISH_FOOT_GIVING).isPositive() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
				 gesturing for you to drop down before [npc.herHim] and kiss [npc.her] [npc.feet]. Having already willingly given up to [npc.herHim] three times in a row, it seems like [npc.name] wants you to fully capitulate to [npc.herHim] and become [npc.her] bitch in the most humiliating manner [npc.she] can think of.
			#ELSEIF(npc.getFetishDesire(FETISH_SADIST).isPositive())
				 gesturing for you to drop down before [npc.herHim] and present your ass so that [npc.she] can give you a spanking. Having already willingly given up to [npc.herHim] three times in a row, it seems like [npc.name] wants you to fully capitulate to [npc.herHim] and become [npc.her] bitch in the most humiliating manner [npc.she] can think of.
			#ELSE
				 gesturing for you to bow down before [npc.herHim] and submit. Having already willingly given up to [npc.herHim] three times in a row, it seems like [npc.name] wants you to fully capitulate to [npc.herHim] and become [npc.her] bitch.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.isFootContentEnabled() && npc.getFetishDesire(FETISH_FOOT_GIVING).isPositive() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
				 declaring, [npc.speech(You've shown yourself to be a submissive bitch, so I thought it's time to make it official. Bow down before me and kiss my feet like the subservient slut you are, and I'll make you my personal bitch!)]
			#ELSEIF(npc.getFetishDesire(FETISH_SADIST).isPositive())
				 declaring, [npc.speech(You've shown yourself to be a submissive bitch, so I thought it's time to make it official. Bow down before me and present me with your ass, and I'll spank you into becoming my personal bitch!)]
			#ELSE
				 declaring, [npc.speech(You've shown yourself to be a submissive bitch, so I thought it's time to make it official. Bow down before me and show me what a subservient slut you are, and I'll make you my personal bitch!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
			With that, [npc.name] flashes you a triumphant smirk, and once again you see that there's a wicked, hungry gleam in [npc.her] [npc.eyes+]. Your powerful arcane aura is clearly turning [npc.herHim] on, and you realise that if you were to submit and accept becoming [npc.her] bitch,
			#IF(game.isNonConEnabled())
				 this horny [npc.race] would surely choose to force [npc.herself] upon you.
			#ELSE
				 this horny [npc.race] would surely want to have sex with you.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			With that, [npc.name] flashes you a triumphant smirk, and once again you see that there's a wicked gleam in [npc.her] [npc.eyes+]. Although your powerful arcane aura is quite clearly turning [npc.herHim] on a little, it doesn't look as though [npc.sheIs] really all that interested in your body, and will most likely use you in other ways if you were to accept becoming [npc.her] bitch.
		#ENDIF
		 With just moments to spare before [npc.sheIs] upon you, the choice of whether to defend yourself or completely surrender to this [npc.race] must be quickly made...
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsSex(If you accept becoming [npc.namePos] bitch, you will be expected to obey [npc.her] commands and be given random orders each time you encounter [npc.herHim].)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_PEACEFUL_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that [npc.name(a)] is prowling around this area, you make sure to stay on high alert, carefully checking each and every dark corner and recess as you walk through the twisting passages. Just as you suspected, as you cautiously pass an inset doorway, a shadowy figure leaps out, blocking your path!
	</p>
	<p>
		You instantly recognise the [npc.fullRace(true)], and as [npc.she] sees that it's you, [npc.she] quickly takes a step back, before apologising, [npc.speech(Oh, sorry, [pc.name]. I thought you were someone else...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_PEACEFUL_PREGNANCY_REVEAL"><![CDATA[
	#IF(npc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(pc.getId()))
		<p>
			As you step forwards and start to say hello, you immediately notice that there's something very different about [npc.name]. [npc.SheIs] cradling [npc.her] stomach with both [npc.hands], and as you look down, you see the consequence of ejaculating inside of [npc.herHim], as [npc.sheIs] now sporting a [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)].
		</p>
		#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
			<p>
				[npc.speech(Yeah, before you ask, it was you! You got me knocked up! It feels so fantastic to be pregnant!)] she explains, the excitement in [npc.her] voice clearly giving away the fact that [npc.sheHasFull] a fetish for being pregnant. After confirming that you're the father of [npc.her] children, [npc.she] continues,
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that'd be great too! And, well, if anything, now that I'm pregnant, I'm hornier than ever, so if you've got a thing for pregnant [npc.girls], then just say the word...)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that'd be great too!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[npc.speech(Yeah, before you ask, it was you. You got me knocked up...)] [npc.she] explains, shuffling [npc.her] feet as [npc.she] confirms that you're the father of [npc.her] children. 
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that'd be great too! And, well, even though I'm pregnant, I'm still getting really horny, so if you've got a thing for pregnant [npc.girls], then just say the word...)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that'd be great too!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As you step forwards and start to say hello, you immediately notice that there's something very different about [npc.name]. [npc.SheIs] cradling [npc.her] stomach with both [npc.hands], and as you look down, you see the consequence of [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()] having ejaculated inside of [npc.herHim], as [npc.sheIs] now sporting a [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)].
		</p>
		#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
			<p>
				[npc.speech(Yeah, before you ask, it was [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()]! They got me knocked up! It feels so fantastic to be pregnant!)] she explains, the excitement in [npc.her] voice clearly giving away the fact that [npc.sheHasFull] a fetish for being pregnant. After confirming that your old companion is the father of [npc.her] children, [npc.she] continues,
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that'd be great too! And, well, if anything, now that I'm pregnant, I'm hornier than ever, so if you've got a thing for pregnant [npc.girls], then just say the word...)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that'd be great too!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[npc.speech(Yeah, before you ask, it was [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()]. They got me knocked up...)] [npc.she] explains, shuffling [npc.her] feet as [npc.she] confirms that your old companion is the father of [npc.her] children. 
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that'd be great too! And, well, even though I'm pregnant, I'm still getting really horny, so if you've got a thing for pregnant [npc.girls], then just say the word...)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that'd be great too!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_PEACEFUL_STILL_PREGNANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(npc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(pc.getId()))
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
				As you step forwards and start to say hello, you see that [npc.name] still sporting a round, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she] laughs,
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant, all thanks to you! If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that would be great too! And, well, if anything, now that I'm pregnant, I'm hornier than ever, so if you've got a thing for pregnant [npc.girls], then just say the word...)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant, all thanks to you! If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that would be great too!)])
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				As you step forwards and start to say hello, you see that [npc.name] still sporting a round, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she] sighs,
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant... If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that would be great too! And, well, even though I'm pregnant, I'm still getting really horny, so if you've got a thing for pregnant [npc.girls], then just say the word...)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant... If you wanted to take responsibility, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that would be great too!)])
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY))
				As you step forwards and start to say hello, you see that [npc.name] still sporting a round, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she] laughs,
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant, all thanks to [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()]! If you wanted to take responsibility for what they've done, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that would be great too! And, well, if anything, now that I'm pregnant, I'm hornier than ever, so if you've got a thing for pregnant [npc.girls], then just say the word...)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant, all thanks to [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()]! If you wanted to take responsibility for what they've done, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that would be great too!)])
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				As you step forwards and start to say hello, you see that [npc.name] still sporting a round, [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she] sighs,
				#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
					 [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant with [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()]'s children... If you wanted to take responsibility for what they've done, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that would be great too! And, well, even though I'm pregnant, I'm still getting really horny, so if you've got a thing for pregnant [npc.girls], then just say the word...)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(That's right, I'm still pregnant with [#npc.getPregnantLitter().getFatherName()]'s children... If you wanted to take responsibility for what they've done, then some flames would always be appreciated. Then again, if you wanted to spend some time with me, that would be great too!)])
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_PEACEFUL_PLAYER_PREGNANCY"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(npc.getId()))
		<p>
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_IMPREGNATION))
				Smiling fondly at you as you approach, [npc.name] suddenly notices that you're sporting a swollen belly, and [npc.she] gasps in delight as [npc.she] looks down at your pregnant bump. [npc.speech(I got you pregnant?! Fuck, that turns me on so much... I knew I'd get you knocked up when I cummed in your hot little pussy!)]
			#ELSE
				Smiling fondly at you as you approach, [npc.name] suddenly notices that you're sporting a swollen belly, and [npc.she] gasps as [npc.she] looks down at your pregnant bump. [npc.speech(I-I got you pregnant?! I really should have pulled out... I don't have any money to support you or anything, but you'll be ok, right?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			You smile back at [npc.name], before confirming that [npc.sheIs] the one who got you pregnant. Stepping forwards, [npc.name] places one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] on your belly, smiling happily as [npc.she] tells you to take care of your children.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Smiling fondly at you as you approach, [npc.name] suddenly notices that you're sporting a swollen belly, and [npc.she] gasps as [npc.she] looks down at your pregnant bump. [npc.speech(Hey, you're pregnant?! I'm sure you'll make a wonderful mother!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_PEACEFUL_CONTINUED_PLAYER_PREGNANCY"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(npc.getId()))
		<p>
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_IMPREGNATION))
				 [npc.speech(You're still pregnant with our kids, huh?)] [npc.name] observes, flashing you a delighted smile as [npc.she] steps forwards and places a [npc.hand] on your swollen belly. [npc.speech(That's so fucking hot... You make sure to take good care of our kids!)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc.speech(You're still pregnant with our kids, huh?)] [npc.name] observes, flashing you a smile as [npc.she] steps forwards and places a [npc.hand] on your swollen belly. [npc.speech(You make sure to take good care of our kids.)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			You smile back at [npc.name], before reassuring [npc.herHim] that you're taking care to look after the children you're having together.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Smiling fondly at you as you approach, [npc.name] notices that you're still sporting a swollen belly, and [npc.she] smiles as [npc.she] looks down at your pregnant bump. [npc.speech(Still pregnant, I see! Make sure to take care of yourself!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_PEACEFUL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping forwards, you greet [npc.herHim], [pc.speech(Hi, [npc.name]. I hope you've been taking care of yourself, and not causing too much trouble.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_PEACEFUL_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The two of you spend the next couple of minutes talking with one another, but your conversation is nothing more than idle chatter, and you quickly find yourself ready to move on. Then again, you could spend some time talking with [npc.name], in order to get to know [npc.herHim] a little better. You could also offer [npc.herHim] some money to help [npc.herHim] out, or, if you were feeling like this has gone far enough, you could always betray [npc.her] trust and attack [npc.herHim]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_PEACEFUL_SEX_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] is quite clearly attracted to you, and, as you're harbouring similar feelings towards [npc.herHim], you step forwards and take hold of [npc.her] [npc.hips]. [pc.speech(I know what you really want, [npc.name]. There's no use denying it, I've noticed the lust in your [npc.eyes]...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before [npc.she] can respond, you press your [pc.lips] against [npc.hers], before slipping your [pc.hands] around to grab [npc.her] [npc.ass+] and pull [npc.her] in against you. Just as you already knew, [npc.name] is desperate to have sex with you, and happily throws [npc.her] [npc.arms] around you, passionately returning your kiss as [npc.she] fully submits to you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_ATTACK_PEACEFUL_SEX_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] is quite clearly attracted to you, and, as you're harbouring similar feelings towards [npc.herHim], you step forwards and tease, [pc.speech(I know what you really want, [npc.name]. All you have to do is come and take it...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Encouraged by your words, [npc.name] steps up against you, and, placing [npc.her] [npc.hands] on your [pc.hips], presses [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours. As you lean in and return the sudden kiss, you feel [npc.her] grip slipping around to grab your [pc.ass+], and with a firm tug, [npc.name] pulls you in against [npc.herHim]. Happily throwing your [pc.arms] around [npc.herHim], you passionately return [npc.namePos] kiss as you fully submit to [npc.herHim]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CAVERN_PEACEFUL_TALK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_PEACEFUL_TALK"><![CDATA[
	#IF(npc.getAffection(pc)<20)
		<p>
			Deciding to spend some time getting to know [npc.name] a little better, you ask, [pc.speech(How are you doing these days, [npc.name]? Do you have somewhere safe to sleep, and do you get enough to eat?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.Name] casts [npc.her] [npc.eyes] to the floor, shuffling [npc.her] [npc.feet] a little as [npc.she] replies, [npc.speech(Nobody ever asks me stuff like that... I guess I'm ok, I usually get enough money to buy food and stuff. I don't really have any fixed place to sleep though...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Do you have any friends or family that can help you?)] you ask, [npc.namePos] previous answer making you more concerned than ever for [npc.her] well-being.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(No...)] [npc.name] replies, letting out a disheartening sigh, before trying to force [npc.herself] to smile back at you. [npc.speech(You're the only friend I've got. Sure, I used to know some other people, but they've all moved on now... I don't know how they're doing, or even where they went...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You see [npc.namePos] [npc.eyes] starting to tear up a little, but before you can say anything to comfort [npc.herHim], [npc.she] turns around and starts to run off, calling out behind [npc.herHim] in a broken voice, [npc.speech(S-Sorry, [pc.name]! I-I've got to get going! Thank you for talking to me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Not wanting to make [npc.herHim] feel too uncomfortable, you decide against chasing after [npc.herHim], and, letting out a sigh, you move off and continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(npc.getAffection(pc)<30)
		<p>
			Wanting to know if [npc.name] has started to get [npc.her] affairs in order, you smile at [npc.herHim] as you ask, [pc.speech(How are things going, [npc.name]? Are you eating enough?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Well, they could always be going better,)] [npc.name] replies, half-heartedly laughing as [npc.she] does [npc.her] best to make light of [npc.her] dire situation. [npc.speech(I mean, I'm fine, I get enough to eat and stuff, but it's really hard to keep going sometimes, you know?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I'm so sorry to hear that,)] you reply, wondering what you can do to help your friend. [pc.speech(You'll be ok, won't you?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Yeah, yeah, don't worry about me!)] [npc.name] says, putting on a brave face. [npc.speech(Things have been a lot better recently. After all, I've got you to talk to these days! It's been a while since I had a real friend...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Before you can say anything in response to that, [npc.name] smiles and continues, [npc.speech(Anyway! I need to get going, I, erm, earned some flames earlier, and I need to go buy some bread before the shops close. Thanks for talking with me again, [pc.name], it really means a lot to me...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Throwing you a smile, [npc.name] turns and runs off. You call out a farewell to [npc.herHim], and [npc.she] briefly turns and waves goodbye, before disappearing around a corner. Letting out a sigh, you move off and continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(npc.getAffection(pc)<40)
		<p>
			Having got to know [npc.name] fairly well by now, and wanting to spend some time talking with [npc.herHim], you ask, [pc.speech(How are you, [npc.name]? You're still getting enough to eat, right?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Yeah, I'm eating well enough, thanks for asking,)] [npc.she] replies, smiling happily at you. [npc.speech(Things really do seem to be getting better for me recently. I mean, I'm still living rough down here, but now at least I've got a friend...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You can't help but smile as you hear [npc.name] saying that, and reply, [pc.speech(I'm glad to hear that you're doing ok for yourself. I'm happy to call you my friend as well. Just make sure to take care of yourself, ok? I'm always concerned about you, and wondering how you're getting on.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Aww, [pc.name]!)] [npc.name] laughs, playfully pushing you on the shoulder as [npc.she] tries to hide [npc.her] emotions. [npc.speech(You don't need to worry about me, I'm fine! I-I've even saved up a couple hundred flames, and was just about to go buy myself some food.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Before you can offer to go with [npc.herHim], [npc.name] continues, [npc.speech(A-Anyway, you've got things to do, and I'm pretty hungry already, so I'll catch you later, ok? It was really great talking with you again!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.Name] suddenly steps forwards and gives you a hug. Responding to [npc.her] gesture in kind, you throw your [pc.arms] around [npc.herHim] and hold [npc.herHim] close for a moment, before the two of you finally step back from one another.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(See you, [pc.name]!)] [npc.name] shouts, before turning around and running off. Letting out a sigh, you move off and continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(npc.getAffection(pc)<50)
		<p>
			Wanting to find out how your friend has been recently, you ask [npc.herHim], [pc.speech(How are you these days, [npc.name]? Still eating well enough?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.NamePos] [npc.eyes] immediately light up as [npc.she] hears that you're asking about [npc.her] well-being. Eager to spend some time talking with you, [npc.she] happily replies, [npc.speech(Oh, I've been fine, thank you, [pc.name]! I've always got enough to eat these days, and I'm feeling so much happier now that I've finally got a really close friend. M-Meeting you was the best thing that's ever happened to me...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I'm so happy to hear that,)] you reply, stepping forwards and throwing your [pc.arms] around [npc.name]. [pc.speech(I'm so happy that I met you, too. You just keep on making sure to take proper care of yourself, ok?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Y-Yes, [pc.name].)] [npc.she] replies, holding you close as the two of you share a loving hug. After a moment, however, [npc.name] pulls back, and, smiling happily at you, [npc.she] says, [npc.speech(I'm honestly doing so much better than when you first met me. A-And I know I never really said it, but I'm so sorry for attacking you...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I forgive you,)] you reply. [pc.speech(I know that you have no choice, what with your current circumstances. I'm sure things will change for the better soon, though.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(I hope so. I've even been asking around in some places to try and get a proper job, but it's hard when I'm living like this. Oh, speaking of which, I'm meant to go for an interview in fifteen minutes or so! I'd better get going!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After telling [npc.name] to do [npc.her] best, the two of you say goodbye, and you wave at [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] runs off and turns a corner. Letting out a sigh, you move off and continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Curious to find out how [npc.name] is holding up these days, you ask [npc.herHim], [pc.speech(How are you, [npc.name]? I hope you're taking proper care of yourself.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Yes, I'm fine, thank you, [pc.name]!)] [npc.she] happily replies, clearly overjoyed by the fact that you're choosing to spend some time talking with [npc.herHim]. [npc.speech(I've been applying for jobs here and there around the city, but it's harder to actually get one than I expected... I just need to keep trying though, I'm sure my luck will change at some point!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(That's the right attitude,)] you reply. [pc.speech(You can do it, I know you can!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Wanting to reassure [npc.name], you step forwards and give [npc.herHim] a big hug. Happily throwing [npc.her] [npc.arms] around you, [npc.she] returns the gesture, pressing [npc.her] body against yours for a moment, before stepping back and smiling lovingly at you. [npc.speech(Thanks, [pc.name]! I'm so happy to be your friend! You're the one thing in my life that doesn't suck...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Before you can say anything in response, [npc.name] quickly continues, [npc.speech(Oh! I almost forgot! I've got another interview in five minutes! I need to get going!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After telling [npc.name] to do [npc.her] best, the two of you say goodbye, and you wave at [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] runs off and turns a corner. Letting out a sigh, you move off and continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_PEACEFUL_CAN_INVITE_HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsExcellent(You know [npc.name] well enough now to feel comfortable with inviting [npc.herHim] to come and live with you.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_PEACEFUL_CAN_INVITE_HOME_REQUIRES_LILAYA_PERMISSION"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsGood(You know [npc.name] well enough now to feel comfortable with inviting [npc.herHim] to come and live with you. You'd need to get Lilaya's permission first, however...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CAVERN_PEACEFUL_OFFER_MONEY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_PEACEFUL_OFFER_MONEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that [npc.name] could always use some money with which to buy [npc.herself] food and clothing, you step forwards and hold out some flames. [pc.speech(I'm worried that you're not getting enough to eat. Here you go, you should buy yourself something good with this.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(R-Really? That's for me?)] [npc.name] asks, stepping forwards and cautiously taking the flames from you. [npc.speech(I-I don't know what to say. Thank you so, so much, [pc.name]! You have no idea how much this will help!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You're very welcome,)] you reply. [pc.speech(Just promise to take care of yourself, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(I will! Thank you! In fact, I'm going to go buy myself some food right now. Thank you so much!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.name] turns around and rushes off, calling out a farewell as [npc.she] disappears around a corner. Letting out a sigh, you move off and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CAVERN_PEACEFUL_OFFER_ROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_PEACEFUL_OFFER_ROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having spent a good amount of time building up the level of trust between you and [npc.name], you feel as though your relationship is now at the point where it would be acceptable to offer [npc.herHim] your help in escaping [npc.her] life of crime. Smiling fondly at your friend, you ask, [pc.speech([npc.Name], I've been wanting to ask you something for a while now... After seeing how hard is it for you to live like this, I wanted to offer you a room in the place where I live. So, do you want to move in with me?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] doesn't say anything at first, and you wonder if perhaps you've inadvertently said the wrong thing, but just as you're wondering what you should say to fix the situation, you see tears start to stream from [npc.namePos] [npc.eyes], and [npc.she] asks in a stuttering voice, [npc.speech(R-Really? Y-You're not teasing me or anything? Y-You actually... I-I mean, y-you really want me to... Y-You're o-offering me a place t-to live?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, that's right. I live over near Dominion's central plaza, and the house is filled with empty rooms, and I just can't stand seeing you living on the streets anymore. So, would you like to-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can finish your sentence, [npc.name] rushes forwards, throwing [npc.her] [npc.arms] around you and crying into your shoulder as [npc.she] wails, [npc.speech(Yes! Thank you! Thank you so much! I-I don't know what to say! Thank you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You pull [npc.name] into a loving hug, and hold [npc.herHim] close until [npc.she] regains control of [npc.her] emotions. As [npc.her] tears of joy finally fade away, [npc.she] hesitantly steps back, before giving you one of the most heart-warming, genuine smiles that you've ever seen. [npc.speech(Thank you so much, [pc.name]... I'll repay your kindness someday!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling [npc.name] that there's no need for [npc.herHim] to feel indebted to you, you take hold of [npc.her] [npc.hand], before setting off towards Lilaya's mansion. On the way, [npc.name] tells you that [npc.sheHas] never had a real home, and while it clearly wasn't [npc.her] intention, [npc.her] words convince you even more that you've done the right thing in helping [npc.herHim] out like this.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a while, you find yourself outside the mansion that you call home, and as you lead [npc.name] up the front steps, [npc.she] gasps, [npc.speech(You live <i>here</i>? W-Wow...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, it's kind of a long story, but my aunt's the daughter of a Lilin, and while this is her house, she has no interest in anything outside the experiments she performs in her lab, so she lets me use all the rooms as I see fit,)] you explain, reaching up to knock on the front door.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(So you're related to a Lilin?!)] [npc.name] gasps once again. [npc.speech(Are you royalty or something?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Haha, well, not quite,)] you reply, but before you can say anything further, the front door swings open, and you're greeted by the familiar sight of the cat-girl maid, Rose.
	</p>
	<p>
		[rose.speech(Ah, [pc.name], welcome back,)] Rose greets you, curtsying and stepping aside to let you and [npc.name] enter. [rose.speech(I see you have company, would you like me to prepare a room?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(One's already been set aside for [npc.herHim],)] your reply. [pc.speech(I was going to let [npc.name] have the guest room that you prepared for me before, remember?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[rose.speech(Ah, of course,)] Rose replies, shutting the door behind you and [npc.name] as the two of you enter the grand entrance hall. The cat-girl maid then turns to address your friend, [rose.speech(Welcome to the household, [npc.name]. If there's anything you need, please don't hesitate to use the pull-cord in your room to summon me. Now, if the two of you will excuse me, I'll inform Mistress Lilaya of your arrival.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Curtsying once more, Rose turns and hurries off back to the lab. Taking hold of [npc.namePos] [npc.hand], you then set off into the mansion, leading [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] new room...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CAVERN_PEACEFUL_OFFER_ROOM_BACK_HOME -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_PEACEFUL_OFFER_ROOM_BACK_HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After just a minute, you find yourself opening the door to [npc.namePos] new room, and, leading [npc.herHim] inside, you turn towards [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] that this is it, [pc.speech(Well, this is your room, [npc.name]. I hope it's alright. You've got an ensuite bathroom over here, and if you put your dirty clothes in the laundry basket, they'll be cleaned for you for the next day.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.NamePos] slowly steps forwards, looking all around in awe as [npc.she] mutters, [npc.speech(I-Is this really happening? I... I get to live <i>here</i>?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, this is your room now. Is everything ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(It's more than ok... I don't know what to say... This is the best thing that's ever happened to me!)] [npc.name] replies, trying to hold back tears of joy. before you can reply, [npc.she] suddenly rushes forwards and throws [npc.her] [npc.arms] around you. [npc.speech(Thank you so, so much! You've changed my life!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You happily return [npc.namePos] hug for a moment, before [npc.she] pulls back and wipes the tears from [npc.her] [npc.eyes]. [npc.speech(I'll keep on looking for a job, and once I've got one, I'll start paying rent. I'll repay you for all of this, I promise!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling [npc.name] to take it easy, and to spend some time getting used to [npc.her] new room, you step over to the door and prepare to take your leave. Before you depart, however, [npc.name] once again thanks you for your kindness, and tells you that [npc.she] is eternally grateful to you for having saved [npc.herHim] from [npc.her] terrible life.
	</p>
	<p>
		Promising [npc.herHim] that you'll be back later to check up on [npc.herHim], you step out of [npc.namePos] room and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- PEACEFUL_TRANSFORMATIONS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PEACEFUL_TRANSFORMATIONS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to be transformed into whatever form [npc.name] finds most pleasing, you ask [npc.herHim] if [npc.she] has any transformative potions which [npc.she]'d like you to drink.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!npc.isMute())
			[npc.speech(Well, now that you mention it...)] [npc.name] replies, before retrieving a
		#ELSE
			Enthusiastically nodding [npc.her] head, [npc.name] hurries to retrieve a
		#ENDIF
		#IF(npc.isUsingForcedTransform(pc) && npc.getPostCombatPotion()!=null && npc.isUsingForcedFetish(pc) && npc.getPostCombatFetishPotion()!=null)
			 couple of curious little bottles from a nearby hiding place.
		#ELSE
			 curious little bottle from a nearby hiding place.
		#ENDIF
		 Grinning at you, [npc.she]
		#IF(!npc.isMute())
			 reveals, [npc.speech(Normally there'd be no way that someone like me could afford transformation potions, but there's this really kind succubus who sometimes finds me and asks if I've seen any humans wandering about. Even if I say no, she still makes me some customised potions so that I can transform any humans that I see... Anyway, you say you want to be transformed?
			#IF(npc.isApplyingPostCombatTransformations(false, true))
				 Just drink this then, your fetishes will be changed to how I like them...
			#ELSE
				 Just drink this then, and I'll turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]...
			#ENDIF
			)]
		#ELSE
			 can't contain [npc.her] excitement and has to take a moment to write out a message for you, <i>'Normally there'd be no way that someone like me could afford transformation potions, but there's this really kind succubus who sometimes finds me and asks if I've seen any humans wandering about. Even if I say no, she still makes me some customised potions so that I can transform any humans that I see... You say you want to be transformed?
			#IF(npc.isApplyingPostCombatTransformations(false, true))
				 Just drink this then, your fetishes will be changed to how I like them...'
			#ELSE
				 Just drink this then, and I'll turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]...'
			#ENDIF
			</i>
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isUsingForcedTransform(pc) && npc.getPostCombatPotion()!=null && npc.isUsingForcedFetish(pc) && npc.getPostCombatFetishPotion()!=null)
			With that, [npc.name] pulls out the little stopper from the top of each bottle, and as you willingly open your mouth, [npc.she] pushes their necks past your [pc.lips+].
		#ELSE
			With that, [npc.name] pulls out the little stopper from the top of the bottle, and as you willingly open your mouth, [npc.she] pushes its neck past your [pc.lips+].
		#ENDIF
		 As the sickly-sweet fluid pours out into your mouth, you can't help but let out a muffled moan in anticipation of the changes which your body is to be subjected to.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!npc.isMute())
			[npc.speech(That's it, drink it all down...)] [npc.name] eagerly pants. More than happy to do as you're told, you swallow down every last drop of the transformative fluid, after which [npc.name] happily grins and exclaims, [npc.speech(Now for the fun part!)]
		#ELSE
			Panting in eager anticipation of what's to come, [npc.name] watches as you swallow down every last drop of the transformative fluid, after which [npc.she] happily grins and waits for the changes to take place...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- CAVERN_PEACEFUL_ATTACK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CAVERN_PEACEFUL_ATTACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough of this joke of a friendship between you and [npc.name], you step forwards and sneer, [pc.speech(You know, I never really expected much of you, being the worthless trash that you are, yet somehow I'm still disappointed by how pathetic you are.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasFetish(FETISH_SADIST))
			You see tears start to well up in [npc.namePos] [npc.eyes] as you deliver the crushing insult, and, feeling particularly sadistic today, you continue, [pc.speech(Aww, what's the matter? Going to cry? You disgust me. To think that people down here put up with the likes of you skulking around. All you're really good for is being a slave. At least then someone could make use of you as a cock-sleeve.)]
		#ELSE
			You see tears start to well up in [npc.namePos] [npc.eyes] as you deliver the crushing insult, and you continue, [pc.speech(Knock it off. You don't get to play the victim here, having attacked and mugged countless innocent people!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Completely broken from being betrayed by the only friend [npc.she] ever had, [npc.name] lets out a miserable sob, tears running down [npc.her] face as [npc.she] mumbles, [npc.speechNoEffects(I-I can't... W-Why would you say that? J-Just l-leave me alone! I-I don't ever w-want to see you again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I don't think so. I'm not letting you go until I've taught you a lesson!)] you say, grinning at [npc.name] as you prepare to attack [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speechNoEffects(F-Fuck you! I-I'll show you!)] [npc.name] shouts, before preparing to defend [npc.herself]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_SEX_PEACEFUL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_PEACEFUL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Both you and [npc.name] let out a happy sigh as the two of you step back from one another. Looking into your [pc.eyes], the [npc.race] smiles and says, [npc.speech(That was great... Thanks [pc.name], I really needed that.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The two of you set about gathering your things, and, satisfied from your sexual encounter, you prepare to continue on your way. Saying goodbye to [npc.name], and promising to come back and see [npc.herHim] soon, you then set off on your journey...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_PEACEFUL_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Both you and [npc.name] let out a sigh as the two of you step back from one another. Looking into your [pc.eyes], the [npc.race] pouts and says, [npc.speech(That was fun, but you didn't exactly satisfy me... Oh well, it was still nice sharing that time with you, [pc.name].)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The two of you set about gathering your things, and, satisfied from your sexual encounter, you prepare to continue on your way. Saying goodbye to [npc.name], and promising to come back and see [npc.herHim] soon, you then set off on your journey...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_ATTRACTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] collapses to the floor, completely defeated. As [npc.she] gazes up at you, desperately whimpering and biting [npc.her] [npc.lip], you see that [npc.she] still has a hungry, lustful look in [npc.her] [npc.eyes]. In defeat, [npc.namePos] arcane aura is completely overwhelmed by the power of your own, and, unable to control [npc.her] burning desire, [npc.she] reaches down to [npc.her] crotch and starts stroking [npc.herself], making pitiful little whining noises as [npc.she] squirms on the floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(~Aah!~ What are you waiting for?! Please! Come fuck me!)] [npc.she] pleads, bucking [npc.her] [npc.hips+] against [npc.her] [npc.hand] as [npc.she] continues touching [npc.herself].
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder if you should indulge [npc.her] request. After all, [npc.she] <i>was</i> planning on doing the same to you, and [npc.she] quite clearly wants it. Then again, maybe it's best to just turn around and take your leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_BETRAYED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] collapses to the floor, completely defeated. [npc.She] glances up at you for a moment, before casting [npc.her] gaze to the floor, and in that brief moment, you see that all of the hope and energy in [npc.namePos] face has totally vanished. Making a pitiful little whining noise, [npc.she] then bursts into tears, sobbing and wailing for a moment before wiping [npc.her] [npc.eyes] and looking up at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(J-Just take all my money and leave!)] [npc.she] pleads, throwing [npc.her] #IFnpc.isFeminine()#THENpurse#ELSEwallet#ENDIF at your feet. [npc.speech(I thought you were different, but you just wanted to hurt me, like all the others!)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.isNonConEnabled())
		<p>
			You wonder if you should do as [npc.she] says, and leave [npc.herHim] alone. Then again, you <i>could</i> take advantage of [npc.her] weakened, vulnerable body...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsBad(After betraying [npc.namePos] trust in such a brutal manner, you can be sure that this will be the last time you ever see [npc.herHim].)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_NO_ATTRACTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] collapses to the floor, completely defeated. [npc.She] glances up at you for a moment, before casting [npc.her] gaze to the floor, and in that brief moment, you see that there's a desperate look of regret in [npc.her] [npc.eyes]. Making pitiful little whining noises, [npc.she] tries to shuffle away from you, clearly worried about what your intentions are.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(J-Just take my money and leave me alone!)] [npc.she] pleads, throwing [npc.her] #IFnpc.isFeminine()#THENpurse#ELSEwallet#ENDIF at your feet.
	</p>
	#IF(game.isNonConEnabled())
		<p>
			You wonder if you should do as [npc.she] says, and leave [npc.herHim] alone. Then again, you <i>could</i> take advantage of [npc.her] weakened, vulnerable body...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to give [npc.name] what it is [npc.she] so desperately craves, you step up to [npc.herHim], before reaching down to take hold of [npc.her] [npc.arm] and pulling [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] [npc.feet]. The moment [npc.she] finds [npc.herself] standing, [npc.name] leans in against you, [npc.moaning], [npc.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Take me! Take me now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Without any further warning, [npc.she] suddenly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours, and, eager to return [npc.her] display of affection, you pull [npc.herHim] into your embrace, passionately returning [npc.her] kiss.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, you push [npc.name] away a little, grinning as you see [npc.her] lust-filled gaze roam up and down your body. Preparing to make your next move, you take a firm grip on [npc.her] [npc.hips+], before [pc.moaning], [pc.speech(This is going to be good...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to give [npc.name] what it is [npc.she] so desperately craves, you step up to [npc.herHim], before reaching down to take hold of [npc.her] [npc.hand]. WIth a disarming smile, you help to pull [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] [npc.feet], and the moment [npc.she] finds [npc.herself] standing, [npc.name] leans in against you, [npc.moaning], [npc.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Take me! Take me now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Without any further warning, [npc.she] suddenly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours, and, happy to return [npc.her] display of affection, you gently pull [npc.herHim] into your embrace, before starting to return [npc.her] passionate kiss.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, you pull back from [npc.name], grinning as you see [npc.her] lust-filled gaze roam up and down your body. Preparing to make your next move, you place your [pc.hands] [npc.her] [npc.hips+], before softly [pc.moaning], [pc.speech(I'll take good care of you...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_ROUGH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to give [npc.name] what it is [npc.she] so desperately craves, you step up to [npc.herHim], before reaching down to grab hold of [npc.her] [npc.arm] and yank [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] [npc.feet]. The moment [npc.she] finds [npc.herself] standing, [npc.name] leans in against you, [npc.moaning], [npc.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Take me! Take me now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Without any further warning, [npc.she] tries to press [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours, but, seeing it coming, and wanting to leave no doubt in [npc.namePos] mind as to who's in charge, you quickly reach up and grab hold of [npc.her] neck, smirking in response to the sound of [npc.her] startled cry.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Don't you <i>dare</i> try to do anything without my permission, bitch!)] you snarl, using your commanding grip to tilt [npc.namePos] head to one side, before leaning in to give [npc.herHim] a forceful kiss. Roughly thrusting your [pc.tongue+] into [npc.her] mouth, you use your free [pc.hand] to reach around and give [npc.her] [npc.ass+] a dominant squeeze.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, you push [npc.name] away, grinning as you see [npc.her] lust-filled gaze roam up and down your body. Preparing to make your next move, you take a dominant grip on [npc.her] [npc.hips+], before growling, [pc.speech(Good bitch. Now submit to your conqueror!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_SUBMIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You really aren't sure what to do next, and start to feel pretty uncomfortable with the fact that you just beat up this poor [npc.race]. Leaning down, you do the first thing that comes into your mind, and start apologising, [pc.speech(Sorry... I was just trying to defend myself, you know... Erm... Is there anything I can do to make it up to you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		For a moment, a look of confusion crosses over [npc.namePos] face, but, as [npc.she] sees that you're genuinely troubled by what you've just done, an evil grin crosses [npc.her] face. [npc.She] stands up, and, grabbing you by the [pc.arm], roughly pulls you into [npc.her] as [npc.she] growls, [npc.speech(How about you start by apologising properly?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.NamePos] strong, dominant grip on your [pc.arm] causes you to let out a lewd little moan, and your submissive nature takes over as you do as [npc.she] asks. [pc.speech(I'm really sorry! Please forgive me! I'll do anything! Anything you ask! Just please, don't be mad!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] roughly yanks you forwards, and with a menacing growl, [npc.she] forces [npc.her] tongue into your mouth. You let out a muffled yelp as your opponent takes charge, but as you feel [npc.her] [npc.hands] reaching down to start roughly groping your ass, you realise that you couldn't be happier with how things have turned out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_BANISH_NPC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Disgusted by the fact that this [npc.race] is assaulting innocent travellers, you step forwards, and, frowning down at [npc.herHim], you state, [pc.speech(I don't want to ever catch you doing this again. The next time I see you, I'll be with the Enforcers, and you can find out for yourself how they'll deal with you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(W-Wait, I-I just needed the money! Y-You can't do th-)] [npc.name] starts to stammer, brought to [npc.her] senses by the threat of the Enforcers getting involved.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not interested in listening to anything this criminal has to say, you cut [npc.herHim] off, [pc.speech(Be quiet! If you need money, go and get a job! How dare you try to justify your criminal activities! Now get out of here, before I decide to get the Enforcers right now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You see tears welling up in [npc.namePos] [npc.eyes], but, realising that [npc.sheIs] in no position to argue, quietly stands up and runs off, not even casting a backwards glance your way.
	</p>
	<p>
		With the way [npc.she] reacted to the threat of the Enforcers, you can be sure that you won't see [npc.herHim] in this alleyway ever again. Feeling pleased with the way you dealt with that lowlife, you set off and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_RAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Reaching down, you grab [npc.namePos] [npc.arm], and, pulling [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] feet, you start grinding yourself up against [npc.herHim]. Seeing the lustful look in your [pc.eyes], [npc.she] lets out a little [npc.sob], desperately trying to struggle out of your grip as you hold [npc.herHim] firmly in your embrace...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_RAPE_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Reaching down, you take hold of [npc.namePos] [npc.arm], and, pulling [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] feet, you start pressing yourself up against [npc.herHim]. Seeing the lustful look in your [pc.eyes], [npc.she] lets out a little [npc.sob], desperately trying to struggle out of your grip as you hold [npc.herHim] in your embrace...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_RAPE_ROUGH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Reaching down, you grab [npc.namePos] [npc.arm], and, roughly yanking [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] feet, you start forcefully grinding yourself up against [npc.herHim]. Seeing the lustful look in your [pc.eyes], [npc.she] lets out a little [npc.sob], desperately trying to struggle out of your grip as you firmly hold [npc.herHim] in your embrace...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_TALK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you look down at the defeated form of the [npc.race] before you, you can't help but feel sorry for [npc.herHim]. After all, [npc.she] must really have been desperate to have attacked you like this, and is undoubtedly the victim of unfortunate circumstances. Taking a step back to show [npc.herHim] that you're no further threat, you say, [pc.speech(Don't worry, I'm not going to do anything to you. I just want to know why you attacked me like that.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(W-What?)] the [npc.race] stammers, caught off guard by the amicable tone of your voice. [npc.speech(Y-You're not going to punish me?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(No, I just want to find out why you're attempting to mug innocent travellers.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(W-Well...)] the [npc.race] stammers. [npc.speech(I-I don't have a job, or anything, and no way to get food without doing this...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You let out a sigh as you hear [npc.her] reason for attacking you. [pc.speech(So you need to steal in order to survive... What's your name?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The [npc.race] looks a little uncomfortable at answering your question at first, but after simply waiting a moment and giving [npc.herHim] time to think, you're rewarded with an answer, [npc.speech(M-My name's [npc.name]... Why do you want to know?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Well, because if I bump into you down here again, I'd like to greet you properly. My name's [pc.name], I hope I didn't hurt you too much back there,)] you reply, standing back upright as [npc.name] pushes [npc.herself] to [npc.her] [npc.feet].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You're going to come back here? A-After I attacked you like that?)] [npc.name] nervously asks, looking as though [npc.sheIs] on the verge of turning and running away.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sure I will. This is a nice shortcut, and besides, I'd like to get to know you a little more in the future,)] you reply, smiling at [npc.name] to try and reassure [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Y-You want to get to know... m-me?)] [npc.name] asks, not quite believing what it is you've just said.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That's right. Look, I need to be on my way now, and I'm sure you'd like to take a moment to think all of this over, but I'll come and find you here some other time, alright?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(O-Ok... That would be good... I-I'll see you another time... [pc.name]...)] [npc.name] stammers. You see [npc.herHim] starting to blush as [npc.she] says your name, but before you can say anything else, [npc.she] turns around and sprints off, leaving you alone once again.
	</p>
	<p>
		Smiling to yourself as you think that you might have just made a new friend, you set off and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- SURRENDER -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SURRENDER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isCowardly())
			Well and truly terrified at the prospect of this [npc.race] choosing to engage you in physical combat, you drop down before [npc.herHim] and offer [npc.herHim] your complete surrender. Letting out an amused chuckle as [npc.she] sees how scared you are, the [npc.race]
		#ELSEIF(pc.isBrave())
			Although not scared of [npc.race], you find yourself unwilling to engage [npc.herHim] in combat, and so you drop down before [npc.herHim] and offer [npc.herHim] your complete surrender. Letting out an annoyed tut as [npc.she] sees the brave look in your [pc.eyes], the [npc.race]
		#ELSE
			Not wanting to engage this [npc.race] in combat, you drop down before [npc.herHim] and offer [npc.herHim] your complete surrender. Letting out an amused chuckle as [npc.she] sees your complete and utter submission, the [npc.race]
		#ENDIF
		#IF(!npc.isMute())
			 pushes you to the ground, before using [npc.her] bodyweight to hold you down and sneer, [npc.speech(How pathetic!)]
		#ELSE
			 pushes you to the ground, and with a wicked sneer on [npc.her] face, [npc.she] uses [npc.her] bodyweight to hold you down.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(npc.isUsingForcedTransform(pc) && npc.getPostCombatPotion()!=null)
		#IF(npc.isUsingForcedFetish(pc) && npc.getPostCombatFetishPotion()!=null)
			<p>
				As [npc.she] pins you to the floor, [npc.she] produces a couple of curious little bottles from somewhere out of sight, and shakes them from side to side
				#IF(!npc.isMute())
					 as [npc.she] taunts, [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]!)]
				#ELSE
					 before your face, allowing you to see that on the side of one of them there's a label which reads '[npc.preferredBody(b)]'.
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				With that, [npc.name] pulls out the little stopper from the top of each bottle, and as you open your mouth to protest, [npc.she] suddenly shoves their necks past your [pc.lips+]. As the sickly-sweet fluid pours out into your mouth, you let out a muffled whine; the only act of resistance that you're able to summon in your current state.
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(!npc.isMute())
					[npc.speech(Come on! Swallow it all down already!)] [npc.she] growls, throwing
				#ELSE
					Clasping [npc.her] [npc.hand] over your mouth, [npc.she] throws
				#ENDIF
				 the now-empty vessels to one side as [npc.she] tries to force you to swallow the combined fluids...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				As [npc.she] pins you to the floor, [npc.she] produces a curious little bottle from somewhere out of sight, and shakes it from side to side
				#IF(!npc.isMute())
					 as [npc.she] taunts, [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]!)]
				#ELSE
					 before your face, allowing you to see that on the side there's a label which reads '[npc.preferredBody(b)]'.
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				With that, [npc.name] pulls out the little stopper from the top of the bottle, and as you open your mouth to protest, [npc.she] suddenly shoves the neck past your [pc.lips+]. As the sickly-sweet fluid pours out into your mouth, you let out a muffled whine; the only act of resistance that you're able to summon in your current state.
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(!npc.isMute())
					[npc.speech(Come on! Swallow it all down already!)] [npc.she] growls, throwing
				#ELSE
					Clasping [npc.her] [npc.hand] over your mouth, [npc.she] throws
				#ENDIF
				 the now-empty vessel to one side as [npc.she] tries to force you to swallow the strange fluid...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As [npc.she] pins you to the floor, [npc.she] produces a curious little bottle from somewhere out of sight, and shakes it from side to side
			#IF(!npc.isMute())
				 as [npc.she] taunts, [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! You're going to end up being my perfect partner; this potion will fix your fetishes and make sure of that!)]
			#ELSE
				 before your face, allowing you to see that on the side there's a warning label which says something about permanent fetish alterations.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, [npc.name] pulls out the little stopper from the top of the bottle, and as you open your mouth to protest, [npc.she] suddenly shoves the neck past your [pc.lips+]. As the sickly-sweet fluid pours out into your mouth, you let out a muffled whine; the only act of resistance that you're able to summon in your current state.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(!npc.isMute())
				[npc.speech(Come on! Swallow it all down already!)] [npc.she] growls, throwing
			#ELSE
				Clasping [npc.her] [npc.hand] over your mouth, [npc.she] throws
			#ENDIF
			 the now-empty vessel to one side as [npc.she] tries to force you to swallow the strange fluid...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_BETRAYED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't carry on fighting any more, and you feel your [pc.legs] giving out beneath you as you collapse to the ground, defeated. A pitiful whine causes you to look up, and you see tears starting to fill [npc.namePos] [npc.eyes] as [npc.she] looks down at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(W-Why did you do this?!)] [npc.she] asks, not even bothering to wait to hear your answer before continuing, [npc.speech(I thought you were different, but you just wanted to hurt me, like all the others! J-Just give me your money!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling you to your feet, [npc.name] roughly pushes you against a nearby wall, [npc.her] sorrow quickly turning to anger as [npc.she] violently forces you hand over some of your cash. Having taken your money, [npc.she] then roughly pushes you to the floor once more.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(I hate you! <i>I hate you!</i>)] [npc.she] screams, tears running down [npc.her] face once more as [npc.she] fails to control [npc.her] emotions. Before you can say anything in your defence, [npc.she] turns around and sprints off at full speed, leaving you all alone once again...
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsBad(After betraying [npc.namePos] trust in such a brutal manner, you can be sure that you'll never see [npc.herHim] again...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_GENERIC_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You simply don't have the energy to continue fighting any more, and with a defeated sigh, you collapse to the ground. A mocking laugh causes you to wearily look up, and you see [npc.name] triumphantly grinning down at you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Player transformations -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF_AND_FETISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hah! That was too easy!)] [npc.she] says, before leaning down and pushing you to the ground.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.she] pins you to the floor, [npc.she] produces a couple of curious little bottles from somewhere out of sight, and shakes them from side to side, grinning. [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.She] pulls out the little stopper from the top of each bottle, and as you open your mouth to protest, [npc.she] suddenly shoves their necks past your [pc.lips+]. As the sickly-sweet fluid pours out into your mouth, you let out a muffled whine; the only act of resistance that you're able to summon in your current state.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Come on! Swallow it all down already!)] [npc.she] growls, throwing the now-empty vessels to one side as [npc.she] tries to force you to swallow the combined fluids...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hah! That was too easy!)] [npc.she] says, before leaning down and pushing you to the ground.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.she] pins you to the floor, [npc.she] produces a curious little bottle from somewhere out of sight, and shakes it from side to side, grinning. [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.She] pulls out the little stopper from the top of the bottle, and as you open your mouth to protest, [npc.she] suddenly shoves the neck past your [pc.lips+]. As the sickly-sweet fluid pours out into your mouth, you let out a muffled whine; the only act of resistance that you're able to summon in your current state.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Come on! Swallow it all down already!)] [npc.she] growls, throwing the now-empty vessel to one side as [npc.she] tries to force you to swallow the strange fluid...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_FETISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hah! That was too easy!)] [npc.she] says, before leaning down and pushing you to the ground.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.she] pins you to the floor, [npc.she] produces a curious little bottle from somewhere out of sight, and shakes it from side to side, grinning. [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! You're going to end up being my perfect partner; this potion will fix your fetishes and make sure of that!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.She] pulls out the little stopper from the top of the bottle, and as you open your mouth to protest, [npc.she] suddenly shoves the neck past your [pc.lips+]. As the sickly-sweet fluid pours out into your mouth, you let out a muffled whine; the only act of resistance that you're able to summon in your current state.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Come on! Swallow it all down already!)] [npc.she] growls, throwing the now-empty vessel to one side as [npc.she] tries to force you to swallow the strange fluid...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Responses -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TF_SPIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not liking the idea of swallowing down the strange liquid in your mouth, you turn your head to one side and spit it onto the floor. Unsurprisingly, [npc.name] isn't at all pleased by what you've just done, and shouts, [npc.speech(You stupid [pc.bitch]! You'll pay for that!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TF_SWALLOW"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasFetish(FETISH_TRANSFORMATION_RECEIVING) || pc.hasFetish(FETISH_KINK_RECEIVING))
			Loving the sound of being transformed by [npc.name], you obediently swallow down the strange liquid that's in your mouth. Seeing that you've obeyed [npc.herHim], [npc.name] grins and exclaims, [npc.speech(Now for the fun part!)]
		#ELSE
			Thinking that it would be best to do as [npc.name] says, you obediently swallow down the strange liquid that's in your mouth. Seeing that you've obeyed [npc.herHim], [npc.name] grins and exclaims, [npc.speech(Now for the fun part!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_COMBAT_TRANSFORMATION -->
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAPE_PLAYER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(I hope you're looking forward to this as much as I am!)] [npc.name] exclaims, the tone of [npc.her] voice dripping with lust as [npc.she] steps towards you and continues, [npc.speech(And if not, then too bad! I'm going to have my fun fucking you, and that's all that matters!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.name] steps forwards and prepares to move you into position...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You want to have some fun with me now, right?)] [npc.name] asks, the tone of [npc.her] voice dripping with lust as [npc.she] steps towards you and continues, [npc.speech(I mean, I'm not going to force you or anything, but some sex sure would be hot right now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.name] steps forwards and awaits your answer...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NO_SEX_POST_TRANSFORM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Pulling you to your feet, [npc.name] pushes you against a nearby wall, before demanding that you hand over your money. Reluctantly, you do as [npc.she] says, and after giving [npc.herHim] some of your cash, [npc.she] roughly throws you back down to the floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You're not good enough for me to be interested in you just yet!)] [npc.she] growls down at you, [npc.speech(Come back and pay me another visit, <i>or else</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect little [npc.preferredBody(b)]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.she] turns around and runs off, leaving you panting and sweating as you attempt to recover from your alarming experience...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NO_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Pulling you to your feet, [npc.name] pushes you against a nearby wall, before demanding that you hand over your money. Reluctantly, you do as [npc.she] says, and after giving [npc.herHim] some of your cash, [npc.she] roughly throws you back down to the floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Don't even <i>think</i> about reporting this to the Enforcers!)] [npc.she] growls down at you, before turning around and running off.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Responses -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="START_DEFEATED_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(npc.isWillingToRape())
		<p>
			[npc.speech(It's time for a good fuck!)] [npc.name] laughs, grabbing your [pc.arm] and pulling you up against [npc.herHim]. Before you can react, [npc.she] lustfully plants a wet kiss on your [pc.lips], before moving [npc.her] [npc.hands] all over your body and starting to dominantly grope you. 
		</p>
		<p>
			Obviously being very happy with how things have turned out, [npc.name] pulls back and growls, [npc.speech(I hope you're ready for this, you dirty slut!!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I could do with taking a break,)] you say to [npc.name], smiling seductively at [npc.herHim].
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(That's what I like to hear!)] [npc.name] exclaims, before eagerly stepping forwards and dominantly pulling you in against [npc.herHim]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] then lustfully plants a wet kiss on your [pc.lips], before pulling back and happily exclaiming, [npc.speech(Now let's get this started!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="START_DEFEATED_SEX_RESIST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(It's time for a good fuck!)] [npc.name] laughs, grabbing your [pc.arm] and pulling you up against [npc.herHim]. Ignoring your cries and protestations, [npc.she] lustfully plants a wet kiss on your [pc.lips], before moving [npc.her] [npc.hands] all over your body and starting to dominantly grope you. 
	</p>
	<p>
		With your struggles doing nothing to dissuade [npc.name] from [npc.her] chosen course of action, [npc.she] growls, [npc.speech(I hope you're ready for this, you dirty slut!!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DEFEATED_REFUSE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to have sex with [npc.name], and seeing that [npc.she] is clearly unwilling to force [npc.herself] on you, you step back and tell [npc.herHim] in no uncertain terms that you don't want to get intimate with [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Just count yourself lucky that I gave you the choice,)] [npc.name] growls, clearly annoyed by the fact that you're refusing [npc.her] advances. With one last snarl, [npc.she] then turns around and walks off, leaving you to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DEFEATED_NO_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking a moment to recover from your encounter, you stand up and brush yourself down, before setting off on your way once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_SEX_VICTORY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_VICTORY_RAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you step back from [npc.name], [npc.she] sinks to the floor, letting out a thankful sob as [npc.she] realises that you've finished. Obviously quite keen to make [npc.her] exit before you decide to do anything else to [npc.herHim], [npc.she] starts frantically gathering [npc.her] belongings.
	</p>
	<p>
		Getting your own things in order, you [pc.step] forwards and smirk down at the still-sobbing [npc.race], wondering what you should do with [npc.herHim] now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_VICTORY_RAPE_BETRAYED"><![CDATA[
	#IF game.isNonConEnabled()
	#THEN
		<p>
			As you step back from [npc.name], [npc.she] sinks to the floor, letting out a pitiful wail as [npc.she] realises that you've finished. Completely broken by the sudden betrayal and rape, [npc.she] starts uncontrollably sobbing and crying.
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a triumphant laugh, you start gathering your things, but before taking your leave, you wonder if you should help yourself to any of [npc.namePos] belongings...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As you step back from [npc.name], [npc.she] sinks to the floor, letting out a deep sigh as [npc.she] realises that you've finished. Still deeply upset at the way you betrayed [npc.her] trust, [npc.she] quickly starts gathering [npc.her] things, intent on leaving this place for good.
		</p>
		<p>
			Similarly getting your things back in order, you wonder if you should help yourself to any of [npc.namePos] belongings before you move on...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>	
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_VICTORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you step back from [npc.name], [npc.she] sinks to the floor, totally worn out from [npc.her] orgasm. Looking up at you, a satisfied smile settles across [npc.her] face, and you realise that you gave [npc.herHim] exactly what [npc.she] wanted.
	</p>
	<p>
		Getting your things in order, you [pc.step] forwards and smirk down at the panting [npc.race], wondering what you should do with [npc.herHim] now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_VICTORY_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you step back from [npc.name], [npc.she] sinks to the floor, letting out a desperate whine as [npc.she] realises that you've finished.
		#IF(npc.isTaur())
			 Unable to reach back to [npc.her] groin, [npc.she] frantically starts rubbing [npc.her] rear-end up against a nearby smooth protrusion of rock in a desperate attempt to masturbate and finish what you started.
		#ELSEIF(npc.hasLegs())
			 [npc.Her] [npc.hands] dart down between [npc.her] [npc.legs], and [npc.she] frantically starts masturbating as [npc.she] seeks to finish what you started.
		#ELSE
			 [npc.Her] [npc.hands] dart down to [npc.her] groin, and [npc.she] frantically starts masturbating as [npc.she] seeks to finish what you started.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_SEX_DEFEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_DEFEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As [npc.name] steps back and sorts [npc.her] clothes out, you sink to the floor, totally worn out from [npc.her] dominant treatment of you. [npc.She] looks down at you, and you glance up to see a very satisfied smile cross [npc.her] face. [npc.She] leans down and pats you on the head. [npc.speech(We should do this again some time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.she] walks off, leaving you panting on the ground. It takes a little while for you to recover from your ordeal, but eventually you feel strong enough to get your things in order and carry on your way.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Bitch content: -->
	
	<!-- Initial submitting: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTING_FEET"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Submitting to [npc.name], you drop down before [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] that you accept being [npc.her] bitch.
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 With a triumphant smirk on [npc.her] face, [npc.she] points to [npc.her] [npc.feet+] and snaps [npc.her] [npc.fingers], indicating that you're to drop down and kiss them.
		#ELSE
			 Letting out a triumphant laugh, [npc.she] repeats [npc.her] demand and points to the ground, ordering, [npc.speech(Kiss my feet to show me that you mean it!)] 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Accepting your place as [npc.namePos] bitch, you do as [npc.she] commands. Dropping your [pc.mouth] down to 
		#IF(npc.getHighestZLayerCoverableArea(CA_FEET)!=null)
			 [npc.her] [npc.feet], you obediently kiss [npc.her] [#npc.getHighestZLayerCoverableArea(CA_FEET).getName()].
		#ELSE
			 the ground, you obediently kiss [npc.her] [npc.feet+].
		#ENDIF
		 Dominantly pushing [npc.her] [npc.feet] into your, [npc.name]
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 forces you to continue orally servicing [npc.her] [npc.feet+].
		#ELSE
			 lets out a mocking laugh and teases, [npc.speech(You really are a dumb bitch aren't you? Enjoying it, bitch? Go on, kiss them some more!)] 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After making you perform this degrading task for several minutes, [npc.name] finally [npc.steps] back and takes [npc.her] [npc.feet] away from your face.
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 Smirking down at you, [npc.she] makes a gesture to get you to sit still, before placing [npc.her] [npc.hands] on [npc.her] hips and preparing to give you further instructions.
		#ELSE
			 Smirking down at you, [npc.she] orders, [npc.speech(Now sit still and listen. I need to make sure that you know your place.)] 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTING_SPANKING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Submitting to [npc.name], you drop down before [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] that you accept being [npc.her] bitch.
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 With a triumphant smirk on [npc.her] face, [npc.she] points to the ground and snaps [npc.her] [npc.fingers], before making a gesture indicating that you're to present [npc.herHim] with your [pc.ass+].
		#ELSE
			 Letting out a triumphant laugh, [npc.she] repeats [npc.her] demand, ordering, [npc.speech(Present me with your ass, bitch! I want you to remember this!)] 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Obediently shuffling around and presenting [npc.name] with your ass, you raise your hips and prepare to receive your spanking. The [npc.race] doesn't keep you waiting long, as [npc.she] quickly drops down next to you and raises [npc.her] [npc.hand+]. Bringing it down with considerable force, [npc.she] delivers a sharp slap to your rear end, causing you to let out an involuntary cry. Smirking at your response, [npc.name] repeats this movement again and again, slapping, swatting, and spanking your [pc.ass+] over and over.
	</p>
	<p>
		After subjecting you to this physical punishment for several minutes, [npc.name] finally takes [npc.her] [npc.hand] away from your ass, before standing up and [npc.stepping] back.
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 Smirking down at you, [npc.she] makes a gesture to get you to sit still, before placing [npc.her] [npc.hands] on [npc.her] hips and preparing to give you further instructions.
		#ELSE
			 Smirking down at you, [npc.she] orders, [npc.speech(Now sit still and listen. I need to make sure that you know your place.)] 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTING_BOW_DOWN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Submitting to [npc.name], you drop down before [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] that you accept being [npc.her] bitch.
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 With a triumphant smirk on [npc.her] face, [npc.she] points to the ground and snaps [npc.her] [npc.fingers], indicating that you're to bow down before [npc.herHim].
		#ELSE
			 Letting out a triumphant laugh, [npc.she] repeats [npc.her] demand and points to the ground, ordering, [npc.speech(Bow down before me and show me that you mean it!)] 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Accepting your place as [npc.namePos] bitch, you do as [npc.she] commands. Dropping your face towards the ground, you submissively bow down to the [npc.race] and repeat your pledge to become [npc.her] bitch. Dominantly lifting [npc.her] [npc.foot(true)] and pushing down on your back, [npc.name]
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 forces you to completely bow down so that you're pressed down against the floor.
		#ELSE
			 forces you down against the floor as [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(You really are a dumb bitch aren't you? That's right, bow down to me!)] 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After making you remain in this submissive position for several minutes, [npc.name] finally takes [npc.her] [npc.foot(true)] off of you and [npc.steps] back.
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 Smirking down at you, [npc.she] makes a gesture to get you to sit still, before placing [npc.her] [npc.hands] on [npc.her] hips and preparing to give you further instructions.
		#ELSE
			 Smirking down at you, [npc.she] orders, [npc.speech(Now sit still and listen. I need to make sure that you know your place.)] 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			Producing a piece of paper and a pen, the [npc.race] scribbles something down, before pointing to [npc.herself] and showing you what [npc.sheHas] written. Looking at the piece of paper, you see that [npc.sheHas] written [npc.her] name as '[npc.name]', but underneath that [npc.sheHas] scrawled 'You will call me [pc.petName(npc)]'. After you've read this, '[pc.petName(npc)]' quickly writes something else down on the paper, before smirking and showing you that it reads 'Your name is [npc.petName(pc)]. Say it back to me.'.
		#ELSE
			Dominantly looming over you as you remain in your submissive position on the floor, the [npc.race] reveals, [npc.speech(My name's [npc.name], but you're to call me '[pc.petName(npc)]'. As for you, I'll give you a new name... I think '[pc.name]' suits you. Say it back to me, [pc.name]. What's your name?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(npc.isApplyingPostCombatTransformations())
		<p>
			#IF(npc.isUsingForcedTransform(pc) && npc.getPostCombatPotion()!=null)
				#IF(npc.isUsingForcedFetish(pc) && npc.getPostCombatFetishPotion()!=null)
					As you repeat your new name back to [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] produces a couple of curious little bottles from somewhere out of sight, and shakes them from side to side
					#IF(!npc.isMute())
						 as [npc.she] taunts, [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]! Now open wide, [pc.name]!)]
					#ELSE
						 before your face, allowing you to see that on the side of one of them there's a label which reads '[npc.preferredBody(b)]'. Motioning for you to open wide and prepare to drink the transformative potions, [npc.name] begins to advance upon you.
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					As you repeat your new name back to [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] produces a curious little bottle from somewhere out of sight, and shakes it from side to side
					#IF(!npc.isMute())
						 as [npc.she] taunts, [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]! Now open wide, [pc.name]!)]
					#ELSE
						 before your face, allowing you to see that on the side there's a label which reads '[npc.preferredBody(b)]'. Motioning for you to open wide and prepare to drink the transformative potion, [npc.name] begins to advance upon you.
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				As you repeat your new name back to [npc.herHim], the [npc.race] produces a curious little bottle from somewhere out of sight, and shakes it from side to side
				#IF(!npc.isMute())
					 as [npc.she] taunts, [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! You're going to end up being my perfect partner; this potion will fix your fetishes and make sure of that! Now open wide, [pc.name]!)]
				#ELSE
					 before your face, allowing you to see that on the side there's a warning label which says something about permanent fetish alterations. Motioning for you to open wide and prepare to drink the transformative potion, [npc.name] begins to advance upon you.
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Flashing you a brief, menacing glare, [npc.name] makes it quite clear that [npc.she] expects instant obedience from you. Having agreed to be [npc.her] submissive bitch, you open wide and accept your fate as being transformed to [npc.namePos] liking. Opening wide, you allow [npc.herHim] to pour the liquid into your mouth...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
			<p>
				Clearly finding you irresistibly attractive, as you repeat your new name back to [npc.herHim], [npc.name] grabs hold of your [pc.arm] and pulls you to your [pc.feet], before grinding up against you and
				#IF(npc.isWillingToRape(pc))
					#IF(!npc.isMute())
						 declaring, [npc.speech(As my bitch, you'll be getting fucked a lot! Now submit to me, [pc.name], and prepare to get fucked!)]
					#ELSE
						 starting to grope and fondle your body. Leaning in to plant a forceful kiss on your [pc.lips+], [npc.namePos] dominant behaviour makes it clear that [npc.sheIs] about to fuck you, whether you like it or not...
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					#IF(!npc.isMute())
						 declaring, [npc.speech(As my bitch, I'm going to be wanting to fuck you a lot! You're up for a quick fuck right now, aren't you?)]
					#ELSE
						 throwing you a questioning look as [npc.she] starts to run [npc.her] [npc.hands] over your body. Clearly wanting to fuck you, [npc.name] waits to hear if you're willing to submit to [npc.herHim] or not...
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				As you repeat your new name back to [npc.herHim], [npc.name] looks down at you and lets out an amused humming noise.
				#IF(!npc.isMute())
					 Clearly not being attracted to you, [npc.name] states, [npc.speech(Come back soon, [pc.name], <i>or else</i>. Ive got plans for you!)]
				#ELSE
					 Clearly not being attracted to you, [npc.name] simply glares at you for a moment, before turning [npc.her] back on you.
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				With that, [npc.she] strides off into the caverns, leaving you panting and sweating as you attempt to recover from your alarming experience...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_TRANSFORMATION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasFetish(FETISH_TRANSFORMATION_RECEIVING) || pc.hasFetish(FETISH_KINK_RECEIVING))
			Loving the sound of being transformed by [npc.name], you obediently swallow down the strange liquid that's in your mouth.
		#ELSE
			Thinking that it would be best to do as [npc.name] says, you obediently swallow down the strange liquid that's in your mouth.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(!npc.isMute())
			 Seeing that you've obeyed [npc.herHim], [npc.name] grins and exclaims, [npc.speech(Now for the fun part, [pc.name]!)]
		#ELSE
			 Seeing that you've obeyed [npc.herHim], [npc.name] flashes you an absolutely delighted grin as [npc.she] waits for the transformative effects to take place.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_TRANSFORMATION_END"><![CDATA[
	#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(pc))
		<p>
			Clearly finding you irresistibly attractive, the moment that your transformations come to end, [npc.name] grabs hold of your [pc.arm] and pulls you to your [pc.feet], before grinding up against you and
			#IF(npc.isWillingToRape(pc))
				#IF(!npc.isMute())
					 declaring, [npc.speech(As my bitch, you'll be getting fucked a lot! Now submit to me, [pc.name], and prepare to get fucked!)]
				#ELSE
					 starting to grope and fondle your body. Leaning in to plant a forceful kiss on your [pc.lips+], [npc.namePos] dominant behaviour makes it clear that [npc.sheIs] about to fuck you, whether you like it or not...
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(!npc.isMute())
					 declaring, [npc.speech(As my bitch, I'm going to be wanting to fuck you a lot! You're up for a quick fuck right now, aren't you?)]
				#ELSE
					 throwing you a questioning look as [npc.she] starts to run [npc.her] [npc.hands] over your body. Clearly wanting to fuck you, [npc.name] waits to hear if you're willing to submit to [npc.herHim] or not...
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As the transformations come to an end, [npc.name] looks down at you and lets out an amused humming noise.
			#IF(!npc.isMute())
				 With [npc.her] transformative potion not having been strong enough to give you the body [npc.she] was looking for, [npc.name] mutters, [npc.speech(You're not good enough for me to be interested in you just yet... Come back soon, [pc.name], <i>or else</i>. I'm going to turn you into my perfect little [npc.preferredBody(b)], if it's the last thing I do!)]
			#ELSE
				 With [npc.her] transformative potion not having been strong enough to give you the body [npc.she] was looking for, [npc.name] simply glares at you for a moment, before turning [npc.her] back on you.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, [npc.she] strides off into the caverns, leaving you panting and sweating as you attempt to recover from your alarming experience...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_FUCKED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Giving you no say in the matter, [npc.name] continues to grope you, and as you open your mouth to say something, [npc.she] leans forwards and pulls you into a dominant kiss. After grinding up against you for a few moments, [npc.she] pulls back and prepares to fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REFUSE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to have sex with [npc.name], and seeing that [npc.she] is clearly unwilling to force [npc.herself] on you, you [pc.step] back and tell [npc.herHim] in no uncertain terms that you don't want to get intimate with [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!npc.isMute())
			[npc.speech(Just count yourself lucky that I gave you the choice, [pc.name],)] [npc.name] growls, clearly annoyed by the fact that you're refusing [npc.her] advances.
		#ELSE
			Flashing you a furious glare, [npc.name] makes it very clear without needing to be able to say anything that [npc.sheIs] extremely annoyed by the fact that you're refusing [npc.her] advances.
		#ENDIF
		 With one last snarl, [npc.she] then turns around and strides off down, leaving you to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_FUCKED_WILLING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Agreeing to have sex with [npc.name], you submit to [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] continues to grope you. Happy with your obedience, [npc.she] leans forwards and pulls you into a dominant kiss as [npc.she] firmly squeezes your [pc.ass+]. After grinding up against you for a few moments, [npc.she] pulls back and prepares to fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a satisfied sigh, the [npc.race] takes a [npc.step] back and brings an end to the sex. As [npc.she] starts to get [npc.her] things back in order, [npc.she]
		#IF(!npc.isMute())
			 teases, [npc.speech(You were a good fuck, [pc.name]... That's just what I needed today...)]
		#ELSE
			 smirks down at you and motions for you to move away from [npc.herHim].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving back, you take a moment in which to catch your breath and get your own things sorted out, during which time [npc.name] finishes getting [npc.her] clothing back in position. With one last triumphant sneer thrown your way, the [npc.race] strides off into the caverns, before turning a corner and disappearing from sight. After taking a moment in which to recover your energy, you look around to make sure that there's no immediate danger and then prepare to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Repeat submitting misc.: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_PAID"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Obediently producing the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames which [npc.name] is demanding, you submissively offer them to [npc.herHim]. Letting out a brief laugh, the [npc.race] snatches the money from your [pc.hands], and with a condescending sneer on [npc.her] face,
		#IF(!npc.isMute())
			 [npc.she] states, [npc.speech(That's all I needed, [pc.name]. I'll probably have something else for you to do the next time I see you. Or maybe I'll just take more of your cash! Hah! So go on, [pc.name], fuck off!)]
		#ELSE
			 [npc.she] motions for you to get away from [npc.herHim].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Hurrying to obey, you rush past [npc.name] and hastily make your exit, quickly leaving [npc.herHim] far behind you. Happy with your decision to continue acting like [npc.her] bitch and hand over [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, you prepare to continue on your way through the bat caverns...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		More than happy to have sex with [npc.herHim], you submit to [npc.name] as [npc.she] continues to grope you. Pleased to see how obedient you are, [npc.she] flashes you a quick smirk, before leaning forwards and pulling you into a dominant kiss as [npc.she] firmly squeezes your [pc.ass+]. After grinding up against you for a few moments, [npc.she] pulls back and prepares to fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Repeat submitting mugging: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that the best way for [npc.name] to get [npc.her] money is by taking it from someone else, you tell [npc.herHim] that you'll assist [npc.herHim] in mugging someone. Flashing you a wicked smirk, [npc.she] motions for you to follow [npc.herHim], and you obediently tag along as [npc.she] leads you through the bat caverns in search of a victim.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although at first it seems like the surrounding area is completely deserted, the two of you suddenly spot a flash of movement up ahead. Rushing forwards and blocking the path of this unfortunate traveller, [npc.name]
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 strikes an intimidating pose and makes a threatening gesture.
		#ELSE
			 shouts, [npc.speech(Stop right there!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Coming to a halt beside [npc.name], you see that your victim is [victim.a_fullRace(true)]. Looking back and forth between you and [npc.name], [victim.she] defiantly calls out, [victim.speech(I'm not scared of you! You'll get nothing from me, so get out of my way!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			Aggressively moving forwards, [npc.name] gestures for you to advance along with [npc.herHim], committing to the plan of taking money from [victim.name] by force...
		#ELSE
			Letting out a mocking laugh, [npc.name] gestures for you to advance as [npc.she] taunts, [npc.speech(So, you're doing this the hard way, huh? Come on, [pc.name], let's beat [victim.herHim] up!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_COMBAT_WON"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Staggering back, [victim.name] collapses to the ground, totally defeated. Holding up [victim.her] [victim.hands] in a clear sign of surrender, [victim.she] pants, [victim.speech(No more... Please...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Showing [npc.her] victim no mercy, [npc.name] roughly searches [victim.name], and upon finding [victim.her]
		#IF(victim.isFeminine())
			 purse,
		#ELSE
			 wallet,
		#ENDIF
		 takes all the flames [npc.she] can find.
	#IF(npc.isAttractedTo(victim) && !npc.hasStatusEffect(SE_RECOVERING_AURA) && (npc.isWillingToRape(victim) || victim.isAttractedTo(npc)))
			 Not satisfied with only taking [victim.her] money, [npc.name] lets out a horny moan, before starting to grope and molest the defeated [victim.race]'s body.
		</p>
		#IF(victim.isAttractedTo(npc))
			<p>
				[victim.speech(~Aah!~ Yes... Fuck me!)] [victim.name] [victim.moansVerb+], letting you know that [victim.sheIs] just as turned on as [npc.name].
			</p>
			<p>
				More than happy to give [victim.herHim] what [victim.she] wants, [npc.name] dominantly pulls the [victim.race] into a forceful, passionate kiss, before breaking it off and
				#IF(npc.isMute())
					 making a gesture to suggest that you can stay and watch if you want to...
				#ELSE
					 addressing you as [npc.she] pants, [npc.speech(You can stay and watch me fuck this bitch as your reward for helping, [pc.name]. Or fuck off, I don't really care either way...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[victim.speech(No! Get away from me!)] [victim.name] cries out, letting you know that [victim.sheIs] not at all interested in having sex with [npc.name].
			</p>
			<p>
				Ignoring [victim.her] protests, [npc.name] dominantly pulls the [victim.race] into a forceful, passionate kiss, before breaking it off and
				#IF(npc.isMute())
					 making a gesture to suggest that you can stay and watch if you want to...
				#ELSE
					 addressing you as [npc.she] pants, [npc.speech(You can stay and watch me rape this bitch as your reward for helping, [pc.name]. Or fuck off, I don't really care either way...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSEIF(game.isNonConEnabled() || victim.isAttractedTo(pc))
			 Having plans other than simply taking [victim.her] money, [npc.name] looks down at [victim.race]
			#IF(npc.isMute())
				 and gestures over in your direction, before making a few hand-signs to imply that you're about to fuck [victim.herHim].
			#ELSE
				 as [npc.she] gestures over towards you, asking, [npc.speech(You feeling horny, slut? How about [pc.name] here gives you a good fuck?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF(victim.isAttractedTo(pc))
			<p>
				[victim.speech(~Aah!~ Yes... Fuck me!)] [victim.name] [victim.moansVerb+] as [victim.she] turns to face you.
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(npc.isMute())
					Turning to flash you a devious smirk, [npc.name] makes a gesture to suggest that you can fuck [victim.name] if you want to...
				#ELSE
					Letting out a brief laugh, [npc.name] turns to flash you a devious smirk, before offering, [npc.speech(You can fuck this bitch as your reward for helping, [pc.name]. Or fuck off, I don't really care either way...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[victim.speech(No! Get away from me!)] [victim.name] cries out as [victim.she] tries to crawl away from you and [npc.name].
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(npc.isMute())
					Turning to flash you a wicked smirk, [npc.name] makes a gesture to suggest that you can rape [victim.name] if you want to...
				#ELSE
					Letting out a mocking laugh, [npc.name] turns to flash you a wicked smirk, before offering, [npc.speech(You can rape this bitch as your reward for helping, [pc.name]. Or fuck off, I don't really care either way...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
			 Pushing [victim.name] down to the ground, [npc.she] pockets the cash and takes [pc.steps] back, before heading back over to where you're standing.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(npc.isMute())
				Gesturing for you to get out of here, [npc.name] dashes past you and disappears into the bat caverns.
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Better get out of here before people are attracted to the noise this cunt's making,)] [npc.she] warns, before dashing past you and disappearing into the bat caverns.
			#ENDIF
			 Not wanting to stick around and have to fight yet more people, you follow [npc.namePos] lead and prepare to make a hasty exit...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_SPECTATE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to stay and watch the show, you look on as [npc.name]
		#IF(victim.isAttractedTo(npc))
			 pulls [victim.name] into another deep kiss. Letting out a passionate moan, the [victim.race] pants, [victim.speech(Yes... ~Mmm!~ Fuck me!)]
		#ELSE
			 pulls [victim.name] into another unwanted kiss. Frantically struggling, the [victim.race] cries out, [victim.speech(No! Stop it, please!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Forcefully grinding [npc.her] body up against [npc.her]
		#IF(!victim.isAttractedTo(npc))
			 unwilling
		#ENDIF
		 partner, [npc.name] lets out another horny [npc.moan] as [npc.she] moves to start
		#IF(victim.isAttractedTo(npc))
			 fucking [victim.herHim]...
		#ELSE
			 raping [victim.herHim]...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_NO_SPECTATE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to stick around and watch as [npc.name] 
		#IF(victim.isAttractedTo(npc))
			 fucks [victim.name],
		#ELSE
			 forces [npc.herself] upon [victim.name],
		#ENDIF
		 you leave the two of them to it and take your exit into bat caverns. As you hurry away from the scene of the mugging, you hear
		#IF(victim.isAttractedTo(npc))
			 the [victim.race] [npc.moaning], [victim.speech(Yes! ~Mmm!~ Fuck me!)]
		#ELSE
			 the [victim.race] crying out, [victim.speech(No! Stop it, please!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning a corner, you leave the noises of [npc.name] and [victim.name] behind you as you continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_FUCK_VICTIM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of the reward which [npc.name] is offering, you [pc.step] forwards and advance upon [victim.name]. As you pull [victim.herHim] to [victim.her] [victim.feet], 
		#IF(victim.isAttractedTo(pc))
			 the [victim.race] pants, [victim.speech(Yes... ~Mmm!~ Fuck me!)]
		#ELSE
			 the [victim.race] cries out, [victim.speech(No! Stop it, please!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling your
		#IF(!victim.isAttractedTo(pc))
			 unwilling
		#ENDIF
		 partner into a deep kiss, you grind your body up against [victim.hers], before letting out a horny [pc.moan] as you move to start
		#IF(victim.isAttractedTo(pc))
			 fucking [victim.herHim]...
		#ELSE
			 raping [victim.herHim]...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_NO_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hurrying away from the scene of the crime, you leave [victim.name] far behind. Only after you've put considerable distance between you and the unfortunate [victim.race] do you finally slow down and continue on your way through the bat caverns...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_SPECTATE_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a satisfied sigh, [npc.name] pushes [victim.name] away from [npc.herHim] and brings an end to the sex. After smirking down at the panting, [victim.moaning] [victim.race], [npc.she] gets [npc.her] clothing back in order, before starting to [npc.walk] off into the bat caverns. Turning and looking at you before [npc.she] departs, [npc.name]
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 motions for you to get out of here, probably due to a concern that the Enforcers will show up soon.
		#ELSE
			 warns, [npc.speech(Better get out of here before people are attracted to the noise this cunt's making.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.name] hurries off into the caves, you find yourself left behind with [victim.name]. Not wanting to stick around and have to fight yet more people, you prepare to make a hasty getaway...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_SPECTATE_SEX_END_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hurrying away from the scene of the crime, you leave [victim.name] far behind. Only after you've put considerable distance between you and the unfortunate [victim.race] do you finally slow down and continue on your way through the bat caverns...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_FUCK_VICTIM_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a satisfied sigh, you push [victim.name] away from you and bring an end to the sex. As you get your things back in order, [npc.name] smirks down at the panting, [victim.moaning] [victim.race], before turning [npc.her] back on the two of you and starting to [npc.walk] off into the bat caverns. Pausing to look back at you over [npc.her] shoulder, the [npc.race]
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 motions for you to get out of here, probably due to a concern that the Enforcers will show up soon.
		#ELSE
			 warns, [npc.speech(Better get out of here before people are attracted to the noise this cunt's making.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.name] hurries off into the caves, you find yourself left behind with [victim.name]. Not wanting to stick around and have to fight yet more people, you prepare to make a hasty getaway...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_FUCK_VICTIM_END_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hurrying away from the scene of the crime, you leave [victim.name] far behind. Only after you've put considerable distance between you and the unfortunate [victim.race] do you finally slow down and continue on your way through the bat caverns...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_REFUSE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to have sex with [victim.name], you tell [npc.name] that you aren't interested in the 'reward' that [npc.sheIs] offering to you. Shrugging [npc.her] shoulders, the [npc.race] turns [npc.her] back on the two of you and starts to [npc.walk] off into the bat caverns. Pausing to look back at you over [npc.her] shoulder, [npc.name]
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 motions for you to get out of here, probably due to a concern that the Enforcers will show up soon.
		#ELSE
			 warns, [npc.speech(Better get out of here before people are attracted to the noise this cunt's making.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.name] hurries off into the caves, you find yourself left behind with [victim.name]. Not wanting to stick around and have to fight yet more people, you prepare to make a hasty getaway...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_REFUSE_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hurrying away from the scene of the crime, you leave [victim.name] far behind. Only after you've put considerable distance between you and the unfortunate [victim.race] do you finally slow down and continue on your way through the bat caverns...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_COMBAT_LOST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Utterly defeated by [victim.name], you collapse to the ground alongside [npc.name], who
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 holds up [npc.her] [npc.hands] to the [victim.race] in a clear sign of surrender.
		#ELSE
			 breathlessly pants, [npc.speech(No more... You got us...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[victim.speech(You two stay right there! My friends are going to make you pay for what you tried to do!)] the [victim.race] shouts. With thoughts of getting [victim.her] gang in on the action, the [victim.race] dashes off at full speed into the caves.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to end up at the mercy [victim.namePos] gang, [npc.name] forces [npc.herself] to [npc.her] [npc.feet], before darting off in a different direction. Finding yourself abandoned to your fate by the [npc.race], you quickly catch your breath and move to follow [npc.her] lead in making a hasty exit.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you start to head off into the caverns, you suddenly hear the sound of loud voices coming from where [victim.name] ran off to. Realising that you only have a few moments in which to make good your escape, you hurry away from the scene of the crime...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_MUGGING_COMBAT_LOST_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Sprinting as fast as you can, you turn a sharp corner and narrowly escape being seen by the angry gang, who you hear rushing onto the scene of the attempted mugging and starting to search for you and [npc.name]. Continuing to move at speed through the bat caverns, you don't stop running until you're sure that you've escaped and left your pursuers far behind...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Repeat submitting pimped out: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_PIMPED_OUT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that the best way for [npc.name] to get [npc.her] money is to use your body, you tell [npc.herHim] that you're willing to get pimped out by [npc.herHim]. Smirking at you as [npc.she] hears this, the [npc.race] gestures for you to follow
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 [npc.herHim], before setting off through the bat caverns.
		#ELSE
			 [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(Happy to act as my whore, [pc.name]? That's fine with me, I've got just the person in mind for you...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Obediently following [npc.name] through the twists and turns of the dark caves, you soon find yourself coming to a halt in front of what looks to be an old, large, wooden shed. [npc.Stepping] forwards, [npc.name] knocks upon the warped timbers of the front door, and a few moments later its rusty hinges are making an ear-splitting screech as it swings partially open. [friend.A_fullRace(true)],
		#IF(friend.hasStatusEffect(SE_SMOKING))
			 who's got a freshly-lit cigarette hanging out of [npc.her] mouth,
		#ELSE
			 who looks as though [friend.sheHas] just got out of bed,
		#ENDIF
		 peers out through the gap in the doorway with a suspicious look on [friend.her] face. Recognising [npc.name], [friend.she] snaps, [friend.speech(What do you want, [npc.name]? I've laid claim to this place, and there's nothing you can say that'll make me move out.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			Clearly knowing that [npc.name] is unable to talk, the [friend.race] grabs a piece of scrap paper and a pen from somewhere just behind the door, before holding it out to [npc.name]. Taking the offered items, [npc.name] quickly scrawls an answer on the paper, and you look over to see that it says; 'Long time no see, [friend.name]. I'm not here for your shed. Want to fuck this [pc.race]? We can haggle over price inside.'.
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Long time no see, [friend.name],)] [npc.name] replies in an uncharacteristically-friendly tone. Flashing '[friend.name]' a smile, [npc.she] motions towards you and makes [npc.her] offer, [npc.speech(I'm not here for your shed. Want to fuck this [pc.race]? We can haggle over price inside.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking you up and down, [friend.name] lets out an approving grunt, before opening the door fully and ushering you and [npc.name] inside. As the door is closed and locked behind you, you find yourself standing in the shed's dingy interior. Although two of the four ceiling-mounted arcane lightbulbs are broken, there's enough light to see that there's a huge pile of unwashed dishes piled up in a rudimentary kitchen sink, while the nearby bin looks to be overflowing with empty pizza boxes and other fast-food packaging. A couple of mismatched, sagging sofas sit in the middle of the room, while the broken remains of a wooden table and chairs have been pushed into the far corner.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			After glancing around the apartment and giving a sincere, approving nod, [npc.name] grabs you by the [pc.arm] and roughly pulls you forwards to stand before [friend.name]. Scrawling an asking price of two thousand flames on [npc.her] piece of paper, [npc.she] shows it to [friend.name] and gestures towards you.
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(I see you've tidied the place up since I was last here,)] [npc.name] says with complete sincerity in [npc.her] voice. Grabbing you by the [pc.arm], [npc.she] roughly pulls you forwards to stand before [friend.name], before stating, [npc.speech([pc.SheIs] called [pc.name], and it's two thousand flames to fuck [pc.herHim].)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[friend.speech(Two thousand flames?! You think I'm made of money?)] the [friend.race] replies, [friend.speech(I'll give you five hundred.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not at all happy with this counter offer, [npc.name] refuses, and with that, the two of them start haggling about the price. After a few minutes an agreement is finally made, and with a grin on [friend.her] face, [friend.name] concludes,
	#IF(friend.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
			 [friend.speech(Right, so eight hundred flames now, and I owe you two hundred the next time I see you. I get to rut [pc.namePos] ass and cum in [pc.herHim] if I want.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With [npc.name] offering [friend.herHim] a nod in agreement, [friend.name] hands over the eight hundred flames, after which [friend.she] points over to a stained mattress in one corner of the room and orders you, [friend.speech(Get down on my bed, [pc.name], and present me with your ass. I'm going to get my money's worth out of your hot butt.)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(friend.hasFetish(FETISH_VAGINAL_GIVING))
			 [friend.speech(Right, so eight hundred flames now, and I owe you two hundred the next time I see you. I get to rut [pc.namePos] cunt and
			#IF(friend.hasFetish(FETISH_IMPREGNATION) && !pc.isPregnant() && !pc.isTaur())
				 try to knock [pc.herHim] up by giving [pc.herHim] a big creampie.
			#ELSE
				 cum in [pc.herHim] if I want.
			#ENDIF
			)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With [npc.name] offering [friend.herHim] a nod in agreement, [friend.name] hands over the eight hundred flames, after which [friend.she] points over to a stained mattress in one corner of the room and orders you, [friend.speech(Get down on my bed, [pc.name], and spread your [pc.legs]. I'm going to get my money's worth out of your hot cunt.)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(friend.hasFetish(FETISH_ORAL_RECEIVING))
			 [friend.speech(Right, so eight hundred flames now, and I owe you two hundred the next time I see you. I get to fuck [pc.namePos] face and make [pc.herHim] swallow if I want.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With [npc.name] offering [friend.herHim] a nod in agreement, [friend.name] hands over the eight hundred flames, after which [friend.she] points over to a stained mattress in one corner of the room and orders you, [friend.speech(Kneel down on my bed, [pc.name], and open that pretty mouth of yours. I'm going to get my money's worth by fucking your throat.)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(friend.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_RECEIVING))
			 [friend.speech(Right, so eight hundred flames now, and I owe you two hundred the next time I see you. I get to have my ass fucked by riding [pc.namePos] cock.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With [npc.name] offering [friend.herHim] a nod in agreement, [friend.name] hands over the eight hundred flames, after which [friend.she] points over to a stained mattress in one corner of the room and orders you, [friend.speech(Lie back on my bed, [pc.name], and present me with your cock. I'm going to get my money's worth out of you by getting you to fuck my ass.)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(friend.hasFetish(FETISH_VAGINAL_RECEIVING))
			 [friend.speech(Right, so eight hundred flames now, and I owe you two hundred the next time I see you. I get to have my cunt fucked by riding [pc.namePos] cock.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With [npc.name] offering [friend.herHim] a nod in agreement, [friend.name] hands over the eight hundred flames, after which [friend.she] points over to a stained mattress in one corner of the room and orders you, [friend.speech(Lie back on my bed, [pc.name], and present me with your cock. I'm going to get my money's worth out of you by getting you to fuck my pussy.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
			 [friend.speech(Right, so eight hundred flames now, and I owe you two hundred the next time I see you. I get to fuck [pc.name] any way I like.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With [npc.name] offering [friend.herHim] a nod in agreement, [friend.name] hands over the eight hundred flames, after which [friend.she] points over to a stained mattress in one corner of the room and orders you, [friend.speech(Get over to my bed, [pc.name]. I'm going to get my money's worth out of you.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_PIMPED_OUT_ANAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.walk] over to [friend.namePos] 'bed', and after dropping down on all fours onto [friend.her] worn, stained mattress, you lift your ass towards [friend.herHim]. Looking back over your shoulder, you see the [friend.race] pulling out [friend.her] [friend.cock+], before dropping down behind you and greedily exposing your [pc.ass+].
		#IF(pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_TORSO_UNDER)!=null && pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_TORSO_UNDER).getWriting()!=null && pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_TORSO_UNDER).getWriting().getText().equalsIgnoreCase('Property of '+npc.getNameIgnoresPlayerKnowledge()))
			 Seeing the words 'Property of [npc.name]' inked as part of your tramp stamp, [friend.name] lets out an amused laugh and calls out, [friend.speech(I see you've got [pc.name] marked as your property. I've paid for it, so don't complain to me if I end up breaking [pc.her] ass.)]
		#ELSE
			 Seeing your [pc.asshole+], [friend.name] lets out a hungry [friend.moan] and calls out to [npc.name], [friend.speech(I've paid for it, so don't complain to me if I end up breaking [pc.her] ass.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			Waving [npc.her] [npc.hand] to show that [npc.she] doesn't care, [npc.name] leans against the back of one of the sofas and prepares to watch you get anally fucked by [friend.name]. 
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Do what you like with [pc.herHim],)] [npc.name] replies, before leaning against the back of one of the sofas and preparing to watch you get anally fucked by [friend.name]. 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[friend.speech(Here I come, [pc.name]. Now moan for me like the whore you are,)] the [friend.race] teases, before impatiently thrusting [friend.her] [friend.cock+] into your [pc.asshole+]. The sudden penetration causes you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan], and you can't help but pant and whine as [friend.name] starts to rhythmically pound your ass...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_PIMPED_OUT_VAGINAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.walk] over to [friend.namePos] 'bed', and after lying back onto [friend.her] worn, stained mattress, you spread your [pc.legs] for [friend.herHim]. Eager to get started, the [friend.race] pulls out [friend.her] [friend.cock+], before dropping down between your [pc.legs] you and greedily exposing your [pc.pussy+].
		#IF(pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN)!=null && pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN).getWriting()!=null && pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN).getWriting().getText().equalsIgnoreCase('Property of '+npc.getNameIgnoresPlayerKnowledge()))
			 Seeing the words 'Property of [npc.name]' inked as part of your womb tattoo, [friend.name] lets out an amused laugh and calls out, [friend.speech(I see you've got [pc.name] marked as your property. I've paid for it, so don't complain to me if I end up breaking [pc.her] cunt.)]
		#ELSE
			 Teasing [friend.her] [friend.fingers+] over your [pc.labia+], [friend.name] lets out a hungry [friend.moan] and calls out to [npc.name], [friend.speech(I've paid for it, so don't complain to me if I end up breaking [pc.her] cunt.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			Waving [npc.her] [npc.hand] to show that [npc.she] doesn't care, [npc.name] leans against the back of one of the sofas and prepares to watch you get fucked by [friend.name]. 
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Do what you like with [pc.herHim],)] [npc.name] replies, before leaning against the back of one of the sofas and preparing to watch you get fucked by [friend.name]. 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(friend.hasFetish(FETISH_IMPREGNATION) && !pc.isPregnant() && !pc.isTaur())
				[friend.speech(I'm going to knock you up, [pc.name],)] the [friend.race] teases, before impatiently grabbing your [pc.legs+] and pushing them apart and back towards your head. Shuffling forwards and positioning [friend.herself] over the top of you, [friend.name] locks you into the mating press position, before lifting [friend.her] hips and sliding the [friend.cockHead+] of [friend.her] cock up and down over your [pc.labia+]. Looking down into your [pc.eyes+], [friend.she] licks [friend.her] [friend.lips] and [friend.moansVerb], [friend.speech(Here I come, [pc.name]. Now moan for me like the whore you are!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Before you can answer, the [friend.race] impatiently thrusts [friend.her] [friend.cock+] deep into your [pc.pussy+]. The sudden penetration causes you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan], and you can't help but pant and whine as [friend.name] starts to rhythmically pound your [pc.pussy+]...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			[friend.speech(Here I come, [pc.name]. Now moan for me like the whore you are,)] the [friend.race] teases, before impatiently thrusting [friend.her] [friend.cock+] into your [pc.pussy+]. The sudden penetration causes you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan], and you can't help but pant and whine as [friend.name] starts to rhythmically pound your [pc.pussy+]...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_PIMPED_OUT_ORAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.walk] over to [friend.namePos] 'bed', and after kneeling down onto [friend.her] worn, stained mattress, you open your mouth for [friend.herHim]. Eager to get started, the [friend.race] pulls out [friend.her] [friend.cock+], before [friend.stepping] forwards and bringing it towards your face.
	</p>
	<p>
		[friend.speech(Hungry for my cock, [pc.name]?)] the [friend.race] teases.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you begin to answer, [friend.name] impatiently grabs the back of your head, and with a single buck of [friend.her] [friend.hips], thrusts [friend.her] [friend.cock+] down your throat. As [friend.she] starts to fuck your face, [friend.she] [friend.moansVerb], [friend.speech(That's it, take it deep, [pc.name]... ~Mmm!~ Suck my cock like the whore you are!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_PIMPED_OUT_ANAL_GIVING_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.walk] over to [friend.namePos] 'bed' and lie back onto [friend.her] worn, stained mattress. Eager to get started, the [friend.race] exposes [friend.her] [friend.ass+], before dropping down over the top of you and greedily exposing your [pc.cock+].
		#IF(pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN)!=null && pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN).getWriting()!=null && pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN).getWriting().getText().equalsIgnoreCase('Property of '+npc.getNameIgnoresPlayerKnowledge()))
			 Seeing the words 'Property of [npc.name]' inked as part of your womb tattoo, [friend.name] lets out an amused laugh and calls out, [friend.speech(I see you've got [pc.name] marked as your property. I've paid for [pc.herHim], so for the moment [pc.sheIs] mine!)]
		#ELSE
			 Looking down at your [pc.cock+], [friend.name] lets out a hungry [friend.moan] and calls out to [npc.name], [friend.speech(I've paid for it, so I'm going to have my fun with [pc.her] cock!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			Waving [npc.her] [npc.hand] to show that [npc.she] doesn't care, [npc.name] leans against the back of one of the sofas and prepares to watch you fuck [friend.namePos] ass.
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Do what you like with [pc.herHim],)] [npc.name] replies, before leaning against the back of one of the sofas and preparing to watch you fuck [friend.namePos] ass. 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Teasing [friend.her] [friend.fingers+] over the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+], [friend.name] forces you to get an erection, before lining it up to [friend.her] [friend.asshole+]. Grinning down at you, [friend.she] teases, [friend.speech(Here I come, [pc.name]. Now moan for me like the whore you are!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [friend.she] impatiently drops down, forcing your [pc.cock+] into [friend.her] [friend.asshole+]. The sudden penetration causes you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan], and you can't help but pant and whine as [friend.name] starts to rhythmically bounce up and down on your [pc.cock+]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_PIMPED_OUT_VAGINAL_GIVING_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.walk] over to [friend.namePos] 'bed' and lie back onto [friend.her] worn, stained mattress. Eager to get started, the [friend.race] exposes [friend.her] [friend.pussy+], before dropping down over the top of you and greedily exposing your [pc.cock+].
		#IF(pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN)!=null && pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN).getWriting()!=null && pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN).getWriting().getText().equalsIgnoreCase('Property of '+npc.getNameIgnoresPlayerKnowledge()))
			 Seeing the words 'Property of [npc.name]' inked as part of your womb tattoo, [friend.name] lets out an amused laugh and calls out, [friend.speech(I see you've got [pc.name] marked as your property. I've paid for [pc.herHim], so for the moment [pc.sheIs] mine!)]
		#ELSE
			 Looking down at your [pc.cock+], [friend.name] lets out a hungry [friend.moan] and calls out to [npc.name], [friend.speech(I've paid for it, so I'm going to have my fun with [pc.her] cock!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			Waving [npc.her] [npc.hand] to show that [npc.she] doesn't care, [npc.name] leans against the back of one of the sofas and prepares to watch you fuck [friend.namePos] cunt.
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Do what you like with [pc.herHim],)] [npc.name] replies, before leaning against the back of one of the sofas and preparing to watch you fuck [friend.namePos] cunt. 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Teasing [friend.her] [friend.fingers+] over the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+], [friend.name] forces you to get an erection, before lining it up to [friend.her] [friend.asshole+]. Grinning down at you, [friend.she] starts rubbing [friend.her] [friend.labia+] over your [pc.cock], teasing, [friend.speech(Here I come, [pc.name]. Now moan for me like the whore you are!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [friend.she] impatiently drops down, forcing your [pc.cock+] into [friend.her] [friend.pussy+]. The sudden penetration causes you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan], and you can't help but pant and whine as [friend.name] starts to rhythmically bounce up and down on your [pc.cock+]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_PIMPED_OUT_GENERIC_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.walk] over to [friend.namePos] 'bed', and after [pc.stepping] onto [friend.her] worn, stained mattress, you turn to face [friend.herHim]. Eager to get started, the [friend.race] grabs hold of you, before pulling you into a sloppy, forceful kiss. Breaking it off with a wet smacking of [friend.her] [friend.lips], [friend.name] teases, [friend.speech(You're mine now, [pc.name]. I want to hear you moan like the whore you are.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling you into [friend.her] body, [friend.name] dominantly grinds up against you as [friend.she] decides how best to fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_PIMPED_OUT_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had [friend.her] fun, [friend.name] collapses down onto the stained mattress which serves as [friend.her] bed, before shouting out to [npc.name], [friend.speech(I've finished with [pc.name]. You can take this whore away now.)]
	</p>
	#IF(npc.isMute())
		<p>
			[npc.Stepping] forwards, [npc.name] gestures for you to quickly gather your things, and after you've done so, [npc.she] grabs hold of your [pc.arm(true)] and impatiently pulls you out of [friend.namePos] shed. Turning to give you a smug grin once the two of you are back out in the bat caverns, [npc.name] makes a motion to indicate that you should be on your way, before turning [npc.her] back on you and [npc.walking] off.
		</p>
		<p>
			With your task of earning some money for [npc.name] having been completed, there's little else for you to do except continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[npc.Stepping] forwards, [npc.name] commands, [npc.speech(Gather your things, [pc.name]. We're leaving.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Hurrying to do as you're told, you quickly get your things back in order, and after you've done so, [npc.name] grabs hold of your [pc.arm(true)] and impatiently pulls you out of [friend.namePos] shed. Turning to give you a smug grin once the two of you are back out in the bat caverns, [npc.she] states, [npc.speech(You did well back there, [pc.name]. I made some good money off of selling your body. Come find me later if you want to do this again.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, [npc.name] turns [npc.her] back on you and [npc.walks] off. With your task of earning some money for [npc.herHim] having been completed, there's little else for you to do except follow the [npc.race]'s example and continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_PIMPED_OUT_SEX_END_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leaving [friend.namePos] shed behind, you set off on your way through the bat caverns, wondering what to think about the fact that you've just willingly been pimped out by [npc.name]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Repeat submitting walkies: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_WALKIES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you obediently drop down in front of [npc.name] and crawl over to [npc.her] side. Letting out a brief laugh, the [npc.race]
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 snaps [npc.her] [npc.fingers] and motions for you to follow [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] sets off at a slow walk through the bat caverns.
		#ELSE
			sets off at a slow walk through the bat caverns, calling back to you as [npc.she] goes, [npc.speech(Keep up, [pc.name]!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to disappoint [npc.name], you crawl as fast as you can and try your best to remain at [npc.her] side as [npc.she] leads you forwards. Thankfully, [npc.her] destination isn't too far away, and after five minutes of crawling along with [npc.herHim], you and [npc.name] arrive at a dingy, run-down bistro built into a gloomy cave. Through the grimy windows you're able to see that it looks to be quite limited on interior space, which is probably why [npc.name]
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 gestures for you to wait outside while [npc.she] goes in to eat.
		#ELSE
			 commands, [npc.speech(Sit here and wait for my return, [pc.name].)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Obediently waiting outside as [npc.name] enters the bistro to get some food, you start to feel the stares of several nearby people who are loitering about nearby. After a couple of minutes have passed, one of these strangers, [stranger.a_fullRace(true)], [stranger.walks] up to where you're sitting, and with a big grin on [stranger.her] face, asks, [stranger.speech(You doing some kind of pet-play with that [npc.race] who went inside? You sure look like a dumb, horny bitch. I bet you're craving a taste of my #IF(stranger.hasPenis())fat cock#ELSEcunt#ENDIF, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(stranger.hasPenis())
			Before you can answer, the [stranger.race] shamelessly whips out [stranger.her] [stranger.cock+] and presents it to you.
		#ELSE
			Before you can answer, the [stranger.race] shamelessly exposes [stranger.her] [stranger.pussy+] and presents it to you.
		#ENDIF
		 With the other nearby strangers looking on in amusement, [stranger.name] waits to see what your reaction will be...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_WALKIES_ORAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turned on at the thought of sucking [stranger.namePos] cock in front of the nearby strangers, you lean over to give it a hot, wet lick. With a triumphant smirk quickly settling on [stranger.her] face, the [stranger.race] teases, [stranger.speech(Yeah, that's what I thought. You're just as much of a slutty bitch as you look.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Proving [stranger.herHim] right, you shuffle around to face the [stranger.race], before parting your [pc.lips+] and taking [stranger.her] [stranger.cock+] into your mouth. Letting out [stranger.a_moan+], [stranger.name] eagerly thrusts [stranger.her] cock down your throat and makes you give [stranger.herHim] a sloppy, public blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_WALKIES_ORAL_VAGINAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turned on at the thought of orally servicing [stranger.namePos] pussy in front of the nearby strangers, you lean over to give it a hot, wet lick. With a triumphant smirk quickly settling on [stranger.her] face, the [stranger.race] teases, [stranger.speech(Yeah, that's what I thought. You're just as much of a slutty bitch as you look.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Proving [stranger.herHim] right, you shuffle around to face the [stranger.race], before pressing your [pc.lips+] against [stranger.her] [stranger.labia+] and pushing your [pc.tongue+] into [stranger.her] hot cunt. Letting out [stranger.a_moan+], [stranger.name] eagerly grabs the back of your head and pulls your face into [stranger.her] groin, forcing you to continue giving [stranger.herHim] some sloppy, public cunnilingus...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_WALKIES_VAGINAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turned on at the thought of getting fucked by [stranger.name] in front of the nearby strangers, you desperately gain access to your [pc.pussy+], before turning around on all fours to present it to [stranger.name]. With a triumphant smirk quickly settling on [stranger.her] face, the [stranger.race] teases, [stranger.speech(Yeah, that's what I thought. You're just as much of a slutty bitch as you look.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping down behind you, the [stranger.race] slides [stranger.her] [stranger.cock+] up and down over your [pc.labia+], before pushing forwards and sinking it into your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out [stranger.a_moan+], [stranger.name] then eagerly starts thrusting [stranger.her] cock in and out of your [pc.pussy+] as [stranger.she] gives you a good public fucking...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_WALKIES_ANAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turned on at the thought of getting fucked by [stranger.name] in front of the nearby strangers, you desperately gain access to your [pc.asshole+], before turning around on all fours to present your ass to [stranger.name]. With a triumphant smirk quickly settling on [stranger.her] face, the [stranger.race] teases, [stranger.speech(Yeah, that's what I thought. You're just as much of a slutty bitch as you look.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping down behind you, the [stranger.race] slides [stranger.her] [stranger.cock+] up and down over your [pc.ass+], before pushing forwards and sinking it into your [pc.asshole+]. Letting out [stranger.a_moan+], [stranger.name] then eagerly starts thrusting [stranger.her] cock in and out of your [pc.ass+] as [stranger.she] gives you a good public anal fucking...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_WALKIES_IGNORE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not at all interested in [stranger.namePos] cock, you turn away from [stranger.herHim] and remain seated outside the bistro. Grunting in disappointment, and to the sound of laughter from the other strangers who were watching, the [stranger.race] [stranger.walks] off and soon disappears from sight.
	</p>
	<p>
		After that, nothing eventful happens during the fifteen minutes you're left waiting for [npc.namePos] return. As [npc.she] makes [npc.her] eventual return and exits the bistro, the [npc.race] looks over at you with a surprised look on [npc.her] face. Letting out a mocking laugh, [npc.she]
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 gestures to imply that [npc.she]'d forgotten you were out here, before making a [npc.hand] movement to shoo you away.
		#ELSE
			 declares, [npc.speech(I'd forgotten than you were out here, [pc.name]! What an obedient thing you are! Anyway, I've got nothing for you to do right now, so get lost.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.name] heads off into the bat caverns, leaving you feeling more than a little embarrassed at the manner of your dismissal...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_WALKIES_IGNORE_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Standing up and brushing yourself down, you head off into the caves and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_WALKIES_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a satisfied [stranger.moan], [stranger.name] pulls [stranger.her] cock away from you and teases, [stranger.speech(You're one slutty bitch. I knew you'd be a good fuck.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the [stranger.race] puts [stranger.her] [stranger.cock+] away, and after taking one last look at you, [stranger.she] [stranger.walks] off and disappears from sight. At that same moment, [npc.name] makes [npc.her] return, and upon exiting the bistro, [npc.she] turns to give you a knowing smirk.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			Gesturing back towards the window of the bistro, [npc.she] implies through [npc.hand(true)] signals that [npc.she] was watching you the whole time. Flashing you another smirk, [npc.she] dismisses you with a wave of [npc.her] [npc.hand(true)] and [npc.walks] off into the bat caverns, leaving you with little else to do but continue on your way...
		#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Couldn't resist getting fucked by that [stranger.race], huh, [pc.name]?)] [npc.she] asks, [npc.speech(Me and the other people inside were watching the two of you through the windows. You're a dirty, horny whore, aren't you?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Not giving you any time in which to respond, [npc.name] dismisses you with a wave of [npc.her] [npc.hand(true)], before [npc.walking] off into the bat caverns, leaving you with little else to do but continue on your way...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_WALKIES_SEX_END_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Standing up and brushing yourself down, you head off into the caves and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Repeat submitting tattooed: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_TATTOOED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Obediently submitting to [npc.namePos] order, you follow along behind [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] sets off into the abt caverns. After a few minutes, you find yourself being led to a pitch-black door that's been set into a solid rock wall and which has been artistically painted with the words '[tattooist.NamePos] Tattoos'. After giving this door a brief, loud knock, [npc.name] [npc.steps] back, and then moment later, it swings outwards to reveal [tattooist.a_race] standing at the top of a steep flight of stairs.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			Gesturing towards you, [npc.name] makes some [npc.hand(true)] signals to imply that you're the one [npc.she] wants tattooed, and as payment, [tattooist.name] can fuck you once [tattooist.sheIs] done.
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Hey, [tattooist.name],)] [npc.name] says in a familiar tone, before gesturing towards you and stating, [npc.speech(This is the bitch I told you about. You tattoo [pc.herHim] as my property, and as payment you can fuck [pc.herHim], like we agreed.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[tattooist.speech(I knew you were selfish, [npc.name], but getting this slut tattooed as your property? Well, whatever, it's not like I care,)] [tattooist.name] grunts. After looking you up and down, [tattooist.she] then turns and [tattooist.walks] down the steps, calling out after [tattooist.herHim], [tattooist.speech(Bring [pc.herHim] down, [npc.name]. I'll get [pc.herHim] inked right away.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Grabbing you by the [pc.arm(true)], [npc.name] leads you down the stairs, and then after turning a corner and passing through a thick, metal door, you find yourself in a brightly-lit tattoo studio. Closing and locking the door behind you, [tattooist.name] gestures towards a bed-like table, commanding,
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled() && pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_TORSO_UNDER)==null && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_ANUS, true))
			#IF(pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN)==null && pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 [tattooist.speech(Lie down on your front. I'll give you your tramp stamp first, then you can turn over for your womb tattoo.)]
			#ELSE
				 [tattooist.speech(Lie down on your front; I'm going to be giving you a tramp stamp.)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 [tattooist.speech(Lie down on your back; I'm going to be giving you a womb tattoo.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_TATTOOED_ASS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again doing as you're told, you lie down face-first on the padded table and hold still as [tattooist.name] exposes your ass and lower back. Dominantly groping your [pc.assSize] butt,
		#IF(pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN)==null && pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
			 the [tattooist.race] grunts, [tattooist.speech(You've got a nice ass. Now let's get you marked up.)]
		#ELSE
			 the [tattooist.race] grunts, [tattooist.speech(Yeah, you look like you'll be a good fuck. Let's get you marked up so I can get on with pounding your ass.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Firing up [tattooist.her] arcane tattoo gun, [tattooist.name] starts to ink a black, tribal pattern onto your lower back. Thankfully, the process isn't at all painful, and only produces a light tingling sensation in the areas where your tramp stamp is being applied. Finishing your tattoo off with the words 'Property of [npc.name]', the [tattooist.race] [tattooist.steps] back and declares, [tattooist.speech(Right, you're done. Now anyone fucking you from behind knows who you belong to.)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_GROIN)==null && pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
		<p>
			Not finished with you yet, [tattooist.name] gives your [pc.ass+] a quick slap, before commanding, [tattooist.speech(Flip over onto your back so that I can give you your womb tattoo.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Whipping out [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+], [tattooist.name] gives your [pc.ass+] a quick slap, before playfully calling out to [npc.name], [tattooist.speech(It says here that this bitch's ass belongs to you. Mind if I use it for a bit?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(npc.isMute())
				Smirking at [tattooist.namePos] words, [npc.name] waves [npc.her] [npc.hand(true)] in a gesture to indicate that [tattooist.she] can go ahead and do what [tattooist.she] likes with you.
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Knock yourself out,)] [npc.name] replies with a big smirk on [npc.her] face.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[tattooist.speech(Raise your ass, [pc.name],)] [tattooist.name] hungrily commands, before [tattooist.stepping] forwards and preparing to fuck you...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_TATTOOED_PUSSY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_alleyway_submission_tattooed_ass))
			Obediently following [tattooist.namePos] command, you flip over and again hold still as [tattooist.name] exposes your [pc.pussy+].
		#ELSE
			Once again doing as you're told, you lie back on the padded table and hold still as [tattooist.name] exposes your [pc.pussy+].
		#ENDIF
		 Unable to resist, [npc.she] slides [npc.fingers+] over your [pc.labia+], before stroking your [pc.clit+] and causing you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan]. Smirking at your reacting, the [tattooist.race] teases, [tattooist.speech(Yeah, you look like you'll be a good fuck. Let's get you marked up so I can get on with pounding your cunt.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_alleyway_submission_tattooed_ass))
			Once again firing up [tattooist.her] arcane tattoo gun, [tattooist.name] inks a pink, heart-themed womb tattoo onto your lower abdomen, before adding the words 'Property of [npc.name]'. With both of your tattoos now complete, [tattooist.name] puts [tattooist.her] tool down and proudly states, [tattooist.speech(These are some of my best works. No matter if you're fucked from the front or behind, everyone's going to know who you belong to.)]
		#ELSE
			Firing up [tattooist.her] arcane tattoo gun, [tattooist.name] starts to ink a pink, heart-themed womb tattoo onto your lower abdomen. Thankfully, the process isn't at all painful, and only produces a light tingling sensation in the areas where your tattoo is being applied. Finishing it off with the words 'Property of [npc.name]', the [tattooist.race] [tattooist.steps] back and declares, [tattooist.speech(Right, you're done. Now anyone fucking your cunt knows who you belong to.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Whipping out [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+], [tattooist.name] starts stroking your [pc.pussy+] as [tattooist.she] playfully calls out to [npc.name], [tattooist.speech(It says here that this bitch's cunt belongs to you. Mind if I use it for a bit?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			Smirking at [tattooist.namePos] words, [npc.name] waves [npc.her] [npc.hand(true)] in a gesture to indicate that [tattooist.she] can go ahead and do what [tattooist.she] likes with you.
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Knock yourself out,)] [npc.name] replies with a big smirk on [npc.her] face.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[tattooist.speech(Spread your [pc.legs], [pc.name],)] [tattooist.name] hungrily commands, before [tattooist.stepping] forwards and preparing to fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_TATTOOED_VAGINAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Submissively doing as you're told, you spread your [pc.legs], allowing [tattooist.name] to [tattooist.step] forwards and start to slide the [tattooist.cockHead+] of [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+] up and down over your [pc.labia+]. Looking down at [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+], you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] in anticipation of what's about to happen.
	</p>
	<p>
		[tattooist.speech(You want it, [pc.name]?)] [tattooist.name] asks in response to your lewd noise. Lining [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+] up to your [pc.pussy+], [tattooist.she] teases, [tattooist.speech(Beg for it, you horny bitch.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Please, fuck me!)] you cry out in desperation. Grabbing your [pc.hips+], the [tattooist.race] gives you what you want, and with a determined thrust, sinks [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+] into your [pc.pussy+]. As you let out another [pc.moan+], [tattooist.name] starts to pump in and out of your [pc.pussy+], while [npc.name] looks on with an amused smirk on [npc.her] face...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_TATTOOED_ANAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Submissively doing as you're told, you raise your [pc.ass+], allowing [tattooist.name] to [tattooist.step] forwards and start to slide the [tattooist.cockHead+] of [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+] up and down over your [pc.ass+]. Looking back over your shoulder at the [tattooist.race], you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] in anticipation of what's about to happen.
	</p>
	<p>
		[tattooist.speech(You want it, [pc.name]?)] [tattooist.name] asks in response to your lewd noise. Lining [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+] up to your [pc.asshole+], [tattooist.she] teases, [tattooist.speech(Beg for it, you horny bitch.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Please, fuck my ass!)] you cry out in desperation. Grabbing your [pc.hips+], the [tattooist.race] gives you what you want, and with a determined thrust, sinks [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+] into your [pc.ass+]. As you let out another [pc.moan+], [tattooist.name] starts to pump in and out of your [pc.asshole+], while [npc.name] looks on with an amused smirk on [npc.her] face...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_TATTOOED_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With a satisfied [tattooist.moan], [tattooist.name] pulls back and allows
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_alleyway_submission_tattooed_pussy))
			 [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+] to slide out of your well-fucked cunt. [tattooist.Stepping] back, [tattooist.she] teases,
		#ELSE
			 [tattooist.her] [tattooist.cock+] to slide out of your well-fucked asshole. Giving your [pc.ass+] a slap, [tattooist.she] [tattooist.steps] back and teases,
		#ENDIF
		 [tattooist.speech(You were a good fuck, [pc.name].)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the [tattooist.race] puts [tattooist.her] cock away and turns to talk with [npc.name], leaving you panting on the padded table. After spending a few minutes lying there and catching your breath, [npc.name] [npc.steps] forwards and looms over you, before
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 gesturing for you to get your things together and get up.
		#ELSE
			 commanding, [npc.speech(Get your things together and get up. The fun's over.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Hurrying to obey, you get up off the table and quickly you sort yourself out, after which [npc.name] gestures for you to leave the same way you came. Calling out as you exit [tattooist.her] tattoo parlour, [tattooist.name] teases, [tattooist.speech(Show those tattoos off as much as you can, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SUBMITTED_REPEAT_TATTOOED_SEX_END_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Heading up the stairs and finding yourself out in the bat caverns once again, you turn to face [npc.name] as [npc.she] follows on and closes the door behind [npc.herHim].
		#IF(npc.isMute())
			 Making [npc.a_hand] sign to imply that you should come back and find [npc.her] again soon, the [npc.race] [npc.walks] off into the caves, before turning a corner and disappearing from sight. With little else to do, you follow [npc.her] example and continue on your way...
		#ELSE
				 Flashing you a devious grin, the [npc.race] commands, [npc.speech(Come back and find me again soon. With those new tattoos of yours, it could be fun to go and pimp you out.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				With that, [npc.name] [npc.walks] off into the caves, before turning a corner and disappearing from sight. With little else to do, you follow [npc.her] example and continue on your way...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
