<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			<p>
				You find yourself standing in front of a rather peculiar shop. Although there's a sign declaring 'Arcane Arts' to be [style.colourGood(open)], the interior is very dimly-lit, and you notice that most of the Arcade's shoppers are giving this particular store a wide berth. Wanting to take a closer look, you walk up to the entrance, and, looking through the glass into the shop's gloomy interior, you see signs of movement behind the counter.
			</p>
			<p>
				A sign hanging in the door's window declares that the [style.colourMinorGood(opening hours are [unit.time(6)]-[unit.time(22)])]. You could step inside and browse the wares on offer if you wanted to.
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				A hanging sign fixed to the wall of the shop in front of you declares the name of the premises as 'Arcane Arts'. Just like the rest of the shops in the arcade, this store is currently [style.colourBad(closed)], although it's apparent from even a cursory glance through the windows that the gloomy interior is stocked with weapons and potions.
			</p>
			<p>
				A sign hanging in the door's window declares that the [style.colourMinorBad(opening hours are [unit.time(6)]-[unit.time(22)])]. You'll have to come back later if you want to browse the wares on offer.
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SHOP_WEAPONS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_vickyIntroduced))
		<p>
			Pushing open the door to Arcane Arts once again, your arrival is announced by the familiar sound of a little bell ringing above you. Just like the other times you've visited, only one other person is inside; the greater wolf-girl Vicky, who's standing behind the shop's counter.
		</p>
		<p>
			As the door swings shut behind you, Vicky's yellow eyes lock onto yours, and her mouth turns up into an unsettling predatory grin. Even though she's only a few [unit.lSizes] away, and you're the only person in the shop, she doesn't utter a single word of greeting, and you find that the shop's already-gloomy atmosphere has quickly become extremely oppressive. As you step forwards to say hello, the wolf-girl suddenly cuts you off, [vicky.speech(If you aren't here to waste my time, I keep the good stuff under the counter here. Want to take a look again?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			The toothy, menacing grin on Vicky's wolf-like face is extremely worrying, but surely she isn't going to attack a customer...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Pushing open the door, your arrival is announced by the sound of a little bell ringing above you. There's only one other person inside; a greater wolf-girl, who's standing behind the shop's counter.
		</p>
		<p>
			As the door swings shut behind you, the wolf-girl's yellow eyes lock onto yours, and her mouth turns up into an unsettling predatory grin. Even though she's only a few [unit.lSizes] away, and you're the only person in the shop, she doesn't utter a single word of greeting, and you find that the shop's already-gloomy atmosphere has quickly become extremely oppressive. You glance around, seeing that there are only odd trinkets and pieces of 'enchanted' junk littering the messy shelves.
		</p>
		<p>
			You start to back off towards the door, but as you do, the wolf-girl finally speaks, [vicky.speech(If you aren't here to waste my time, I keep the good stuff under the counter here. I'm Vicky by the way, welcome to my shop...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You look across to the wolf-girl to see that she's beckoning you over to her. The toothy grin on her wolf-like face is extremely worrying, but surely she isn't going to attack a customer...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SHOP_WEAPONS_OFFER_BODY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I was wondering... If you'd like to use me...)] you say, looking sheepishly up at Vicky.
	</p>
	<p>
		[vicky.speech(Sounds good to me, bitch,)] she growls, before leaping over the counter, roughly grabbing you by the [pc.arms], and shoving you towards the store's counter, before turning and locking the front door. [vicky.speech(I love fucking submissive customers like you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply, Vicky bounds over towards you, before grabbing you by the waist and hurling you back onto the counter-top. Stepping forwards, she [npc.verb(position)] herself
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			 between your legs,
		#ELSE
			 right up in front of you,
		#ENDIF
		 making a point to grind her huge erection up against your crotch as she snarls, [vicky.speech(I hope you like it rough!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SHOP_WEAPONS_RAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling more than a little intimidated by the overbearing wolf-girl's attitude, you try to back away towards the front door, muttering, [pc.speech(E-Erm... M-Maybe I'll come back later...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Sensing your weakness, Vicky suddenly leaps over the counter and pounces on you. Grabbing hold of your shoulders, and, with considerable force, slamming you back against the wall, she snarls, [vicky.speech(So you came to waste my time, huh? I don't put up with that shit!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You let out a startled cry as the aggressive wolf-girl suddenly throws you to the floor. Looking up as you struggle to your feet, you see Vicky quickly locking the front door, before she turns around and bounds over to you. [vicky.speech(You're just begging to be fucked!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(W-Wait! No! L-Let me go! I- ~Aaah!~)] Your protests are cut short as Vicky grabs you by the waist and hurls you down onto the counter-top.
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping forwards, she [npc.verb(position)] herself right up behind you, making a point to grind her huge erection up against your [pc.ass+] as she snarls, [vicky.speech(Scream and cry as much as you want! I hope you like it rough, because I don't go easy with pathetic bitches like you!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARTHURS_PACKAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Actually, I'm here to collect a package,)] you say, stepping towards the shop's front desk, [pc.speech(it should be addressed to 'Arthur'...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You allow your voice to trail off as a low, rumbling growl starts to fill the room. Vicky narrows her eyes a little, continuing to emit a menacing snarl as she allows her gaze to wander up and down your body. Feeling more than a little concerned with the wolf-girl's behaviour, you take a step back, preparing yourself in case she decides to attack.
	</p>
	<p>
		[vicky.speech(Don't worry, I don't bite,)] she snaps, thankfully bringing her intimidating growls to an end, before bending down to retrieve something from behind her desk. As she crouches out of sight, you hear a faint snarl as Vicky finishes her sentence, [vicky.speech(much...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After just a moment, she suddenly springs to her feet, before placing a small cardboard box down on the desk in front of her. Looking into your eyes once more, she snarls, [vicky.speech(I've been holding on to this for some time, you know. It's quite <i>frustrating</i> when people don't collect their orders immediately.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Without warning, Vicky suddenly grabs hold of the desk, and in one swift, alarming manoeuvre, vaults over the counter-top and pounces towards you. Caught with your back against the wall, you suddenly find yourself face-to-face with the aggressive wolf-girl. Showing a complete lack of respect for your personal space, she roughly presses her body right up against yours, staring hungrily into your eyes as she growls, [vicky.speech(It's so frustrating, in fact, that I'm going to need some <i>compensation</i>. It's a one-hundred flame fee for late collections like this. If you can't pay... I'm sure we can work <i>something</i> out...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Vicky presses herself close to you, and you feel her hot breath falling on your neck as she starts letting out a low growl once again. As she traps you against the wall, you suddenly feel something hard, and alarmingly-large, pressing against your leg. Looking down, you see a huge erection tenting out the fabric of the wolf-girl's skirt, which she then starts to dominantly rub up against you. [vicky.speech(So what's it going to be? You got the flames? Or am I going to have to fuck the payment out of you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARTHURS_PACKAGE_BOUGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I can pay the fee,)] you say, side-stepping the wolf-girl before producing one-hundred flames.
	</p>
	<p>
		Vicky looks noticeably disappointed as you hand over the money, and, after walking back around to the correct side of the counter, she pushes the package towards you. [vicky.speech(Go on then, it's all yours. If you wanted to take a look at my goods, or if you ever get curious about what you just missed out on, then let me know.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Vicky leans back against the wall as you take the package, before fixing her gaze onto your face as she waits to see what you'll do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARTHURS_PACKAGE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That second option doesn't sound so bad...)] you say, grinning up at Vicky as she roughly presses you against the wall.
	</p>
	<p>
		[vicky.speech(Suits me, bitch,)] she growls, before grabbing you by the [pc.arms] and shoving you towards the store's counter, before turning and locking the front door. [vicky.speech(I love fucking submissive customers like you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply, Vicky bounds over towards you, before grabbing you by the waist and hurling you back onto the counter-top. Stepping forwards, she [npc.verb(position)] herself
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			 between your legs,
		#ELSE
			 right up in front of you,
		#ENDIF
		 making a point to grind her huge erection up against your crotch as she snarls, [vicky.speech(I hope you like it rough!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARTHURS_PACKAGE_RAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling more than a little intimidated by the overbearing wolf-girl's advances, you try to slip away, muttering, [pc.speech(E-Erm... M-Maybe I'll come back later...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Sensing your weakness, Vicky grabs hold of your shoulders, and, with considerable force, slams you back against the wall, snarling, [vicky.speech(Playing hard-to-get, huh? I don't have time for that shit!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You let out a startled cry as the aggressive wolf-girl suddenly throws you to the floor. Looking up as you struggle to your feet, you see Vicky quickly locking the front door, before she turns around and bounds over to you. [vicky.speech(You're just begging to be fucked!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(W-Wait! No! L-Let me go! I- ~Aaah!~)] Your protests are cut short as Vicky grabs you by the waist and hurls you down over the counter-top.
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping forwards, she [npc.verb(position)] herself right up behind you, making a point to grind her huge erection up against your [pc.ass+] as she snarls, [vicky.speech(Scream and cry as much as you want! I hope you like it rough, because I don't go easy with pathetic bitches like you!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARTHURS_PACKAGE_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not at all amused by Vicky's little performance, you look her straight in the eyes, and, firmly pushing her away, you state, [pc.speech(I'm leaving now. I'll be back later for the package.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not giving the wolf-girl any time to respond, you stride over to the door, pull it open, and step out into the Shopping Arcade.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VICKY_POST_SEX_PACKAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Vicky steps back, grinning down at you as she growls, [vicky.speech(You're a pretty good fuck. I guess this counts as payment for your package. If you wanted to take a look at my goods, or if you ever want to be my bitch again, then let me know.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The wolf-girl strides over to the store's front door, barely giving you a moment to get your things in order before unlocking it and walking back behind her counter. You quickly finish gathering your things, and, taking the package from on top of the counter, you prepare to make your next move. Vicky leans back against the wall, fixing her gaze onto your face as she waits to see what you'll do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VICKY_POST_SEX_RAPE_PACKAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Vicky steps back, grinning down at you as she growls, [vicky.speech(You're a pretty good fuck; I love it when bitches like you try to put up a fight. I guess this counts as payment for your package. If you wanted to take a look at my goods, or if you ever want to be my bitch again, then let me know.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The wolf-girl strides over to the store's front door, barely giving you a moment to get your things in order before unlocking it and walking back behind her counter. You quickly finish gathering your things, and, taking the package from on top of the counter, you prepare to make your next move. Vicky leans back against the wall, fixing her gaze onto your face as she waits to see what you'll do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VICKY_POST_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Vicky steps back, grinning down at you as she growls, [vicky.speech(You're a pretty good fuck. If you wanted to take a look at my goods, or if you ever want to be my bitch again, then let me know.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The wolf-girl strides over to the store's front door, barely giving you a moment to get your things in order before unlocking it and walking back behind her counter. You quickly finish gathering your things, and, scrambling to your [pc.feet], you prepare to make your next move. Vicky leans back against the wall, fixing her gaze onto your face as she waits to see what you'll do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VICKY_POST_SEX_RAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Vicky steps back, grinning down at you as she growls, [vicky.speech(You're a pretty good fuck; I love it when bitches like you try to put up a fight. If you wanted to take a look at my goods, or if you ever want to be my bitch again, then let me know.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The wolf-girl strides over to the store's front door, barely giving you a moment to get your things in order before unlocking it and walking back behind her counter. You quickly finish gathering your things, and prepare to make your next move. Vicky leans back against the wall, fixing her gaze onto your face as she waits to see what you'll do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
