<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The self proclaimed bargain store seems almost out of place amongst the hustle and bustle of the shopping arcade.
		 While most of the stores in the arcade are grand and intimidating, the unassuming nature of the store gives off an aura of calm amidst the crazy shoppers.
		 The single entrance stands slightly ajar with a large and tacky "welcome" sign hung on front.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Upon pushing your way through the swinging door, a small bell at the top announces you entry.
		 At first glance, the store seems to have no theme, with books, outfits, and... are those weapons?
	</p>
	<p>
		[akari.speech(Oh shit, a customer!)]
		 From behind the seemingly endless shelves of miscellaneous items, a crescendo of soft footsteps seem to approach you at an impossible speed.
		 Nearly tripping over herself, a small kitsune hurries around the corner and down the aisle to greet you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[akari.speech(*huff* ... *huff* S-sorry, My name is Hayashi Akari, and I run this little shop!)]
		 She takes a deep breath to steady herself before continuing.
		 [akari.speech(Before you ask, yes I am a youko, yes I am old enough to own a store, and no I cannot grant wishes.)]
		 The small youko girl's smile is contagious, and you find yourself almost mirroring her cheeky grin
		 
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(There go all my questions I guess.)]
		 you jokingly admit.
		 [npc.name] shoots you a toothy smile in response, before becoming seemingly captivated by an object across the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		[akari.speech(Well it was nice meeting you, now if you excuse me, the display over there is a bit crooked.)]
		 [akari.speech(Let me know if you need anything [pc.ms]... umm...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech([pc.name])]
	</p>
		[akari.speech([pc.name]! Let me know if you need anything [pc.name]!)]
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRY_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Upon pushing your way through the swinging door, a small bell at the top of the door announces you entry.
		 At first glance, the store seems to have no theme, with books, outfits, and... are those weapons?
	</p>
	<p>
		[akari.speech(I'll be there in just a minute!)]
		a small voice calls out from behind the shelves.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(It's okay [npc.name], it's me)]
		you call out. While [npc.name]'s energy is seemingly endless, you wouldn't want to make her hurry when she doesn't need to.
	</p>
	<p>
		[akari.speech(Oh! [pc.name]! Welcome back, what can I help you with?)]
	</p> 
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_AKARI"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(What is this place?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.name]'s smile widens at your question, her fingertips brushing over on of the items on the counter for a moment before she answers.
		[akari.speech(This is my shop and it's full of treasures, most of them I gathered myself but recently there's been a massive influx of people trading me things.)]

		She pauses for a moment to bite her lip again, her body shifting slightly as she considers her next words carefully.
		 Her eyes drifting over the store for a moment, no doubt hurt by the lack of people in it.
		 Sighing softly she turns her gaze back to you.
		[akari.speech(Though honestly, it's kind of quiet. I just had to relocate, I sort of have too much stuff now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You have a feeling that any strange items that appear in your world will probably end up in this shop.
	</p>
	]]>
</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="TRADE"><![CDATA[
		<p>
			You look around the numerous shelves for something to buy.
			 Upon closer inspection, it appears that the store is more or less sorted into three sections, weapons, clothing, and misc items.
		</p>
		<p>
			[akari.speech(Go ahead and help yourself, I'll come help you when you are ready)] the small fox girl says.
		</p>
		<p>
			What are you going to explore?
		</p>
		]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech([npc.name]!, I'm gonna head out.)] you call out.
	</p>
	<p>
		[akari.speech(Bye [pc.name]! Come back again.)]
		 She shouts after you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
	
	
	