<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Most of the clothing stores in the shopping arcade are small, one-story affairs, with a limited selection of goods on offer.
		 The establishment before you appears to be the exception to this rule, and takes the form of a huge, two-story clothing department bearing the sign 'Nyan's Clothing Emporium'.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_GREETING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping through the open pair of wide, glass doors, you find yourself in a large, modern-looking clothing store.
		 As you walk through the building, you discover that not only is this the largest shop in the arcade, but that it's also the busiest.
		 Crowds of shoppers block many of the aisles that you'd like to walk down, and every member of staff that you see is busily occupied with other customers.
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding that it might be best to try and find a smaller, quieter clothing store, you turn around and start to head for the exit.
		 As you do so, you hear a nervous voice calling out from behind you,
		 [nyan.speech(E-Erm, excuse me? C-Can I help you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning once more, this time in the direction that the timid voice came from, you find yourself face-to-face with a lesser cat-girl.
		 As you look into her bright blue eyes, her cheeks instantly turn a deep shade of red, and she glances down at the floor and starts shuffling her feet, 
		[nyan.speech(H-Hello... T-There's nobody else available, you see, s-so I thought maybe I could help. Oh, erm, I-I'm Nyan... I probably should have said that first... W-Welcome to my store...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		If it wasn't for the fact that she's wearing a staff uniform, and has a little name tag pinned to her blouse reading 'Nyan; Store Manager', you're not sure if you would have believed that she's the store's owner.
		 In an attempt to put the anxious cat-girl at ease, you ignore the fact that she's visibly trembling and explain your situation to her,
		 [pc.speech(Pleased to meet you Nyan, it's an impressive place you've got here! I was having a little difficulty finding anything in amongst all these crowds, however...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(O-Oh, sorry! E-Everything we have on display can also b-be found back in our stockroom. F-Follow me and I'll show you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		In what appears to be an almost desperate attempt to escape further conversation, Nyan hurries past you and rushes off towards a door bearing the sign 'Staff Only'.
		 Doing as she instructed, you follow her through the door into the store's stockroom.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_GREETING_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping through the open pair of wide, glass doors, you find 'Nyan's Clothing Emporium' to be just as busy as ever.
		 Crowds of shoppers block almost every aisle, and if it wasn't for Nyan's offer to personally show you around her stockroom, you don't think you'd ever manage to get any shopping done in here.
	</p>
	<p>
		Scanning around for any sign of the store's nervous owner, you suddenly hear a familiar squeak coming from behind you,
		 [nyan.speech(A-Ah! H-Hello again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You turn around to see Nyan looking down at her feet as she shuffles them about on the shop's laminate flooring,
		 [pc.speech(Hi Nyan, how are y-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(I-I'm fine! T-Thanks for asking,)] Nyan bursts out, interrupting you in her haste to answer,
		 [nyan.speech(I-I can show you the stockroom again if y-you'd like! F-Follow me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following Nyan into her store's stockroom once again, you wonder what to take a look at this time...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_GREETING_REPEAT_PREGNANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Entering the store, you're surprised to find that Nyan is nowhere in sight.
		 Pushing through the throngs of people, you manage to catch one of the employees not busy with a customer, and upon asking after Nyan, you're pointed in the direction of the stock room.
	</p>
	<p>
		Entering the familiar room, you discover that Nyan is indeed in here, murmuring to herself behind a stack of boxed clothing.
		 Wringing her hands and staring at her feet, something has quite clearly got her more worked up than usual, and you notice that she jumps a little as she sees you approach.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(What's wrong Nyan?)]
		 you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(O-Oh... well um...)] she says haltingly, [nyan.speech(Do y-you remember when w-we...you know...)] she blushes fiercely and says in a very quiet voice, [nyan.speech(Had s-sex...?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You smile at the memory and nod.
		 Nyan smiles nervously back, before continuing,
		 [nyan.speech(W-Well my tummy felt a little funny a-after so I took a t-test and...a-and...)]
		 She closes her eyes and takes a deep breath, bunching up the bottom of her skirt as if gathering her courage before blurting out,
		 [nyan.speech(I'm pregnant with your baby!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After her outburst, she just stands there; eyes scrunched closed, trembling hands clenching her skirt, she seems to be waiting for an admonishment.
		 Stepping forwards, you sweep her into your arms, wishing that you'd been able to record the surprised squeak that bursts out of her mouth.
		 She blinks in surprise as you hold her close, before pulling back a little and staring at you with open mouthed shock,
		 [nyan.speech(W-W-What? You're not a-angry?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You hold her at arm's length for a moment, smiling as you shake your head,
		 [pc.speech(Why would I be angry? This is great news!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		A visible tension seems to melt from her entire being as the nervous cat-girl cutely smiles back and snuggles into your [pc.arms],
		 [nyan.speech(W-Will you come b-by and visit from time to t-time?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You instantly agree, and can't help but grin as you notice that she's looking happier than you've ever seen her before.
		 Still nestled against your chest, Nyan mumbles,
		 [nyan.speech(D-Did you need something w-while we're in the s-stockroom?)]
	</p>
	<p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_STOCK_ROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The stockroom of Nyan's Clothing Emporium looks pretty much exactly as you'd expected it be.
		 Ceiling-height shelving units are stocked full of clothes, shoes, and accessories of all different sorts, and there's a distinctive 'new clothing' smell lingering in the air.
	</p>
	<p>
		Nyan's heels clatter across the laminate flooring as she hurries to retrieve a notepad that she uses to track what's currently in stock.
		 Rushing back over to you, she fumbles with the little pad and almost drops it on the floor,
		 [nyan.speech(A-Ah! S-Sorry, I don't usually interact with customers, s-so sorry if I'm a little unprofessional... A-Anyway, let me know what you'd like t-to see, and I'll show y-you what I've got in stock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You start to thank the nervous cat-girl, but she suddenly squeaks out and cuts you off,
		 [nyan.speech(O-Oh! A-and I forgot! I-I was going to do a t-trial of offering to buy old clothes from customers, s-so if you wanted to, I-I could buy some old clothing from you...
			 O-Oh, I interrupted you... S-Sorry...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thanking Nyan for her time, you explain to her that you need to get going now.
		 Hurrying to put her little notepad away, she stutters,
		 [nyan.speech(W-well, thanks for choosing to s-shop here! If you ever want t-to come back, just find me and I-I'll show you what's in stock back here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can respond, Nyan turns around and runs off deeper into the stockroom.
		 You're pretty sure that there aren't any other exits in that direction, and that she was just unable to continue the conversation any longer.
	</p>
	<p>
		You step out of the stockroom, and, after pushing your way through a crowd of customers that's loitering around the store's exit, you head back out into the shopping arcade.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_SUPPLIER_PROBLEM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you look around Nyan's stockroom, you can't help but notice the fact that all of her wares are very 'ordinary'.
		 You expected to see at least one or two items of enchanted or unusual clothing, but there's nothing of that sort on any of the shelves.
		 Turning to the nervous cat-girl who's hovering at your side, you ask her about this state of affairs,
		 [pc.speech(You don't happen to have any enchanted clothing hidden away somewhere, do you, Nyan? You've got a good selection stored back here, but I was looking for something a little special.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(Ah! W-Well, erm, you see, ah, I-I used to, but then they said they wouldn't be offering any, a-and they'd already driven the others away, s-so I can't really get anything like that anymore,)]
		 Nyan blurts out, tripping over her own words in her haste to offer an explanation,
		  [nyan.speech(s-so I'm really sorry, b-but no...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Slow down, Nyan,)]
		 you say, trying to calm her down,
		 [pc.speech(I don't fully understand.
		  Who are 'they', and who are these others that they drove away?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Your questions seem a little too much for Nyan to handle, and, reaching up to place her paw-like hands on her heaving chest, she scrunches her eyes closed and tries to focus on calming her breathing down.
		 Not wanting to exasperate the delicate cat-girl, you keep quiet and wait for her to get into a state in which she'd be comfortable responding.
		 As you stand there in silence, you take a moment to think about how miraculous it is, considering her extreme nervousness, for Nyan to have risen to the position of owning her own store.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a minute or two, the cat-girl's breathing has slowed to a regular rate, and she opens her eyes and smiles,
		 [nyan.speech(Sorry about that... I can get a little overwhelmed sometimes, and I have to perform those breathing exercises to avoid having a panic attack... I should be alright now...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'm sorry, I didn't mean to get you worked up, will you be ok?)]
		 you ask, although the fact that she didn't stutter once in her last reply has already given you your answer.
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(Don't worry, I'll be fine,)]
		 she smiles as she responds,
		 [nyan.speech(but to answer your question, 'they' are a pair of clothing suppliers, who I have no choice but to use.
		 I used to stock enchanted clothing, you see, but all of the good suppliers were driven out of business by this new pair...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Nyan lets out a distressed sigh, and you can tell that the composure she gained from performing her breathing exercises is quickly starting to waver,
		 [nyan.speech(I-It wasn't due to fair c-competition either; they i-intimidated and threatened everyone into l-leaving, and now, ah, I-I have no choice b-but to use them!
		 I-I tried complaining to the enforcers, b-but t-they said the other s-suppliers were refusing t-to cooperate!
		 I know they were threatened into s-silence! I-It's not fair!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Sensing that Nyan is on the verge of a panic attack, you decide that it would be best to drop the subject for the moment,
		 [pc.speech(Thank you for telling me about it, Nyan, but we should carry on looking at the clothing you've got in here, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Nyan lets out a relieved sigh as she casts her eyes down at her clipboard, clearly grateful for the fact that you're dropping the subject for now.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_OFFER_HELP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it'd be best to get Nyan into a more relaxed state before offering your help with her supplier problem, you walk around the storeroom for a little while, asking innocuous questions about the sorts of clothing on each shelf.
		 Just as you'd hoped, the subject is one that she's very comfortable talking about, and after a little while she stops stuttering and begins to offer some clothing-related trivia of her own volition.
	</p>
	<p>
		Eventually you decide that the time is right, and turn towards the nervous cat-girl with a disarming smile on your face,
		 [pc.speech(I was thinking about that problem with those suppliers that you were telling me about before.
		  If you could tell me where these suppliers are, I'd be willing to go and talk to them on your behalf.
		  I'm sure that I could convince them to let the others return.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(Really? Y-You'd do that for me?)]
		 Nyan replies, the steady tone that she'd been speaking in while talking about clothing instantly starting to give way to her nervousness again,
		 [nyan.speech(I-I could o-offer a reward if you could convince them t-to let the others back. I-I could give you f-five thousand flames, a-and a discount on s-shopping here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That's generous of you,)]
		 you say, trying to move the conversation forwards before Nyan starts having a panic attack,
		 [pc.speech(so could you tell me where they are? You said that there were two of them before, but what are their names, and what do they look like?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(W-Wolfgang and K-Karl are their names,)]
		 Nyan stammers,
		 [nyan.speech(a-and they're b-both dobermanns. T-They still operate out of the public s-supplier depot, over in the c-corner of the Shopping Arcade.
		 It used to h-house all of the clothing suppliers t-that provided goods to t-this area of D-Dominion, not just the S-Shopping Arcade, but n-now it's just t-those t-two in there... 
		 I-It looks like it's all c-closed up, as it f-fell into disrepair after everyone w-was forced out.
		 E-Even the Arcade owners are scared to m-make them tidy it up...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thanks, Nyan. I'll get all of this sorted out soon, don't you worry!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(Mhmm,)]
		 Nyan mumbles, blushing a little as she looks to the floor,
		 [nyan.speech(T-Thank you, [pc.name]... Y-You're so... k-kind...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_REPORT_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that now's as good a time as any to report your success with the supplier problem, you turn to Nyan,
		 [pc.speech(I sorted out that problem with the suppliers for you.
		 Wolfgang and Karl have agreed to let the other suppliers back, so you'll be able to stock enchanted clothing again.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		An excited little squeak bursts out from between Nyan's lips, causing her to instinctively clasp her paw-like hands over her mouth,
		 [nyan.speech(Eep! T-Thank you s-so much, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You smile at Nyan's genuine reaction to the news, which unintentionally makes matters worse for the nervous cat-girl.
		 As she sees your happy expression, Nyan's cheek turn a deep shade of scarlet, and she averts her eyes as she stutters,
		 [nyan.speech(I-I said, t-that is, I mean, I-I, erm, well, t-there w-was the reward I-I p-promised, h-hold on please! Eep!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Without any further further warning, Nyan suddenly runs off, leaving you all alone in the stockroom.
		 Knowing that she'll be back once she's calmed down, you lean against one of the shelves and let out a sigh.
		 The delicate cat-girl seems more nervous than ever today, and you wonder if there's any way you could help her overcome her anxiety.
		 Perhaps once all this supplier business is taken care of, you could try to get to know her a little better.
	</p>
	<p>
		Any further thoughts on the matter are interrupted, as Nyan suddenly returns, rushing up to you and thrusting a little wad of cash into your [pc.hands],
		 [nyan.speech(P-Please take this!)]
		 she squeaks, before stepping back,
		 [nyan.speech(A-And I c-can give y-you a t-twenty-five percent d-discount too!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thank you, Nyan,)]
		 you reply, smiling,
		 [pc.speech(I'm just happy to have helped!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[nyan.speech(I-I really a-appreciate it, [pc.name],)]
		 Nyan stammers, looking at the ground,
		 [nyan.speech(I-I d-don't have a-a [pc.girlfriend] o-or anything...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		This revelation comes out of nowhere, and as you prepare to respond, Nyan suddenly realises what she just said,
		 [nyan.speech(Eep! I-I mean, n-no, I-I meant that I-I don't have a-anyone I could have a-asked to help! I-I didn't mean, that is, I-I wasn't asking y-you, n-not that I w-wouldn't, b-but, aaaaaah!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Unable to deal with the situation, Nyan turns and sprints off.
		 As she turns the corner at the end of the storeroom, you get one last glimpse of her scarlet-coloured cheeks.
		 This time, considering the state that she's in, you doubt that she'll be back any time soon.
		 It would probably be best to come back a little later, once Nyan's had some time to cool-off.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="NYAN_EXIT_EMBARRASSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having been deserted by the panic-stricken cat-girl, you walk out of the stockroom and head towards the shop's exit.
		 After pushing your way through a crowd of customers who're loitering around the large glass doors, you head back out into the shopping arcade.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
