<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- EXTERIOR -->

	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While there are a few restaurants and other sit-down eateries scattered throughout the Shopping Arcade, there is a conspicuous lack of places which offer food to take out. The sole exception to this is the store in front of you, which, from the outside, is reminiscent of an old-fashioned sweet shop, with large glass windows displaying all manner of exotic-looking food and drink.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			 The words 'Ralph's Snacks' are painted in cursive gold lettering above the entrance, while a little sign hanging in the door's window informs you that the [style.colourMinorGood(opening hours are between [unit.time(6)] and [unit.time(22)])]. As the store is currently [style.colourGood(open)], you could step inside and take a look around if you wanted to...
		#ELSE
			 The words 'Ralph's Snacks' are painted in cursive gold lettering above the entrance, while a little sign hanging in the door's window informs you that the [style.colourMinorBad(opening hours are between [unit.time(6)] and [unit.time(22)])]. As the store is currently [style.colourBad(closed)], you'll have to come back later if you wanted to take a look inside...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CANDI_LIPSTICK -->

	<htmlContent tag="CANDI_LIPSTICK"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ralphAskedAboutHundredKisses))
		<p>
			Wanting to finally get your [pc.hands] on the lipstick set Candi is looking for, you ask Ralph if he still has 'A Hundred Kisses' for sale. Much to your relief, he replies, [ralph.speech(Yeah, I've still got it locked up safely behind the counter. If you want it, it's going to be the same deal as before; [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] flames.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As you think about whether it would be a good idea to spend so much money on lipstick or not, Ralph continues,
			#IF(game.getSecondsPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().ralphSexTimer<60*60*22)
				 [ralph.speech(I can't afford to take any more time out today, so I can't offer you any alternative to the price in flames. Maybe tomorrow I'll give you the chance to have me try and knock you up again.)]
			#ELSEIF(pc.isPregnant())
				 [ralph.speech(There's no other deal I can offer you, seeing as you're already pregnant.)]
			#ELSEIF(pc.hasIncubationLitter(ORIFICE_VAGINA))
				 [ralph.speech(There's no other deal I can offer you, seeing as you're already stuffed full of eggs.)]
			#ELSEIF(!pc.hasVagina())
				 [ralph.speech(Seeing as you haven't got a pussy, there's no other deal I can offer you.)]
			#ELSEIF(!pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 [ralph.speech(Seeing as I can't get access to your pussy, there's no other deal I can offer you.)]
			#ELSE
				 [ralph.speech(Of course, if you want to have a go at my alternative deal, there's always that option available to you. All you need to do is lie down on my desk and let me put a kid or two in your belly. Of course, I'll have to test after I'm done that I've got you pregnant, but if I have, I'll give you the lipsticks for free...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			With the horse-boy waiting to hear what your decision will be, you wonder whether you should buy the lipsticks or not...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Knowing that this is the final hurdle before being able to get [brax.name] as your very own slave, you tell Ralph that you've heard he has the lipstick set, 'A Hundred Kisses', for sale, and that you were interested in purchasing it from him.
		</p>
		<p>
			[ralph.speech(Hah, is that so?)] Ralph laughs, leaning heavily down against the counter-top and grinning at you as he replies, [ralph.speech(I only ever told one person that I had that for sale, just one, and I've already had over ten people asking to buy it! The price turned out to be a little too steep for each of them, however, so it's still in my possession... How does fifty-thousand flames sound to you?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As exclusive as it might be, fifty-thousand flames for a set of lipsticks is nothing less than outrageous. Without expressing too much shock, you ask Ralph if he's willing to drop the price at all, to which he replies,
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().ralphDiscount>0)
				 [ralph.speech(After what you did for me before, of course! I'll give you the same [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]-percent discount as I do on everything else in my shop. That'd make it [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] flames, just for you!)]
			#ELSE
				 [ralph.speech(Sorry, but unless you're willing to do something for a special discount, then that's a no. Fifty-thousand flames is my final price.)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Just as you're wondering whether it would be worth paying that much for what is, ultimately, gaining [brax.name] as a slave, Ralph says,
			#IF(pc.isPregnant())
				 [ralph.speech(You know, if you weren't pregnant, I could have offered you a special deal, but seeing as you've already got a bun in the oven, there's nothing else I can do for you.)]
			#ELSEIF(pc.hasIncubationLitter(ORIFICE_VAGINA))
				 [ralph.speech(You know, if your womb wasn't stuffed full of eggs, I could have offered you a special deal, but seeing as you're 'unavailable', there's nothing else I can do for you.)]
			#ELSEIF(!pc.hasVagina())
				 [ralph.speech(You know, if you had a pussy, I could have offered you a special deal, but seeing as you're lacking the necessary parts, there's nothing else I can do for you.)]
			#ELSEIF(!pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 [ralph.speech(You know, if your pussy wasn't locked up like that, I could have offered you a special deal, but seeing as you're 'unavailable', there's nothing else I can do for you.)]
			#ELSE
				 [ralph.speech(Of course, if you're looking for an alternative deal, there's always another option available to you... All you'd need to do is lie down on my desk here#IF(pc.hasLegs()), spread your legs,#ENDIF and let me put a kid or two in your belly. Of course, I'll have to test after I'm done that I've got you pregnant, but if I have, I'll give you the lipsticks for free...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="CANDI_LIPSTICK_PURCHASE_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling Ralph that you're not going to buy the lipsticks right now, you step away from him and return to browsing the shelves...
	</p>
	<p>
		Most of the goods aren't anything special, and are just the typical sorts of food and drink that you could pick up anywhere. What sets this shop apart, however, is a special display of arcane-imbued consumables. The prices aren't listed, and instead, a little label reads 'Please ask Ralph for assistance with these items'.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CANDI_LIPSTICK_START_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of Ralph's alternative deal, you playfully bite your lip and seductively declare your willingness to let him try and impregnate you. With a hungry grin quickly settling on his horse-like face, the shopkeeper steps around from the other side of his counter, before quickly moving over to lock the front door. Drawing the blinds so that no members of the public can see in, he then moves back over to stand before you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[ralph.speech(I wouldn't offer this to just anyone, you know,)] the horse-boy says, reaching out to run his hands over your [pc.hips+], before sliding them around to grab your [pc.ass+] and then dominantly pulling you in against his muscular chest. [ralph.speech(So, are you ready for me to make you a mommy?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you open your mouth to say yes, the horse boy leans forwards and presses his lips against yours. Immediately thrusting his tongue into your mouth, he starts greedily groping and squeezing your [pc.ass+], before moving up to fondle your [pc.breasts+]. The two of you continue kissing one another like this for just a few moments, before Ralph suddenly pulls back and growls into your ear, [ralph.speech(Enough of the foreplay, it's time to breed you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Grabbing hold of your [pc.hips+] once more, the horny horse-boy manhandles you over to the shop's counter, before
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 getting you to step up onto it with the front legs of your feral [pc.legRace]'s body, and then to lie down on its surface, thereby presenting your rear-facing genitals to him.
		#ELSE
			 pushing you down, face-first, over the surface.
		#ENDIF
		 Looking back over your shoulder, you see Ralph quickly unzipping his trousers, before fishing out his massive, rapidly-hardening horse-cock. Seeming to then remember something important, he grabs a couple of '[#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getNamePlural(false)]' from out of a nearby drawer, before swallowing one himself and then getting you to take the other. Telling you that you're sure to get pregnant now, he moves on to quickly gain access to your [pc.pussy+], and you suddenly find yourself letting out a gasp as you feel his wide, flared head impatiently prodding forwards between your [pc.labia+].
	</p>
	<p>
		Somehow managing to keep his lust under control for a few moments more, Ralph teases you with the promise of penetration, [ralph.speech(You want me to make you the mother of my children, don't you? Go on, beg for my cock! Beg for me to breed you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		By this point you're getting desperate for Ralph to start fucking you, and you eagerly cry out for him to breed you. Half-way through your submissive request, he suddenly obliges, and, thrusting forwards, he rams his hot, fat horse-cock deep into your hungry pussy. Arching your back#IF(pc.hasLegs()) and spreading your [pc.legs]#ENDIF, you let out a wild [pc.moan] as you feel Ralph take hold of your [pc.hips+] and start to pump into and out of your [pc.pussy+]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CANDI_LIPSTICK_PURCHASE -->

	<htmlContent tag="CANDI_LIPSTICK_PURCHASE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] flames is an acceptable price to pay in order to gain [brax.name] as your slave, you tell Ralph that you'd like to buy the lipstick set, 'A Hundred Kisses'. As he hears this, the horse-boy's face lights up, and with a voice full of surprised delight, he asks, [ralph.speech(Would you like it delivered to a particular address, or do you want to take it with you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be faster to take it back to Candi yourself, you decline the offer of having it delivered. Retrieving it from a locked cupboard nearby, Ralph places 'A Hundred Kisses' down on the counter before you. Although the box appears to be simple enough in design, it is flawless in construction, and is made from a combination of dark leather and rich mahogany. Opening the hinged lid, Ralph shows you that all one hundred of the individual lipsticks are contained within, and, happy with the product, you hand over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] flames in exchange for it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking you for your custom, Ralph then asks if there's anything else he can help you with today...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_BREEDING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having pumped his seed directly into your womb, and therefore having gotten what he wanted, Ralph steps back, letting out a satisfied growl as he looks down at your creampied-pussy. As you push yourself up off the counter and back onto your [pc.feet], the horse-boy grabs a nearby arcane pregnancy tester, before stepping forwards and saying, [ralph.speech(Let's find out if you're a mommy! Remember, you only get the lipsticks if I've knocked you up...)]
	</p>
	[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_BREEDING_SUCCESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With the pregnancy test showing a positive result, Ralph reaches forwards to run his hand over your stomach, smiling in delight as he exclaims, [ralph.speech(You're going to make an excellent mother! I knew my virile seed would have no trouble in getting you knocked up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting Ralph have his fun for a moment, you soon remind him of his end of the bargain, and that he now owes you the lipstick set, 'A Hundred Kisses'. Obviously valuing his success at having bred you far more than the monetary value of the lipstick set, the impregnation-obsessed horse-boy doesn't seem at all upset to be handing over the valuable item to you for free, and happily retrieves it from a locked cupboard nearby. Although the box appears to be simple enough in design, it is flawless in construction, and is made from a combination of dark leather and rich mahogany. Opening the hinged lid, Ralph shows you that all one hundred of the individual lipsticks are contained within, and, happy with the product, you take it and prepare to continue on your way.
	</p>
	<p>
		Remarking one last time about how your womb has been claimed by his strong seed, Ralph moves across the store to unlock the front door, before returning to his counter and asking if there's anything else he can help you with today...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_BREEDING_FAILURE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With the pregnancy test showing a negative result, Ralph lets out a sigh and exclaims, [ralph.speech(I can't believe I didn't get you pregnant from that! Well, there's always tomorrow, if you want to come back and try again then...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having failed to impregnate you, Ralph moves across the store to unlock the front door, before returning to his counter and asking if there's anything else he can help you with today...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_BREEDING_INTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping away from Ralph, you return to browsing the shelves of his shop...
	</p>
	<p>
		Most of the goods aren't anything special, and are just the typical sorts of food and drink that you could pick up anywhere. What sets this shop apart, however, is a special display of arcane-imbued consumables. The prices aren't listed, and instead, a little label reads 'Please ask Ralph for assistance with these items'.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	
</dialogue>
