<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR_OPEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The establishment before you, once boarded up and closed, is now quite clearly open for business.
		 The words 'Supplier Depot; bulk clothing sales and storage' have recently been re-painted in bold yellow lettering above the entrance, and there's a little 'open for business' sign hanging in the doorway.
		 The boarding that once covered the wide glass windows has all been torn down, allowing you to see into the clean, well-lit reception area.
	</p>
	<p>
		From where you're standing, you can see that there's a lesser mouse-girl sitting behind the reception's front desk.
		 A few of the Depot's clients are talking with each other as they relax on a trio of plain green sofas.
		 You wonder if you should step inside, or continue on your way to elsewhere in the Shopping Arcade...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR_REFURBISHING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The establishment before you is one of the few in the Shopping Arcade that's not open for business, but you're sure that all of that will change very soon.
		 The words 'Supplier Depot; bulk clothing sales and storage' have recently been re-painted in bold yellow lettering above the entrance, but the windows are all still boarded up, and the 'closed' sign remains hanging in the doorway.
	</p>
	<p>
		Peeking through some of the gaps in the boarding, you see numerous workmen painting the walls and fitting new lights into the ceiling.
		 You know that it won't be long before this place re-opens, which will allow Nyan to stock enchanted clothing once again.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR_CLOSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The establishment before you is one of the few in the Shopping Arcade that's not open for business.
		 The words 'Supplier Depot; bulk clothing sales and storage' are written in inviting yellow lettering above the entrance, the wide glass windows are all boarded up, and there's a little 'closed' sign hanging in the doorway.
		 The name suggests that this place used to deal primarily in bulk transactions for other stores, and so even if it were still open, it wouldn't be a suitable place for you to shop at.
	</p>
	<p>
		Peeking through some of the gaps in the boarding, you're surprised to see that a couple of the lights are still on inside.
		 You reason that it's probably for some unseen workmen refurbishing the back rooms, and decide to move on to find a more interesting store.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR_CLOSED_NYAN_INFO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The establishment before you is one of the few in the Shopping Arcade that's not open for business.
		 The words 'Supplier Depot; bulk clothing sales and storage' are written in inviting yellow lettering above the entrance, but the windows are all boarded up, and there's a little 'closed' sign hanging in the doorway.
	</p>
	<p>
		This is definitely the place that Nyan told you about, and, peering through some of the gaps in the boarding, you see that a couple of the lights are still on inside.
		 Moving over to the door, you give it an experimental push, and discover that despite the sign, it's not locked.
		 You wonder if you should enter the Depot now, or come back at another time...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_EMPTY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From the long, wooden desk that runs parallel to the back wall, you can safely assume that this room was once used as a reception area.
		 Apart from that one piece of furniture, and a couple of empty crates stacked near the entrance, the place is completely empty.
		 The boards covering the windows block out most of the light from the Shopping Arcade, leaving this area illuminated primarily by two dim arcane-powered bulbs dangling from the ceiling.
	</p>
	<p>
		Besides the one that you just used to make your entrance, there's only one other door that leads out of this room, which is positioned behind the dust-covered reception desk.
		 The words 'Private: Staff Only' are printed on a metal sign that's affixed to it, but you're not sure if that's a recent addition, or a remnant of the time when this place was open to the public.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_EMPTY_STAFF_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The Depot's storage area is sure to be behind that door, and you wonder if you should continue through it now, or come back another time...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_EMPTY_STAFF_DOOR_UNLOCKING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You walk up to the door, flinching a little as one of the floorboards loudly creaks beneath your feet.
		 Stopping in your tracks, you wait for a moment to find out if anyone's heard your approach.
	</p>
	<p>
		Thankfully, there's nothing to be heard but silence, and after a minute, you continue towards the door.
		 Placing your [pc.hand] on the doorknob, you twist down and push forwards, finding that this door, much like the entrance, has been left unlocked.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you open the door, you find yourself looking down a long, dimly lit corridor, which appears to stretch to the very rear of the building.
		 On either side, you see several wide openings linking this passage to the Depot's storage areas.
		 The thing that draws your attention the most, however, is the the sound of a male's deep laughter echoing out from a room at the far end of the corridor.
		 You realise that there's no possibility of the occupants of this building hearing your arrival when they're making such a racket, and you confidently push the door fully open, leaving you with a clear path to the rest of the building.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_POPULATED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The long, wooden reception desk that runs parallel to the back wall has been sanded down and polished since the first time you saw it.
		 The walls, ceiling, and floor have all undergone a complete refurbishment, and where once there was a stack of empty boxes, you now see a few of the Depot's new clients talking with one other as they relax on a trio of plain green sofas.
	</p>
	<p>
		The brown-haired mouse-girl who's sitting behind the reception desk watches you through a pair of steel-framed glasses, and as you look her way, she smiles and calls out a greeting, before continuing with the paperwork in front of her.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_POPULATED_STAFF_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You know that the Depot's storage area is behind the door marked 'Private: Staff Only', and you wonder if you should ask the mouse-girl if you can go back there...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_POPULATED_STAFF_DOOR_UNLOCKING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to pay [wolfgang.name] another visit, you approach the mouse-girl receptionist,
		 [pc.speech(Hello, I was wondering if it would be possible to see [wolfgang.name].)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[femaleNPC.speech(Ah, you must be [pc.name]! [wolfgang.Name]'s already told me to let you through, so please go ahead!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The mouse-girl beckons for you to walk around to her side of the desk, giving you permission to come and go through the staff door as you please.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		This corridor runs from the Depot's reception area all the way to the back of the building.
		 On either side, several wide openings link this passage to the storage areas.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STORAGE_ROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing in a huge, double-height storage room.
		 Numerous metal shelving units, stacked full of countless wooden crates, are arranged in rows throughout the expansive area.
		 Most of these crates appear to have been firmly sealed shut, but there are several that you pass which appear to have already been half-opened...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STORAGE_ROOM_SEARCHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[style.italicsBad(You have already searched through all of the open crates in this room!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STORAGE_ROOM_SEARCHING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You doubt that it would be worth your time trying to open each and every crate to see what's inside, but checking the ones that appear to have already been half-opened would only take you a moment.
		 Deciding that you'll spend a few minutes to look through them, you start rummaging around to see what you find...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach the end of the corridor, you hear the deep rumble of a pair of male voices, occasionally interspersed with a roar of laughter, growing louder and louder.
		 You discover that the noise is coming from behind a frosted-glass door labelled as 'Supplier Offices'.
		 A long list of names is displayed beneath this, and you see that with the exception of the entry at the very bottom, reading 'Wolfgang & Karl', all the rest have been crossed out. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing no alternative but to make a bold entrance, you reach for the handle of the door, and, pushing it open, you step forwards.
		 Although the room that you enter was once quite clearly a waiting-area for the offices located down the short corridor in front of you, several desks, tables, sofas, and chairs have been dragged into this area in order to turn it into a haphazard hangout.
		 Numerous empty bottles of the beer 'Canine Crush' are scattered about all over the area, and countless empty pizza-boxes and takeaway cartons are piled up in one corner of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		The most striking feature in front of you, however, is the pair of black-and-brown-furred greater dobermann-morphs, who both instantly push their chairs back and jump to their feet as you enter.
		 The one closest to you is a little taller and more muscular than the other, and although they're both wearing black jeans, shirts, and heavy work-boots, this larger dobermann is sporting a pair of gold-framed aviators.
		 It's this larger of the two who's the first to speak, and he adopts a menacing pose as he growls,
		 [wolfgang.speech(Who the hell are you?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'm [pc.name], and I assume you're Wolfgang?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(So what if I am?! You've got some nerve barging in here uninvited! What the hell do you want?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You step forwards, wondering if it'd be better to try and convince this pair to give up peacefully, or to launch straight into fighting them...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_PACIFIED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach the end of the corridor, you hear the steady hum of numerous voices growing louder and louder.
		 You discover that the noise is coming from behind the familiar frosted-glass door labelled as 'Supplier Offices'.
		 The long list of names beneath that title have all been restored, and you can't help but smirk as you see that the pair 'Wolfgang & Karl' have been put at the very top this time around. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that this area is now safe for you to enter, you reach for the handle of the door, and, pushing it open, you step forwards into a very neat and orderly waiting area.
		 The room has been completely refurbished since the first time you saw it, and the haphazard arrangement of desks, tables, and chairs has been replaced by several clean sofas and coffee tables.
		 Walking forwards down the the short corridor in front of you, you look left and right at the names on each of the office doors that you pass.
		 Finally, you read the plaque 'Wolfgang & Karl: Security'.
	</p>
	<p>
		Grinning at the pair's self-appointed title, you reach out and knock the door, before pushing it open and stepping inside as you hear the familiar voice of [wolfgang.name] call out,
		 [wolfgang.speech(Enter!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Once again you find yourself standing before the pair of black-and-brown-furred greater dobermann-morphs, who both instantly push their chairs back and jump to their feet as you enter.
		 [wolfgang.Name] smirks as he sees that it's you,
		 [wolfgang.speech(Hello again [pc.name], what can we do for you this time?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_ENFORCER_REACTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach the end of the corridor, you hear the deep rumble of a pair of male voices, occasionally interspersed with a roar of laughter, growing louder and louder.
		 You discover that the noise is coming from behind a frosted-glass door labelled as 'Supplier Offices'.
		 A long list of names is displayed beneath this, and you see that with the exception of the entry at the very bottom, reading 'Wolfgang & Karl', all the rest have been crossed out. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing no alternative but to make a bold entrance, you reach for the handle of the door, and, pushing it open, you step forwards.
		 Although the room that you enter was once quite clearly a waiting-area for the offices located down the short corridor in front of you, several desks, tables, sofas, and chairs have been dragged into this area in order to turn it into a haphazard hangout.
		 Numerous empty bottles of the beer 'Canine Crush' are scattered about all over the area, and countless empty pizza-boxes and takeaway cartons are piled up in one corner of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		The most striking feature in front of you, however, is the pair of black-and-brown-furred greater dobermann-morphs, who both instantly push their chairs back and jump to their feet as you enter.
		 The one closest to you is a little taller and more muscular than the other, and although they're both wearing black jeans, shirts, and heavy work-boots, this larger dobermann is sporting a pair of gold-framed aviators.
		 It's this larger of the two who's the first to speak, and he adopts a menacing pose as he growls,
		 [wolfgang.speech(We both know that you Enforcers have nothing on us! Why don't you turn around and fuck off back to your cozy little desk job at your HQ?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That attitude isn't going to get you far with me,)]
		 you say, matching the dobermann's gaze as you step forwards,
		 [pc.speech(I assume you're Wolfgang?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(So what if I am?! You've got some nerve barging in here like this! What the hell do you Enforcers want this time?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder if it'd be better to use the fact that Wolfgang has mistaken you for an Enforcer to try and convince him to give up peacefully, or to launch straight into a fight...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach the end of the corridor, you hear the familiar rumbling of Wolfgang's and Karl's voices, occasionally interspersed with a roar of laughter, growing louder and louder.
		 The noise is once again coming from behind the frosted-glass door labelled as 'Supplier Offices'.
		 Coming to a halt, you look down again at the long list of crossed-out names that are displayed beneath that heading, with the pair 'Wolfgang & Karl' being the only one left intact. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing no alternative but to make a bold entrance, you reach for the handle of the door, and, pushing it open, you step forwards.
		 Although the room that you enter was once quite clearly a waiting-area for the offices located down the short corridor in front of you, several desks, tables, sofas, and chairs have been dragged into this area in order to turn it into a haphazard hangout.
		 Numerous empty bottles of the beer 'Canine Crush' are scattered about all over the area, and countless empty pizza-boxes and takeaway cartons are piled up in one corner of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		The pair of black-and-brown-furred greater dobermann-morphs, Wolfgang and Karl, instantly push their chairs back and jump to their feet as you enter.
		 Once again you note that Wolfgang is a little taller and more muscular than Karl, and although they're both wearing black jeans, shirts, and heavy work-boots, Wolfgang is sporting a pair of gold-framed aviators.
		 It's Wolfgang who's the first to speak once again, and he adopts a menacing pose as he growls,
		 [wolfgang.speech(You again?! What, didn't have enough fun the last time you were here?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(This time's different,)]
		 you state, clenching your fists as you glare at the dobermann.
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(Ah, you've been practising your cock-sucking for me, have you?)]
		 Karl mocks, before he and Wolfgang burst out laughing.
	</p>
	<p>
		You step forwards, wondering if it'd be better to try and convince this pair to give up peacefully, or to launch straight into fighting them...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_REPEAT_ENFORCER_REACTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach the end of the corridor, you hear the familiar rumbling of Wolfgang's and Karl's voices, occasionally interspersed with a roar of laughter, growing louder and louder.
		 The noise is once again coming from behind the frosted-glass door labelled as 'Supplier Offices'.
		 Coming to a halt, you look down again at the long list of crossed-out names that are displayed beneath that heading, with the pair 'Wolfgang & Karl' being the only one left intact. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing no alternative but to make a bold entrance, you reach for the handle of the door, and, pushing it open, you step forwards.
		 Although the room that you enter was once quite clearly a waiting-area for the offices located down the short corridor in front of you, several desks, tables, sofas, and chairs have been dragged into this area in order to turn it into a haphazard hangout.
		 Numerous empty bottles of the beer 'Canine Crush' are scattered about all over the area, and countless empty pizza-boxes and takeaway cartons are piled up in one corner of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		The pair of black-and-brown-furred greater dobermann-morphs, Wolfgang and Karl, instantly push their chairs back and jump to their feet as you enter.
		 Once again you note that Wolfgang is a little taller and more muscular than Karl, and although they're both wearing black jeans, shirts, and heavy work-boots, Wolfgang is sporting a pair of gold-framed aviators.
		 It's Wolfgang who's the first to speak once again, and he adopts a menacing pose as he growls,
		 [wolfgang.speech(You again?! What, didn't have enough fun the last time you were here?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(This time's different,)]
		 you state, clenching your fists as you glare at the dobermann.
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(Ah, you've been practising your cock-sucking for me, have you? You Enforcers should strive to be able to take my knot!)]
		 Karl mocks, before he and Wolfgang burst out laughing.
	</p>
	<p>
		You step forwards, wondering if it'd be better to try and convince this pair to give up peacefully, or to launch straight into fighting them...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_CONVINCE_THEM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it would be a good idea to try diplomacy before the situation resorts to violence, you explain the situation to Wolfgang,
		 [pc.speech(I've heard that you and Karl intimidated and threatened all the other clothing suppliers that used to work here.
		 I don't know how you managed to get away with this for so long, but I'm here to put an end to it.
		 You and Karl both need to agree to allow the other suppliers back.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As he hears the sincerity in your voice, Wolfgang narrows his eyes and snarls,
		 [wolfgang.speech(And why would we do that?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Because your inability to provide enchanted clothing to the stores here in the Arcade is unacceptable!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Hah!)]
		 Wolfgang exclaims,
		 [wolfgang.speech(And here I was getting worried that you had something on us!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(This has all been a huge waste of our time,)]
		 Karl growls from the other side of the room,
		 [karl.speech(I want to know what you're going to offer us as compensation.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Good point Karl,)]
		 Wolfgang snarls,
		 [wolfgang.speech(I think five-hundred flames ought to do the trick. Or maybe you'd like to pay another way...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wolfgang and Karl both grin hungrily at you, and as their lecherous gaze roams up and down over your body, you realise that they aren't going to let you simply walk away from this...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_CONVINCE_THEM_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding once again to try diplomacy before the situation resorts to violence, you explain the situation to Wolfgang,
		 [pc.speech(As I said last time, I know that you and Karl intimidated and threatened all the other clothing suppliers that used to work here, and I'm here to put an end to it.
		 You and Karl both need to agree to allow the other suppliers back.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As he hears the sincerity in your voice, Wolfgang narrows his eyes and snarls,
		 [wolfgang.speech(And have you got a real reason as to why we should do that this time?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Because your actions are immoral, and you're hurting the business of all the clothing stores here in the Arcade!)]
		 you reason.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Hah!)]
		 Wolfgang exclaims,
		 [wolfgang.speech(And here I was getting worried that you'd found some dirt on us!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(Yet again, this has all been a huge waste of our time,)]
		 Karl growls from the other side of the room,
		 [karl.speech(I want to know what you're going to offer us as compensation.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Good point Karl,)]
		 Wolfgang snarls,
		 [wolfgang.speech(I think five-hundred flames ought to do the trick. Or maybe you'd like to pay another way...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wolfgang and Karl both grin hungrily at you, and as their lecherous gaze roams up and down over your body, you realise that they aren't going to let you simply walk away from this...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_PAID_OFF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to get into a fight, and definitely not willing to offer your body to these thugs, you hand over five-hundred flames to Wolfgang,
		 [pc.speech(There you go. I'll be leaving now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Hah! Fine, get out of here while I'm still in a good mood!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not needing to be told twice, you turn around and make your exit, hurrying down the corridor and escaping out into the safety of the Shopping Arcade...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_ENFORCER_BLUFF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to make the most of the fact that Wolfgang has mistaken you for an Enforcer, you put on your most serious look as you stare him down,
		 [pc.speech(Did you really think you'd get away with openly intimidating and threatening the other suppliers?
		 We couldn't act before due to a lack of witnesses who were willing to testify against you, but that's changed.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Bullshit!)]
		 Wolfgang aggressively snaps, but as he speaks, you detect the faint hint of worry in his voice,
		 [wolfgang.speech(If you had anything on us, there'd be a lot more of you, and we'd be in cuffs already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That's very observant of you, but I'm afraid you've come to the wrong conclusion,)]
		 you grin, encouraged to continue with your bluff by the slight wavering in Wolfgang's voice,
		 [pc.speech(I'm alone because we thought it would work out better for everyone if I came to offer you a deal.
		 In exchange for not arresting you both, you're going to agree to let the other suppliers move back in.
		 We Enforcers don't have a problem with you two continuing to work out of here, but one more report about intimidation, blackmail, or assault, and you two can live out the rest of your days as slaves.
		 Understood?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite their best efforts to maintain their composure, there's a noticeable look of worry in both of the dobermanns' eyes.
		 It's obvious that they're guilty, and the threat of enslavement, combined with the offer of an easy way out, seems to be just enough to convince these thugs to give up,
		 [wolfgang.speech(So we just need to let the other suppliers back, and all this goes away?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That's right,)]
		 you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Fine,)]
		 Wolfgang sighs,
		 [wolfgang.speech(it was getting pretty dull around here anyway...
		 We'll let the other suppliers back, but this isn't an admission of guilt!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Of course,)]
		 you smile, thrilled that your bluff worked so perfectly,
		 [pc.speech(We Enforcers don't have much time on our hands these days, so as part of this deal, you two are going to contact the other suppliers, apologise to them, and tell them they can come back.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Hah! So that's the real reason you're offering us this deal, is it? Not enough of you to spare to come and arrest us?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You say nothing, and after a moment, Wolfgang continues,
		 [wolfgang.speech(Fine! It doesn't look like we have much of a choice in the matter, anyway. Now, is that all?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		There's nothing else that needs to be done, except report back to Nyan of your success...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_OFFER_BODY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight, and unwilling to hand over any of your money, you bite your [pc.lip] and allow your gaze to roam up and down over Wolfgang's powerful, muscular body,
		 [pc.speech(I'm sure we can work something out...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The two dobermanns move forwards, grinning lustfully as they reach out to grope to fondle your body.
		 You let out a small [pc.moan] as Wolfgang presses up against you, grinding his huge bulge against your [pc.leg].
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(I'm using [pc.her] mouth,)]
		 Karl growls as he reaches up to take hold of your shoulders.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(That's fine with me,)]
		 Wolfgang replies, stepping back a little and allowing Karl to push you down onto all fours.
	</p>
	<p>
		You look back to see Wolfgang kneel down behind you, and can't help but gasp as he grabs hold of your [pc.hips+] and roughly pulls you into his groin.
		 Karl drops to his knees in front of you, and, turning your head forwards, you find yourself staring at the huge bulge between his legs.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Ready for a rough fucking, slut?)]
		 Wolfgang growls, causing you to let out another [pc.moan] in response...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_ENFORCER_THANKS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling more than a little turned-on at the thought of being fucked while wearing an Enforcer's uniform, you bite your [pc.lip] and allow your gaze to roam up and down over Wolfgang's powerful, muscular body,
		 [pc.speech(Well, this all went a lot smoother than I was expecting. How about I show you boys how thankful I am for your cooperation...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The two dobermanns move forwards, grinning lustfully as they instantly pick up on what you mean.
		 You let out a small [pc.moan] as Wolfgang presses up against you, grinding his huge bulge against your [pc.leg] as both he and Karl start to grope to fondle your body.
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(I'm using [pc.her] mouth,)]
		 Karl growls as he reaches up to take hold of your shoulders, before snarling into your ear,
		 [karl.speech(You aren't the first Enforcer to suck my cock, bitch.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(That's fine with me,)]
		 Wolfgang replies, stepping back a little and allowing Karl to push you down onto all-fours,
		 [wolfgang.speech(I wonder if [pc.she]'s going to be as tight as the last one...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You look back to see Wolfgang kneel down behind you, and can't help but gasp as he grabs hold of your [pc.hips+] and roughly pulls you into his groin.
		 Karl drops to his knees in front of you, and, turning your head forwards, you find yourself staring at the huge bulge between his legs.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Ready for a rough fucking, Enforcer slut?)]
		 Wolfgang growls, causing you to let out another [pc.moan] in response...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_VICTORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wolfgang and Karl stagger back, before collapsing down onto a very shabby-looking sofa.
		 Looking up and you and panting, Wolfgang begs,
		 [wolfgang.speech(N-No more! Please!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smirking, you step forwards, looking down at the defeated pair as you make your demands known,
		 [pc.speech(Unless you want me to keep coming back and beating you both into submission, you're going to find and apologise to the other suppliers, and let them come back to work here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Fine! We'll tell them to come back! Just... No more!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You can tell from the sincerity in Wolfgang's voice that he means what he says, and you breathe a sigh of relief as you realise that your work here is done.
		 You could leave and let Nyan know of your success right away, or perhaps take this opportunity to have a little fun...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_VICTORY_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You aren't interested in having any sort of sexual experience with these two losers, so you turn around and walk out of the office.
		 Travelling back down the Depot's long corridor, it only takes a moment before you're walking through the reception area and stepping back out into the Shopping Arcade.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_VICTORY_FUCK_THEM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The sight of these two dobermanns collapsed down before you is too much for you to resist.
		 Deciding to have some fun, you step forwards, grinning,
		 [pc.speech(Alright boys, unless you want to keep on fighting, you're going to get down on all fours and present yourselves to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wolfgang and Karl both let out a distressed groan, but, realising that they have no choice in the matter, reluctantly do as you say.
		 Dropping down onto all fours, the two dobermanns shuffle around to present their asses towards you.
		 As they do this, the power of your arcane aura starts to overwhelm their initial reluctance, and by the time they're fully in position, you hear their concerned groans quickly turn into lewd panting.
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping down onto your knees behind them, you reach forwards and grope their asses, grinning to yourself as they respond by letting out a desperate whine,
		 [pc.speech(Good boys! It's time to have some fun!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_VICTORY_SUB_FUCKED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The sight of these two dobermanns collapsed down before you is too much for you to resist.
		 Deciding to have some fun, you step forwards, grinning,
		 [pc.speech(Alright boys, seeing as you've both been so good and agreed to do as you're told, I think you deserve a little reward!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wolfgang and Karl both let out a cautious groan, unsure of what exactly you mean.
		 Hoping to clear things up for them, you step forwards, before dropping down onto all fours and [pc.moaning],
		 [pc.speech(I'll let you both decide which of you gets my mouth, and which of you gets to fuck me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(I'm using [pc.her] mouth,)]
		 Karl quickly growls as he pushes himself up off the sofa.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(That's fine with me,)]
		 Wolfgang replies, following his partner's lead as he shuffles forwards on his knees to position himself behind you,
		 [wolfgang.speech(this is a pleasant surprise...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You look back and gasp as Wolfgang grabs hold of your [pc.hips+] and roughly pulls you into his groin.
		 Karl drops to his knees in front of you, and, turning your head forwards, you find yourself staring at the huge bulge between his legs.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(You may have beaten us, but I'm not going to hold back from giving you a rough fucking,)]
		 Wolfgang growls, causing you to let out a delighted [pc.moan] in response.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Good boys!)]
		 you cry,
		 [pc.speech(Don't hold back from having your fun now!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_DEFEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to continue fighting, you stagger back and collapse down onto a very shabby sofa,
		 [pc.speech(No more! I-I can't go on!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The two dobermanns move towards you, grinning lustfully as they gaze down at your vulnerable body.
		 Wolfgang is the first to make a move, reaching down to grab hold of your [pc.arm], before pulling you off of the sofa and down onto all fours.
		 Overwhelmed by the arousing power of your aura, you find yourself letting out a small [pc.moan] as Karl growls,
		[karl.speech(I'm using [pc.her] mouth.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(That's fine with me,)]
		 Wolfgang replies, kneeling down behind you before grabbing hold of your [pc.hips+] and roughly grinding his huge bulge against your [pc.ass+].
		 Karl drops to his knees in front of you, and, turning your head forwards, you find yourself staring at the huge bulge between his legs.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Ready for a rough fucking, slut?)]
		 Wolfgang growls, causing you to let out another [pc.moan] in response...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_PACIFIED_FUCK_THEM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The sight of the two big, strong dobermanns is too much for you to resist, and you feel your dominant side taking control as you step forwards, grinning,
		 [pc.speech(I'm here to make sure that you boys are behaving. We wouldn't want there to be any trouble kicking off because of you two, now, would we?
		 I think that , you're going to get down on all fours and present yourselves to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(We haven't been causing any trouble,)]
		 Wolfgang responds.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not satisfied with his response, you step forwards, tracing your [pc.fingers] over [wolfgang.name]'s muscular abdomen, before dropping your [pc.hand] down to grab the huge bulge between his legs, 
		 [pc.speech(I really don't know if I can trust you... I think I'm going to need you both to prove how good you are these days. So get down on all fours and present yourselves to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wolfgang and Karl both let out a distressed groan, but, realising that they have no choice in the matter, reluctantly do as you say.
		 Dropping down onto all fours, the two dobermanns shuffle around to present their asses towards you.
		 As they do this, the power of your arcane aura starts to overwhelm their initial reluctance, and by the time they're fully in position, you hear their concerned groans quickly turn into lewd panting.
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping down onto your knees behind them, you reach forwards and grope their asses, grinning to yourself as they respond by letting out a desperate whine,
		 [pc.speech(Good boys! It's time to have some fun!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_PACIFIED_SUB_FUCKED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The sight of the two big, strong dobermanns is too much for you to resist, and you step forwards, grinning,
		 [pc.speech(Alright boys, seeing as you've both been so good recently, I think you deserve a little reward!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wolfgang and Karl both let out a hungry growl, grinning as you step forwards and drop down onto all fours before them,
		 [pc.speech(I'll let you both decide which of you gets my mouth, and which of you gets to fuck me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(I'm using [pc.her] mouth,)]
		 Karl quickly growls.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(That's fine with me,)]
		 Wolfgang replies, dropping to his knees to position himself behind you,
		 [wolfgang.speech(this is a pleasant surprise...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You look back and gasp as Wolfgang grabs hold of your [pc.hips+] and roughly pulls you into his groin, before grinding his huge bulge against your [pc.ass+].
		 Karl drops to his knees in front of you, and, turning your head forwards, you find yourself staring at an equally impressive bulge between his legs.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(You're desperate for a good rough fucking, aren't you bitch?)]
		 Wolfgang growls, causing you to let out a delighted [pc.moan] in response.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Good boys!)]
		 you cry,
		 [pc.speech(Don't hold back from having your fun now!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OFFICE_PACIFIED_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I was just dropping by to make sure that you two are behaving yourselves.
		 You haven't been getting into any trouble recently, have you?)]
		 you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(No, everything's fine here,)]
		 Wolfgang responds,
		 [wolfgang.speech(We decided to drop the whole clothing supply thing, and just focus on security instead.
		 It's a lot more fun this way...)]
	</p><p>
		[pc.speech(Well, don't let me hear that you two have been causing trouble again, ok?)]
		 you say, before turning around and making your exit.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_WILLING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wolfgang steps back, sinking down onto a nearby sofa as he grins,
		 [wolfgang.speech(You're a good fuck, slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Karl likewise moves away from you, grabbing a bottle of Canine Crush and twisting off the cap as he grins,
		 [karl.speech(Come back any time you want another taste of my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You grin at the dobermanns, and after getting your things together, you move towards the exit.
		 Turning around in the doorway, you flash them a smile, before reminding them of your deal,
		 [pc.speech(I hope you'll be good boys now! Contact those other suppliers as soon as you can!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wolfgang and Karl agree once again to do as you ask, and, satisfied that your work here is done, you move to make your exit.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_WILLING_DOMMED_THEM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You step back, allowing Wolfgang and Karl to crawl away and collapse onto to a nearby sofa,
		 [pc.speech(You two were pretty good fucks!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You grin at the dobermanns, and after getting your things together, you move towards the exit.
		 Turning around in the doorway, you flash them a smile, before reminding them of your deal,
		 [pc.speech(I hope you'll be good boys now! Contact those other suppliers as soon as you can!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wolfgang and Karl agree once again to do as you ask, and, satisfied that your work here is done, you move to make your exit.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_WILLING_PACIFIED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wolfgang steps back, sinking down onto a nearby sofa as he grins,
		 [wolfgang.speech(You're a good fuck, slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Karl likewise moves away from you, grabbing a bottle of Canine Crush and twisting off the cap as he grins,
		 [karl.speech(Come back any time you want another taste of my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You grin at the dobermanns, and after getting your things together, you move towards the exit.
		 Turning around in the doorway, you flash them a smile as you say farewell,
		 [pc.speech(You two carry on being good boys now! I'll see you soon!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_WILLING_DOMMED_THEM_PACIFIED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You step back, allowing Wolfgang and Karl to crawl away and collapse onto to a nearby sofa,
		 [pc.speech(Good boys! You two sure are good fucks!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You grin at the dobermanns, and after getting your things together, you move towards the exit.
		 Turning around in the doorway, you flash them a smile as you say farewell,
		 [pc.speech(You two carry on being good boys now! I'll see you soon!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_FUCKED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wolfgang steps back, sinking down onto a nearby sofa as he grins,
		 [wolfgang.speech(You're a good fuck, slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Karl likewise moves away from you, grabbing a bottle of Canine Crush and twisting off the cap as he grins,
		 [karl.speech(Come back any time you want another taste of my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Completely exhausted both from your fight and the rough sex, you hurriedly get your things together and move towards the exit.
		 The dobermanns continue to bombard you with lewd comments and wolf-whistles as you rush out of the door, and with their taunting laughter ringing in your ears, you hurry down the corridor and back out into the Shopping Arcade.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
</dialogue>
