<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OUTSIDE_NIGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking through the area of Dominion known as 'Nightlife', which is currently fully living up to its name. The bright colours of neon signs join with the soft glow of lampposts to illuminate the street before you, which is packed with crowds of revellers. Many of these people are quite clearly drunk, and noisily shout and make lewd comments at those around them as they stagger between the many clubs and bars that fill this area.
	</p>
	<p>
		Every now and then, you pass couples, and sometimes even groups, who have given in to their alcohol-fuelled lust and are publicly having sex with one another. The Enforcers who patrol this area don't seem to care one bit about these lewd displays, and sometimes even to stop to watch the exhibitionists going at it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking past these crowds to the establishments which have attracted them, you see all sorts of different bars and clubs open for business. The vast majority of them, however, seem to either be completely full, or to have huge queues trailing out into the streets.
	</p>
	<p>
		Out of all the establishments that you pass, the only one which you'd have any hope of getting into tonight is the nightclub, 'The Watering Hole'. Although it looks to be just as good as any of the other clubs in this area, it's positioned near the far end of the street, which makes it a little less popular with the crowds of casual clubbers.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OUTSIDE_NIGHT_STORM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking through the area of Dominion known as 'Nightlife', which is currently deserted due to the ongoing arcane storm. The bright colours of neon signs join with the soft glow of lampposts to illuminate the empty street before you.
	</p>
	<p>
		While all the bars and clubs that fill this area are still open for business, the vast majority of them seem to already be completely full. The only place which looks to still have some room left is the nightclub, 'The Watering Hole'.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OUTSIDE_DAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking through the area of Dominion known as 'Nightlife', which, due to the fact that it's currently day time, is all but deserted. The clubs and bars that line the streets are all closed, and the only people walking about in this area are those that are on their way to other parts of the city.
	</p>
	<p>
		Reading one of the club's signs as you pass, you see that all of the establishments in this area open at seven in the evening, and close at five the following morning. If you wanted to visit one of the clubs or bars, you'd have to come back at that time.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OUTSIDE_DAY_STORM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking through the area of Dominion known as 'Nightlife', which, due to the fact that there's an ongoing arcane storm, is completely deserted. The clubs and bars that line the streets are all closed, and there isn't a single non-demon in sight.
	</p>
	<p>
		Reading one of the club's signs as you pass, you see that all of the establishments in this area open at seven in the evening, and close at five the following morning. If you wanted to visit one of the clubs or bars, you'd have to come back at that time.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="OUTSIDE_LIGHTS_OUT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[style.boldYellow(Lights Out)]
		<br/>
		A neon sign reading 'Lights Out' is positioned above a short, steep staircase that leads down to a basement bar. A second neon sign declares that the bar's opening hours are from
		#IF(game.isHourBetween(18, 4))
			 [style.colourMinorGood([unit.time(18)]-[unit.time(4)])], and as such the bar is currently [style.colourGood(open)].
		#ELSE
			 [style.colourMinorBad([unit.time(18)]-[unit.time(4)])], and as such the bar is currently [style.colourBad(closed)].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Interior: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_ENTRANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Walking up to the entrance of the club, you push the front door open and step inside. As it swings shut behind you, you find yourself standing in a large, well-lit entrance hall, and before you, a winding queue leads up to a pair of white doors. The walls have been decorated with savannah-themed murals, which, combined with the club's name 'The Watering Hole', as well as the pair of imposing zebra-boy bouncers standing guard at the front of the queue, gives the club an African theme.
	</p>
	<p>
		The larger of the two zebra-boys catches sight of you as you enter, and, calling out over the faint background bass of the club's music system, he addresses you, [jules.speech(Hey, you at the back! You can skip the queue if you want!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		From the amused smile on his face, you can tell that he's trying to trick you, but before you can offer a reply, he continues, [jules.speech(All you've got to do is come over here and suck my cock!)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_DEMON)
		<p>
			Before you can react, the other zebra-boy angrily punches his companion and berates him, [style.speechMasculine(What the fuck are you saying, Jules?! Can't you see [pc.sheIs] a demon?!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[jules.speech(Ah, come on, I'm just teasing [pc.herHim],)] Jules laughs, before turning back towards you. [jules.speech(No harm meant!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			It looks like you'll have to join the back of the queue and wait in line to get into the club, which you guess will take about half an hour. Then again, you could use your status as a demon to cut the queue, or even take Jules up on his offer...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			The other zebra-boy sighs and crosses his arms, before turning to his companion and berating him, [style.speechMasculine(Come on Jules, knock it off. Kruger's already warned you about scaring the customers off.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[jules.speech(Ah, come on, I'm just teasing [pc.herHim],)] Jules laughs, before turning back towards you. [jules.speech(No harm meant!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			It looks like you'll have to join the back of the queue and wait in line to get into the club, which you guess will take about half an hour. Then again, if you didn't want to wait, you could always take Jules up on his offer...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_ENTRANCE_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Walking up to the entrance of the club once again, you push the front door open and step inside. As it swings shut behind you, you find yourself standing in a large, well-lit entrance hall, and before you, a winding queue leads up to a pair of white doors. The walls have been decorated with savannah-themed murals, which, combined with the club's name 'The Watering Hole', as well as the pair of imposing zebra-boy bouncers standing guard at the front of the queue, gives the club an African theme.
	</p>
	<p>
		The usual pair of zebra-boys are standing guard at the front of the queue, and as you enter, Jules sees you and calls out over the faint background bass of the club's music system,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_suckedJulesCock))
			 [jules.speech(Hey, my little cocksucker's back! Come over here and get on your knees, and you can skip the queue again!)]
		#ELSE
			 [jules.speech(Hey, it's you again! You gonna suck my cock this time, or what?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_DEMON)
		<p>
			Before you can react, the other zebra-boy angrily berates Jules, [style.speechMasculine(You're going to get the two of us fired, you fucking idiot! Can't you see [pc.sheIs] a demon?!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[jules.speech(Relax, man, [pc.she] knows I'm just teasing [pc.herHim],)] Jules laughs.
		</p>
		<p>
			It looks like you'll have to join the back of the queue and wait in line to get into the club, which you guess will take about half an hour. Then again, you could use your status as a demon to cut the queue, or even take Jules up on his offer...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			The other zebra-boy leans back against the wall and sighs, [style.speechMasculine(Damn it, Jules...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			It looks like you'll have to join the back of the queue and wait in line to get into the club, which you guess will take about half an hour. Then again, if you didn't want to wait, you could always take Jules up on his offer...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_ENTRANCE_START_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to take Jules up on his offer, you cut the queue and [pc.walk] up to the large zebra-boy, before telling him that you'll suck his cock.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_DEMON)
			[jules.speech(Hah! I told you I'd get my cock sucked tonight, and by a demon no less!)]
		#ELSE
			[jules.speech(Hah! I told you I'd get my cock sucked tonight!)]
		#ENDIF
		 Jules happily states to his partner, before turning back towards you and commanding, [jules.speech(Go on then, slut, get down on your knees.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you drop down onto your knees in front of Jules. You hear several of the people waiting in the queue behind you starting to gasp and laugh as you shuffle forwards and prepare to suck the zebra-boy's cock.
	</p>
	<p>
		[jules.speech(Get it out for me,)] Jules commands, thrusting his hips forwards.
	</p>
	<p>
		You quickly move to do as you're told, and happily pull down his black jeans. Thanks to the pair of crotchless briefs that Jules is wearing, your move results in your face being just [unit.sizes] away from his huge, rapidly-hardening horse-cock. Without any warning, the zebra-boy bucks his hips forwards, slapping his fat, ebony shaft against your face as he lets out a triumphant laugh, [jules.speech(Hah! Now let's find out how good you are at sucking cock!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_ENTRANCE_JULES_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself back at the entrance to the club, you
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_fuckedJules))
			 can't help but remember the 'proper fuck' Jules gave you in his office.
		#ELSE
			 remember Jules's offer of giving you a 'proper fuck'.
		#ENDIF
		 Deciding that the zebra-boy's fat cock is what you need right now, you [pc.step] out through the doors and immediately catch his eye.
	</p>
	<p>
		[jules.speech(Leaving already?)] he asks, [jules.speech(Hey, how about another blowjob some time? You're not half bad at giving head.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Walking] over to Jules, you tell him that giving him a blowjob isn't going to cut it, and that a 'proper fuck' is what you need right now.
	</p>
	<p>
		[jules.speech(Hey, cover for me for ten minutes while I bang this slut,)] Jules says to his colleague, before taking you by the [pc.hand(true)] and leading you over to a nearby door marked as 'Staff Only'.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculine(For fuck's sake,)] the other zebra-boy sighs as Jules leads you into a small, dingy office. Calling out after you as the door swings shut, the bouncer shouts, [style.speechMasculine(Don't leave a mess in there this time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Dominantly pulling you into his chest, Jules greedily gropes your body and grunts in a deep voice, [jules.speech(Time to give you a proper fucking, slut.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_JULES_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having finished sucking his cock, you stand up in front of Jules, who grins at you as he steps to one side in order to let you pass.
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_fuckedJules))
			 [jules.speech(Good job, slut. Go on in, and if you can't find someone to fuck, then come and let me know and I'll give you a proper fuck again.)]
		#ELSE
			 [jules.speech(Good job, slut. Go on in, I'm sure you'll find plenty more cocks to service inside. If not, come and let me know and I'll give you a proper fuck.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_ENTRANCE_PASSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing beside the pair of white doors which lead back out into the club's entrance hall. From here you could choose to take your leave, or instead turn around and head back into the club.
	</p>
	#IF(!flags.hasFlag(FLAG_fuckedJulesTonight))
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_fuckedJules))
			<p>
				Having been given a 'proper fuck' by Jules on a previous occasion, you could return to the zebra-boy bouncer and tell him that you want a repeat performance...
			</p>
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_suckedJulesCock))
			<p>
				Remembering that Jules had offered to give you a 'proper fuck' after giving him a blowjob, you could return to the zebra-boy bouncer and tell him that you want him...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_ENTRANCE_WAITING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you're definitely <i>not</i> going to suck Jules's cock, you step forwards and take your place at the back of the queue.
	</p>
	<p>
		It takes about thirty minutes before you're standing before the pair of zebra-boy bouncers. After just a minute more, Jules steps to one side in order to let you pass. [jules.speech(Go on in then.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_ENTRANCE_SKIP_QUEUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to take advantage of your status as a demon, you stride forwards and coldly ask Jules if he has any idea who you are.
	</p>
	<p>
		[jules.speech(Hey, I was just joking, I didn't mean to offend you,)] the zebra-boy sheepishly replies. Realising that he might be in serious trouble, he steps aside and waves you on through, saying as he does so, [jules.speech(I'm sorry, please go on in and have a good evening.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_ENTRANCE_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping through the double doors, you enter the club proper, which you discover to be absolutely packed with people of all different races. The chatter, laughter, and shouting from the crowd is joined by loud, bassy background music, making it very hard to make out what anyone's saying unless you're standing right beside them.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like the entrance hall, the main interior looks to have an African theme to it, and although the lights are very dim, you can clearly see zebra-stripes, leopard-spots, and savannah-style trees painted onto the walls. The floor beneath your feet is covered in light wooden boards, which, combined with the light blue colour of the high ceiling, gives the club a spacious feel to it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although you can't directly see it through the crowds in front of you, a wooden sign hanging from the ceiling on the far side of the club's huge interior tells you where the bar is. You wonder if you should go straight there and get a drink, or try to find someone to flirt with first...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_JULES_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(jules.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			[jules.speech(Fuck, I needed that tonight. You're a decent lay, slut,)] Jules grunts as he brings an end to things.
		#ELSE
			[jules.speech(You're done already?! Fuck, you're a lousy lay, slut,)] Jules grunts in annoyance as you bring an end to things before he's had the chance to orgasm.
		#ENDIF
		 After quickly using some wet wipes to clean himself off, he pulls on his clothes and states, [jules.speech(I've got to get back to work, and I can't leave you in here. Hurry up and get ready.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you quickly get your things back in order, before exiting the dingy office via the same door through which you entered. Giving your [pc.ass+] a hard slap as he follows you out, Jules returns to his place at the doors to the club.
	</p>
	<p>
		[jules.speech(Go on, you probably want a drink or something after that,)] Jules says to you, before holding open the door and gesturing for you to head inside.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculine(How romantic,)] the other zebra-boy sarcastically chuckles.
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as Jules says, you pass him by and enter the club once again. The chatter, laughter, and shouting from the crowd is joined by loud, bassy background music, making it very hard to make out what anyone's saying unless you're standing right beside them.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like the entrance hall, the main interior looks to have an African theme to it, and although the lights are very dim, you can clearly see zebra-stripes, leopard-spots, and savannah-style trees painted onto the walls. The floor beneath your feet is covered in light wooden boards, which, combined with the light blue colour of the high ceiling, gives the club a spacious feel to it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although you can't directly see it through the crowds in front of you, a wooden sign hanging from the ceiling on the far side of the club's huge interior tells you where the bar is. You wonder if you should go straight there and get a drink, or try to find someone else to have some more fun with tonight...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Main club content: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_MAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The interior of 'The Watering Hole' is absolutely packed with people of all different races. The chatter, laughter, and shouting from the crowd is joined by loud, bassy background music, making it very hard to make out what anyone's saying unless you're standing right beside them.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like the entrance hall, the main interior looks to have an African theme to it, and although the lights are very dim, you can clearly see zebra-stripes, leopard-spots, and savannah-style trees painted onto the walls. The floor beneath your feet is covered in light wooden boards, which, combined with the light blue colour of the high ceiling, gives the club a spacious feel to it.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEARCH_GENDER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		There are so many different sorts of people in the club that you're sure of being able to find the type of person you want. First you need to decide what gender you'd like your partner to be...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEARCH_RACE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having decided upon the gender of the person you'd like to spend the night with, you now need to figure out what race your partner should be...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEARCH_GENERATE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having decided upon the sort of person you'd like to find, you set about searching through the bustling crowds of clubbers. Before long, you catch sight of [npc.a_raceFull(true)] standing all alone; just the sort of person you were looking for! Walking up to [npc.herHim], you introduce yourself, and [npc.she] smiles at you as [npc.she] replies,
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(O-Oh, h-hello. I'm [npc.name]. I came here with a friend, but they left to go dancing...)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Hi! I'm [npc.name]! This club's really great, isn't it?)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Hello! I'm [npc.name]! I haven't seen you here before!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		The two of you chat for a little while, and it soon becomes apparent that [npc.name] would like to spend [npc.her] time with you. With your new partner in tow, you wonder where you should head to next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_CONTACTS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although there's a seemingly endless supply of new people to meet in the club, you find yourself wanting to spend some more time with one of your previous partners. With this thought in mind, you start looking through the crowds to see if you can find your friend...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_FIND_CONTACT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Before long, you catch sight of [npc.a_raceFull(true)] standing all alone, and as you approach, you see that it's [npc.name]; just the person you were looking for! Walking up to [npc.herHim], you say hello, and [npc.she] happily smiles at you as [npc.she] recognises you from before.
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(O-Oh, [pc.name]! Hi! H-How are you doing? I came here with a friend, but they left me standing alone again...)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech([pc.Name]! Hi again! How are you doing?!)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Oh, [pc.name]! Hi! How are you?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		The two of you chat for a little while, and it soon becomes apparent that [npc.name] would like to spend some of [npc.her] time with you once again. With your familiar partner in tow, you wonder where you should head to next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_IMPORT_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can import any of your previously exported characters in order to add them to your contacts list. Once imported, this character will show up in your 'Contacts (as dom)' list.
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>You can export any character in the game by viewing their character sheet and pressing the little export button in the bottom-right of the screen.</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_IMPORT_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can import any of your previously exported characters in order to add them to your contacts list. Once imported, this character will show up in your 'Contacts (as sub)' list.
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>You can export any character in the game by viewing their character sheet and pressing the little export button in the bottom-right of the screen.</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_PARTNER_LEAVES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Completely fed up with your rude behaviour, [npc.name]
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN lets out a sigh, before casting [npc.her] [npc.eyes] to the floor and stuttering, [npc.speech(Y-You're not very nice. I-I'm going to go and find my friend. B-Bye...)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN crosses [npc.her] [npc.arms] and glares angrily at you. [npc.speech(You're a real [pc.bitch], you know that, right?!)]
			#ELSE rolls [npc.her] [npc.eyes] and sighs, [npc.speech(I'm out of here. You're no fun at all.)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can say anything to change [npc.her] mind, [npc.name] turns around and dashes off into the crowd. Letting out a sigh, you hope that you'll have better luck with the next one...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_PARTNER_TOO_WASTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] has had far too much to drink, and, stumbling over to one side, she trips and collapses to the ground. As you move to help [npc.herHim], you hear a shrill voice call out behind you, [genericFemale.speech([npc.Name]! Are you ok?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Rushing past you, [npc.namePos] friend kneels down and starts helping [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] [npc.feet]. You move to help [npc.namePos] friend, and the two of you drag [npc.herHim] over towards the nearest seating area, before placing [npc.herHim] down on an unoccupied sofa. Turning to face you, [npc.her] friend sighs, [genericFemale.speech(Thanks for the help. This isn't the first time [npc.nameHas] been in this situation. I'll stay with [npc.herHim] and help [npc.herHim] sober up. Maybe you'll get to have a better time with [npc.herHim] next time?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As there's not much more you can do to help, you say goodbye to [npc.namePos] friend, before returning to the area where [npc.she] collapsed. Maybe you should try to avoid getting your next partner into that sort of state...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_MAIN_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You lean in towards [npc.name], and, shouting out over the background noise in order to make yourself heard, spend the next few minutes talking with [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TALK_CONTENT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN[npc.She] seems to be a little shy, resulting in you doing most of the talking.
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN[npc.She] acts in a very confident manner, and ends up shouting over you a few times in [npc.her] excitement.
			#ELSE[npc.She] listens attentively to what you have to say, before happily continuing the conversation.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		 After exchanging opinions on the state of the club and how crowded it is, [npc.name] ends up talking a little about
		#IF npc.getHistory()==OCCUPATION_NPC_UNEMPLOYED || npc.getHistory()==OCCUPATION_NPC_UNIVERSITY_STUDENT
		#THEN [npc.her] friends and some of the things they get up to in Dominion.
		#ELSE [npc.her] job as [npc.a_jobName].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] seems to appreciate the fact that you're taking the time to get to know [npc.herHim] a little better, and as the conversation comes to an end, [npc.she] smiles happily at you and asks what you'd like to do next.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_MAIN_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You step up close to [npc.name], and, in order to make yourself heard over the background noise, lean in towards [npc.herHim] and raise your voice as you offer [npc.herHim] a compliment on [npc.her] appearance.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_FLIRT_CONTENT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN[npc.She] instantly blushes as [npc.she] hears what you've just said, and, shuffling [npc.her] [npc.feet], [npc.she] smiles back at you in an awkward attempt to get you to continue.
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN[npc.She] throws you a confident smile as [npc.she] hears what you've just said, and, stepping forwards, [npc.she] tells you that flattery will get you everywhere.
			#ELSE[npc.She] throws you a playful smile as [npc.she] hears what you've just said, and, stepping forwards, [npc.she] asks you what else you like about [npc.herHim].
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		 For the next several minutes, the two of you flirt with one another, exchanging compliments and suggestive words over the background music and chatter.
	</p>
	<p>
		From [npc.her] body language and the smile on [npc.her] face, you can tell that you're making a good impression on [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_MAIN_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping up to [npc.name], you lean forwards and press your [pc.lips+] against [npc.hers]. Letting out a muffled [npc.moan], [npc.she] happily presses [npc.her] body against yours, pushing [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth and desperately returning your kiss.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_KISS_CONTENT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Sliding your 
		#IF pc.getTongueLengthValue() > 2
		#THEN[pc.tongueLength]
		#ENDIF
		 tongue around inside [npc.namePos] mouth, you reach up and take hold of the sides of [npc.her] head, letting out [pc.a_moan+] as you continue kissing [npc.herHim]. From the way [npc.she] wraps [npc.her] [npc.arms] around you and tilts [npc.her] head to one side, you can tell that [npc.name] is loving every moment of this.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a short while, you break off the kiss, smiling happily at [npc.name] as [npc.she] lets out a desperate little [npc.moan].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_MAIN_KISS_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping up to [npc.name], you lean forwards and try to kiss [npc.herHim]. Before your [pc.lips] can find their target, however, [npc.name] quickly pulls back with an astonished look of disapproval on [npc.her] face.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hey! Watch it!)] [npc.she] shouts, frowning at you as [npc.she] pushes you away.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_MAIN_GROPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leaning in against [npc.name], you place your [pc.hands] on [npc.her] [npc.hips], before starting to let your touch roam across [npc.her] body.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_GROPE_CONTENT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Slipping your [pc.hand] down over [npc.her] [npc.legs], you start groping and stroking [npc.her] groin.
		#IF npc.hasPenis()
		#THEN Running your [pc.fingers] over the [npc.penisSize] bulge of [npc.her] cock, you let out a cheeky laugh before giving it a few firm strokes.
		#ENDIF
		#IF npc.hasBreasts()
		#THEN Lifting your free [pc.hand] up to [npc.her] chest, you grope and squeeze one of [npc.her] [npc.breastSize] [npc.breasts], before moving over to give the
			#IF npc.getBreastRows()>1
			#THEN others some attention.
			#ELSE other one some attention.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.Name] lets out a quiet little [npc.moan] in response to your touch, before gently leaning in against you and panting heavily into your [pc.ear], [npc.speech(~Aah!~ Y-Yes... D-Don't stop...)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.Name] lets out [npc.a_moan+] in response to your touch, before eagerly pressing [npc.herself] against you and panting heavily into your [pc.ear], [npc.speech(~Aah!~ Oh yeah babe, keep going! ~Mmm!~ Yeah, just like that!)]
			#ELSE [npc.Name] lets out [npc.a_moan+] in response to your touch, before leaning in against you and panting heavily into your [pc.ear], [npc.speech(~Aah!~ Yes... Keep going!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Encouraged by [npc.her] eager response, you spend the next few minutes feeling [npc.name] up, before finally pulling back and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_MAIN_GROPE_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leaning in against [npc.name], you place your [pc.hands] on [npc.her] [npc.hips], before trying to work your touch down to [npc.her] groin. [npc.She] instantly pulls away in response to your exploratory movements, and with an angry expression on [npc.her] face, [npc.she] shouts out over the club's background noise,
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(S-Stop it! That's too much!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(What the fuck?! Keep your [pc.hands] to yourself!)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Hey! Cut that out! Keep your [pc.hands] to yourself!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You step back, giving [npc.name] some space and letting [npc.herHim] cool off. As [npc.her] expression softens a little, you move forwards again and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_MAIN_SAVE_CLUBBER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you need to take a break from [npc.name], you call out over the background noise of the club, [pc.speech(I've got to head off for a while, but I'll catch you later, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] seems a little deflated, but puts on a smile as [npc.she] responds, [npc.speech(Sure thing, I'll see you another time.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.she] moves off into the crowd, leaving you standing alone once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_MAIN_LOSE_COMPANY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that [npc.name] isn't all you were hoping [npc.she]'d be, you call out over the background noise of the club, [pc.speech(I've got to head off now. Have a good night!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] seems a little deflated, but as you move away from [npc.herHim], [npc.she] shrugs [npc.her] shoulders and moves off into the crowd.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Around the edges of the club's main floor, there are several jungle-themed seating areas, and it's in one of these that you currently find yourself standing. Taking a look around, you see that the enclosure is filled with numerous small booths, each one semi-enclosed by fake tropical plants and dark wooden fencing. In each of these booths, a semi-circular black leather sofa surrounds a clean wooden table. Most of these sofas are occupied by couples, who are either talking or making out with one another, although you do see a few that are currently empty.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although there's no wall to partition these seating areas from the crowds that fill the main floor, they're still the quietest parts of the club, by virtue of being the furthest you can get from the loud speakers positioned above the central dance floor. 
	</p>
	<p>
		If you were to find someone to start chatting to back out in the main area of the club, you could come and sit with them in one of these booths, but by yourself, there's not much to do in here. Turning around to face the main body of the club, you prepare to step back out into the crowds...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_WITH_PARTNER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Around the edges of the club's main floor, there are several jungle-themed seating areas, and it's in one of these that you currently find yourself standing. Taking a look around, you see that the enclosure is filled with numerous small booths, each one semi-enclosed by fake tropical plants and dark wooden fencing. In each of these booths, a semi-circular black leather sofa surrounds a clean wooden table. Most of these sofas are occupied by couples, who are either talking or making out with one another, although you do see a few that are currently empty.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although there's no wall to partition these seating areas from the crowds that fill the main floor, they're still the quietest parts of the club, by virtue of being the furthest you can get from the loud speakers positioned above the central dance floor. 
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!pc.isTaur())
			#IF(!npc.isTaur())
				Leading [npc.name] over to an empty booth, you sit down with [npc.herHim], before leaning forwards over the table and preparing to make your next move...
			#ELSE
				Taking a quick look around the area, you see that there's an empty extra-large booth, which appears to be specifically designed to seat someone with a lower body like [npc.namePos]. Leading [npc.herHim] over to the wide sofa, you sit down next to [npc.herHim], before shuffling up close and preparing to make your next move...
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(!npc.isTaur())
				Taking a quick look around the area, you see that there's an empty extra-large booth, which appears to be specifically designed to seat someone with a lower body like yours. Leading [npc.name] over to the wide sofa, you sit down next to [npc.herHim], before shuffling up close and preparing to make your next move...
			#ELSE
				Taking a quick look around the area, you see that there's an empty extra-large booth, which appears to be specifically designed to seat people with lower bodies like yours and [npc.namePos]. Leading [npc.herHim] over to the wide sofa, you sit down next to [npc.herHim], before shuffling up close and preparing to make your next move...
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_FOOTSIE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!pc.isTaur() && !npc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Moving your [pc.foot] under the table, you slowly run it up the length of [npc.namePos] [npc.legs].
			#IF(npc.isShy())
				 [npc.She] starts to blush in response to your sudden touch, and, shuffling around on [npc.her] seat, [npc.she] shyly smiles at you and bites [npc.her] [npc.lip].
			#ELSE
				#IF(npc.isConfident())
					 [npc.She] lets out a playful laugh in response to your sudden touch, before eagerly [npc.spreadingHerLegs] in order to entice you into taking it a step further.
				#ELSE
					 [npc.She] playfully smiles at you in response to your sudden touch, and, [npc.spreadingHerLegs], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and encourages you to take it a step further.
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Encouraged by [npc.her] reaction, you slide your [pc.foot] all the way up [npc.namePos] [npc.leg+], before gently starting to press your [pc.toes] into [npc.her] groin. [npc.She] lets out [npc.a_moan+] as you stimulate
			#IF npc.hasPenis() && npc.hasVagina()
			#THEN both [npc.her] cock and pussy
			#ELSE
				#IF npc.hasPenis()
				#THEN [npc.her] cock
				#ELSE
					#IF npc.hasVagina()
					#THEN [npc.her] pussy
					#ELSE [npc.her] genderless mound
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
			 with your [pc.foot], and you can't help but grin in delight at [npc.her] reaction.
		</p>
		<p>
			For the next few minutes, you continue playing with [npc.herHim] under the table, before finally dropping your [pc.foot] back down to the floor and grinning at the now-panting [npc.race].
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(!npc.isTaur())
			<p>
				Leaning your humanoid upper body in against [npc.name], you slip your [pc.hand] down over [npc.her] [npc.legs], before starting to grope and stroke [npc.her] groin.
				#IF(npc.hasPenis())
					 Running your [pc.fingers] over the [npc.penisSize] bulge of [npc.her] cock, you let out a cheeky laugh before giving it a few firm strokes.
				#ENDIF
				#IF(npc.hasBreasts())
					 Lifting your free [pc.hand] up to [npc.her] chest, you start cupping and squeezing one of [npc.her] [npc.breastSize] [npc.breasts], before moving over to give the
					#IF(npc.getBreastRows()>1)
						 others some attention.
					#ELSE
						 other one some attention.
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(npc.isShy())
					[npc.Name] lets out a quiet little [npc.moan] in response to your touch, before gently leaning in against you and panting heavily into your [pc.ear], [npc.speech(~Aah!~ Y-Yes... D-Don't stop...)]
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.isConfident())
						[npc.Name] lets out [npc.a_moan+] in response to your touch, before eagerly pressing [npc.herself] against you and panting heavily into your [pc.ear], [npc.speech(~Aah!~ Oh yeah babe, keep going! ~Mmm!~ Yeah, just like that!)]
					#ELSE
						[npc.Name] lets out [npc.a_moan+] in response to your touch, before leaning in against you and panting heavily into your [pc.ear], [npc.speech(~Aah!~ Yes... Keep going!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				Encouraged by [npc.her] eager response, you spend the next few minutes feeling [npc.name] up, before finally pulling back and wondering what to do next...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Due to the fact that the two of you have rather unusual lower bodies, you and [npc.name] have ended up sitting down with your humanoid upper-bodies next to one another. In such a position, it'd be impossible to reach over far enough to give [npc.namePos] groin a grope, so, thinking up a quick excuse to move over to [npc.her] lower half, you tell [npc.herHim] that the sofa's cushion looks to be about to fall off.
			<p>
			<p>
				Telling your partner to remain seated, you stand up and quickly step forwards, before kneeling down and patting the sofa's cushion. Instead of then standing up again, you slide your [pc.hand] up and over [npc.namePos] animalistic rump, before moving down to [npc.her] groin and starting to grope and stroke [npc.her] crotch.
				#IF(npc.hasPenis())
					 Running your [pc.fingers] over the [npc.penisSize] bulge of [npc.her] cock, you let out a cheeky laugh before giving it a few firm strokes.
				#ENDIF
				#IF(npc.hasVagina())
					 Lifting your free [pc.hand] up to behind [npc.her] hind legs, you start playing with the sensitive area around [npc.her] [npc.pussy+], grinning to yourself as you press down on [npc.her] [npc.labia+].
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(npc.isShy())
					[npc.Name] lets out a quiet little [npc.moan] in response to your touch, before gently bucking [npc.her] animalistic body back against you and panting heavily, [npc.speech(~Aah!~ Y-Yes... D-Don't stop...)]
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.isConfident())
						[npc.Name] lets out [npc.a_moan+] in response to your touch, before gently bucking [npc.her] animalistic body back against you and panting heavily, [npc.speech(~Aah!~ Oh yeah babe, keep going! ~Mmm!~ Yeah, just like that!)]
					#ELSE
						[npc.Name] lets out [npc.a_moan+] in response to your touch, before gently bucking [npc.her] animalistic body back against you and panting heavily, [npc.speech(~Aah!~ Yes... Keep going!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				Encouraged by [npc.her] eager response, you spend the next few minutes feeling [npc.name] up, before finally standing up and moving back over to sit beside [npc.herHim] once more...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_FOOTSIE_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!pc.isTaur() && !npc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Moving your [pc.foot] under the table, you slowly run it up the length of [npc.namePos] [npc.legs].
			#IF(npc.isShy())
				 [npc.She] instantly blushes, and, desperately shuffling away on [npc.her] seat, [npc.she] shyly stutters, [npc.speech(D-Don't do that please!)]
			#ELSE
				#IF(npc.isConfident())
					 [npc.She] lets out an angry cry, before reaching down under the table, grabbing your [pc.foot], and pushing it away. [npc.speech(Keep your [pc.feet] to yourself!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.She] lets out a shocked cry, before shuffling away on the sofa to get away from your [pc.foot]. [npc.speech(Stop that!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			With your playful advances spurned, you let your [pc.foot] drop back down to the floor. [npc.Name] crosses [npc.her] [npc.arms] and leans back on the sofa, glaring angrily at you for a moment, before letting [npc.her] expression soften.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(!npc.isTaur())
			<p>
				Leaning in against [npc.name], you place your [pc.hands] on [npc.her] [npc.hips], before trying to work your touch down to [npc.her] groin.
				#IF npc.isShy()
					 [npc.She] instantly blushes, and, desperately shuffling away on [npc.her] seat, [npc.she] shyly stutters, [npc.speech(D-Don't do that please!)]
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.isConfident())
						 [npc.She] lets out an angry cry, before shuffling away on [npc.her] seat and reprimanding you, [npc.speech(Keep your [pc.hands] to yourself!)]
					#ELSE
						 [npc.She] lets out a shocked cry, before shuffling away on [npc.her] seat and reprimanding you, [npc.speech(Stop that!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				You step back, giving [npc.name] some space and letting [npc.herHim] cool off. As [npc.her] expression softens a little, you move forwards again and wonder what to do next...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Due to the fact that the two of you have rather unusual lower bodies, you and [npc.name] have ended up sitting down with your humanoid upper-bodies next to one another. In such a position, it'd be impossible to reach over far enough to give [npc.namePos] groin a grope, so, thinking up a quick excuse to move over to [npc.her] lower half, you tell [npc.herHim] that the sofa's cushion looks to be about to fall off.
			<p>
			<p>
				Telling your partner to remain seated, you stand up and quickly step forwards, before kneeling down and patting the sofa's cushion. Instead of then standing up again, you slide your [pc.hand] up and over [npc.namePos] animalistic rump, before starting to move your touch over between [npc.her] hind legs.
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(npc.isShy())
					 [npc.She] instantly blushes as [npc.she] feels this, and, desperately shuffling away on [npc.her] seat, [npc.she] shyly stutters, [npc.speech(D-Don't do that please!)]
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.isConfident())
						 [npc.She] lets out an angry cry, before shuffling away on [npc.her] seat and reprimanding you, [npc.speech(Keep your [pc.hands] to yourself!)]
					#ELSE
						 [npc.She] lets out a shocked cry, before shuffling away on [npc.her] seat and reprimanding you, [npc.speech(Stop that!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				Having had your daring advances rejected, you stand up and return to your seat, giving [npc.name] some space and letting [npc.herHim] cool off. As [npc.her] expression softens a little, you move forwards again and wonder what to do next...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_SEX_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!pc.isTaur())
		#IF(!npc.isTaur())
			<p>
				Sliding around on the semi-circular sofa, you lean in against [npc.name], which results in [npc.herHim] letting out a hungry [npc.moan]. Taking that as a sign of consent, you lift yourself up and sit in [npc.her] lap, before leaning forwards and pressing your [pc.lips+] against [npc.hers].
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.Name] responds to your move by reaching up and wrapping [npc.her] [npc.arms] around you, pulling you into [npc.her] embrace as [npc.she] returns your passionate kiss. After a moment of making out with one another, you pull back, before [pc.moaning] down at [npc.name], [pc.speech(Come on, [npc.name]! Fuck me!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.speech(~Mmm~ Come here then,)] [npc.she] [npc.moans] in response, pulling you back into a lustful kiss as [npc.she] prepares to do as you ask...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Sliding off the semi-circular sofa, you kneel down beside [npc.namePos] hind-quarters, which results in [npc.herHim] letting out a hungry [npc.moan]. Taking that as a sign of consent, you reach forwards and give [npc.her] groin a firm stroke, before leaning in and planting a kiss on [npc.her] animalistic crotch.
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.Name] responds to your move by first letting out yet another horny [npc.moan], and then, taking care not to tread on you, by getting up to [npc.her] feet and stepping forwards in order to fully present [npc.her] rear end to you. [npc.speech(~Mmm~ Come on then,)] [npc.she] [npc.moans], looking back over [npc.her] shoulder, [npc.speech(There's plenty of room here for us to have some fun...)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF(!npc.isTaur())
			<p>
				Desperate to have sex with [npc.name], you tell [npc.herHim] to remain seated, before quickly standing up and turning around. Positioning yourself so that your animalistic rear end is facing your partner, you take a step backwards, lowering your groin down into [npc.her] lap as you [pc.moan], [pc.speech(Please... Fuck me...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.speech(~Mmm!~ How could anyone say no to that?)] [npc.Name] [npc.moans] in response, reaching up to take hold of your hind-quarters as [npc.she] prepares to do as you ask...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Desperate to have sex with [npc.name], you pointedly tell [npc.herHim] that this special extra-large booth in which the two of you are sitting is easily large enough in which to have some fun. Taking hold of your partner's [npc.hands], you get [npc.herHim] to stand up with you as you [pc.moan], [pc.speech(Please... Fuck me...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.speech(~Mmm!~ How could anyone say no to that?)] [npc.Name] [npc.moans] in response, grinning hungrily at you as [npc.she] prepares to do as you ask...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_SEX_AS_SUB_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Desperate to have sex with [npc.name], you start to make your move, but, sensing what it is you want, [npc.she] quickly lets out a frustrated sigh and pushes you away.
		#IF(npc.isShy())
			 Stuttering in embarrassment, [npc.she] exclaims, [npc.speech(P-Please stay on your side!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF(npc.isConfident())
				 With a frown on [npc.her] face, [npc.she] scolds, [npc.speech(Hey! Calm down! Keep to your side of the sofa!)]
			#ELSE
				 With a frown on [npc.her] face, [npc.she] tells you off, [npc.speech(Keep to your side of the sofa!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Reluctantly doing as [npc.she] asks, you move back around to your initial position. Waiting a moment for [npc.name] to stop frowning at you, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_SEX_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!pc.isTaur())
		#IF(!npc.isTaur())
			<p>
				Sliding around on the semi-circular sofa, you lean in against [npc.name], which results in [npc.herHim] letting out a desperate little [npc.moan]. Taking that as a sign of consent, you wrap your [pc.arms] around [npc.herHim] and pull [npc.herHim] into your lap, before moving your head forwards and pressing your [pc.lips+] against [npc.hers].
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.Name] responds to your move by leaning heavily down against you, letting out muffled [npc.moans] as [npc.she] returns your passionate kiss. After a moment of making out with one another, [npc.name] pulls back, before [pc.moaning] down at you,
				#IF(npc.isShy())
					 [npc.speech(P-Please... Fuck me...)]
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.isConfident())
						 [npc.speech(~Mmm~ Come on babe! Fuck me already!)]
					#ELSE
						 [npc.speech(Oh yes! Fuck me!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(~Mmm~ Come here then,)] you [npc.moan] in response, pulling [npc.name] down into a lustful kiss as you prepare to do as [npc.she] asks...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Eager to have sex with [npc.name], you tell [npc.herHim] that it's time the two of you had some real fun. Taking [npc.her] excited [npc.moan] as an indication that [npc.sheIs] just as impatient to get started as you are, you waste no time in telling [npc.herHim] to stand up and turn around, so that [npc.sheIs] presenting [npc.her] animalistic groin to you.
			</p>
			<p>
				Upon receiving your further instructions for [npc.herHim] to lower [npc.her] hind-quarters into your lap, [npc.name] does as you command, before looking back over [npc.her] shoulder and [npc.moaning],
				#IF(npc.isShy())
					 [npc.speech(P-Please... Fuck me...)]
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.isConfident())
						 [npc.speech(~Mmm~ Come on babe! Fuck me already!)]
					#ELSE
						 [npc.speech(Oh yes! Fuck me!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Eager to have sex with [npc.name], you tell [npc.herHim] that it's time the two of you had some real fun. Taking [npc.her] excited [npc.moan] as an indication that [npc.sheIs] just as impatient to get started as you are, you waste no time in taking [npc.her] [npc.hands] in yours, before getting [npc.herHim] to stand up with you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Grinning as [npc.name] impatiently steps forwards to press [npc.herself] against you, you reassure [npc.herHim] that this specially-designed booth is more than large enough for some mounting to take place. Upon hearing this,
			#IF(npc.isShy())
				 [npc.name] blushes profusely and eagerly stammers, [npc.speech(O-Oh yes... P-Please... Fuck me...)]
			#ELSE
				#IF(npc.isConfident())
					 [npc.name] bites [npc.her] lip and [npc.moans], [npc.speech(~Mmm~ Come on then, babe! Fuck me already!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.name] bites [npc.her] lip and [npc.moans], [npc.speech(Oh yes! Fuck me!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_SEX_AS_DOM_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Sliding around on the semi-circular sofa, you lean in against [npc.name], which causes [npc.herHim] to let out a frustrated sigh. Pushing you away,
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.she] stutters, [npc.speech(P-Please stay on your side!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.she] scolds, [npc.speech(Hey! Calm down! Keep to your side of the sofa!)]
			#ELSE [npc.she] frowns at you as [npc.she] tells you off, [npc.speech(Keep to your side of the sofa!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Reluctantly doing as [npc.she] asks, you move back around to your initial position. Waiting a moment for [npc.name] to stop frowning at you, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Disentangling yourselves from one another, the two of you let out a synchronised, deeply-satisfied sigh. Collapsing down on the sofa next to you, [npc.name] grins as [npc.she] leans forwards and plants a quick kiss on your lips. [npc.speech(~Mmm~ That was fantastic...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After spending a few minutes to get [npc.her] things in order, [npc.name] turns to you and smiles.
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(I-I need to get going now. I'll meet you here again another time, right?)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(I've gotta get out of here now, but I'll catch you again, right?)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(I need to leave now, but I'll see you again, won't I?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_AFTER_SEX_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Disentangling yourselves from one another, the two of you let out a synchronised sigh. Collapsing down on the sofa next to you, [npc.name] crosses [npc.her] [npc.arms] and lets out a frustrated huff, [npc.speech(You didn't exactly satisfy me, you know...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After spending a few minutes to get [npc.her] things in order, [npc.name] turns to you and smiles.
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(I-I need to get going now. That wasn't the best sex, but I still had fun... I'll meet you here again another time, right?)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(I've gotta get out of here now. You're pretty lousy at fucking, but I'd still like to hang out with you again. I'll catch you here another time, right?)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(I need to leave now. I don't really mind too much about the disappointing sex, so I'll see you again, won't I?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_AFTER_SEX_SEE_AGAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Of course I'll see you again!)] you enthusiastically reply, smiling up at [npc.name] as [npc.she] stands up.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Great! Have a safe trip home!)] [npc.she] responds, leaning down to kiss you again before turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		With [npc.namePos] [npc.scent+] still lingering in the air, you lean back and let out another deeply satisfied sigh. After watching [npc.herHim] walk off into the crowd, you stand up, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_AFTER_SEX_DO_NOT_SEE_AGAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Erm, yeah, sure,)] you hesitantly reply, secretly hoping that you never see [npc.name] again.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Eugh, you could at least <i>try</i> to sound sincere,)] [npc.she] responds, letting out an annoyed huff before turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		With [npc.namePos] [npc.scent+] still lingering in the air, you lean back and let out a relieved sigh. After watching [npc.herHim] walk off into the crowd, you stand up, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_AFTER_SEX_DO_NOT_SEE_AGAIN_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Not likely,)] you reply, leaning back on the sofa and smirking at [npc.name]. [pc.speech(I just wanted an easy fuck. Now go on, get out of here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN[npc.speech(Y-You asshole! Y-You could at least pretend to care!)] [npc.name] stammers, tears welling up in [npc.her] [npc.eyes] as [npc.she] turns and taking [npc.her] leave.
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN[npc.speech(Fine. If that's the way it is, fuck you too, you fucking [pc.bitch].)] [npc.name] snaps, glaring down at you for a moment before turning on [npc.her] heel and taking [npc.her] leave.
			#ELSE[npc.speech(Eugh. What [pc.a_bitch]. Fuck you too.)] [npc.name] snaps, before quickly turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With [npc.namePos] [npc.scent+] still lingering in the air, you lean back and let out a relieved sigh. After watching [npc.herHim] walk off into the crowd, you stand up, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_SAVE_CLUBBER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you need to take a break from [npc.name], you lean forwards over the table and say, [pc.speech(Sorry [npc.name], but I've got to head off for a while. I'll catch you later, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] sinks down on the sofa a little, but puts on a smile as [npc.she] responds, [npc.speech(Ok [pc.name], I hope I'll see you another time.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.she] stands up, and with one last smile your way, [npc.she] heads off into the crowd. With a sigh, you stand up and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_LOSE_COMPANY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you don't want to be with [npc.name] anymore, you lean forwards over the table and sigh, [pc.speech(I'm not really having much fun here. Have a good night.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] immediately stands up, before frowning at you as [npc.she] responds, [npc.speech(Well, ok. See you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.she] turns around and heads off into the crowd. With a sigh, you stand up and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(!pc.isTaur() && !npc.isTaur())
			You lean forwards over the table towards [npc.name], and, over the background noise, spend the next few minutes chatting with [npc.herHim].
		#ELSE
			You lean in towards [npc.name] a little, and, over the background noise, spend the next few minutes chatting with [npc.herHim].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEATING_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You slide around on the sofa to get a little closer to [npc.name], and, in order to make yourself heard over the background noise, lean in towards [npc.herHim] and raise your voice as you offer [npc.herHim] a compliment on [npc.her] appearance.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Just like everything else in the club, the bar has what could be described as an African theme to it, with savannah-styled murals painted on the walls and fake jungle plants hanging from the ceiling. The five or so barmaids working behind the counter fit into this theme as well, as all but one is a zebra-girl, with the exception being a particularly energetic-looking lioness.
	</p>
	<p>
		It's quite apparent from the way she's giving out orders to the zebra-girls that this lioness is the one in charge. She also so happens to be the one nearest to where you're standing, and as she finishes serving one of the many customers leaning against the long counter-top, she turns towards you and smiles.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[kalahari.speech(Heya, hun!)] the lioness says, stepping forwards as she greets you, [kalahari.speech(I haven't seen your #IFpc.isFeminine()#THENpretty#ELSEhandsome#ENDIF face in here before!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(This is my first time here,)] you reply, returning the friendly lioness's smile.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kalahari.speech(The name's Kalahari,)] she says, winking at you as she places both hands on the bar's counter. As you give Kalahari your name in return, she leans forwards, and you can't help but glance down at her cleavage. Her [kalahari.breastSize] breasts are barely contained by the short tube top she's wearing, and, shaking her assets from side to side, she lets out a laugh, [kalahari.speech(Haha! Sorry, don't mind me, I just like to give all the cute customers a little show!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply, she stands back upright, and, grinning cheekily at you, she asks, [kalahari.speech(So, what can I get you then, hun?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Just like everything else in the club, the bar has what could be described as an African theme to it, with savannah-styled murals painted on the walls and fake jungle plants hanging from the ceiling. The five or so barmaids working behind the counter fit into this theme as well, as all but one is a zebra-girl, with the exception being the lioness, Kalahari.
	</p>
	<p>
		It's quite apparent from the way she's giving out orders to the zebra-girls that Kalahari is still the most senior barmaid working here. She also so happens to be the one nearest to where you're standing, and as she finishes serving one of the many customers leaning against the long counter-top, she turns towards you and smiles.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turning towards [npc.name], you lean against the bar, and, shouting out over the background noise in order to make yourself heard, spend the next few minutes talking with [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Moving closer towards [npc.name], you lean against the bar, and, raising your voice in order to be heard over the background noise, you offer [npc.herHim] a compliment on [npc.her] appearance.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping up to [npc.name], you lean forwards and press your [pc.lips+] against [npc.hers]. Letting out a muffled [npc.moan], [npc.she] happily presses [npc.her] body against yours, pushing [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth and desperately returning your kiss.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KISS_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping up to  [npc.name], you lean forwards and try to kiss [npc.herHim]. Before your [pc.lips] can reach [npc.hers], however, [npc.she] quickly pulls away and shouts out,
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(H-Hey! C-Calm down!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Woah! Steady on!)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Hey! Calm down!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With your advances spurned, you lean back against the bar, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_GROPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You grope and feel up [npc.name].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_GROPE_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leaning in against [npc.name], you place your [pc.hands] on [npc.her] [npc.hips], before trying to work your touch down to [npc.her] groin. [npc.She] instantly pulls away in response to your exploratory movements, and with an angry expression on [npc.her] face, [npc.she] shouts out over the club's background noise,#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(S-Stop it! That's too much!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(What the fuck?! Keep your [pc.hands] to yourself!)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Hey! Cut that out! Keep your [pc.hands] to yourself!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You step back and lean against the bar in order to give [npc.name] some space. As [npc.her] expression softens a little, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_SAVE_CLUBBER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you need to take a break from [npc.name], you call out over the sound of the background noise of the club, [pc.speech(Sorry [npc.name], but I've got to head off for a while. I'll catch you later, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] leans against the bar, looking a little deflated, before putting on a smile as [npc.she] responds, [npc.speech(Sure thing [pc.name], I hope I'll see you another time.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With one last smile thrown your way, [npc.name] turns and heads off into the crowd. With a sigh, you turn back to face the bar and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_LOSE_COMPANY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough of [npc.name], you lean forwards and shout out over the noise of the club, [pc.speech(Hey [npc.name], I'm not really feeling this. I need some time alone.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] lets out a sigh, before making a dismissive gesture with [npc.her] [npc.hand] and replying, [npc.speech(Whatever. Have a good night.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.she] turns around and walks off, leaving you alone at the bar as you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI"><![CDATA[
	#IFkalahari.isVisiblyPregnant()
	#THEN
		#IFkalahari.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc)
		#THEN
			<p>
				[kalahari.speech(Heya, hun!)] the still-pregnant lioness says, winking at you as she places both hands on the bar's counter. As you return Kalahari's greeting, she reaches down to absent-mindedly stroke her swollen belly, before leaning forwards and flashing you her cleavage. [kalahari.speech(Hey, you think my boobs have got bigger from being knocked up?)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				As Kalahari moves towards you to say hello, you realise that there's something wrong in the way she's moving, and, looking down at her stomach, you see that her belly is visibly swollen. Seeing what it is you're looking at, the happy lioness lets out a laugh, before stepping forwards and leaning heavily down on the counter-top. [npc.speech(Hey, [pc.name]! You've noticed I'm pregnant already, huh?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Yeah,)] you reply, smiling back at Kalahari.
			</p>
			#IFkalahari.getPregnantLitter().getFatherId()==kruger.getId()
			#THEN
			<p>
				Leaning forwards, the lioness flashes you a wild grin, before saying, [kalahari.speech(I got one of those pregnancy testers to make sure, but it turns out that Daddy's the father! That threesome we had sure was something...)] 
			</p>
			#ELSE
			<p>
				Leaning forwards, the lioness flashes you a wild grin, before saying, [kalahari.speech(I got one of those pregnancy testers to make sure, and it turns out that you're the father! I'll make sure to take good care of myself while carrying our kids around, don't worry!)] 
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Well, if there's anything I can help with, you just need to ask,)] you reply.
			</p>
			<p>
				[kalahari.speech(Thanks, but there's no need to worry about that, Daddy's already sorted out everything I need! Oh, and speaking of, I told him that you're the one who got me knocked up already, and he seemed all cool about it.)]
			</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
	<p>
		[kalahari.speech(Heya, hun!)] the lioness says, winking at you as she places both hands on the bar's counter. As you return Kalahari's greeting, she leans forwards, presenting her cleavage to you. Her [kalahari.breastSize] breasts are barely contained by the short tube top she's wearing, and, shaking her assets from side to side, she lets out a laugh, [kalahari.speech(Haha! Like what you see?)]
	</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Before you can reply, she quickly stands back upright, and, grinning cheekily at you, she asks, [npc.speech(Anyway, what can I get you then, hun?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get to know Kalahari a little better, you lean forwards over the bar and ask her how her night's going. Eager to have someone to talk to, Kalahari enthusiastically starts telling you how her day's been, before moving on to describe some of the customers she's served tonight.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although there are several other people waiting to be served, Kalahari tells one of the zebra-girl barmaids to deal with them, choosing to continue chatting with you over doing her job. You and Kalahari then spend the next several minutes talking and laughing with one another, before the sociable lioness crosses her arms and steps back, waiting for you to decide what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Smiling at Kalahari, you compliment her on her appearance, which causes her to let out a playful laugh and retort with a flattering remark of her own. Kalahari leans forwards as you start flirting with one another, flashing you her cleavage before reaching up to press her breasts together.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your eyes are drawn down to the lioness's provocative display, which causes her to let out a delighted laugh. Glancing around, she makes sure that she's not drawn too much attention from the other customers, before suddenly pulling up her tube top and flashing you her breasts.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI_FLIRT_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Just as quickly as she lifted it up, Kalahari then pulls her tube top back down to cover her [kalahari.breasts+] once more. From the delighted smile on her face, you can tell that she's having a lot of fun with you, and you wonder if you'll be able to take things a little further...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI_BREAK_KRUGER_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can tell from the way Kalahari keeps on glancing hungrily at your body that she wants to spend some time with you. Leaning forwards over the bar, you ask, [pc.speech(Have you got time for a break from work? Want to go find somewhere to sit with me?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Kalahari enthusiastically replies in the affirmative, and, getting the attention of one of the zebra-girls behind her, she calls out, [kalahari.speech(Hey, Asha, I'm taking a break! You're in charge!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning back to you, the happy lioness points to the far end of the bar, grinning as she says, [kalahari.speech(I'll see you down the end over there!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're instructed, you walk down to the far end of the bar, where you meet Kalahari as she steps out from behind the counter. Excitedly reaching down to grab your [pc.hand], the energetic lioness presses herself against you, before starting to pull you over to one corner of the club. [kalahari.speech(Come on! Let's go sit in the VIP area!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Allowing Kalahari lead the way, you soon find yourself standing before the pair of lion bouncers who are guarding the entrance to the VIP seating area. Seeing Kalahari, they both step to one side and let the two of you in. As you step foot into the exclusive area of the club, you glance around, noting that the area has several semi-enclosed seating booths in it, furnished with expensive-looking leather sofas and black marble tables.
	</p>
	<p>
		Instead of leading you over to one of the empty booths, Kalahari pulls you towards one of the very few that are already occupied. [kalahari.speech(Come on, I've got to introduce you to the boss before we can have some fun!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're led towards the booth on the furthest side of the room, you see that the occupants are one large male lion, with a couple of zebra-girls and lionesses sitting to either side of him. Coming to a halt in front of the booth, Kalahari happily introduces you, [kalahari.speech(Hi Daddy! This is my friend, [pc.name]. [pc.Name], this is Kruger, my dad, and the owner of the club.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Kruger grunts in acknowledgement as you greet him, before looking up at Kalahari and growling, [kruger.speech(Have you decided to stop playing around as a barmaid yet? You know you don't have to keep doing this.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[kalahari.speech(Eugh! Why do you have to bring that up <i>every</i> time?! I'm happiest when I'm working, I don't want to sit around doing nothing all the time like you do!)] Kalahari sharply replies, before turning back to you. [kalahari.speech(Come on, [pc.name], let's go sit down.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Grabbing your [pc.hand] again, Kalahari quickly leads you off to the booth furthest away from Kruger's. Collapsing down onto the sofa, her annoyed frown rapidly softens into a friendly smile as she pulls you down next to her. Shuffling forwards to press herself against you, Kalahari sighs, [kalahari.speech(Sorry about Daddy, he's always like that. Anyway, I've got thirty minutes for my break, let's have a good time!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI_BREAK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can tell from the way Kalahari keeps on glancing hungrily at your body that she wants to spend some time with you again. Leaning forwards over the bar, you ask, [pc.speech(Hey, Kalahari, have you got a break coming up? Want to go hang out in the VIP area again?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Kalahari enthusiastically replies in the affirmative, and, getting the attention of one of the zebra-girls behind her, she calls out, [kalahari.speech(Asha, I'm going for a break! You're in charge!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning back to you, the happy lioness points to the far end of the bar, grinning as she says, [kalahari.speech(I'll see you down the end over there again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're instructed, you walk down to the far end of the bar, where you meet Kalahari as she steps out from behind the counter. Excitedly reaching down to grab your [pc.hand], the energetic lioness presses herself against you, before starting to pull you over to one corner of the club. [kalahari.speech(Come on! Let's go have some fun!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After just a moment, you find yourself stepping past the lion bouncers and into the VIP area. After saying hello to Kruger, you and Kalahari find an empty booth that's out of sight of her father. Collapsing down onto the sofa, the lioness pulls you down next to her. Shuffling forwards to press herself against you, Kalahari sighs, [kalahari.speech(Alright, I've got thirty minutes for my break again. Let's have a good time!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_KALAHARI_BREAK_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get to know Kalahari a little better, you ask her about her job working for her father, Kruger, and then move on to talking about her life in Dominion.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she dislikes the way her father doesn't want her to work, Kalahari reveals that she's still very fond of him. She tells you that she lives in a separate wing of her father's house, and from what you can gather, it sounds like her family is very wealthy.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a while of chatting about miscellaneous happenings in the city, Kalahari sits back and lets out a happy sigh, offering you an opportunity to move on to something else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_KALAHARI_BREAK_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Shuffling up close to Kalahari, you flash her you most #IFpc.isFeminine()#THENseductive#ELSEcharming#ENDIF smile, before complimenting her on her appearance. The lioness blushes a little as she hears what you have to say, before retorting with a flattering remark of her own.
	</p>
	<p>
		As the two of you start flirting with one another, Kalahari shuffles a little closer, rubbing her leg up against yours and gazing longingly into your eyes. This continues for a few minutes, before she shuffles back on the sofa a little and waits for you to make the next move...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_KALAHARI_BREAK_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to take things a step further, you lean in towards Kalahari, tilting your head to one side as you go in for a kiss. Closing her eyes, the lioness responds in kind, and you feel her hot breath on your face as she leans in and presses her [kalahari.lips+] against yours. Your tongues slip into one another's mouths, and, with a muffled moan, you start making out with one another.
	</p>
	<p>
		You suddenly feel Kalahari take hold of your [pc.hand], and, shuffling even closer against you, she lifts your [pc.hand] up and slips it under her tube top. Giving the horny lioness what she so desperately wants, you start groping and squeezing her [kalahari.breasts+] beneath the fabric of her top. You feel her [kalahari.nipples+] getting hard beneath your touch, and, stopping to gently pinch and stoke them, you cause [kalahari.a_moan+] to burst out of her mouth.
	</p>
	<p>
		This continues for several minutes; the two of you passionately kissing one another as you play with the lioness's breasts. Eventually, however, Kalahari pulls away, licking her lips and letting out a submissive whine as she prepares for you to take the next step...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_KALAHARI_BREAK_GROPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With Kalahari's big [kalahari.eyeColour] eyes filled with burning, submissive desire, you press forwards against her, placing one [pc.hand] on her thigh, and #IFpc.getArmRows()==1#THENthe other#ELSEanother#ENDIF on her [kalahari.breasts+].
	</p>
	<p>
		[kalahari.speech(~Mmm~ Want to take a peek?)] Kalahari giggles, her voice dripping with lust. Answering in the affirmative, you grin as Kalahari pulls her tube top up, allowing her [kalahari.breasts+] to bounce free.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_KALAHARI_BREAK_GROPE_AFTER_BREAST_REVEAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking hold of your [pc.hand], Kalahari presses it against her breasts, letting out a deep moan as you start groping and squeezing her pillowy mounds. With your [pc.hand] that's resting on her thigh, you allow your touch to drop down between the lioness's legs, and, thanks to the incredibly short micro-skirt she's wearing, you're able to immediately start rubbing her pussy through the fabric of her thong.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kalahari.speech(Fuck... Yes...)] Kalahari sighs, reaching down between her legs to pull her thong to one side. [kalahari.speech(Stroke my little pussy...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You glance down between Kalahari's legs to see her [kalahari.pussy+] fully on display. 
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_KALAHARI_BREAK_GROPE_AFTER_PUSSY_REVEAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as the horny lioness asks, you tease your [pc.fingers] up and down over her [kalahari.labia], before homing in on her little clit and starting to rub it in a gentle, circular motion. Kalahari starts desperately making submissive little panting noises as she fails to control her lust, and with her cheeks starting to flush red from the excitement, she leans in over your shoulder and moans, [kalahari.speech(Yes... ~Aah~ Yes... Come on... Let's fuck...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder if you should do as she asks, and fuck her right here on the sofa...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI_BREAK_SEX_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!pc.isTaur())
		<p>
			With the way Kalahari is lewdly panting, combined with the fact that she's completely exposing herself to you, there's no other option in your mind but to give her what she's so desperately craving. Reaching forwards, you take hold of the horny lioness, and in one swift movement, pull her into your lap.
		</p>
		<p>
			[kalahari.speech(Yes! ~Mmm!~ Fuck me, yes, fuck me!)] she moans, leaning forwards to frantically plant a sloppy kiss on your lips.
		</p>
		<p>
			Determined to do just as she says, you reach up and give Kalahari's exposed breasts a squeeze, causing her to let out yet another desperate moan, before pulling her forwards and preparing to have sex with her...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With the way Kalahari is lewdly panting, combined with the fact that she's completely exposing herself to you, there's no other option in your mind but to give her what she's so desperately craving. Reaching forwards, you take hold of the horny lioness, and in one swift movement, pull her to her feet as you stand up on the [pc.feet] of your animalistic lower body.
		</p>
		<p>
			[kalahari.speech(Yes! ~Mmm!~ There's more than enough room here... Fuck me... Yes, fuck me!)] she moans, leaning forwards to frantically plant a sloppy kiss on your lips.
		</p>
		<p>
			Determined to do just as she says, you reach up and give Kalahari's exposed breasts a squeeze, causing her to let out yet another desperate moan, before pulling her forwards and preparing to have sex with her...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Not used as of 0.3.3.10 as Kalahari was meant to be too submissive to want to dom. -->
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI_BREAK_SEX_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With the way Kalahari is lewdly panting, combined with the fact that she's completely exposing herself to you, there's no other option in your mind but to let her have her way with you. Shuffling forwards, you reposition yourself in order to slide forwards into her into your lap.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, Kalahari, fuck me!)] you [pc.moan], leaning forwards to frantically plant a sloppy kiss on her lips.
	</p>
	<p>
		Determined to do just as you say, Kalahari reaches up and grabs your [pc.hands], before planting them on her exposed breasts. Giving them a gentle squeeze, you cause the lioness to let out a desperate moan, before she pulls you forwards and prepares to have sex with you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI_BREAK_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You and Kalahari both collapse down onto the sofa, panting from exertion. Looking across at the lioness, you see her happily smiling at you, before she moans, [kalahari.speech(Fuck... That was fantastic...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, that was great,)] you reply, before moving to get your things in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		Kalahari follows suit, pulling her thong and tube top back into position, before brushing off her micro-skirt and standing up. [kalahari.speech(I've got to get back to work now. We should do this again another night!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Agreeing with the happy lioness, you stand up and walk along beside her as you both head back out past the pair of lion bouncers. Turning to plant a kiss on your cheek, Kalahari laughs, before whispering into your ear, [kalahari.speech(I really can't wait for the next time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she bounds off in the direction of the bar, leaving you standing alone outside the VIP area.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_BAR_KALAHARI_BREAK_AFTER_SEX_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You and Kalahari both collapse down onto the sofa, panting from exertion. Looking across at the lioness, you see her pouting at you, before she sighs, [kalahari.speech(That was fun and all, but you didn't exactly satisfy me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Maybe next time I'll get you to cum,)] you reply, before moving to get your things in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		Kalahari lets out another frustrated sigh, before pulling her thong and tube top back into position, brushing off her micro-skirt, and standing up in front of you. [kalahari.speech(I've got to get back to work now. We should do this again another night, but next time, you've got to get me to climax!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Agreeing with the demanding lioness, you stand up and walk along beside her as you both head back out past the pair of lion bouncers. Turning to plant a kiss on your cheek, Kalahari laughs, before whispering into your ear, [kalahari.speech(I really can't wait for the next time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she bounds off in the direction of the bar, leaving you standing alone outside the VIP area.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_KALAHARI_BREAK_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you've had enough of hanging out with Kalahari, you sit back and sigh, [pc.speech(Sorry, Kalahari, I'm feeling pretty tired tonight. Maybe we can have some real fun another time?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[kalahari.speech(Aww... Ok then...)] Kalahari replies, sulking a little as she stands up and gets her clothing in order. [kalahari.speech(Well, I'd better get back to the bar.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You stand up and walk along beside Kalahari as you both head back out past the pair of lion bouncers. Turning to plant a quick kiss on your cheek, Kalahari laughs, before whispering into your ear, [kalahari.speech(I'm looking forward to seeing what 'fun' you have in mind for next time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she bounds off in the direction of the bar, leaving you standing alone outside the VIP area. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_KALAHARI_BREAK_OUT_OF_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[kalahari.speech(Aww, it looks like my break time is over,)] Kalahari sighs, before standing up and getting her clothing in order. [kalahari.speech(I'd better get back to the bar.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You stand up and walk along beside Kalahari as you both head back out past the pair of lion bouncers. Turning to plant a quick kiss on your cheek, Kalahari laughs, before whispering into your ear, [kalahari.speech(We should have some real fun next time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she bounds off in the direction of the bar, leaving you standing alone outside the VIP area. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_VIP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In one corner of the club, there's a seating area which is quite unlike the others. Most of the frontage is blocked off by a dark glass wall, and the single opening is guarded by a pair of muscular lion bouncers. Looking through this opening reveals the interior to be furnished with numerous semi-circular booths, each one housing a polished black marble table and a long, curved leather sofa.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you approach, one of the bouncers recognises you from before, and asks, [style.speechMasculineStrong(You're Kalahari's friend, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, that's me,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculineStrong(Kruger said you can head on in if you returned. I'm sure he'd like to talk to you,)] the bouncer explains, before stepping to one side in order to let you pass.
	</p>
	<p>
		You could head over to Kruger's booth, or turn back and return to the main part of the club...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_VIP_BLOCKED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In one corner of the club, there's a seating area which is quite unlike the others. Most of the frontage is blocked off by a dark glass wall, and the single opening is guarded by a pair of muscular lion bouncers. Looking through this opening reveals the interior to be furnished with numerous semi-circular booths, each one housing a polished black marble table and a long, curved leather sofa.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you approach, one of the bouncers shakes his head at you, making it clear that you're not allowed in. Perhaps if you were to befriend one of the members of staff, you'd be able to gain access to this VIP area, but for now, you'll have to remain in the main body of the club.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_VIP_KRUGER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'll pay Kruger a visit, you step forwards into the VIP area and start walking towards the far end of the room. Immediately, you spot the large lion sitting down in his usual booth, surrounded by the regular group of zebra-girls and lionesses. Kruger notices your approach, and nods his head to the seat beside him, indicating that you should come and sit next to him.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kruger.speech(Move it, Zoya,)] Kruger growls to the zebra-girl next to him. Zoya quickly stands up, vacating the sofa in order for you to take her place.
	</p>
	<p>
		[kruger.speech(Come on, [pc.name]. Sit down. I don't bite... much,)] the lion snarls, but despite his choice of words and the mildly-threatening tone of his voice, you don't sense any real malice behind his offer.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!pc.isTaur())
			Doing as he instructs, you sit down next to Kruger, who turns towards you and smirks, before growling,
		#ELSE
			Doing as he instructs, and finding the sofa large enough to accommodate your lower body, you sit down next to Kruger, who turns towards you and smirks, before growling,
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
			#IF(pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(kruger))
				 [kruger.speech(Still pregnant, I see.)]
			#ELSE
				#IF(pc.isCharacterPossiblyFather(kruger.getId()))
					 [kruger.speech(You've gone and got yourself knocked up, I see. If they're my kids, they'll be strong, so there's nothing to worry about.)]
				#ELSE
					 [kruger.speech(You've gone and got yourself knocked up, I see.)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 [kruger.speech(Kalahari's told me you're a decent sort, so that's good enough for me.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		The girls sitting around you lean back against the sofa and listen in, knowing to keep quiet while Kruger's attention is fixed on you. Looking across at the grinning lion, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_VIP_KRUGER_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to get to know Kruger a little better, you ask him about how his nightclub is doing, before moving the conversation on to be about his daughter, Kalahari.
	</p>
	<p>
		From what you can gather from his growling, rumbling responses, it seems as though his business is doing quite well. The tone of his voice softens as the two of you start talking about Kalahari, and Kruger explains how he likes to keep a close eye on his daughter in order to make sure that she doesn't end up making the same mistakes as her mother did. What those mistakes were, you're not able to find out, as every time you try to steer the conversation in that direction, Kruger simply lets out a deep growl.
	</p>
	<p>
		The girls seated around the two of you all pretend to be relaxing and quietly talking amongst themselves, but you can tell that they're listening in to everything Kruger reveals about himself.
	</p>
	<p>
		Even though Kruger's expression doesn't change, you can detect a slight softening in his tone as he speaks to you, letting you know that he's enjoying the time you're spending talking with him.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_VIP_KRUGER_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to flirt with Kruger a little, you offer him a compliment on his appearance, before shuffling forwards a little and brushing your [pc.hand] against his leg. The large lion lets out a happy growl, and, turning to fully face you, he rests his arm on the top of the sofa, just behind your neck, before returning your compliment in kind. 
	</p>
	<p>
		You and Kruger spend the next several minutes laughing and flirting with one another, all the while continuing to stroke your [pc.hand] against his leg. Every now and then, one of the girls sitting around you offers some input to the proceedings, which invariably includes a suggestion for Kruger to 'make you his bitch'.
	</p>
	<p>
		Each time Kruger hears this, he lets out an amused growl, and, by not stopping the girls from saying such things, you can tell that he's thinking it too...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_VIP_KRUGER_KISSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can tell that Kruger is desperate to kiss you, and, with the feeling being mutual, you shuffle across on the sofa in order to press your body against his. Slightly tilting your head to one side, you purse your [pc.lips] and let out a gentle sigh.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your provocative move instantly returns the result you were hoping for, as the huge lion lets out a deep, rumbling growl, before dominantly taking hold of your head and pressing his lips against yours. As you let out a muffled moan and close your eyes, you feel his tongue pushing its way into your mouth, and you surrender yourself completely to the dominant lion as he passionately makes out with you.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a few minutes, Kruger breaks off the kiss, and you suddenly become aware of the fact that the girls around you are all giggling and gossiping amongst one another. As you lean back against the sofa, one of the lionesses leans across and addresses Kruger, [genericFemale.speech(Go on, Kruger. Break [pc.herHim] in! We all want to see you fuck [pc.herHim]...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Kruger simply lets out an amused growl in response. Although you can tell that he's warming up to that idea, he doesn't seem interested in doing anything without first receiving an indication of consent from you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_VIP_KRUGER_FELT_UP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Sensing that Kruger wants to have some physical contact with you, and desperately craving the feeling of his strong hands running over your body, you shuffle up against him, before very suggestively placing a hand on his inner-thigh. Instantly, Kruger's hands are all over you, and you let out [pc.a_moan+] as he starts dominantly groping and squeezing your [pc.breasts+].
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			The zebra-girl on the other side of you leans across, reaching down to take hold of your thigh and giving it a sharp tug as she snaps, [genericFemale.speech(Spread your legs, slut.)]
		#ELSE
			The zebra-girl on the other side of you leans across and reaches down to give your [pc.leg] a smack as she snaps, [genericFemale.speech(Present yourself, slut.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(!pc.isTaur())
		<p>
			#IF(pc.hasLegs())
				Doing as you're told, you lean back on the sofa and part your [pc.legs] for Kruger,
			#ELSE
				Doing as you're told, you lean back on the sofa and present yourself to Kruger,
			#ENDIF
			 who instantly reaches down with his free hand to stroke and stimulate
			#IF pc.hasPenis() && pc.hasVagina()
			#THEN both your cock and pussy.
			#ELSE
				#IF pc.hasPenis()
				#THEN your cock.
				#ELSE
					#IF pc.hasVagina()
					#THEN your pussy.
					#ELSE your genderless mound.
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[kruger.speech(Good [pc.girl]...)] Kruger growls into your [pc.ear]. [kruger.speech(You're loving this, aren't you?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You desperately [pc.moan] in the affirmative, bucking your [pc.hips+] up against the dominant lion's hand as he continues stroking up and down. After a while of this, he finally pulls back, grinning at you in delight.
		</p>
		<p>
			As the excitement comes to an end, the zebra-girl who told you present yourself leans in over your shoulder, before whispering in your [pc.ear], [genericFemale.speech(Go on, bitch, let Kruger fuck you like the desperate slut you are.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Doing as you're told, you lean back on the sofa and part your [pc.legs] for the zebra-girl, who's instantly joined by one of the nearby lionesses. Together, they reach down to start stroking and exploring your animalistic groin, quickly discovering
			#IF(pc.hasPenis() && pc.hasVagina())
				 that you have both a cock and pussy.
				</p>
				<p>
					[genericFemale.speech([pc.SheIs] packing both kinds of fun down here, boss,)] the lioness reports, [genericFemale.speech(And [pc.sheIs] already hard and wet...)]
			#ELSE
				#IF(pc.hasPenis())
					 that you have [pc.a_cock+].
				</p>
				<p>
					[genericFemale.speech([pc.SheHas] only got a cock down here, boss,)] the lioness reports, [genericFemale.speech(And [pc.sheIs] already hard...)]
				#ELSE
					#IF(pc.hasVagina())
						 that you have [pc.a_pussy+].
					</p>
					<p>
						[genericFemale.speech([pc.SheHas] got a nice pussy down here for you, boss,)] the lioness reports, [genericFemale.speech(And [pc.sheIs] already getting wet at the thought of your cock thrusting deep inside of it...)]
					#ELSE
						 that you have a genderless mound.
						</p>
						<p>
							[genericFemale.speech([pc.SheHas] got nothing down here, boss,)] the lioness reports, [genericFemale.speech(You'll have to use [pc.her] ass...)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[kruger.speech(Is that so?)] Kruger growls into your [pc.ear], [kruger.speech(You're loving this, aren't you, [pc.girl]?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You desperately [pc.moan] in the affirmative, pushing your chest out against the dominant lion's hands as he continues groping you. After a while of this, he finally pulls back, grinning at you in delight as you pant in excitement.
		</p>
		<p>
			Before either of you can make a further move, the zebra-girl who told you open your legs leans in over your shoulder, before harshly whispering in your [pc.ear], [genericFemale.speech(Go on, bitch, let Kruger fuck you like the desperate slut you are.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_VIP_KRUGER_SEX_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
		<p>
			Desperate to have sex with Kruger, you lean into him, before tilting your head to one side and pressing your lips against his. The two of you share a passionate kiss for a moment, before you pull back and desperately plead for him to fuck you. The lion-boy lets out a deep, rumbling growl of approval as he hears your request, and after reaching up to take hold of your shoulders, he pushes you down onto your knees in front of him. Glaring down at you with a hungry look in his eyes, he growls, [kruger.speech(You can start by sucking my cock, then I'll give you a good fuck!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			One of the zebra-girls to your right lets out a giggle and leans over towards you, then with a level of ease suggesting that she's done this countless times before, she swiftly pulls down both Kruger's trousers and underwear. Thanks to this, you suddenly find yourself presented with the lion-boy's [kruger.cockLengthValue], ebony cock, which rapidly rises to full erection. Just like the rest of Kruger's body, his throbbing dick has an anthropomorphic, feline quality to it, and you can't help but let out an eager, submissive whine as you see a series of soft, backwards-facing barbs lining its length. The surrounding lion and zebra-girls let out a chorus of giggles as they hear your reaction, and before you can make a move, the zebra-girl who exposed Kruger's cock suddenly pushes your face into the lion-boy's groin and commands, [genericFemale.speech(Show Kruger some respect, slut. Start licking.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out yet another deep, rumbling groan, Kruger spreads his legs a little and impatiently pushes his hips into your face, causing his hot cock to grind up against your [pc.lips+]. Turned on by what's happening, and eager to do as you're told, you dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start licking the lion-boy's hard, ebony shaft. Working your way up to the [kruger.cockHead+], you open wide and take him into your mouth, and with the lion-boy's harem excitedly commenting on your performance, you start to give Kruger a blowjob...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.isTaur())
		#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
			<p>
				Wanting nothing more than to have sex with Kruger right here and now, you lean into him and desperately plead for him to fuck you. The lion-boy lets out a deep, rumbling growl of approval as he hears your request, and after reaching up to take hold of your shoulders, he gives you a firm push and growls, [kruger.speech(I can't get a blowjob from you, so get your pussy down in my lap!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				One of the zebra-girls to your right lets out a giggle and leans over towards the lion-boy, then with a level of ease suggesting that she's done this countless times before, she swiftly pulls down both Kruger's trousers and underwear. Thanks to this, the lion-boy's [kruger.cockLengthValue], ebony cock is suddenly fully exposed, and you watch in delight as it rapidly rises to full erection. Just like the rest of Kruger's body, his throbbing dick has an anthropomorphic, feline quality to it, and you can't help but let out an eager, submissive whine as you see a series of soft, backwards-facing barbs lining its length. The surrounding lion and zebra-girls let out a chorus of giggles as they hear your reaction, and before you can make a move, the zebra-girl who exposed Kruger's cock suddenly pulls your [pc.legRace] lower body around to face the lion-boy, before exposing your [pc.pussy+] and pushing you down into his groin. Giving your rump a quick smack, she commands, [genericFemale.speech(Show Kruger some respect, slut. Rub that horny little [pc.legRace]-cunt over his cock and beg for him to fuck you!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Letting out yet another deep, rumbling groan, Kruger spreads his legs a little and impatiently bucks his hips, causing his hot cock to grind up against your [pc.labia+]. Turned on by what's happening, and eager to do as you're told, you start gyrating your [pc.hips+] back into the lion-boy, and as his hard, ebony shaft slides up over your [pc.pussy+], you desperately beg for him to fuck you. Clearly eager to get started, the lion-boy responds to your request by giving you what you want, and you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] as you feel his cock push its way into your [pc.pussy+]. The moment he penetrates you, Kruger's harem starts excitedly commenting on your performance, and you continue to let out a stream of erotic [pc.moans] as you get fucked in front of them...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Wanting nothing more than to have sex with Kruger right here and now, you lean into him and desperately plead for him to fuck you. The lion-boy lets out a deep, rumbling growl of approval as he hears your request, and after reaching up to take hold of your shoulders, he gives you a firm push and growls, [kruger.speech(I can't get a blowjob from you, so get your ass down in my lap!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				One of the zebra-girls to your right lets out a giggle and leans over towards the lion-boy, then with a level of ease suggesting that she's done this countless times before, she swiftly pulls down both Kruger's trousers and underwear. Thanks to this, the lion-boy's [kruger.cockLengthValue], ebony cock is suddenly fully exposed, and you watch in delight as it rapidly rises to full erection. Just like the rest of Kruger's body, his throbbing dick has an anthropomorphic, feline quality to it, and you can't help but let out an eager, submissive whine as you see a series of soft, backwards-facing barbs lining its length. The surrounding lion and zebra-girls let out a chorus of giggles as they hear your reaction, and before you can make a move, the zebra-girl who exposed Kruger's cock suddenly pulls your [pc.legRace] lower body around to face the lion-boy, before exposing your [pc.asshole+] and pushing you down into his groin. Giving your rump a quick smack, she commands, [genericFemale.speech(Show Kruger some respect, slut. Rub that horny little [pc.legRace]-asshole over his cock and beg for him to fuck you!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Letting out yet another deep, rumbling groan, Kruger spreads his legs a little and impatiently bucks his hips, causing his hot cock to grind up against your [pc.ass+]. Turned on by what's happening, and eager to do as you're told, you start gyrating your [pc.hips+] back into the lion-boy, and as his hard, ebony shaft slides up over your [pc.asshole+], you desperately beg for him to fuck you. Clearly eager to get started, the lion-boy responds to your request by giving you what you want, and you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] as you feel his cock push its way into your [pc.asshole+]. The moment he penetrates you, Kruger's harem starts excitedly commenting on your performance, and you continue to let out a stream of erotic [pc.moans] as you get fucked in front of them...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
			<p>
				Wanting nothing more than to have sex with Kruger right here and now, you lean into him and desperately plead for him to fuck you. The lion-boy lets out a deep, rumbling growl of approval as he hears your request, and while dominantly reaching down between your [pc.legs] to give your [pc.pussy+] a good grope, he growls, [kruger.speech(I can't get a blowjob from you, so get this hot cunt of yours in my lap!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Upon hearing this, one of the zebra-girls to your right quickly leans over towards the lion-boy, then with a level of ease suggesting that she's done this countless times before, she swiftly pulls down both Kruger's trousers and underwear. Thanks to this, the lion-boy's [kruger.cockLengthValue], ebony cock is suddenly fully exposed, and you watch in delight as it rapidly rises to full erection. Just like the rest of Kruger's body, his throbbing dick has an anthropomorphic, feline quality to it, and you can't help but let out an eager, submissive whine as you see a series of soft, backwards-facing barbs lining its length. The surrounding lion and zebra-girls let out a chorus of giggles as they hear your reaction, and before you can make a move, the zebra-girl who exposed Kruger's cock suddenly pulls you to your [pc.feet], and after making sure that your [pc.pussy+] is fully exposed, she pushes you down into the lion-boy's lap. Giving your rump a quick smack, she commands, [genericFemale.speech(Show Kruger some respect, slut. Rub that horny little cunt over his cock and beg for him to fuck you!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Letting out yet another deep, rumbling groan, Kruger spreads his legs a little and impatiently bucks his hips, causing his hot cock to grind up against your [pc.labia+]. Turned on by what's happening, and eager to do as you're told, you start gyrating your [pc.hips+] into the lion-boy, and as his hard, ebony shaft slides up over your [pc.pussy+], you look into his [kruger.eyes+] and desperately beg for him to fuck you. Clearly eager to get started, the lion-boy responds to your request by taking hold of your [pc.hips+] and pulling you down, and you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] as you feel his cock push its way into your [pc.pussy+]. The moment he penetrates you, Kruger's harem starts excitedly commenting on your performance, and you continue to let out a stream of erotic [pc.moans] as you get fucked in front of them...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Wanting nothing more than to have sex with Kruger right here and now, you lean into him and desperately plead for him to fuck you. The lion-boy lets out a deep, rumbling growl of approval as he hears your request, and while dominantly reaching around to give your [pc.ass+] a good grope, he growls, [kruger.speech(I can't get a blowjob from you, so get this hot ass of yours in my lap!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Upon hearing this, one of the zebra-girls to your right quickly leans over towards the lion-boy, then with a level of ease suggesting that she's done this countless times before, she swiftly pulls down both Kruger's trousers and underwear. Thanks to this, the lion-boy's [kruger.cockLengthValue], ebony cock is suddenly fully exposed, and you watch in delight as it rapidly rises to full erection. Just like the rest of Kruger's body, his throbbing dick has an anthropomorphic, feline quality to it, and you can't help but let out an eager, submissive whine as you see a series of soft, backwards-facing barbs lining its length. The surrounding lion and zebra-girls let out a chorus of giggles as they hear your reaction, and before you can make a move, the zebra-girl who exposed Kruger's cock suddenly pulls you to your [pc.feet], and after making sure that your [pc.asshole+] is fully exposed, she pushes you down into the lion-boy's lap. Giving your rump a quick smack, she commands, [genericFemale.speech(Show Kruger some respect, slut. Rub that horny little asshole over his cock and beg for him to fuck you!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Letting out yet another deep, rumbling groan, Kruger spreads his legs a little and impatiently bucks his hips, causing his hot cock to grind up against your [pc.ass+]. Turned on by what's happening, and eager to do as you're told, you start gyrating your [pc.hips+] into the lion-boy, and as his hard, ebony shaft slides up over your [pc.ass+], you look into his [kruger.eyes+] and desperately beg for him to fuck you. Clearly eager to get started, the lion-boy responds to your request by taking hold of your [pc.hips+] and pulling you down, and you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] as you feel his cock push its way into your [pc.asshole+]. The moment he penetrates you, Kruger's harem starts excitedly commenting on your performance, and you continue to let out a stream of erotic [pc.moans] as you get fucked in front of them...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_VIP_KRUGER_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You collapse down to one side of Kruger, panting from exertion. As you take a moment to catch your breath, the dominant lion lets out a satisfied growl, before starting to get his clothing in order. [kruger.speech(That was fun.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah,)] you pant, smiling across at him.
	</p>
	<p>
		[genericFemale.speech(Mmm, yeah, that was a good show,)] one of the lionesses states, smiling at you as the rest of the girls nod in approval.
	</p>
	<p>
		Getting your own things in order, you stand up and tell Kruger that you need to head off for a while. Grunting in acknowledgement, he looks up at you and smiles. [kruger.speech(Come back soon [pc.name]. I want to take you for another ride.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Saying goodbye, you head off across the VIP area, before exiting back out into the main section of the club once more.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_VIP_KRUGER_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you've got other things to do, you turn to Kruger and explain, [pc.speech(I've got to head off now, Kruger. Maybe I'll get time to stop by later.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Kruger leans back on the sofa, and, letting out a deep growl, he replies, [kruger.speech(Sure. See you later.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, you stand up and head off across the VIP area, before exiting back out into the main section of the club.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DANCE_FLOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The middle of the club is taken up by a large dance floor, which is currently occupied by a huge crowd of revellers. It's from here that the bassy background music originates, and, looking up towards the ceiling, you see a series of arcane-powered loudspeakers, which are clearly responsible for blaring out the generic club music.
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite the huge amount of people dancing in front of you, there's still some space left. You could walk forwards and start to dance if you really wanted to.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DANCE_FLOOR_DANCE_SOLO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping forwards onto the dance floor, you allow yourself to get into the flow of the music, and, moving your body from side to side, start dancing with the revellers around you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although fun at first, you can't help but think that this would be a lot more enjoyable if you had someone to dance with. With such thoughts creeping up at the back of your mind, you start to lose your enthusiasm, and return to the edge of dance floor once more.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DANCE_FLOOR_DANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As this is the origin of the loud music which blares out throughout the club, you have to raise your voice to a shout in order to communicate with [npc.name]. Leaning in over [npc.her] shoulder, you ask, [pc.speech(Do you want to have a go at dancing for a while?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		From the happy smile and nod of [npc.her] head, you're sure that your suggestion is well approved of. Reaching down to take hold of [npc.namePos] [npc.hand], you lead [npc.herHim] onto the dance floor, before turning to return [npc.her] smile. 
	</p>
	<p>
		For the next several minutes, you and [npc.name] dance with one another, smiling and laughing as you get into the flow of the music and start to really enjoy yourselves. After a while of this, however, you both start to get a little worn out and thirsty, and when you see [npc.namePos] [npc.arms] drop to [npc.her] sides, you know that [npc.sheHas] had enough.
	</p>
	<p>
		Leading [npc.name] back out to the edge of the dance floor, you turn and smile at [npc.herHim], feeling happy with your decision to go dancing as you see the genuine look of enjoyment on [npc.her] face.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DANCE_FLOOR_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can tell that [npc.name] is wanting to be kissed, and, happy to give [npc.herHim] what [npc.she] wants, you take hold of [npc.her] [npc.hips] and pull [npc.herHim] up against you. Leaning forwards, you tilt your head slightly to one side, before pressing your [pc.lips] against [npc.hers].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DANCE_FLOOR_KISS_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping up to [npc.name], you lean forwards and try to kiss [npc.herHim]. Before your [pc.lips] can find their target, however, [npc.name] quickly pulls back with an astonished look of disapproval on [npc.her] face.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hey! Watch it!)] [npc.she] shouts over the noise of the dance floor, frowning angrily at you as [npc.she] pushes you away.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DANCE_FLOOR_GROPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In amongst the crowds of dancers, you lean in against [npc.name] and take hold of [npc.her] [npc.hips]. [npc.She] happily leans in against you, [npc.moaning] into your [pc.ear] as your [pc.hands] start roaming over [npc.her] body.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DANCE_FLOOR_GROPE_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leaning in against [npc.name], you place your [pc.hands] on [npc.her] [npc.hips], before trying to work your touch down to [npc.her] groin. [npc.She] instantly pulls away in response to your exploratory movements, and with an angry expression on [npc.her] face, [npc.she] shouts out over the noise of the dance floor,
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(S-Stop it! That's too much!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(What the fuck?! Keep your [pc.hands] to yourself!)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Hey! Cut that out! Keep your [pc.hands] to yourself!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You step back, giving [npc.name] some space and letting [npc.herHim] cool off. As [npc.her] expression softens a little, you move forwards again and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DANCE_FLOOR_SAVE_CLUBBER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you need to take a break from [npc.name], you shout out over the noise of the crowds and music, [pc.speech(Sorry [npc.name], but I've got to head off for a while! I'll catch you later, ok?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name]'s face drops as [npc.she] hears that you're leaving, before putting on a smile as [npc.she] leans forwards and shouts, [npc.speech(Sure thing [pc.name], I hope I'll see you another time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With one last smile thrown your way, [npc.name] turns and heads off into the crowd. With a sigh, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DANCE_FLOOR_LOSE_COMPANY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that [npc.name] isn't all you were hoping [npc.she]'d be, you call out over the background noise of the club, [pc.speech(I've got to head off now. Have a good night!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] seems a little deflated, but as you move away from [npc.herHim], [npc.she] turns around and starts dancing with someone else on the dance floor.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The club's toilets are far larger and cleaner than those of a typical nightclub, with at least twenty individual stalls running down one wall. Opposite the stalls, sinks and mirrors provide a place for the club's revellers to clean themselves, while plastered over the far wall there are a few dozen posters.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you walk past one of the open stalls, you see that someone's cut glory holes in the walls to either side, and obscene writing is scrawled beside each one. From the splatters of cum on the floor, you can tell that this stall sees regular use...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_GLORY_HOLE_USING_GET_READY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Entering one of the empty stalls adjacent to the one in which strangers service the glory holes, you push the door shut behind you, before turning to face the hole in the wall. As you do this, you hear someone enter the stall on the other side, and after just a moment, you see a flash of movement behind the glory hole.
	</p>
	<p>
		[game.random(
		[npc.speech(Come on, put your cock through here!)]
		|[npc.speech(Show me your cock! I need your cum!)]
		|[npc.speech(Come on babe, give me your cock!)])] a lust-filled voice suddenly calls out through the hole.
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder if you should do as [npc.name] says, or change your mind and make a hasty exit.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_GLORY_HOLE_START_USING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having already waited long enough, you quickly step up to the glory hole,
		#IF(pc.hasPenis())
			 preparing to have your [pc.cock+] sucked by the stranger on the other side.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasVagina())
			 preparing to have your [pc.pussy+] licked by the stranger on the other side.
		#ELSE
			 preparing to have your genderless mound licked by the stranger on the other side.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.she] sees the approach of your groin, [npc.name] lets out [npc.a_moan+], before shuffling closer to the wall and firmly pressing [npc.her] open mouth up against the hole. 
		#IF(!npc.isMute())
			 Letting out [npc.a_moan+], [npc.she] impatiently encourages you to get started, [game.random(
			[npc.speech(Oh yeah, come on! Let this whore show you what [npc.sheIs] capable of!)]
			|[npc.speech(~Mmm!~ Oh yeah! Let's get started!)]
			|[npc.speech(Oh yeah, babe! I'll show you how much of a slut I am!)])]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_GLORY_HOLE_USING_POST_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You step back from the glory hole, grinning as you hear [npc.name] let out a happy little [npc.moan]. As you get your things in order, you see a flash of movement through the hole, before the creak of a stall's door announces the horny slut's exit.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just a moment later, you're ready to continue back out into the club, and, reaching down to unlock the door of your stall, you open it and step back out into the toilets.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_GLORY_HOLE_SERVICING_GET_READY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling horny and eager to pleasure some stranger's cocks, you step into the cum-splattered stall. Having seen you enter, someone quickly steps into the stall adjacent to yours, before quickly pushing [npc.her] [npc.a_cock+] through the hole. As you look across at the [npc.cock+], its owner
		#IFnpc.isFeminine()
		#THEN barks out a sharp command,
		#ELSE lets out a deep grunt,
		#ENDIF
		 [game.random(
		[npc.speech(Come on slut, get to work!)]
		|[npc.speech(Start sucking, slut!)]
		|[npc.speech(Come on, you dirty slut, get started already!)])]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can respond, you hear someone else enter the stall on the other side, and, turning to look at the glory hole behind you, you see [npc2.a_cock+] thrusting forwards. With a buck of [npc2.her] [npc2.hips], this second stranger calls out,
		 [game.random(
		[npc2.speech(Come on whore. You can use your mouth, but if you've got a cunt, I want to give that a good fuck too!)]
		|[npc2.speech(Hurry up, whore! I want to fuck your ass, or even better, your cunt, if you've got one!)]
		|[npc2.speech(You can start with your mouth, but I want to fuck your ass, whore! Or even better, your slutty cunt, if you've got one!)])]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking back and forth between the cocks on offer, you wonder if you should do as the strangers say, and get started on servicing them. Then again, you could always change your mind and leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_GLORY_HOLE_START_SERVICING_PUBLIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to leave the stall's door open, so that anyone can come and watch you servicing these strangers' cocks, you kneel down on the floor of the toilet. Biting your lip, you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] as you prepare to show everyone what a dirty slut you are...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_GLORY_HOLE_START_SERVICING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Closing and locking the stall's door, you kneel down on the floor of the toilet, ready to service these strangers' cocks. Biting your lip, you can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] as you prepare to show them what a dirty slut you are...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_GLORY_HOLE_SERVICING_POST_SEX_PUBLIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You step back from the glory holes, grinning to yourself as you hear the strangers letting out a satisfied groan. The crowd that gathered to watch your slutty display starts to disperse, and as they leave, you start to get your things in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just a moment later, you're ready to continue back out into the club, and, stepping out of your stall, you head back out into the toilets. Glancing back at the stalls that were to either side of yours, you see that the occupants have already departed, leaving you with no clue as to whose cocks you just serviced...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_GLORY_HOLE_SERVICING_POST_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You step back from the glory holes, grinning to yourself as you hear the strangers letting out a satisfied groan. As you get your things in order, you see flashes of movement through the holes to either side of you, before the creaking of doors announces each of the strangers' exits.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just a moment later, you're ready to continue back out into the club, and, reaching down to unlock the door of your stall, you open it and step back out into the toilets. Glancing back at the stalls that were to either side of yours, you see that the occupants have already departed, leaving you with no clue as to whose cocks you just serviced...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking hold of [npc.namePos] [npc.hand], you lead [npc.herHim] into one of the stalls, before turning and locking the door behind you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Yes... Let's fuck already!)] [npc.she] moans, stepping forwards and leaning heavily against you, before pressing [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against your mouth.
	</p>
	<p>
		Returning [npc.namePos] kiss, you wrap your [pc.arms] around [npc.her], before letting your touch roam up and down [npc.her] body as you start to feel [npc.herHim] up. After a moment, [npc.she] pulls back, grinning wildly at you as [npc.she] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(~Mmm!~ Come on, [pc.name], fuck me...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun with [npc.name], the two of you collapse back against the toilet stall's walls, panting from exertion.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Fuck... That was great...)] [npc.name] sighs, smiling happily at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		You agree with [npc.namePos] assessment, and after the two of you have got your things in order, you unlock the stall's door and step over to the sinks. [npc.Name] splashes some water on [npc.her] face, before turning to smile at you.
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(I-I need to get going now. I'll meet you here again another time, right?)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(I've gotta get out of here now, but I'll catch you again, right?)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(I need to leave now, but I'll see you again, won't I?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_AFTER_SEX_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun with [npc.name], the two of you collapse back against the toilet stall's walls, panting from exertion. After a moment, [npc.name] crosses [npc.her] [npc.arms] and lets out a frustrated huff, [npc.speech(You didn't exactly satisfy me, you know...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After the two of you have got your things in order, you unlock the stall's door and step over to the sinks. [npc.Name] splashes some water on [npc.her] face, before turning to smile at you.
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(I-I need to get going now. That wasn't the best sex, but I still had fun... I'll meet you here again another time, right?)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(I've gotta get out of here now. You're pretty lousy at fucking, but I'd still like to hang out with you again. I'll catch you here another time, right?)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(I need to leave now. I don't really mind too much about the disappointing sex, so I'll see you again, won't I?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_AFTER_SEX_SEE_AGAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Of course I'll see you again!)] you enthusiastically reply, smiling at [npc.name] as [npc.she] steps back from the sink.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Great! Have a safe trip home!)] [npc.she] responds, stepping forwards to kiss you on the cheek before turning and leaving the toilets.
	</p>
	<p>
		With [npc.namePos] [npc.scent+] still lingering in the air, you let out a deeply satisfied sigh, and after taking a moment to reflect on what just happened, you wonder what you should do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_AFTER_SEX_DO_NOT_SEE_AGAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Erm, yeah, sure,)] you hesitantly reply, secretly hoping that you never see [npc.name] again.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Eugh, you could at least <i>try</i> to sound sincere,)] [npc.she] responds, letting out an annoyed huff before turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		With [npc.namePos] [npc.scent+] still lingering in the air, you let out a relieved sigh, and after taking a moment to reflect on what just happened, you wonder what you should do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_AFTER_SEX_DO_NOT_SEE_AGAIN_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Not likely,)] you reply, crossing your [pc.arms] and smirking at [npc.name]. [pc.speech(I don't think it's a good idea to get into a relationship with some slut who likes to get fucked in a club's toilet.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN[npc.speech(Y-You asshole! Y-You could at least pretend to care!)] [npc.name] stammers, tears welling up in [npc.her] [npc.eyes] as [npc.she] turns and rushes out of the room.
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN[npc.speech(Fine. If that's the way it is, fuck you too, you fucking [pc.bitch].)] [npc.name] snaps, glaring down at you for a moment before turning on [npc.her] heel and storming out of the room.
			#ELSE[npc.speech(Eugh. What [pc.a_bitch]. Fuck you too.)] [npc.name] snaps, before quickly turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With [npc.namePos] [npc.scent+] still lingering in the air, you let out a relieved sigh, and after taking a moment to reflect on what just happened, you wonder what you should do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_SEX_REJECTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking hold of [npc.namePos] [npc.hand], you try to pull [npc.herHim] over to one of the stalls in order to have sex with [npc.herHim], but [npc.she] angrily pushes you away, shouting, [npc.speech(I'm not going to fuck you in a toilet!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		A couple of the people at the sinks turn around and laugh as they hear that, and, ignoring their smirks, you turn towards [npc.name] and sigh, [pc.speech(Fine, fine. Let's do something else then.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Rolling [npc.her] [npc.eyes], [npc.name] crosses [npc.her] [npc.arms] and waits to see what you want to try next.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_USE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping into one of the empty stalls, you turn and lock the door behind you, before making use of the toilet. After a few moments, you flush it and unlock the stall's door, before stepping over to the sinks and washing your [pc.hands].
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've finished, you turn to face the room and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_WASH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling like you could do with having a quick clean, you step over to the sinks and thoroughly wash your [pc.hands], before splashing some water on your [pc.face]. Grabbing a paper towel from the nearby dispenser, you quickly dry yourself off, before turning to face the room and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_TOILETS_POSTERS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Walking] over to the far side of the room, you stop and take a look at the posters which are plastered all over the wall. Most of them are of a promotional nature, and display images of music bands, the newest cosmetic and clothing brands, or different types of food and drink.
	</p>
	<p>
		A few of these posters have a more sinister nature, however, and you see that they're displaying mug shots of dangerous-looking criminals. Wanted for crimes ranging from robbery and #IF(game.isNonConEnabled())rape#ELSEassault#ENDIF to kidnapping and sedition, the posters promise that these criminals will be caught eventually, and anyone caught aiding them will join them in a punishment of lifetime enslavement.
	</p>
	<p>
		The final poster of any note displays an idyllic scene of a happy family living in the countryside. The writing beneath promises a better life for anyone willing to leave Dominion and take the voyage over the 'Endless Sea' to the land beyond.
		#IF(game.isPlotDiscovered())
			 Knowing that this land must be mainland Europe, you can't help but doubt that the emigrating citizens of Dominion will have a life there similar to the one shown on the poster.
		#ELSE
			 Taking another look at the scene displayed upon the poster, you can't help but wonder what this promised land is like in reality.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Having seen all there is, you [pc.step] away from the posters and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_PLAYERS_ROOM_CLUBBER_TAKEN_HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Raising your voice to be heard over the background noise of the club, you lean in over [npc.namePos] shoulder and ask, [pc.speech(You want to come back to my place?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] grins as you pull back, nodding [npc.her] head and replying, [npc.speech(Sure, that sounds fun! Lead the way!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the [npc.race] in tow, you make your way out of the club, before heading back down Dominion's wide central boulevard towards Lilaya's mansion.
		#IFgame.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM
		#THEN
			#IFnpc.isVulnerableToArcaneStorm()
			#THEN Due to the ongoing arcane storm, [npc.name] keeps on trying to pull you to one side and start having sex with you, but you're determined to get back home before starting anything like that, and, pulling [npc.herHim] along, you continue on your way back home.
			#ELSE Although there's an ongoing arcane storm, [npc.name] is just as unaffected by it as you, and the two of you chat happily with one another as you travel back home.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE The journey is pretty uneventful, and you chat happily with one another as you travel back home.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Before long, you find yourself walking up the steps to the front door of the mansion, and [npc.name] stops in [npc.her] tracks as [npc.she] exclaims,
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(N-No way! You live here?! I-It's huge!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Woah! You live here?! This place is massive!)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Oh wow, you live here?! It's huge...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, it's a long story, I suppose it's sort of the family estate,)] you say, knocking the door.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, the door swings inwards, and Rose curtsies as she welcomes you back, [rose.speech(Good evening, [pc.name]. I see you have a guest. Will they need a room prepared?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping inside, you reply, [pc.speech(No, it's ok Rose, we'll just be in my room.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leading [npc.name] up the stairs and along the corridor, you can't help but smile as you hear [npc.herHim] gasping in astonishment at the size of the mansion. Opening the door to your room, you show [npc.name] inside, before turning to smile at [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_PLAYERS_ROOM_CLUBBER_TAKEN_HOME_CHANGE_MIND"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having got [npc.name] back into your room, you suddenly find yourself having second thoughts about the whole thing, and, looking across at [npc.herHim], you explain, [pc.speech(Hey, [npc.name], I'm sorry, but I'm not really feeling this right now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Oh...)] [npc.name] sighs, looking rather deflated.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'd like to see you at the club again, perhaps we can have some fun another time?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Yeah, that'd be good,)] [npc.name] replies, throwing you a half-hearted smile before turning to take [npc.her] leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		You show [npc.name] back down to the front door, and, after saying goodbye and returning to your room, you collapse down onto your bed and let out a deep sigh. You spend the next few minutes lying down and relaxing, before getting back on your [pc.feet] and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_PLAYERS_ROOM_CLUBBER_TAKEN_HOME_CHANGE_MIND_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having got [npc.name] back into your room, you suddenly find yourself having second thoughts about the whole thing, and, looking across at [npc.herHim], you bluntly state, [pc.speech(I don't really feel like fucking you after all.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Eugh, you could have at least tried to be diplomatic about it,)] [npc.name] snaps, before turning and walking over to the door.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Rose can show you out,)] you shout out after [npc.name], tugging on the bell-pull in order to summon the cat-girl maid.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.name] storms out of your room, Rose appears to show [npc.herHim] back down to the front door. Stepping back to collapse down onto your bed, you let out a deep sigh, and after lying down for a few minutes, you stand back up, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_PLAYERS_ROOM_CLUBBER_TAKEN_HOME_SEX_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking hold of [npc.namePos] [npc.hand], you lead [npc.herHim] over to your bed, before turning and pulling [npc.herHim] close.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Yes... Let's fuck already!)] [npc.she] moans, leaning heavily against you as [npc.she] presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against your mouth.
	</p>
	<p>
		Returning [npc.namePos] kiss, you wrap your [pc.arms] around [npc.her], before letting your touch roam up and down [npc.her] body as you start to feel [npc.herHim] up. After a moment, [npc.she] pulls back, grinning wildly at you as [npc.she] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(~Mmm!~ Come on, [pc.name], fuck me...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_PLAYERS_ROOM_CLUBBER_TAKEN_HOME_SEX_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking hold of [npc.namePos] [npc.hand], you lead [npc.herHim] over to your bed, before turning and wrapping your [pc.arms] around [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Yes... Let's fuck already!)] [npc.she] sighs, stepping forwards and leaning heavily against you, before pressing [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against your mouth.
	</p>
	<p>
		Returning [npc.namePos] kiss, you let out a muffled [pc.moan] as you slip your tongue into [npc.her] mouth. After spending the next few minutes kissing one another, you pull back and softly moan, [pc.speech(~Mmm!~ Come on, [npc.name], fuck me...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BACK_HOME_AFTER_CLUBBER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun with [npc.name], the two of you collapse down onto your bed, panting from exertion.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Fuck... That was great...)] [npc.name] sighs, smiling happily at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		You agree with [npc.namePos] assessment, and after spending a moment catching your breath, the two of you stand up and get your things in order. Stepping over to you, [npc.name] plants a quick kiss on your cheek, before smiling and saying,
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(I-I need to get going now. I'll meet you at the club again another time, right?)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(I've gotta get out of here now, but I'll see you at the club again, right?)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(I need to leave now, but I'll see you at the club another time, won't I?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BACK_HOME_AFTER_CLUBBER_SEX_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun with [npc.name], the two of you collapse down onto your bed, panting from exertion. After a moment, [npc.name] crosses [npc.her] [npc.arms] and lets out a frustrated huff, [npc.speech(You didn't exactly satisfy me, you know...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After spending a moment catching your breath, the two of you stand up and get your things in order. Stepping over to you, [npc.name] plants a quick kiss on your cheek, before smiling and saying,
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN [npc.speech(I-I need to get going now. That wasn't the best sex, but I still had fun... I'll meet you at the club again another time, right?)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN [npc.speech(I've gotta get out of here now. You're pretty lousy at fucking, but I'd still like to hang out with you again. I'll catch you at the club another time, right?)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(I need to leave now. I don't really mind too much about the disappointing sex, so I'll see you at the club again, won't I?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BACK_HOME_AFTER_SEX_SEE_AGAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Of course I'll see you again!)] you enthusiastically reply, smiling at [npc.name].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Great! I can't wait to see you again!)] [npc.she] responds, stepping over towards the door.
	</p>
	<p>
		You show [npc.name] back down to the front door, and, after saying goodbye and returning to your room, you collapse down onto your bed and let out a deep sigh. You spend the next few minutes lying down and relaxing, before getting back on your [pc.feet] and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BACK_HOME_AFTER_SEX_DO_NOT_SEE_AGAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Erm, yeah, sure,)] you hesitantly reply, secretly hoping that you never see [npc.name] again.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Eugh, you could at least <i>try</i> to sound sincere,)] [npc.she] responds, letting out an annoyed huff before turning and heading over to the door.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Rose can show you out,)] you shout out after [npc.name], tugging on the bell-pull in order to summon the cat-girl maid.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.name] storms out of your room, Rose appears to show [npc.herHim] back down to the front door. Stepping back to collapse down onto your bed, you let out a deep sigh, and after lying down for a few minutes, you stand back up, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BACK_HOME_AFTER_SEX_DO_NOT_SEE_AGAIN_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Not likely,)] you reply, crossing your [pc.arms] and smirking at [npc.name]. [pc.speech(I just wanted to give you a good fuck. I'm not interested in seeing you again.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isShy()
		#THEN[npc.speech(Y-You asshole! Y-You could at least pretend to care!)] [npc.name] stammers, tears welling up in [npc.her] [npc.eyes] as [npc.she] turns and runs over to the door.
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isConfident()
			#THEN[npc.speech(Fine. If that's the way it is, fuck you too, you fucking [pc.bitch].)] [npc.name] snaps, glaring down at you for a moment before turning on [npc.her] heel and heading over to the door.
			#ELSE[npc.speech(Eugh. What [pc.a_bitch]. Fuck you too.)] [npc.name] snaps, before quickly turning and heading over to the door.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Rose can show you out,)] you shout out after [npc.name], tugging on the bell-pull in order to summon the cat-girl maid.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.name] storms out of your room, Rose appears to show [npc.herHim] back down to the front door. Stepping back to collapse down onto your bed, you let out a deep sigh, and after lying down for a few minutes, you stand back up, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Dominant partner content -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_CHANGE_LOCATION_BAR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN [npc.speech(It's pretty hot in here. Come on, let's go and get something to drink,)] [npc.name] says, before taking your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers] and setting off in the direction of the bar. [npc.speech(I'll get you something nice!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Fuck, it's boiling in here! Come on [pc.babe], I'm thirsty,)] [npc.name] says, before taking your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers] and pulling you along behind [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] sets off in the direction of the bar.
			#ELSE [npc.speech(It's really hot in here. Come on, let's go and get something to drink,)] [npc.name] says, before taking your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers] and setting off in the direction of the bar.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Weaving your way through the bustling crowds which fill the club's main floor, both you and [npc.name] soon find yourselves standing before the bar. Thankfully, there's a gap in the crowd that's gathered to order drinks, and you and your partner step forwards to fill it. Leaning against the counter, you wonder what [npc.name] will decide to do now that you're here...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_CHANGE_LOCATION_DANCE_FLOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN [npc.speech(Let's head over to the dance floor,)] [npc.name] suggests, before taking your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers] and setting off towards the middle of club's main floor. [npc.speech(I love dancing!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Come on [pc.babe], I want to see you shaking that hot body of yours for me,)] [npc.name] says, before grabbing your [pc.hand] and pulling you along behind [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] sets off in the direction of the dance floor. [npc.speech(And don't you try dancing off with someone else! You're mine for tonight!)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Hey, [pc.name], let's go and check out the dance floor,)] [npc.name] says, before taking your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers] and setting off towards the middle of club's main floor. [npc.speech(After all, dancing is what's going to the club's all about!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Weaving your way through the bustling crowds which fill the club's main floor, both you and [npc.name] soon find yourselves stepping forwards onto the edge of the dance floor. As [npc.name] turns to face you, you wonder if [npc.sheIs] going to want to start dancing right away...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_CHANGE_LOCATION_SEATING_AREA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN [npc.speech(I think we'd be able to talk with one another a little easier if we went and sat down,)] [npc.name] says, before taking your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers] and setting off towards the nearest seating area. [npc.speech(We can also give our legs a rest for a while!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(My [npc.legs] are fucking killing me!)] [npc.name] complains, before grabbing your [pc.hand] and pulling you along behind [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] sets off towards the nearest seating area. [npc.speech(Come on, I want to sit down for a while!)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Come on, [pc.name], let's go and sit down for a little while,)] [npc.name] says, before taking your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers] and setting off towards the nearest seating area. [npc.speech(My [npc.legs] are aching from standing up for so long!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Weaving your way through the bustling crowds which fill the club's main floor, both you and [npc.name] soon find yourselves stepping into one of the club's many seating areas.
		#IF(!pc.isTaur())
			#IF(!npc.isTaur())
				 The noisy music originating from the central dance floor is a little quieter over here, and as you and [npc.name] sit down in one of the vacant booths, you wonder if [npc.sheIs] going to want to take this opportunity to talk with you for a little while...
			#ELSE
				 Taking a quick look around the area, [npc.name] spots an empty extra-large booth, which appears to be specifically designed to seat someone with a lower body like [npc.hers]. Leading you over to the wide sofa, [npc.name] gets you to sit down beside [npc.herHim], and you wonder if [npc.sheIs] going to want to take this opportunity to talk with you for a little while...
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(!npc.isTaur())
				 Taking a quick look around the area, [npc.name] spots an empty extra-large booth, which appears to be specifically designed to seat someone with a lower body like yours. Leading you over to the wide sofa, [npc.name] gets you to sit down beside [npc.herHim], and you wonder if [npc.sheIs] going to want to take this opportunity to talk with you for a little while...
			#ELSE
				 Taking a quick look around the area, [npc.name] spots an empty extra-large booth, which appears to be specifically designed to seat people with lower bodies like yours and [npc.hers]. Leading you over to the wide sofa, [npc.name] gets you to sit down beside [npc.herHim], and you wonder if [npc.sheIs] going to want to take this opportunity to talk with you for a little while...
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_CHANGE_LOCATION_TOILETS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN [npc.speech(Sorry, [pc.name], I need to use the toilet,)] [npc.name] apologises. [npc.speech(I'll only be a moment, so you're ok waiting for me over there, right?)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Come on, [pc.babe]! Watching your hot body all night's got me all fired up. The bouncers don't give a shit about people fucking in the toilets, so let's go do it in there,)] [npc.name] crudely states, before grabbing your [pc.hand] and pulling you along behind [npc.herHim] as [npc.she] sets off towards the toilets. [npc.speech(I hope you're better than the last fuck I had here!)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Come on, [pc.name], let's go have some fun!)] [npc.name] says, before taking your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers] and setting off towards the toilets. [npc.speech(The bouncers don't care about people fucking in there!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Weaving your way through the bustling crowds which fill the club's main floor, both you and [npc.name] soon find yourselves stepping into the club's toilet. Only the thudding bass from the club's music system can be heard in here, and as [npc.name] leads you inside, you hear some very erotic moans coming from one of the many stalls that run along one side of the wall...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_SEARCH_GENERATE_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having decided upon the sort of person you'd like to find, you set about searching through the bustling crowd of clubbers. Before long, you catch sight of [npc.a_raceFull(true)] standing all alone; just the sort of person you were looking for! Loitering around nearby, you try to catch [npc.her] [npc.eye], and are delighted when, after just a moment, [npc.she] notices you and starts to approach.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN As [npc.she] steps up before you, the [npc.race] throws you a charming smile and introduces [npc.herself], [npc.speech(I couldn't help but notice that you're all alone over here. I'm [npc.name], are you looking for some company for this evening?)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Hey [pc.babe]! You're lookin' awful lonely over here, and I can tell that you're wantin' a real good time. I'm [npc.name], and you can stick with me tonight, alright?)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Hello! I saw you standing all alone over here, and thought you could use some company. I'm [npc.name], by the way, do you want to hang out together?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, that sounds good,)] you reply, before introducing yourself and confirming that you're here without a partner this evening. You then spend the next few minutes talking with [npc.name], allowing [npc.herHim] to take the lead in conversation. It very quickly becomes apparent that [npc.she] wants to show you a good time this evening, and, leading [npc.herHim] on, you wonder where [npc.she]'ll take you first...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_CONTACTS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although there's a seemingly endless supply of new people to meet in the club, you find yourself wanting to spend some more time with one of your previous partners. With this thought in mind, you start looking through the crowds to see if you can find your friend...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_FIND_CONTACT_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Before long, you catch sight of [npc.a_raceFull(true)] standing all alone, and as you approach, you see that it's [npc.name]; just the person you were looking for! Loitering around nearby, you try to catch [npc.her] [npc.eye], and are delighted when, after just a moment, [npc.she] notices you and starts to approach.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN As [npc.she] steps up before you, [npc.name] throws you a warm smile and greets you, [npc.speech(Hello again, [pc.name], how are you? Are you looking for some company this evening?)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Hey, [pc.babe]! You're lookin' for a good time again, aren't you? Well, you just stick with me again tonight, alright?)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Hi, [pc.name]! I saw you standing all alone, and thought you might want some company. You want to hang out together again?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, that sounds good,)] you reply, before spending the next few minutes talking with [npc.name], allowing [npc.herHim] to take the lead in conversation. It very quickly becomes apparent that [npc.she] wants to show you a good time this evening, and, leading [npc.herHim] on, you wonder where [npc.she]'ll take you first...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_LEAVES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a frustrated sigh, [npc.name] [npc.steps] away from you and says,
		#IF(npc.isKind())
			[npc.speech(This really isn't working out. I think I'm going to leave now...)]
		#ELSE
			#IF(npc.isSelfish())
				[npc.speech(You're being a real cunt. Fuck this, I'm off.)]
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(This isn't working out. I'm off.)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As the [npc.race] turns and starts to head off into the club, you wonder how to respond...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_LEAVES_SAVE_CLUBBER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting this to be the end of your relation with [npc.name], you quickly say that despite how the evening has gone, you hope to see [npc.herHim] again.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isKind())
			[npc.speech(Fine... I guess I could meet up with you here again some other time... See you later,)] [npc.name] sighs, before continuing forwards and taking [npc.her] leave.
		#ELSE
			#IF(npc.isSelfish())
				[npc.speech(Really? After all the shit you just pulled? You'd better not be such a drag the next time we're doing this,)] [npc.name] bluntly responds, before abruptly turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Really? Well, I guess we could give it another go. I'll catch you around some other time,)] [npc.name] responds, before continuing forwards and taking [npc.her] leave.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that you're alone once more, you wonder what you should do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_LEAVES_LOSE_COMPANY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling as though you've had enough of [npc.namePos] company to last a lifetime, you call out after [npc.herHim] that you don't ever want to see [npc.herHim] again.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isKind())
			[npc.speech(That suits me. Bye, [pc.name],)] [npc.name] unhappily responds, before continuing forwards and taking [npc.her] leave.
		#ELSE
			#IF(npc.isSelfish())
				[npc.speech(Yeah, fuck you too, [pc.bitch]. Have fun getting fucked by one of your other cunt friends,)] [npc.name] rudely responds, before storming off to another part of the club.
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(The feeling's mutual,)] [npc.name] dismissively responds, before continuing forwards and taking [npc.her] leave.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that you're alone once more, you wonder what you should do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_DRINK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN
			#IF pc.isFeminine()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Let me buy you a drink, [pc.name]. Most of the stuff they sell here is pretty potent, but they also offer Feline's Fancy. You like that, right?)] [npc.name] asks, smiling at you as [npc.she] awaits your response.
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Let me buy you a drink, [pc.name]. Most of the stuff they sell here is pretty potent, but they also offer Canine's Crush. You like that, right?)] [npc.name] asks, smiling at you as [npc.she] awaits your response.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(I'm gonna get you a drink, [pc.babe]! And none of that weak shit, alright? They sell Black Rat's Rum here, so I'm getting you a glass of that,)] [npc.name] states, before turning and trying to get the attention of one of the zebra-girl barmaids. [npc.speech(Hey, come on! Over here, I'm lookin' to get served!)]
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Would you like a drink, [pc.name]? They sell Wolf Whiskey here, which is far better than all their other stuff. Here, let me order you a glass,)] [npc.name] says, before turning and trying to get the attention of one of the zebra-girl barmaids.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You could accept [npc.namePos] offer of a drink, which will surely make [npc.herHim] happy, or tell [npc.herHim] that you're not thirsty, which will undoubtedly disappoint [npc.herHim]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_ACCEPT_WOLF_WHISKEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thanks, [npc.name]!)] you shout out over the background noise of the club. [pc.speech(I'd love a glass of that!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Flashing you a smile, [npc.name] quickly calls over one of the barmaids, before placing [npc.her] order. [npc.speech(Yeah, two glasses of Wolf Whiskey, please!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After just a moment, the zebra-girl is placing the beverages on the counter before you, and, after [npc.name] pays for both of your drinks, the two of you talk with one another while drinking the strong whiskey. [npc.Name] finishes [npc.hers] first, and steps a little closer towards you as [npc.she] teases you in a friendly manner about taking so long to drink yours.
	</p>
	<p>
		Laughing and flirting back with [npc.name], you soon place your empty glass down on the counter before you. Smiling at your partner, you feel the alcohol starting to have an effect, and coyly brush up against [npc.herHim] as you thank [npc.herHim] for the drink.
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that the two of you have quenched your thirsts, you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_REFUSE_WOLF_WHISKEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Hey, wait!)] you call out, tugging [npc.namePos] [npc.arm] and stopping [npc.herHim] from ordering you a drink. [pc.speech(I don't want to get drunk tonight, ok? Wolf Whiskey is far too much.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Huh. Suit yourself,)] [npc.name] bluntly responds, not even trying to hide the annoyance in his voice. [npc.speech(I guess we'll just stick to water, huh?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, water's fine,)] you reply, disappointed that [npc.name] took your refusal so personally.
	</p>
	<p>
		Having confirmed that you're ok having a non-alcoholic beverage, [npc.name] gets the nearest barmaid's attention, before buying two bottles of Vanilla Water. Turning towards you, [npc.she] hands one to you and sighs, [npc.speech(Well, we can find fun stuff to do other than drinking.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Agreeing with your partner, and eager to make up for the disappointment of refusing the whiskey, you start chatting with [npc.name]. After just a few minutes, [npc.she] seems to have forgotten [npc.her] annoyance of a moment before, and, after the two of you have finished your bottles of water, you wonder what [npc.she] will want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_ACCEPT_FELINES_FANCY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thank you, [npc.name]!)] you shout out over the background noise of the club. [pc.speech(I'd love a glass of Feline's Fancy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Flashing you a charming smile, [npc.name] turns towards the bar, and, after getting the attention of the nearest zebra-girl barmaid, orders
		#IF npc.isFeminine()
		#THEN two glasses of the creamy alcoholic beverage.
		#ELSE one glass of the creamy alcoholic beverage, and one bottle of Canine Crush for [npc.herself].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After just a moment, the zebra-girl is placing the beverages on the counter before you, and, after [npc.name] has paid, the two of you start talking with one another while enjoying your drinks. [npc.Name] finishes [npc.hers] first, and continues leading the flow of conversation while [npc.she] calmly waits for you to finish yours.
	</p>
	<p>
		After listening to [npc.name] talk about [npc.herself] for a little while, you soon find yourself placing your empty glass down on the counter before you. Smiling at your partner, you feel the alcohol starting to have an effect, and coyly brush up against [npc.herHim] as you thank [npc.herHim] for the drink.
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that the two of you have quenched your thirsts, you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_ACCEPT_BEER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thank you, [npc.name]!)] you shout out over the background noise of the club. [pc.speech(I'd love a bottle of beer!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Flashing you a charming smile, [npc.name] turns towards the bar, and, after getting the attention of the nearest zebra-girl barmaid, orders
		#IF npc.isFeminine()
		#THEN one bottle of Canine Crush, and one glass of Feline's Fancy for [npc.herself].
		#ELSE two bottles of Canine Crush.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After just a moment, the zebra-girl is placing the beverages on the counter before you, and, after [npc.name] has paid, the two of you start talking with one another while enjoying your drinks. [npc.Name] finishes [npc.hers] first, and continues leading the flow of conversation while [npc.she] calmly waits for you to finish yours.
	</p>
	<p>
		After listening to [npc.name] talk about [npc.herself] for a little while, you soon find yourself placing your empty bottle down on the counter before you. Smiling at your partner, you feel the alcohol starting to have an effect, and coyly brush up against [npc.herHim] as you thank [npc.herHim] for the drink.
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that the two of you have quenched your thirsts, you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_REFUSE_FELINES_FANCY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thank you, but I don't want anything alcoholic,)] you explain. [pc.speech(Just a water would be fine for me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That's fair enough,)] [npc.name] replies, doing [npc.her] best to hide the disappointment in [npc.her] voice. [npc.speech(I'll get us a couple of bottles of water then.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.name] gets the nearest barmaid's attention, before buying two bottles of Vanilla Water. Turning towards you, [npc.she] hands you your drink, before leaning against the bar and starting to chat with you. After just a few minutes, the two of you have finished your bottles of water, and you wonder what [npc.she] will want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_REFUSE_BEER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thank you, but I don't want anything alcoholic,)] you explain. [pc.speech(Just a water would be fine for me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That's fair enough,)] [npc.name] replies, doing [npc.her] best to hide the disappointment in [npc.her] voice. [npc.speech(I'll get us a couple of bottles of water then.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.name] gets the nearest barmaid's attention, before buying two bottles of Vanilla Water. Turning towards you, [npc.she] hands you your drink, before leaning against the bar and starting to chat with you. After just a few minutes, the two of you have finished your bottles of water, and you wonder what [npc.she] will want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_ACCEPT_RUM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You wait by [npc.namePos] side as [npc.she] orders two glasses of Rum, and after just a moment, the barmaid places the beverages down on the counter in front of you. Paying for your drinks, [npc.name] turns towards you and grins. [npc.speech(Drink it down, [pc.babe]! And you'd better be grateful. This stuff ain't cheap!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you quickly empty the glass of Rum, before smiling at [npc.name] as [npc.she] compliments you on the speed at which you gulped it down. Almost immediately, you start to feel the potent effects of the strong alcohol, and, leaning in against your partner, you let out a flirtatious laugh as you feel [npc.herHim] reach around to squeeze your [pc.ass+].
	</p>
	<p>
		Steadying yourself against the bar's counter, you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_REFUSE_RUM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Hey, wait!)] you call out, stopping [npc.name] before [npc.she] can place [npc.her] order. [pc.speech(I don't want to get drunk, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Eugh, you ungrateful [pc.bitch]!)] [npc.name] snaps, before turning towards the barmaid who stepped forwards to take [npc.her] order. [npc.speech(Forget it, I'm not ordering anything. Go serve someone else.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You step back from [npc.name], frowning at [npc.herHim] in response to [npc.her] uncalled-for insult. Before you can say anything regarding the matter, [npc.she] moves back up beside you and apologises, [npc.speech(Sorry, [pc.babe]. I shouldn't have said that. Anyway, no harm done, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I suppose,)] you reply, wondering if you should ditch this rude [npc.race]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN Leaning against the bar's counter, [npc.name] starts flirting with you, offering you compliments on your appearance and mannerisms. [npc.Her] charming words are carefully chosen, and [npc.she] makes no move to initiate physical contact, preferring to wait and judge your response before taking things any further...
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN Leaning against the bar's counter, [npc.name] starts crudely flirting with you, offering you some very blunt compliments on your body shape and general appearance. While not the most charming, [npc.her] words do seem to be genuine, but before you can offer a response to this blunt style of flirting, [npc.she] quickly moves to initiate physical contact. Placing one [npc.hand] on your [pc.hips+], [npc.she] suddenly moves [npc.her] touch down to squeeze your [pc.ass+], grinning as [npc.she] tells you that [npc.she]'d like to do a lot more than just grope it...
			#ELSE Leaning against the bar's counter, [npc.name] starts flirting with you, offering you compliments on your appearance and mannerisms. [npc.Her] words are a little crude at times, but [npc.her] flattery does seem to be completely genuine, and, as further proof of [npc.her] good intentions, [npc.she] chooses to wait and judge your response before taking things any further...
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_FLIRT_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN
		<p>
			Smiling coyly at your partner, you offer [npc.herHim] some compliments of your own, which soon leads to an escalation in the sexual nature of your flirtatious conversation. Before long, you're both laughing and playfully touching one another, and while [npc.name] does [npc.her] best to keep things from going too far, several racy and highly suggestive comments have been made by both parties before the flirting comes to an end.
		</p>
		<p>
			As the two of you smile fondly at one another, you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
		</p>
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN
			<p>
				Blushing at [npc.namePos] indecent remarks, you find yourself getting more than a little turned on by [npc.her] direct comments and physical contact. Pushing your [pc.ass+] back against [npc.her] [npc.hand], you lean in towards [npc.name] and offer [npc.herHim] some very racy and suggestive comments of your own. This quickly leads into your partner making even more blunt, sexual remarks, which are accompanied by yet more squeezing and groping of your [pc.ass+].
			</p>
			<p>
				After a short while, [npc.name] pulls back, putting an end to the flirting. As you smile fondly at the [npc.race], you wonder what [npc.she] will want to do next...
			</p>
			#ELSE
			<p>
				Smiling coyly at your partner, you offer [npc.herHim] some compliments of your own, which soon leads to an escalation in the sexual nature of your flirtatious conversation. Before long, you're both laughing and playfully touching one another, which quickly escalates into a little more forceful contact from [npc.name], and [npc.she] dominantly slaps you on the ass a couple of times to accompany [npc.her] good-natured teasing.
			</p>
			<p>
				Several racy and highly suggestive comments have been made by both of you before the flirting comes to an end. As the two of you grin mischievously at one another, you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
			</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_FLIRT_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN
		<p>
			You're not really feeling the vibe that [npc.nameIs] giving off, and, pulling away from [npc.herHim] slightly, you tell [npc.herHim] that you'd like to keep the conversation a little less heated. Regretfully accepting your request, [npc.name] leans back against the bar, allowing a heavy silence to fall between the two of you for a moment, before continuing the conversation in a cooler manner than before.
		</p>
		<p>
			As the talk between the two of you starts to dry up, you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
		</p>
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN
			<p>
				You let out a shocked gasp as [npc.name] starts roughly squeezing your [pc.ass+], and, pushing [npc.herHim] away from you, you shout, [pc.speech(What do you think you're doing?! Stop that!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.Name] lets out a mocking laugh, before replying, [npc.speech(Ah, you're a feisty one, aren't you?! Come on, you know you love the attention!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Despite [npc.namePos] playful attempt to shrug off your angry response, you can tell from the tone of [npc.her] voice that [npc.sheIs] very annoyed. As further evidence of [npc.her] disgruntlement, [npc.she] turns away form you and leans heavily down against the bar, allowing a heavy silence to fall between the two of you. the flirting.
			</p>
			<p>
				Just as you're considering turning and walking off, [npc.name] pushes off from the bar's counter, before turning to face you once more...
			</p>
			#ELSE
			<p>
				You're not really feeling the vibe that [npc.nameIs] giving off, and, pulling away from [npc.herHim], you tell [npc.herHim] that you'd like to keep the conversation a little less heated. Clicking [npc.her] [npc.tongue] in annoyance, [npc.she] leans back against the bar, before allowing a heavy silence to fall between the two of you.
			</p>
			<p>
				After a little while, [npc.name] steps back from the bar's counter, before turning to face you once more...
			</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_GROPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN Feeling an increase in sexual tension between the two of you, [npc.name] steps up beside you, and, with a playful, flirtatious remark, places [npc.her] [npc.hand] on your [pc.hips+]. As [npc.she] starts to slide [npc.her] touch down and around to your [pc.ass+], you wonder if you should play along, and let [npc.herHim] feel you up, or quickly put a stop to this unsolicited contact.
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN Suddenly stepping forwards and pressing [npc.herself] against you, [npc.name] quickly places [npc.her] [npc.hands] on your [pc.hips+], before sliding [npc.her] touch down and around to firmly grab your [pc.ass+]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(Mmm, your hot ass belongs to me tonight!)]
			#ELSE Suddenly stepping forwards and pressing [npc.herself] against you, [npc.name] quickly places [npc.her] [npc.hands] on your [pc.hips+], before starting to slide [npc.her] touch down and around towards your [pc.ass+]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(Mmm, you're so sexy...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_GROPE_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turned on by [npc.namePos] dominant move, you happily lean in against [npc.herHim], letting out [pc.a_moan+] as [npc.she] starts feeling you up.
		#IF pc.hasBreasts()
		#THEN
				#IF npc.isKind()
				#THEN As one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] slip around to gently grope your [pc.ass+], [npc.name] lifts [npc.her] other one up to give your [pc.breasts+] a firm squeeze, drawing yet another [pc.moan] out of your mouth. Encouraged by your eager response, [npc.name] presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, passionately kissing you while continuing to run [npc.her] [npc.hands] over your body.
				#ELSE
					#IF npc.isSelfish()
					#THEN After a moment of using both of [npc.her] [npc.hands] to greedily grope your [pc.ass+], [npc.name] then shifts [npc.her] focus onto your chest. Letting go of your [pc.ass], [npc.she] quickly reaches up to give your [pc.breasts+] a firm, dominant squeeze, drawing yet another [pc.moan] out of your mouth. Encouraged by your eager response, [npc.she] then dominantly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, roughly kissing you while continuing to grope and fondle every part of your body.
					#ELSE As one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] slip around to greedily grope your [pc.ass+], [npc.name] lifts [npc.her] other one up to give your [pc.breasts+] a firm squeeze, drawing yet another [pc.moan] out of your mouth. Encouraged by your eager response, [npc.name] dominantly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, passionately kissing you while continuing to run [npc.her] [npc.hands] all over your body.
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
		#ELSE
				#IF npc.isKind()
				#THEN Encouraged by your lewd cry, [npc.she] slips both of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around your waist, before moving down to give your [pc.ass+] a firm squeeze. As you start to let out another [pc.moan], [npc.name] presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, passionately kissing you while continuing to grope and squeeze your [pc.ass].
				#ELSE
					#IF npc.isSelfish()
					#THEN Encouraged by your lewd cry, [npc.she] starts roughly squeezing and groping your [pc.ass+]. As you start to let out another [pc.moan], [npc.she] then dominantly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, roughly kissing you while continuing to have fun playing with your [pc.ass].
					#ELSE Encouraged by your lewd cry, [npc.she] slips both of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around your waist, before moving down to give your [pc.ass+] a firm, dominant squeeze. As you start to let out another [pc.moan], [npc.name] moves to press [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, passionately kissing you while continuing to grope and squeeze your [pc.ass].
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF pc.hasPenis()
	#THEN
		<p>
			#IF npc.isKind()
			#THEN As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to start rubbing up against your inner thigh. [pc.Moaning] lewdly into [npc.her] mouth, you press yourself ever closer against [npc.name] as [npc.her] [npc.fingers] roam up to stroke and squeeze your groin. Rubbing [npc.her] [npc.hand] against your [pc.cock+], [npc.she] pulls back from the kiss, grinning at you as [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(Mmm, getting hard already, are we?)]
			#ELSE
				#IF npc.isSelfish()
				#THEN As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to start dominantly rubbing up against your inner thigh. [pc.Moaning] lewdly into [npc.her] mouth, you press yourself ever closer against [npc.name] as [npc.her] [npc.fingers] roam up to roughly grope and squeeze your groin. Rubbing [npc.her] [npc.hand] against your [pc.cock+], [npc.she] pulls back from the kiss, before teasing, [npc.speech(You're getting hard already, huh? You just wait until I'm fucking you...)]
				#ELSE As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to start rubbing up against your inner thigh. [pc.Moaning] lewdly into [npc.her] mouth, you press yourself ever closer against [npc.name] as [npc.her] [npc.fingers] roam up to stroke and squeeze your groin. Rubbing [npc.her] [npc.hand] against your [pc.cock+], [npc.she] pulls back from the kiss, grinning at you as [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(Mmm, getting hard already? Perhaps we should head somewhere quiet...)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF pc.hasVagina()
		#THEN
			<p>
				#IF npc.isKind()
				#THEN Moving [npc.her] touch down beneath your [pc.cock+], [npc.name] curls [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starts gently rubbing at your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out an amused chuckle, [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(You getting wet down there too? Perhaps we could go back to my place soon. I'll make sure to take care of all your needs...)]
				#ELSE
					#IF npc.isSelfish()
					#THEN Moving [npc.her] touch down beneath your [pc.cock+], [npc.name] curls [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starts dominantly rubbing at your [pc.pussy+]. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(You're getting wet down there, aren't you, slut? What a whore, letting yourself get used like this in public! Fuck, I can't wait to fuck you tonight...)]
					#ELSE Moving [npc.her] touch down beneath your [pc.cock+], [npc.name] curls [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starts firmly rubbing at your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(You're getting wet, aren't you [pc.name]? Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF pc.hasVagina()
		#THEN
			<p>
				#IF npc.isKind()
				#THEN As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to gently rub at your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out an amused chuckle, [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(You getting wet down there? Perhaps we could go back to my place soon. I'll make sure to take care of you...)]
				#ELSE
					#IF npc.isSelfish()
					#THEN As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to dominantly rub at your [pc.pussy+]. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(You're getting wet down there, aren't you, slut? What a whore, letting yourself get used like this in public! Fuck, I can't wait to fuck you tonight...)]
					#ELSE As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to firmly rub at your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(You're getting wet, aren't you [pc.name]? Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				#IF npc.isKind()
				#THEN As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to gently rub at your genderless mound. Pulling back a little and biting [npc.her] [npc.lip], [npc.she] sighs, [npc.speech(Mmm, nothing down there, huh? Well, I'm sure we can have some fun, regardless. Perhaps we could go back to my place soon...)]
				#ELSE
					#IF npc.isSelfish()
					#THEN As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to dominantly rub at your genderless mound. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(You haven't got any genitals, huh? Well, I can still use your mouth and ass. Fuck, I can't wait to see what your orgasms are like, what with having nothing down there...)]
					#ELSE As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to firmly rub at your genderless mound. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(Mmm, nothing down there, huh? Well, I'm sure we can have some fun, regardless. Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_GROPE_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Shocked at [npc.namePos] brazen attempt to start feeling you up right here in front of everyone at the bar, you push [npc.herHim] away from you, before shouting out over the noise of the club, [pc.speech(What do you thin you're doing?! Stop that!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN [npc.speech(Sorry! I got a little carried away,)] [npc.name] sheepishly apologises, releasing [npc.her] grip on your [pc.hips] and stepping back to give you some space.
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Aww, don't be like that, [pc.babe],)] [npc.name] says, keeping [npc.her] tight grip on your [pc.ass+]. Completely shocked by [npc.her] refusal to listen, you end up pushing [npc.herHim] back once again, this time with a considerable amount of force. Thankfully, [npc.name] has to let go of you in order to steady [npc.herself], and you furiously shout at [npc.herHim] not to try anything like that again.
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Sorry! I thought that's what you wanted,)] [npc.name] tries to explain, releasing [npc.her] grip on your [pc.hips] and stepping back to give you some space.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Not amused in the slightest by [npc.her] attempt to feel you up, you angrily tell [npc.name] to keep [npc.her] [npc.hands] to [npc.herself]. After giving [npc.herHim] a piece of your mind, your outrage quickly fades away, and, letting out a sigh, you tell [npc.name] that you're happy to let [npc.herHim] continue leading the way.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_INVITE_HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leaning forwards, [npc.name] calls out over the noise of the crowd, [npc.speech(Hey, [pc.name], it's pretty loud and hot in here, and I was thinking of heading back home. Would you like to come back to my place?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After all the flirting you and [npc.name] have done this evening, you're both feeling very turned on, and you know that this invitation is an offer for the two of you to have sex back at [npc.namePos] house. You wonder if you should accept the offer, or turn [npc.herHim] down. If you were to refuse, [npc.name] will leave the club, but depending on the manner in which you say no, you could meet [npc.herHim] here again another time...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_INVITE_HOME_REFUSE_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sorry, [npc.name],)] you reply, [pc.speech(I'm not really feeling up for that this evening. I'd still like to see you here in the club another time, and maybe I'll come back to your place then?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That sounds good, I'll catch you here another time then, [pc.name],)] [npc.name] replies, before leaning forwards to give you a quick kiss on the cheek. [npc.speech(I'll head off now, bye!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You return [npc.her] farewell, watching as [npc.she] heads off into the crowd in the direction of the exit. Turning back towards the bar, you wonder what to do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_INVITE_HOME_REFUSE_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, I don't think so,)] you flatly reply. [pc.speech(This evening's been pretty boring, and I'm thinking you'll be as lousy in bed as have been at showing me a good time. Bye.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Huh, well, if that's how you feel, then fine,)] [npc.name] replies, turning [npc.her] back on you and marching off into the crowd in the direction of the exit.
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a frustrated sigh, you turn back towards the bar, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN Stepping forwards, [npc.name] tilts [npc.her] head to one side, leaning in against you as [npc.she] tries to give you a kiss. With just a moment before [npc.her] [npc.lips] press against yours, you need to decide whether to return [npc.her] amorous gesture, or to pull away and tell [npc.herHim] to back off...
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN Stepping forwards, [npc.name] tilts [npc.her] head to one side, before reaching out to grab your [pc.hips] and pull you up against [npc.herHim]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] moves to give you a kiss, and with just a moment before [npc.her] [npc.lips] press against yours, you need to decide whether to return [npc.her] amorous gesture, or to pull away and tell [npc.herHim] to back off...
			#ELSE Stepping forwards, [npc.name] tilts [npc.her] head to one side, leaning in against you as [npc.she] tries to give you a kiss. With just a moment before [npc.her] [npc.lips] press against yours, you need to decide whether to return [npc.her] amorous gesture, or to pull away and tell [npc.herHim] to back off...
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_KISS_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a happy [pc.moan], you lean in against [npc.name], mirroring [npc.her] movement and tilting your head to one side as [npc.her] [npc.lips+] press against yours.
		#IF npc.isSelfish()
		#THEN
			#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false)
			#THEN Taking a firm, dominant grip on your [pc.hips+], [npc.name] thrusts [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth, before starting to greedily make out with you. As [npc.her] [npc.tongue+] slides over yours, you feel [npc.her] [npc.hands] reach around to give your [pc.ass+] a firm squeeze, and, using this grip, [npc.she] roughly pulls you up against [npc.herHim].
			#ELSE As your mouth is blocked, [npc.name] has to make do with kissing your [pc.lips] and face. Taking a firm, dominant grip on your [pc.hips+], [npc.her] [npc.hands] reach around to give your [pc.ass+] a firm squeeze, and, using this grip, [npc.she] roughly pulls you up against [npc.herHim].
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false)
			#THEN Taking a firm grip on your [pc.hips+], [npc.name] slides [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth, before starting to passionately make out with you. As [npc.her] [npc.tongue+] slides over yours, you feel [npc.her] [npc.hands] reach around to give your [pc.ass+] a gentle squeeze, and, using this grip, [npc.she] firmly pulls you up against [npc.herHim].
			#ELSE As your mouth is blocked, [npc.name] has to make do with kissing your [pc.lips] and face. Taking a firm grip on your [pc.hips+], [npc.her] [npc.hands] reach around to give your [pc.ass+] a gentle squeeze, and, using this grip, [npc.she] roughly pulls you up against [npc.herHim].
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After a few minutes of this, your partner finally pulls back, allowing you to catch your breath as you grin happily at [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_KISS_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN Not wanting to be kissed by [npc.name], you pull back from [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] to keep [npc.her] distance. Immediately doing as you ask, [npc.she] apologises, [npc.speech(Sorry, [pc.name]! I got a little carried away, and misjudged the mood.)]
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN Not wanting to be kissed by [npc.name], you pull back from [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] to keep [npc.her] distance. Reluctantly doing as you ask, [npc.she] steps to one side and gives your [pc.ass+] a playful smack, before grinning lustfully at you. [npc.speech(Come on, [pc.name]! You can't fool yourself! You know you want me...)]
			#ELSE Not wanting to be kissed by [npc.name], you pull back from [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] to keep [npc.her] distance. Reluctantly doing as you ask, [npc.she] sighs, [npc.speech(Sure thing, [pc.name]. Perhaps you'll be up for some real fun later on tonight...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With no real harm done, you half-heartedly smile at the [npc.race], wondering what [npc.she] will try next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN Leaning against the bar, [npc.name] throws you a charming smile, before attempting to strike up a conversation with you. Spending a couple of minutes talking about
		#ELSE Leaning against the bar, [npc.name] smiles at you, before attempting to strike up a conversation. Spending a couple of minutes talking about
		#ENDIF
		#IF npc.getHistory()==OCCUPATION_NPC_UNEMPLOYED || npc.getHistory()==OCCUPATION_NPC_UNIVERSITY_STUDENT
		#THEN some of [npc.her] friends and the things they get up to in Dominion, [npc.she] then pauses to offer you a chance to give your input.
		#ELSE [npc.her] job as [npc.a_jobName], [npc.she] then pauses to offer you a chance to give your input.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_TALK_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You happily offer your opinion on [npc.namePos] everyday activities, before moving on to discuss several other things with [npc.herHim]. The conversation soon really starts to flow, and before too long, the two of you are chatting away and laughing with one another as though you're old friends.
	</p>
	<p>
		Soon enough, however, the two of you are ready to move on from idle chatter, and you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_BAR_TALK_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You roll your [pc.eyes] and let out a sigh, making it quite clear that you have no interest in talking about [npc.namePos] mundane everyday activities. [npc.She] doesn't take the hint at first, and continues trying to talk with you for a couple more minutes, but your persistent, dismissive humming noises and deep sighs soon cause [npc.herHim] to fall silent.
	</p>
	<p>
		Hoping that [npc.sheHasFull] something a little more fun planned for this evening, you wait to find out what [npc.she]'ll want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_DANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] takes your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers], before trying to lead you out onto the dance floor. [npc.speech(Come on, [pc.name]! Let's dance together!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You could allow yourself to be pulled out onto to dance floor, or tell [npc.name] that you're not interested in dancing right now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_DANCE_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Happy to have some fun dancing with [npc.name], you allow [npc.herHim] to lead you out onto the dance floor. Quickly finding yourselves in the middle of the noisy crowd of revellers, [npc.name] turns to face you, and, flashing you a smile, starts to dance to the music. You follow [npc.namePos] lead, and, dancing alongside one another, the two of you laugh and share smiles as you join the exuberant crowd in making the most of your evening. 
	</p>
	<p>
		After a short while, the heat and energy of the crowd starts to get a little too much for both of you, and, taking hold of your [pc.hand] once more, [npc.name] leads you back out to the edge of the dance floor, where [npc.she] turns and smiles at you. [npc.speech(That was fun! I think I need a breather now, though.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Agreeing with [npc.namePos] assessment, you join [npc.herHim] in taking a moment to catch your breath, before wondering what it is that [npc.she]'ll want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_DANCE_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You really don't feel like dancing, and pull your [pc.hand] away from [npc.namePos]. As [npc.she] turns around to see what's wrong, you shout out over the booming music and tell [npc.herHim] that you're not going to dance.
	</p>
	<p>
		A clear look of disappointment flashes across the [npc.race]'s face, but [npc.she] doesn't kick up a fuss about the fact that you're not interested in dancing with [npc.herHim]. Stepping back out to the edge of the dance floor, you wonder what it is that [npc.she]'ll want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_DANCE_GROPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isSelfish()
		#THEN Using the bustling crowd of dancers as cover, [npc.name] suddenly steps forwards and presses [npc.herself] against you. Quickly placing [npc.her] [npc.hands] on your [pc.hips+], [npc.she] slides [npc.her] touch down and around to firmly grab your [pc.ass+]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] [npc.moans] into your [pc.ear], [npc.speech(Mmm, your hot ass belongs to me tonight!)]
		#ELSE Using the bustling crowd of dancers as cover, [npc.name] suddenly steps forwards and presses [npc.herself] against you. Quickly placing [npc.her] [npc.hands] on your [pc.hips+], [npc.she] starts to slide [npc.her] touch down and around towards your [pc.ass+]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] [npc.moans] into your [pc.ear], [npc.speech(Mmm, you're so sexy...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_DANCE_GROPE_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turned on by [npc.namePos] dominant move, you happily lean in against [npc.herHim], letting out [pc.a_moan+] as [npc.she] starts feeling you up.
		#IF pc.hasBreasts()
		#THEN
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN After a moment of using both of [npc.her] [npc.hands] to greedily grope your [pc.ass+], [npc.name] then shifts [npc.her] focus onto your chest. Letting go of your [pc.ass], [npc.she] quickly reaches up to give your [pc.breasts+] a firm, dominant squeeze, drawing yet another [pc.moan] out of your mouth. Encouraged by your eager response, [npc.she] then dominantly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, roughly kissing you while continuing to grope and fondle every part of your body.
			#ELSE As one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] slip around to greedily grope your [pc.ass+], [npc.name] lifts [npc.her] other one up to give your [pc.breasts+] a firm squeeze, drawing yet another [pc.moan] out of your mouth. Encouraged by your eager response, [npc.name] dominantly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, passionately kissing you while continuing to run [npc.her] [npc.hands] all over your body.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN Encouraged by your lewd cry, [npc.she] starts roughly squeezing and groping your [pc.ass+]. As you start to let out another [pc.moan], [npc.she] then dominantly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, roughly kissing you while continuing to have fun playing with your [pc.ass].
			#ELSE Encouraged by your lewd cry, [npc.she] slips both of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around your waist, before moving down to give your [pc.ass+] a firm, dominant squeeze. As you start to let out another [pc.moan], [npc.name] moves to press [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, passionately kissing you while continuing to grope and squeeze your [pc.ass].
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF pc.hasPenis()
	#THEN
		<p>
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to start dominantly rubbing up against your inner thigh. [pc.Moaning] lewdly into [npc.her] mouth, you press yourself ever closer against [npc.name] as [npc.her] [npc.fingers] roam up to roughly grope and squeeze your groin. Rubbing [npc.her] [npc.hand] against your [pc.cock+], [npc.she] pulls back from the kiss, before teasing, [npc.speech(You're getting hard already, huh? You just wait until I'm fucking you...)]
			#ELSE As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to start rubbing up against your inner thigh. [pc.Moaning] lewdly into [npc.her] mouth, you press yourself ever closer against [npc.name] as [npc.her] [npc.fingers] roam up to stroke and squeeze your groin. Rubbing [npc.her] [npc.hand] against your [pc.cock+], [npc.she] pulls back from the kiss, grinning at you as [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(Mmm, getting hard already? Perhaps we should head somewhere quiet...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF pc.hasVagina()
		#THEN
			<p>
				#IF npc.isSelfish()
				#THEN Moving [npc.her] touch down beneath your [pc.cock+], [npc.name] curls [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starts dominantly rubbing at your [pc.pussy+]. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(You're getting wet down there, aren't you, slut? What a whore, letting yourself get used like this in public! Fuck, I can't wait to fuck you tonight...)]
				#ELSE Moving [npc.her] touch down beneath your [pc.cock+], [npc.name] curls [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starts firmly rubbing at your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(You're getting wet, aren't you [pc.name]? Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF pc.hasVagina()
		#THEN
			<p>
				#IF npc.isSelfish()
				#THEN As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to dominantly rub at your [pc.pussy+]. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(You're getting wet down there, aren't you, slut? What a whore, letting yourself get used like this in public! Fuck, I can't wait to fuck you tonight...)]
				#ELSE As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to firmly rub at your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(You're getting wet, aren't you [pc.name]? Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				#IF npc.isSelfish()
				#THEN As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to dominantly rub at your genderless mound. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(You haven't got any genitals, huh? Well, I can still use your mouth and ass. Fuck, I can't wait to see what your orgasms are like, what with having nothing down there...)]
				#ELSE As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to firmly rub at your genderless mound. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(Mmm, nothing down there, huh? Well, I'm sure we can have some fun, regardless. Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_DANCE_GROPE_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Shocked at [npc.namePos] brazen attempt to start feeling you up right here in front of everyone on the dance floor, you push [npc.herHim] away from you, before shouting out over the deafening music, [pc.speech(What do you thin you're doing?! Stop that!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isSelfish()
		#THEN [npc.speech(Aww, don't be like that, [pc.babe],)] [npc.name] replies, keeping [npc.her] tight grip on your [pc.ass+]. Completely shocked by [npc.her] refusal to listen, you end up pushing [npc.herHim] back once again, this time with a considerable amount of force. Thankfully, [npc.name] has to let go of you in order to steady [npc.herself], and you furiously shout at [npc.herHim] not to try anything like that again.
		#ELSE [npc.speech(Sorry! I thought that's what you wanted,)] [npc.name] tries to explain, releasing [npc.her] grip on your [pc.hips] and stepping back to give you some space.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Not amused in the slightest by [npc.her] attempt to feel you up, you angrily tell [npc.name] to keep [npc.her] [npc.hands] to [npc.herself]. After giving [npc.herHim] a piece of your mind, your outrage quickly fades away, and, letting out a sigh, you tell [npc.name] that you're happy to let [npc.herHim] continue leading the way.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_DANCE_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isSelfish()
		#THEN Stepping forwards, [npc.name] tilts [npc.her] head to one side, before reaching out to grab your [pc.hips] and pull you up against [npc.herHim]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] moves to give you a kiss, and with just a moment before [npc.her] [npc.lips] press against yours, you need to decide whether to return [npc.her] amorous gesture, or to pull away and tell [npc.herHim] to back off...
		#ELSE Stepping forwards, [npc.name] tilts [npc.her] head to one side, leaning in against you as [npc.she] tries to give you a kiss. With just a moment before [npc.her] [npc.lips] press against yours, you need to decide whether to return [npc.her] amorous gesture, or to pull away and tell [npc.herHim] to back off...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_DANCE_KISS_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a happy [pc.moan], you lean in against [npc.name], mirroring [npc.her] movement and tilting your head to one side as [npc.her] [npc.lips+] press against yours.
		#IF npc.isSelfish()
		#THEN
			#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false)
			#THEN Taking a firm, dominant grip on your [pc.hips+], [npc.name] thrusts [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth, before starting to greedily make out with you. As [npc.her] [npc.tongue+] slides over yours, you feel [npc.her] [npc.hands] reach around to give your [pc.ass+] a firm squeeze, and, using this grip, [npc.she] roughly pulls you up against [npc.herHim].
			#ELSE As your mouth is blocked, [npc.name] has to make do with kissing your [pc.lips] and face. Taking a firm, dominant grip on your [pc.hips+], [npc.her] [npc.hands] reach around to give your [pc.ass+] a firm squeeze, and, using this grip, [npc.she] roughly pulls you up against [npc.herHim].
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false)
			#THEN Taking a firm grip on your [pc.hips+], [npc.name] slides [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth, before starting to passionately make out with you. As [npc.her] [npc.tongue+] slides over yours, you feel [npc.her] [npc.hands] reach around to give your [pc.ass+] a gentle squeeze, and, using this grip, [npc.she] firmly pulls you up against [npc.herHim].
			#ELSE As your mouth is blocked, [npc.name] has to make do with kissing your [pc.lips] and face. Taking a firm grip on your [pc.hips+], [npc.her] [npc.hands] reach around to give your [pc.ass+] a gentle squeeze, and, using this grip, [npc.she] roughly pulls you up against [npc.herHim].
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After a few minutes of this, your partner finally pulls back, allowing you to catch your breath as you grin happily at [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_DANCE_KISS_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isSelfish()
		#THEN Not wanting to be kissed by [npc.name], you pull back from [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] to keep [npc.her] distance. Reluctantly doing as you ask, [npc.she] steps to one side and gives your [pc.ass+] a playful smack, before grinning lustfully at you. [npc.speech(Come on, [pc.name]! You can't fool yourself! You know you want me...)]
		#ELSE Not wanting to be kissed by [npc.name], you pull back from [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] to keep [npc.her] distance. Reluctantly doing as you ask, [npc.she] sighs, [npc.speech(Sure thing, [pc.name]. Perhaps you'll be up for some real fun later on tonight...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With no real harm done, you half-heartedly smile at the [npc.race], wondering what [npc.she] will try next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_FLIRT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(!pc.isTaur() && !npc.isTaur())
			#IF(npc.isKind())
				Leaning forwards over the small table, [npc.name] starts flirting with you, offering you compliments on your appearance and mannerisms. [npc.Her] charming words are carefully chosen, and [npc.she] makes no move to initiate physical contact, preferring to wait and judge your response before taking things any further...
			#ELSE
				Leaning forwards over the small table, [npc.name] starts flirting with you, offering you compliments on your appearance and mannerisms. [npc.Her] words are a little crude at times, but [npc.her] flattery does seem to be completely genuine, and, as further proof of [npc.her] good intentions, [npc.she] chooses to wait and judge your response before taking things any further...
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(npc.isKind())
				Leaning in towards you a little, [npc.name] starts flirting with you, offering you compliments on your appearance and mannerisms. [npc.Her] charming words are carefully chosen, and [npc.she] makes no move to initiate physical contact, preferring to wait and judge your response before taking things any further...
			#ELSE
				Leaning in towards you a little, [npc.name] starts flirting with you, offering you compliments on your appearance and mannerisms. [npc.Her] words are a little crude at times, but [npc.her] flattery does seem to be completely genuine, and, as further proof of [npc.her] good intentions, [npc.she] chooses to wait and judge your response before taking things any further...
			#ENDIF

		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_FLIRT_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN
		<p>
			Smiling coyly at your partner, you offer [npc.herHim] some compliments of your own, which soon leads to an escalation in the sexual nature of your flirtatious conversation. Before long, you're both laughing and playfully touching one another, and while [npc.name] does [npc.her] best to keep things from going too far, several racy and highly suggestive comments have been made by both parties before the flirting comes to an end.
		</p>
		<p>
			As the two of you smile fondly at one another, you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
		</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Smiling coyly at your partner, you offer [npc.herHim] some compliments of your own, which soon leads to an escalation in the sexual nature of your flirtatious conversation. Before long, you're both laughing and playfully touching one another, which quickly escalates into a little more forceful contact from [npc.name], and [npc.she] dominantly slaps you on the ass a couple of times to accompany [npc.her] good-natured teasing.
			</p>
			<p>
				Several racy and highly suggestive comments have been made by both of you before the flirting comes to an end. As the two of you grin mischievously at one another, you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_FLIRT_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN
			<p>
				You're not really feeling the vibe that [npc.nameIs] giving off, and, leaning back on your seat, you tell [npc.herHim] that you'd like to keep the conversation a little less heated. Regretfully accepting your request, [npc.name] backs off, allowing a heavy silence to fall between the two of you for a moment, before continuing the conversation in a cooler manner than before.
			</p>
			<p>
				As the talk between the two of you starts to dry up, you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				You're not really feeling the vibe that [npc.nameIs] giving off, and, pulling away from [npc.herHim], you tell [npc.herHim] that you'd like to keep the conversation a little less heated. Clicking [npc.her] [npc.tongue] in annoyance, [npc.she] leans back on [npc.her] seat, before allowing a heavy silence to fall between the two of you.
			</p>
			<p>
				After a little while, [npc.name] leans forwards once more, and you wonder what [npc.sheIs] going to do now...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_FOOTSIE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(!pc.isTaur() && !npc.isTaur())
			[npc.Name] throws you a playful smile, but before you can ask [npc.herHim] what's on [npc.her] mind, you suddenly feel [npc.her] [npc.foot] rubbing against your [pc.leg]. Your partner playfully laughs as [npc.she] starts to lift [npc.her] [npc.foot] up towards your groin, and you realise that unless you say something, [npc.sheIs] going to press it right into your crotch!
		#ELSE
			#IF(!pc.isTaur())
				#IF(npc.isKind())
					Feeling an increase in sexual tension between the two of you, [npc.name] shuffles up to press [npc.herself] against you, and, with a playful, flirtatious remark, places [npc.her] [npc.hand] on your [pc.hips+]. As [npc.she] starts to slide [npc.her] touch down and around to your [pc.ass+], you wonder if you should play along, and let [npc.herHim] feel you up, or quickly put a stop to this unsolicited contact.
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.isSelfish())
						Suddenly shuffling forwards and pressing [npc.herself] against you, [npc.name] quickly places [npc.her] [npc.hands] on your [pc.hips+], before sliding [npc.her] touch down and around to your [pc.ass+]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(Mmm, all of this belongs to me tonight!)]
					#ELSE
						Suddenly shuffling forwards and pressing [npc.herself] against you, [npc.name] quickly places [npc.her] [npc.hands] on your [pc.hips+], before starting to slide [npc.her] touch down and around to your [pc.ass+]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(Mmm, you're so sexy...)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Due to the fact that you have a rather unusual lower body, your rear end is quite outside of [npc.namePos] reach. This proves to be an issue for your partner, as, after making a feeble excuse about the cushion you're sitting on about to fall off the sofa, [npc.she] stands up and quickly moves over to kneel down beside your hind-quarters.
				<p>
				#IF(npc.isKind())
					After giving the sofa's cushion a quick pat, [npc.name] makes playful, flirtatious remark, before placing [npc.her] [npc.hand] on your [pc.hips+]. As [npc.she] starts to slide [npc.her] touch down between your [pc.legs], you wonder if you should play along, and let [npc.herHim] get a good feel of your lower half, or quickly put a stop to this unsolicited contact.
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.isSelfish())
						After giving the sofa's cushion a quick pat, [npc.name] confidently places [npc.her] [npc.hands] on your [pc.hips+], before immediately sliding [npc.her] touch down between your [pc.legs]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(Mmm, all of this belongs to me tonight!)]
					#ELSE
						After giving the sofa's cushion a quick pat, [npc.name] quickly places [npc.her] [npc.hands] on your [pc.hips+], before starting to slide [npc.her] touch down between your [pc.legs]. Leaning forwards, [npc.she] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(Mmm, you're so sexy...)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_FOOTSIE_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!pc.isTaur() && !npc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Happy to let [npc.name] do as [npc.she] wants, you [pc.spreadYourLegs] and sink down on your seat a little lower, pushing your groin out towards [npc.herHim] beneath the table. Biting your [pc.lip] and putting on your most seductive smile, you softly [pc.moanVerb], [pc.speech(Yes... Keep going...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Seemingly eager to do as you ask, [npc.name] runs [npc.her] [npc.foot] up the inside of your thigh, but before [npc.she] presses forwards into your groin, [npc.she] suddenly pulls back. Alarmed at [npc.her] sudden change in direction, you let out a pleading [pc.moan], which is exactly what [npc.name] was hoping for, as [npc.she] lets out yet another playful laugh, [npc.speech(Haha! You want me to continue, huh?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Yes!)] you instantly reply, the enthusiasm in your voice causing a huge grin to break out over [npc.namePos] face. 
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.hasLegs())
				[npc.speech(Well, if you insist,)] [npc.she] says, teasing [npc.her] [npc.foot+] up the length of your [pc.leg], before running down the inside of your thigh. Spreading your [pc.legs] a little wider, you again bite your [pc.lip] and plead for [npc.name] to continue.
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Well, if you insist,)] [npc.she] says, teasing [npc.her] [npc.foot+] up the length of your [pc.leg]. Feeling [npc.herHim] getting closer to your groin, you again bite your [pc.lip] and plead for [npc.name] to continue.
			#ENDIF
			 This time, your partner does exactly what you're asking for, and quickly pushes forwards to press [npc.her] [npc.foot] directly into your crotch.
		</p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenis())
			<p>
				You instantly let out [pc.a_moan+] as you feel the pressure rubbing against your [pc.cock+]. Looking into [npc.namePos] [npc.eyes+], you once again beg for [npc.herHim] to continue, and, eager to draw another of those [pc.moans] from between your [pc.lips], [npc.she] does exactly that.
			</p>
			#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				<p>
					Moving [npc.her] [npc.foot] down beneath your [pc.cock+], [npc.name] suddenly pushes forwards, ramming [npc.her] [npc.toes] up against your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out yet another [pc.moan+], you can't help but blush from the intense stimulation that [npc.namePos] [npc.foot] is applying to your [pc.clit+].
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				<p>
					You instantly let out [pc.a_moan+] as you feel [npc.her] [npc.toes] pressing firmly in against your [pc.pussy+]. Looking into [npc.namePos] [npc.eyes+], you once again beg for [npc.herHim] to continue, and, eager to draw another of those [pc.moans] from between your [pc.lips], [npc.she] does exactly that.
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					You instantly let out [pc.a_moan+] as you feel [npc.her] [npc.toes] pressing firmly in against your genderless mound. Looking into [npc.namePos] [npc.eyes+], you once again beg for [npc.herHim] to continue, and, eager to draw another of those [pc.moans] from between your [pc.lips], [npc.she] does exactly that.
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			This continues for several minutes, all of which are spent with you squirming about and [pc.moaning] from the delightful stimulation that [npc.namePos] [npc.foot+] is applying to your groin. Eventually, however, [npc.she] runs [npc.her] [npc.foot] back down the inside of your thigh, before dropping it to the floor and smiling playfully at you. [npc.speech(You really like that sort of stuff, huh?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You happily reply in the affirmative, and, panting from the intense stimulation, you push yourself back upright on your seat and prepare yourself for [npc.namePos] next move...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(!pc.isTaur())
			<p>
				Turned on by [npc.namePos] dominant move, you happily lean in against [npc.herHim], letting out [pc.a_moan+] as [npc.she] starts feeling you up.
				#IF pc.hasBreasts()
				#THEN
					#IF(npc.isSelfish())
						 After a moment of using both of [npc.her] [npc.hands] to greedily grope your [pc.ass+], [npc.name] then shifts [npc.her] focus onto your chest. Greedily reaching up, [npc.she] gives your [pc.breasts+] a firm, dominant squeeze, drawing yet another [pc.moan] out of your mouth. Encouraged by your eager response, [npc.she] then roughly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, thrusting [npc.her] tongue into your mouth while continuing to grope and fondle your [pc.breasts+].
					#ELSE
						 As one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] slips around to greedily grope your [pc.ass+], [npc.name] lifts [npc.her] other one up to give your [pc.breasts+] a firm squeeze, drawing yet another [pc.moan] out of your mouth. Encouraged by your eager response, [npc.name] dominantly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, passionately kissing you while lifting [npc.her] first hand to join the other in groping and fondling your chest.
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					#IF(npc.isSelfish())
					#THEN
						 Encouraged by your lewd cry, [npc.she] starts roughly squeezing and groping your [pc.ass+]. As you start to let out another [pc.moan], [npc.she] then dominantly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, roughly kissing you while continuing to have fun playing with your [pc.ass].
					#ELSE
						 Encouraged by your lewd cry, [npc.she] slips both of [npc.her] [npc.hands] around your waist, before moving down to give your [pc.ass+] a firm, dominant squeeze. As you start to let out another [pc.moan], [npc.name] moves to press [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, passionately kissing you while continuing to grope and squeeze your [pc.ass].
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			#IF pc.hasPenis()
			#THEN
				<p>
					#IF(npc.isSelfish())
						As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] down to start dominantly rubbing up against your inner thigh. [pc.Moaning] lewdly into [npc.her] mouth, you press yourself ever closer against [npc.name] as [npc.her] [npc.fingers] roam down to roughly grope and squeeze your groin. Rubbing [npc.her] [npc.hand] against your [pc.cock+], [npc.she] pulls back from the kiss, before teasing, [npc.speech(You're getting hard already, huh? You just wait until I'm fucking you...)]
					#ELSE
						As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] down to start rubbing up against your inner thigh. [pc.Moaning] lewdly into [npc.her] mouth, you press yourself ever closer against [npc.name] as [npc.her] [npc.fingers] roam down to stroke and squeeze your groin. Rubbing [npc.her] [npc.hand] against your [pc.cock+], [npc.she] pulls back from the kiss, grinning at you as [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(Mmm, getting hard already? Perhaps we should head somewhere quiet after this...)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				#IF(pc.hasVagina())
					<p>
						#IF(npc.isSelfish())
							Moving [npc.her] touch down beneath your [pc.cock+], [npc.name] curls [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starts dominantly rubbing at your [pc.pussy+]. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(You're getting wet down there, aren't you, slut? What a whore, letting yourself get used like this! Fuck, I can't wait to fuck you tonight...)]
						#ELSE
							Moving [npc.her] touch down beneath your [pc.cock+], [npc.name] curls [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starts firmly rubbing at your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(You're getting wet, aren't you [pc.name]? Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				#THEN
					<p>
						#IF(npc.isSelfish())
							As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] down to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to dominantly rub at your [pc.pussy+]. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(You're getting wet down there, aren't you, slut? What a whore, letting yourself get used like this! Fuck, I can't wait to fuck you tonight...)]
						#ELSE
							As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] down to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to firmly rub at your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(You're getting wet, aren't you [pc.name]? Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ELSE
					<p>
						#IF(npc.isSelfish())
						#THEN
							As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] down to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to dominantly rub at your genderless mound. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(You haven't got any genitals, huh? Well, I can still use your mouth and ass. Fuck, I can't wait to see what your orgasms are like, what with having nothing down there...)]
						#ELSE
							As the two of you continue making out with one another, [npc.name] moves one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] down to your groin, before curling [npc.her] [npc.fingers] up and starting to firmly rub at your genderless mound. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(Mmm, nothing down there, huh? Well, I'm sure we can have some fun, regardless. Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Turned on by [npc.namePos] dominant move, you happily buck your animalistic rear end back against [npc.herHim], letting out [pc.a_moan+] as [npc.she] starts feeling you up.
			</p>
			#IF pc.hasPenis()
			#THEN
				<p>
					#IF(npc.isSelfish())
						Wasting no time, [npc.name] quickly moves [npc.her] [npc.fingers] down to roughly grope and squeeze your groin. Rubbing [npc.her] [npc.hand] against your [pc.cock+], [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(You're getting hard already, huh? You just wait until I'm fucking you...)]
					#ELSE
						Encouraged by your eager response, [npc.name] moves [npc.her] [npc.hands] down to start rubbing against your inner thigh. [pc.Moaning] lewdly in response to [npc.her] touch, you shuffle back against [npc.name], encouraging [npc.herHim] to let [npc.her] [npc.fingers] roam down to stroke and squeeze your groin. Rubbing [npc.her] [npc.hand] against your [pc.cock+], [npc.she] grins at you as [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(Mmm, getting hard already? Perhaps we should head somewhere quiet after this...)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				#IF(pc.hasVagina())
					<p>
						#IF(npc.isSelfish())
							Moving [npc.her] touch up above your [pc.cock+], [npc.name] uses [npc.her] [npc.fingers] to start dominantly rubbing at your [pc.pussy+]. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(Getting wet down here, huh, slut? What a whore, letting yourself get used like this! Fuck, I can't wait to fuck you tonight...)]
						#ELSE
							Moving [npc.her] touch up above your [pc.cock+], [npc.name] uses [npc.her] [npc.fingers] to start firmly rubbing at your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(You're getting wet, [pc.name]... Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				#THEN
					<p>
						#IF(npc.isSelfish())
							Wasting no time, [npc.name] quickly moves [npc.her] [npc.fingers] down to start dominantly rubbing at your [pc.pussy+]. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(Getting wet down here, huh, slut? What a whore, letting yourself get used like this! Fuck, I can't wait to fuck you tonight...)]
						#ELSE
							Encouraged by your eager response, [npc.name] moves [npc.her] [npc.hands] down to start rubbing against your inner thigh. [pc.Moaning] lewdly in response to [npc.her] touch, you shuffle back against [npc.name], encouraging [npc.herHim] to let [npc.her] [npc.fingers] roam down to firmly rub at your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(You're getting wet, [pc.name]... Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ELSE
					<p>
						#IF(npc.isSelfish())
						#THEN
							Wasting no time, [npc.name] quickly moves [npc.her] [npc.fingers] down to start dominantly rubbing at your genderless mound. Leaning in towards you, [npc.she] lets out a commanding growl, [npc.speech(You haven't got any genitals, huh? Well, I can still use your mouth and ass. Fuck, I can't wait to see what your orgasms are like, what with having nothing down there...)]
						#ELSE
							Encouraged by your eager response, [npc.name] moves [npc.her] [npc.hands] down to start rubbing against your inner thigh. [pc.Moaning] lewdly in response to [npc.her] touch, you shuffle back against [npc.name], encouraging [npc.herHim] to let [npc.her] [npc.fingers] roam down to firmly rub at your genderless mound. Letting out a horny [npc.moan], [npc.she] bites [npc.her] [npc.lip] and sighs, [npc.speech(Mmm, nothing down there, huh? Well, I'm sure we can have some fun, regardless. Fuck, you're so fucking hot...)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_FOOTSIE_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!pc.isTaur() && !npc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Not wanting [npc.namePos] [npc.feet] anywhere near your groin, you quickly shuffle away from [npc.her] touch, before angrily frowning at [npc.herHim]. [pc.speech(Hey! Cut that out!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Ah, sorry, [pc.name],)] [npc.name] apologises. [npc.speech(I thought you might like that sort of thing...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You quickly inform [npc.name] that you definitely don't, and, after a few moments of heavy silence between the two of you, [npc.she] seems ready to try something else...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Not wanting [npc.namePos] [npc.hands] anywhere near your groin, you quickly shuffle away from [npc.her] touch, before angrily frowning at [npc.herHim]. [pc.speech(Hey! Cut that out!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Ah, sorry, [pc.name],)] [npc.name] apologises. [npc.speech(I thought you might like that sort of thing...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You quickly inform [npc.name] that you definitely don't, and, after a few moments of heavy silence between the two of you, [npc.she] seems ready to try something else...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_INVITE_HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leaning forwards, [npc.name] suddenly asks, [npc.speech(Hey, [pc.name], it's getting a little late for me, and I was thinking of heading back home. Would you like to come back to my place?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After all the flirting you and [npc.name] have done this evening, you're both feeling very turned on, and you know that this invitation is an offer for the two of you to have sex back at [npc.her] house. You wonder if you should accept the offer, or turn [npc.herHim] down. If you were to refuse, [npc.name] will leave the club, but depending on the manner in which you say no, you could meet [npc.herHim] here again another time...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SIT_DOWN_INVITE_HOME_REFUSE_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sorry, [npc.name],)] you reply, [pc.speech(I'm not really feeling up for that this evening. I'd still like to see you here in the club another time, and maybe I'll come back to your place then?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That sounds good, I'll catch you here another time then, [pc.name],)] [npc.name] replies, before shuffling round and leaning forwards to give you a quick kiss on the cheek. [npc.speech(I'll head off now, bye!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You return [npc.her] farewell, watching as [npc.she] stands up and heads off in the direction of the exit. Waiting until [npc.sheHas] departed, you wonder what to do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SIT_DOWN_INVITE_HOME_REFUSE_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, I don't think so,)] you flatly reply. [pc.speech(This evening's been pretty boring, and I'm thinking you'll be as lousy in bed as have been at showing me a good time. Bye.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Huh, well, if that's how you feel, then fine,)] [npc.name] replies, before standing up and marching off in the direction of the exit.
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a frustrated sigh, you wait until [npc.sheHas] departed, before standing up and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_KISS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Shuffling around on the seat until [npc.sheIs] pressing against you, [npc.name] tilts [npc.her] head to one side, before leaning in and trying to give you a kiss. With just a moment before [npc.her] [npc.lips] press against yours, you need to decide whether to return [npc.her] amorous gesture, or to pull away and tell [npc.herHim] to back off...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_KISS_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a happy [pc.moan], you lean in against [npc.name], mirroring [npc.her] movement and tilting your head to one side as [npc.her] [npc.lips+] press against yours.
		#IF pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false)
		#THEN Reaching up to take hold of the sides of your head, [npc.name] slides [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth, before starting to passionately make out with you. As [npc.her] [npc.tongue+] slides over yours, you feel the heat of [npc.her] body pressing against yours, and you can't help but let out a satisfied, and very muffled, sigh.
		#ELSE As your mouth is blocked, [npc.name] has to make do with kissing your [pc.lips] and face. As [npc.she] reaches up to take hold of the sides of your head, you feel the heat of [npc.her] body pressing against yours, and you can't help but let out a satisfied, and very muffled, sigh.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After a few minutes of this, your partner finally pulls back, allowing you to catch your breath as you grin happily at [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_KISS_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN Not wanting to be kissed by [npc.name], you pull back from [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] to keep [npc.her] distance. Immediately doing as you ask, [npc.she] apologises, [npc.speech(Sorry, [pc.name]! I got a little carried away, and misjudged the mood.)]
		#ELSE Not wanting to be kissed by [npc.name], you pull back from [npc.herHim] and tell [npc.herHim] to keep [npc.her] distance. Reluctantly doing as you ask, [npc.she] sighs, [npc.speech(Sure thing, [pc.name]. Perhaps you'll be up for some real fun later on tonight...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With no real harm done, you half-heartedly smile at the [npc.race], wondering what [npc.she] will try next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] shuffles up right next to you on the seat, and, leaning in towards you, [npc.she] whispers in a playful tone, [npc.speech(You know, nobody would notice if we had sex right here in this booth. Come on, it'll be so exciting!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isTaur())
			With that, [npc.she] quickly reaches forwards and takes hold of your [pc.hands], before trying to get you to stand up with [npc.herHim]. [npc.SheIs] clearly desperate to start having sex with you...
		#ELSE
			#IF(!pc.isTaur())
				With that, [npc.she] quickly reaches forwards and tries to pull you into [npc.her] lap, clearly desperate to start having sex with you...
			#ELSE
				With that, [npc.she] quickly reaches forwards and tries to get to you stand up, clearly desperate for you to reposition yourself so that your animalistic rear end is in [npc.her] lap...
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF(npc.isTaur())
		<p>
			Letting out a delighted [pc.moan] in response to [npc.namePos] suggestion, you allow yourself to be pulled to your [pc.feet] before [npc.herHim]. Once in this position, [npc.name] quickly leans forwards, before planting a passionate kiss on your [pc.lips+]. Eagerly returning [npc.her] display of affection, the two of you start passionately making out with one another.
		</p>
		<p>
			After a few moments of this, [npc.name] breaks away, before grinning and letting out [npc.a_moan] of [npc.her] own, [npc.speech(Mmm, yeah, now let's have some real fun!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(!pc.isTaur())
			<p>
				Letting out a delighted [pc.moan] in response to [npc.namePos] suggestion, you allow yourself to be pulled into [npc.her] lap. Once in this position, [npc.name] quickly leans forwards, before planting a passionate kiss on your [pc.lips+]. Eagerly returning [npc.her] display of affection, the two of you start passionately making out with one another.
			</p>
			<p>
				After a few moments of this, [npc.name] breaks away, before grinning and letting out [npc.a_moan] of [npc.her] own, [npc.speech(Mmm, yeah, now let's have some real fun!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Letting out a delighted [pc.moan] in response to [npc.namePos] suggestion, you do as [npc.she] then instructs, and, getting to your [pc.feet], you turn around so that your animalistic groin is facing [npc.herHim]. Looking back over your shoulder, you bite your lip as you then lower your rear end into [npc.her] lap, letting out [pc.a_moan+] as you prepare for [npc.herHim] to use you.
			</p>
			<p>
				Having got you to do as [npc.she] wanted, [npc.name] grins and lets out [npc.a_moan] of [npc.her] own, [npc.speech(Mmm, yeah, now let's have some real fun!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_SEX_REFUSE_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You gently push [npc.name] back, before sighing, [pc.speech(Sorry, [npc.name], I'm not really feeling up for that. I'd still like to see you here in the club another time, but I really don't want sex right now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Alright, that's fair enough. It's getting kind of late for me anyway, so I should get going,)] [npc.name] replies, before leaning forwards to give you a quick kiss on the cheek. [npc.speech(I'll head off now, bye!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You return [npc.her] farewell, watching as [npc.she] stands up and heads off in the direction of the exit. Waiting until [npc.sheHas] departed, you wonder what to do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_SEX_REFUSE_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You roughly shove [npc.name] away from you, causing [npc.herHim] to fall off [npc.her] seat. With an angry frown on your face, you scowl, [pc.speech(There's no way I'm fucking someone like you! Go on, get out of here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Fucking [pc.bitch],)] [npc.name] snaps, before standing up and marching off in the direction of the exit.
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a frustrated sigh, you wait until [npc.sheHas] departed, before standing up and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isKind())
			Leaning forwards over the table, [npc.name] throws you a charming smile, before attempting to strike up a conversation with you. Spending a couple of minutes talking about
		#ELSE
			Leaning forwards over the table, [npc.name] smiles at you, before attempting to strike up a conversation. Spending a couple of minutes talking about
		#ENDIF
		#IF(npc.getHistory()==OCCUPATION_NPC_UNEMPLOYED || npc.getHistory()==OCCUPATION_NPC_UNIVERSITY_STUDENT)
			 some of [npc.her] friends and the things they get up to in Dominion, [npc.she] then pauses to offer you a chance to give your input.
		#ELSE
			 [npc.her] job as [npc.a_jobName], [npc.she] then pauses to offer you a chance to give your input.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_TALK_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You happily offer your opinion on [npc.namePos] everyday activities, before moving on to discuss several other things with [npc.herHim]. The conversation soon really starts to flow, and before too long, the two of you are chatting away and laughing with one another as though you're old friends.
	</p>
	<p>
		Soon enough, however, the two of you are ready to move on from idle chatter, and you wonder what [npc.name] will want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SIT_DOWN_TALK_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You roll your [pc.eyes] and let out a sigh, making it quite clear that you have no interest in talking about [npc.namePos] mundane everyday activities. [npc.She] doesn't take the hint at first, and continues trying to talk with you for a couple more minutes, but your persistent, dismissive humming noises and deep sighs soon cause [npc.herHim] to fall silent.
	</p>
	<p>
		Hoping that [npc.sheHasFull] something a little more fun planned for this evening, you wait to find out what [npc.she]'ll want to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TOILETS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Firmly holding your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers], [npc.name] tries to pull you into the nearest empty stall, looking back over [npc.her] shoulder and grinning as [npc.she] says, [npc.speech(Come on, [pc.babe]! You've been teasing me all evening, now it's time for a good fuck!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Several of the people standing at the sinks turn their heads and laugh at [npc.namePos] loud statement, and you find yourself ready to tell your partner what you've been wanting to say all night...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TOILETS_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ah, yes! Take me, [npc.name]!)] you submissively cry, your heart racing at the thought of having sex with such a dominant [npc.race].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(That's what I like to hear!)] [npc.she] growls, pulling you into the stall and locking the door behind you. Before you're able to say anything else, [npc.she] forcefully presses [npc.her] [npc.lips+] against yours, passionately making out with you as one of [npc.her] [npc.hands] drop down to grope your crotch.
	</p>
	<p>
		After just a moment, [npc.she] pulls back, before grinning at you and letting out [npc.a_moan], [npc.speech(Mmm, yeah, let's get down to it!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TOILETS_SEX_START_REFUSE_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I-I'm not having sex in a toilet!)] you shout, pulling your [pc.hand] away from [npc.name] and standing your ground.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Eugh! Stupid [pc.bitch]!)] [npc.name] snaps, before squaring up to you and growling, [npc.speech(You'd better put out the next time I see you here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can respond to [npc.her] outrageous comment, [npc.she] storms off out of the toilets, leaving you standing alone amidst several onlookers, who immediately start whispering and laughing amongst themselves...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TOILETS_SEX_START_REFUSE_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(There's no way I'm having sex in a toilet!)] you shout, pulling your [pc.hand] away from [npc.name] and standing your ground.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Eugh! Stupid [pc.bitch]!)] [npc.name] snaps, before squaring up to you and growling, [npc.speech(You'd better put out the next time I see you here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF pc.isFeminine()
		#THEN [pc.speech(Fuck off!)] you shout, slapping [npc.name] across the face.
		#ELSE [pc.speech(Fuck off!)] you shout, roughly pushing [npc.name] away from you.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You fucking [pc.bitch]! Don't ever speak to me again!)] [npc.name] shouts in return, before storming off out of the toilets, leaving you standing alone amidst several onlookers, who immediately start whispering and laughing amongst themselves...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_SAVE_CLUBBER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling as though you've had enough of [npc.name] for one evening, but not wanting to break all contact with [npc.herHim], you clear your throat and explain, [pc.speech(Hey, [npc.name], sorry, but I'm feeling a little tired. I'm going to have to head off now, but I'll see you here again, right?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN [npc.speech(Oh, ok. Yeah, I'll catch you around some other time. See you later then, [pc.name],)] [npc.name] responds, smiling at you before turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Well, if you're gonna be like that, then fine. I hope you're not going to be such a drag the next time we're doing this,)] [npc.name] bluntly responds, before abruptly turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Yeah, sure thing, [pc.name]. I'll catch you around some other time. Take care,)] [npc.name] responds, smiling at you before turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that you're alone once more, you wonder what you should do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_LOSE_COMPANY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling as though you've had enough of [npc.namePos] company to last a lifetime, you let out an annoyed sigh, [pc.speech(I've had just about enough of you. I'm leaving. Don't bother to come say hello if you ever see me again, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN [npc.speech(Well, that was unexpected, but sure, if that's what you want. Bye, [pc.name],)] [npc.name] unhappily responds, before turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(Well, fuck you too, [pc.bitch]. Have fun getting fucked by one of your other cunt friends,)] [npc.name] rudely responds, before turning and storming off to another part of the club.
			#ELSE [npc.speech(Well, that was pretty blunt. Whatever. Bye,)] [npc.name] dismissively responds, before turning and taking [npc.her] leave.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that you're alone once more, you wonder what you should do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TAKEN_HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sure, that sounds fun,)] you reply, smiling at [npc.name] as [npc.she] takes hold of your [pc.hand], before leading you out of the club.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_RAIN
		#THEN As the two of you step out into the street, you're greeted by a thundering torrent of rain. Thankfully, [npc.name] has an umbrella with [npc.herHim], and the two of you walk closely side-by-side beneath its protective canopy as you make your way back to [npc.her] house.
		#ELSE
			#IF game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_SNOW
			#THEN As the two of you step out into the street, you're greeted by the sight of heavy snowfall. Thankfully, [npc.name] has an umbrella with [npc.herHim], and the two of you walk closely side-by-side beneath its protective canopy as you make your way back to [npc.her] house.
			#ELSE
				#IF game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM
				#THEN As the two of you step out into the street, you're greeted by the rumbling sound of arcane thunder. [npc.Name] instantly seems to be heavily affected by its arousing effects, and, without warning, pulls you up against [npc.herHim] and plants a passionate kiss on your [pc.lips]. After a moment of making out with one another, you gently push [npc.herHim] back, before reminding [npc.herHim] of your destination. Trying to shake [npc.her] head clear, [npc.she] takes hold of your [pc.hand], and the two of you set off at a run back to [npc.her] house, stopping ever now and then to kiss one another.
				#ELSE As the two of you step out into the busy street, [npc.name] turns towards you and smiles. Still holding your [pc.hand] in [npc.hers], [npc.she] tells you in what direction [npc.her] house is, and, setting off that way, the two of you make your way to [npc.her] house.
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		It doesn't take too long to get back to [npc.her] home, which turns out to be an apartment in one of the well-kept buildings lining Dominion's main boulevards. After stepping inside, the two of you make your way up a staircase to the second floor, where [npc.name] produces a key and unlocks the door to [npc.her] apartment.
	</p>
	<p>
		From [npc.her] home's expensive decor, as well as it's prime location in one of the most desirable parts of Dominion, you can tell that [npc.name] is very well off. You don't have too much time to appreciate your surroundings, however, because as soon as the door closes behind you, your partner wraps [npc.her] [npc.arms] around you, before pulling you into a passionate kiss.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment of making out with one another, [npc.name] takes hold of your [pc.hand] once more, before pulling you along towards one of [npc.her] apartment's interior doors. [npc.speech(Come on, [pc.name], my bedroom's right this way!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You realise that this is the last chance you'll have to change your mind, so if you were having second thoughts, now's the time to let [npc.name] know...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TAKEN_HOME_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Desperate to start having sex with [npc.name], you happily let [npc.herHim] lead you into [npc.her] bedroom. Stopping just in front of [npc.her] double-size bed, [npc.name] turns to face you, before passionately kissing you once again.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Moaning] happily into [npc.namePos] mouth, you allow yourself to be pulled in against [npc.her] chest, and, as the two of you prepare to have sex, you find yourself thinking how fortunate you are to have your evening turn out like this...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TAKEN_HOME_CHANGE_MIND"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stopping in your tracks, you shuffle your [pc.feet] a little as you tell [npc.name] what's on your mind, [pc.speech(Sorry, [npc.name], I'm having second thoughts about all this... I don't know if I can carry on.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Releasing your [pc.hand], [npc.name] turns to face you with a smile. [npc.speech(That's fine, don't worry about it, [pc.name]! I wouldn't want you to do this if you were feeling uncomfortable.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thanks for understanding. Perhaps I'll see you at the club another time?)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(I hope so, I really enjoyed our time together this evening. Have a safe journey home.)] [npc.name] says, smiling at you once again as [npc.she] leads you to the front door.
	</p>
	<p>
		After saying your goodbyes, [npc.Name] leans forwards and kisses you on the cheek. As the door shuts behind you, you let out a small sigh of relief. You're glad that you had the willpower to say no back there, and as you travel down the stairs and out into the street beyond, you feel happy that you didn't end up having sex with [npc.name]. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TAKEN_HOME_CHANGE_MIND_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You know, on second thoughts, I don't really want to get fucked by someone like you,)] you bluntly state, pulling your [pc.hand] away from [npc.name] and turning towards the door. [pc.speech(I don't know what I was thinking...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Oh... Well, bye, I guess,)] [npc.name] responds, clearly a little flustered by your abrupt change in attitude.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Don't bother saying hello if you see me at the club again,)] you call out behind you as you pull open the front door. Before [npc.name] can even respond, you step out and slam it behind you, before making your way down the stairs and out into the street beyond.
	</p>
	<p>
		Happy that you didn't get carried away and have sex with [npc.name], you set off on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TAKEN_HOME_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The two of you fall back on the bed, panting and sweating as you both stare up at the ceiling. As you're lying there, [npc.name] rolls over next to you, and pulls you into a loving hug.
	</p>
	<p>
		You spend the next ten minutes or so lying in [npc.namePos] embrace, before finally telling [npc.herHim] that you need to be on your way. Standing up and gathering your things, you head to the front door, with your partner walking along beside you.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.she] opens the door for you, [npc.name] asks if [npc.she]'ll see you at the club again, and you turn to give [npc.herHim] your answer...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TAKEN_HOME_AFTER_SEX_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The two of you fall back on the bed, panting and sweating as you both stare up at the ceiling. As you're lying there, [npc.name] makes a frustrated whining noise, and, rolling over next to you, [npc.she] sighs, [npc.speech(You didn't exactly satisfy me, you know...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You spend the next ten minutes or so lying next to [npc.name], before finally telling [npc.herHim] that you need to be on your way. Standing up and gathering your things, you head to the front door, with your partner walking along beside you.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.she] opens the door for you, [npc.name] asks if [npc.she]'ll see you at the club again, and you turn to give [npc.herHim] your answer...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TAKEN_HOME_AFTER_SEX_SEE_AGAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sure, I'll see you at the club again,)] you happily reply. [pc.speech(I had a really great time with you tonight.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Great, I had a fantastic evening as well,)] [npc.name] responds, before leaning forwards and kissing you on the cheek. [npc.speech(Bye, [pc.name], I'll see you another time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After saying farewell, you travel down the stairs and out into the street beyond. With a big smile on your face, you set off on your way... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TAKEN_HOME_AFTER_SEX_DO_NOT_SEE_AGAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Erm, yeah, well, I'm more of a one-night-stand kind of person,)] you reply. [pc.speech(I had a really great time with you tonight, but I don't know if seeing you again is a good idea.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Ah,)] [npc.name] responds, sounding more than a little disappointed. [npc.speech(Well, at least we had one great evening together.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After saying a quick goodbye, you travel down the stairs and out into the street beyond. Letting out a satisfied sigh, you set off on your way... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TAKEN_HOME_AFTER_SEX_DO_NOT_SEE_AGAIN_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I really just wanted a quick fuck,)] you reply. [pc.speech(I knew you'd be good for it, but now that I'm satisfied, there's no way I want to see you again.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Oh, well, I didn't expect that,)] [npc.name] responds, sounding more than a little surprised.
	</p>
	<p>
		Before [npc.she] can say anything else, you turn your back on [npc.herHim] and take your leave. Travelling down the stairs and out into the street beyond, you let out a satisfied sigh before setting off on your way... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_PARTNER_DOM_LEAVES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF npc.isKind()
		#THEN [npc.speech(Sorry, [pc.name], I'm not really having a good time. I'm leaving, have a good evening,)] [npc.name] says, half-heartedly smiling at you before turning and heading off into the crowd.
		#ELSE
			#IF npc.isSelfish()
			#THEN [npc.speech(You're just far too much of [pc.a_bitch] to be worth my time. See ya,)] [npc.name] says, before abruptly turning and heading off into the crowd.
			#ELSE [npc.speech(I'm really not having fun, [pc.name]. I'm off. Perhaps try being less of [pc.a_bitch] in the future,)] [npc.name] says, before abruptly turning and heading off into the crowd.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Finding yourself all alone in the club once again, you wonder what you should do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TOILETS_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had [npc.her] fun, [npc.name] quickly starts getting [npc.her] clothes back in order, grinning happily at you as [npc.she] does so. [npc.speech(You were a good fuck, slut. You've got no idea how many prudes back out at the last minute when I try to fuck them in here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.name] crudely compliments you, you start getting your own things sorted out, but before you've finished, your partner suddenly opens the stall door, exposing you to the rest of the room. Completely oblivious to what [npc.sheIs] doing, [npc.name] steps out of the stall, and in front of everyone, asks, [npc.speech(You'll come find me in the club if you want another good fuck, won't you [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hurriedly getting the last of your things in order, you step forwards and reply...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TOILETS_AFTER_SEX_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Putting an end to the sex, you quickly start getting your things back in order, ignoring [npc.name] as [npc.she] complains, [npc.speech(You haven't even satisfied me, and you want to stop fucking? For fuck's sake... I would've been better off bringing some other slut back here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.name] continues to blather on, you step past [npc.herHim] and open the stall door, exposing [npc.herHim] to the rest of the room. Quickly getting [npc.her] clothes back in order, [npc.name] follows you as you step out of the stall, and in front of everyone, [npc.she] asks, [npc.speech(You'll come find me in the club if you want a real fuck, won't you [pc.name]? You've got to make it up to me for what you just did back there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning around to face [npc.name], you give [npc.herHim] your reply...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TOILETS_AFTER_SEX_SEE_AGAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, sure, I'll see you around another time.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Good,)] [npc.name] replies. [npc.speech(I had fun tonight, even if you could have put a little more effort into it back there.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not even waiting to hear your reply, [npc.name] steps past you and hurries out of the room, leaving you standing alone in the toilets...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TOILETS_AFTER_SEX_DO_NOT_SEE_AGAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I don't know... I mean, I think doing this once might be enough for me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Fine, whatever,)] [npc.name] dismissively replies. [npc.speech(You were a lousy fuck anyway. I'll find someone better.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not even waiting to hear your reply, [npc.name] steps past you and hurries out of the room, leaving you standing alone in the toilets...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WATERING_HOLE_DOM_PARTNER_TOILETS_AFTER_SEX_DO_NOT_SEE_AGAIN_RUDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Not likely. There's no way I'm having sex with you again.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Well, fuck you too, [pc.bitch],)] [npc.name] snaps. [npc.speech(You were a lousy fuck anyway.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not even waiting to hear your reply, [npc.name] steps past you and hurries out of the room, leaving you standing alone in the toilets...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
