<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- LAB -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB"><![CDATA[
	#IF(lilaya.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_LILAYA_HOME_LAB)
		<p>
			Lilaya's laboratory is located in this particular corner of the house, and as you approach it, you see that the door has been left wide [style.colourGood(open)]. With no physical barrier blocking your way, you could simply step forwards and enter the lab, or continue on your way and choose to come back at another time.
		</p>
		#IF(!flags.hasFlag(FLAG_acexp_lilaya_daily_voyeurism))
			<p>
				As you stand before the door to Lilaya's laboratory, a lewd idea forms in your mind. Your demonic aunt and her cat-girl maid are always up to something whenever you enter, and you could try to sneak up on them and see for yourself what they're doing. All it would take is to move very quietly, and once you're inside, you're sure that you could find a good spot from which to observe them...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Lilaya's laboratory is located in this particular corner of the house, and as you approach it, you see that the door has been firmly [style.colourBad(closed)]. Considering the current hour, it's most likely that your [lilaya.relation(pc)] and her cat-girl maid have both retired to their rooms in order to get a good night's sleep. If you wanted to discuss something with Lilaya, you'll have to come back later during the day.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_PREGNANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach the door to Lilaya's lab, you notice that it's been firmly pulled shut. A little piece of paper has been stuck on it, and you see that your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] has left you a handwritten note:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		#IF(lilaya.isCondomBroke())
			<i>Hey [pc.name], I know the condom breaking wasn't your fault, but I need some time alone. I don't want anyone seeing me pregnant. Come back later after I've given birth.</i>
		#ELSE
			<i>Hey [pc.name], would you kindly fuck off and give me some time alone? I don't want anyone seeing me pregnant, especially not you! Come back later after I've given birth.</i>
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a defeated sigh, you decide to do as the note asks, and step back from the door.
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsBad(It doesn't look as though you're going to be able to get back in until Lilaya's pregnancy has run its course. Maybe Rose could help?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="LAB_PREGNANCY_RISK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach the door to Lilaya's lab, you notice that it's been firmly pulled shut. A little piece of paper has been stuck on it, and you see that demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] has left you a handwritten note:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		#IF(lilaya.isCondomBroke())
			<i>Hey [pc.name], I may have overreacted a little, but this really is all your fault for buying cheap crappy condoms. I'm keeping this door locked until I know if I'm pregnant or not.</i>
		#ELSEIF(lilaya.isAmazonsSecretImpregnation())
			<i>Hey [pc.name], I thought you could do with taking some time to think about what 'don't use Amazon's Secret next time you fucking asshole' could possibly mean. I'm keeping this door locked until I know if I'm pregnant or not. You'd better hope I'm not.</i>
		#ELSE
			<i>Hey [pc.name], I thought you could do with taking some time to think about what 'pull out next time you fucking asshole' could possibly mean. I'm keeping this door locked until I know if I'm pregnant or not. You'd better hope I'm not.</i>
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a defeated sigh, you decide to leave Lilaya alone for now, and step back from the door. It looks like you'll just have to wait until she's calmed down before seeing her again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_PREGNANCY_RESOLVED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking towards the door to Lilaya's laboratory, and as you get closer, you see that it's once again been left wide open. Realising that Lilaya's pregnancy must now have been resolved, you wonder if you should enter her lab right now, or continue on your way and choose to come back at another time.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- LAB_ENTRY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_DEMON_REACTION_PREGNANCY_RESOLVED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As Lilaya hasn't seen you since you were transformed into a demon by Lyssieth, you ready yourself for the worst as you step through the open doorway into her lab.
	</p>
	<p>
		On the opposite side of the room, you see your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] sitting at one of the long lab tables, busily performing an experiment. Noticing your entry out of the corner of her eye, she looks across and shoots you a furious glare, before starting to stand up. As she gets to her feet, you notice that she has a flat belly, so although there's still the issue of you being a demon at hand, at least the issue of her pregnancy has been resolved.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_DEMON_REACTION_NO_PREGNANCY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As Lilaya hasn't seen you since you were transformed into a demon by Lyssieth, you ready yourself for the worst and step through the open doorway into her lab.
	</p>
	<p>
		On the opposite side of the room, you see the half-demon who's now your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] sitting at one of the long lab tables, busily performing an experiment. Noticing your entry out of the corner of her eye, she looks across and shoots you a furious glare, before standing up and marching over to you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_DEMON_REACTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(I simply do <i>not</i> even know what to say!)] she yells in a shrill voice, before contradicting her statement by continuing, [lilaya.speech(I already heard from Meraxis via the resonance stone all about what mommy did! A full demon?! I didn't believe her at first! H-How could you?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(How else am I to defeat the other elder lilin without a demon's power?)] you respond with your own question as you try to reason with Lilaya. [pc.speech(Surely you can see how this is for the best?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Oh, I can see how it's for the best alright,)] Lilaya replies, crossing her arms and letting her voice take on a sinister, icy tone, [lilaya.speech(For my entire life, I've been begging mommy to turn me into a full demon, but no matter what I said, she always refused, telling me that she'd sworn never to turn anyone into a demon ever again. Now that she's quite clearly proven that her word means <i>nothing</i>, she has no choice but to finally give me what I want.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Lilaya, please, there's no-)] you start to reason, finding your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s cold, calculating voice to be of some concern, but you're not able to get even one sentence out before her composure breaks. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(<b><i>No!</i></b>)] she screams, [lilaya.speech(I won't hear any of it! Both you and mommy have betrayed me, so you can make it up to me by convincing her to finally turn me into a real demon! I <i>hate</i> being a half-demon! <b><i>I hate it!</i></b>)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although most of her anger seems directed at your now-shared mother, Lilaya is definitely more than a little upset with you. As you're wondering whether to agree with her demands and convince Lyssieth to transform her into a full demon, she continues,
		#IF(lilaya.getTotalTimesHadSex(pc)>0)
			 [lilaya.speech(And don't think for <i>one second</i> that I'm going to let you fuck me again until you agree to do as I say!)]
		#ELSE
			 [lilaya.speech(And don't think for <i>one second</i> that I'm going to offer you any special tests until you agree to do as I say!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that demonic transformations are permanent, you wonder what you should choose to say...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_PREGNANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping inside Lilaya's laboratory, you quickly scan the interior for any sign of life.
	</p>
	<p>
		On the opposite side of the room, you see your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] sitting at one of the long lab tables, busily performing an experiment. Noticing your entry out of the corner of her eye, she looks across and glares angrily at you, before starting to stand up. As she gets to her feet, you notice that her movements are slightly unusual, and as she steps around the table that she was working at, you see the cause of her clumsy motions taking the form of a clearly swollen belly.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Yes, that's right!)] she angrily shouts, before marching over towards you.
		#IF(lilaya.isCondomBroke())
			 [lilaya.speech(You ended up getting me pregnant! This is all your fault for using such cheap, crappy condoms! Why couldn't you have just pulled out instead?!)]
		#ELSEIF(lilaya.isAmazonsSecretImpregnation())
			 [lilaya.speech(You ended up getting me pregnant! I <i>told</i> you to pull back before you orgasmed! I knew this would happen!)]	
		#ELSE
			 [lilaya.speech(You ended up getting me pregnant! I <i>told</i> you to pull out! I knew this would happen!)]		
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Not giving you a chance to talk, she continues furiously scolding you, before launching into the reason as to why she's so upset to be pregnant, [lilaya.speech(You <i>know</i> I'm just a half-demon! That means all my kids end up as imps! Do you have any idea of how embarrassing and shameful it is to be called an 'imp-breeder', or 'imp-fucker'?! <i>Do you?!</i>)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you start to answer in the negative, Lilaya suddenly whacks you on the arm, and, with tears in her eyes, she shouts, [lilaya.speech(Get out! <b>Get out!</b>)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You try to apologise as your furious [lilaya.relation(pc)] marches you over to the door of her lab, but your words fall on deaf ears. With one last furious yell, she pushes you out into the corridor, before slamming the door shut and locking it behind you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.italicsBad(It doesn't look as though you're going to be able to get back in until Lilaya's pregnancy has run its course...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_NOT_PREGNANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping inside Lilaya's laboratory, you quickly scan the interior for any sign of life.
	</p>
	<p>
		On the opposite side of the room, you see your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] sitting at one of the long lab tables, busily performing an experiment. Noticing your entry out of the corner of her eye, she looks across and narrows her eyes at you, before standing up and marching over to where you're standing.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(You're a very lucky [pc.girl],)] she firmly states as she approaches, [lilaya.speech(As you can see, I'm not pregnant. You'd have been in so much trouble if I was!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(lilaya.isCondomBroke())
			[pc.speech(Well, it wasn't my fault the condom broke. Everything worked out fine in the end anyway,)] you say, sensing that Lilaya's anger won't last.
		#ELSE
			[pc.speech(Everything worked out fine in the end then,)] you say, sensing that Lilaya's anger won't last.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		True enough, she lets out a resigned sigh as you say that, and, lowering her voice, she continues, [lilaya.speech(Yes, it did. As we only ever give birth to imps, it's extremely embarrassing and shameful for half-demons to get pregnant. Even those who know that I'm the recognised daughter of Lyssieth herself would call me 'imp-breeder' or 'imp-fucker' behind my back... I <i>hate</i> being pregnant!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reassuring your [lilaya.relation(pc)] that everything's ok, you walk her back over to her lab table, where she lets out one final sigh and says that she forgives you for not pulling out like she asked. As her thoughts turn back to the sex which the two of you had, Lilaya starts hungrily staring at your body, and, with a sultry tone in her voice, she traces a finger over your chest and asks,
		#IF(lilaya.isCondomBroke())
			 [lilaya.speech(Now that you're here, would you like me to run some more <i>tests</i>? With the condition that you've got a proper condom this time, or that you'll be sure to pull out...)]
		#ELSE
			 [lilaya.speech(Now that you're here, would you like me to run some more <i>tests</i>? With the condition that you'll promise not to get me pregnant, of course...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder if you should take her up on that offer, or discuss some other business with her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_PREGNANCY_RESOLVED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping inside Lilaya's laboratory, you quickly scan the interior for any sign of life.
	</p>
	<p>
		On the opposite side of the room, you see your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] sitting at one of the long lab tables, busily performing an experiment. Noticing your entry out of the corner of her eye, she looks across and narrows her eyes at you, before standing up and marching over to where you're standing.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(I've decided to forgive you,)] she firmly states as she approaches, and as she comes to stand before you, you take note of the fact that her belly is flat once again. [lilaya.speech(As you can see, I've given birth, and the imps that you got me knocked up with are no doubt out there in Submission somewhere, causing trouble for everyone! They even tried stealing some of my lab equipment as they left...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sorry for the trouble,)] you say.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(lilaya.isCondomBroke())
			Your [lilaya.relation(pc)] lets out a resigned sigh as you say that, and, lowering her voice, she continues, [lilaya.speech(Yes, well, I've already forgiven you. It wasn't really your fault that the condom broke. Just know now that I <i>hate</i> being pregnant, so don't let this happen again.)]
		#ELSEIF(lilaya.isAmazonsSecretImpregnation())
			Your [lilaya.relation(pc)] lets out a resigned sigh as you say that, and, lowering her voice, she continues, [lilaya.speech(Yes, well, I've already forgiven you. Just know now that I <i>hate</i> being pregnant, so when I say pull back before you orgasm, I mean it.)]
		#ELSE
			Your [lilaya.relation(pc)] lets out a resigned sigh as you say that, and, lowering her voice, she continues, [lilaya.speech(Yes, well, I've already forgiven you. Just know now that I <i>hate</i> being pregnant, so when I say pull out, I mean it.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Reassuring your [lilaya.relation(pc)] that you now appreciate how much she dislikes being pregnant, you walk her back over to her lab table, where she lets out one final sigh and says that she really did try to warn you about pulling out. As her thoughts turn back to the sex which the two of you had, Lilaya starts hungrily staring at your body, and, with a sultry tone in her voice, she traces a finger over your chest and asks,
		#IF(lilaya.isCondomBroke())
			 [lilaya.speech(Now that you're here, and that whole business is behind us, would you like me to run some more <i>tests</i>? With the condition that you've got a proper condom this time, or that you'll be sure to pull out...)]
		#ELSE
			 [lilaya.speech(Now that you're here, and that whole business is behind us, would you like me to run some more <i>tests</i>? With the condition that you'll promise not to get me pregnant, of course...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder if you should take her up on that offer, or discuss some other business with her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_BASE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping inside Lilaya's laboratory, you quickly scan the interior for any sign of life.
	</p>
	<p>
		On the opposite side of the room, you see your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] sitting at one of the long lab tables, with her back to the door. Open books and sheets of paper litter the tabletop and floor around her, but she seems far more interested in something other than work at the moment. Rose is straddling her lap, leaning in against Lilaya's chest as she whispers down to her demonic mistress. You see your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s hand reaching up Rose's skirt, and from the movement of her arm, you can tell that she's fingering her cat-girl maid.
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can say anything, you hear some surprising words coming out of Rose's mouth as she moans down into Lilaya's ear,
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_NAUGHTY_ROSE"><![CDATA[
		 [rose.speech(~Mmm!~ That's right, you horny little slut. ~Aah!~ Come on, please your Mistress!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_NAUGHTY_ROSE"><![CDATA[
		 [rose.speech(~Mmm!~ That's right, slut. ~Aah!~ Do a good job, and maybe this'll be the year I let you fuck me!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_NAUGHTY_ROSE"><![CDATA[
		 [rose.speech(~Mmm!~ Come on, slut, you can do better than that! ~Aah!~ Yes, get those fingers in deeper!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_NAUGHTY_ROSE"><![CDATA[
		 [rose.speech(~Ooh!~ You dirty little slut! ~Mmm!~ That's right, focus on my clit a little more!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_NAUGHTY_ROSE"><![CDATA[
		 [rose.speech(~Ooh!~ Yes, that's it, slut, focus on my clit! ~Mmm!~ Maybe I'll let you use your tongue tonight!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_ROSE_TOLD_ON_YOU_DEMON"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Rose hooks her arms around Lilaya's neck and leans back, letting out a deep moan as her owner's fingers continue working away between her legs. She suddenly notices you out of the corner of her eye, and, turning to give you an evil grin, she pointedly grinds down against your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)], before letting out a little eek and jumping to her feet as she feigns surprise. [rose.speech(M-Mistress! [pc.NameIsFull] here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya, upon hearing that, mirrors her maid's movements and jumps out of her chair. [lilaya.speech([pc.Name]! E-Erm, w-we were just... Doing an experiment! Yes! Isn't that right, Rose?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[rose.speech(Yes, Mistress!)] Rose squeaks in agreement, [rose.speech(That's right!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Brushing down her skirt, Lilaya blushes a little and clears her throat, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ Well, it's a good job that you came here to see me, [pc.name]. Rose has already told me all about your little adventure in my room with my underwear. So, what do you have to say for yourself?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're indebted to Lilaya for allowing you to live here, you see no other option but to apologise. Stepping forwards, you make up an excuse and say, [pc.speech(I'm sorry, Lilaya. I don't know what came over me. It must be this arcane aura of mine... or something...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Hmm... Well, I've already told you that you're not getting any sex from me until you help me convince mommy to turn me into a full demon. As you're quite clearly desperate for it, perhaps you should just do as I say already!)] Lilaya exclaims in her sternest voice.
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder if you should agree to convince Lyssieth to permanently transform Lilaya into a full demon, or just ask about some other business...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_BASE_END_DEMON"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Rose hooks her arms around Lilaya's neck and leans back, letting out a deep moan as her owner's fingers continue working away between her legs. She suddenly notices you out of the corner of her eye, and, letting out a little eek, she quickly leaps up onto her feet. [rose.speech(M-Mistress! [pc.NamePos] here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya, upon hearing that, mirrors her maid's movements and jumps out of her chair. [lilaya.speech([pc.Name]! E-Erm, w-we were just... Doing an experiment! Yes! Isn't that right, Rose?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[rose.speech(Yes, Mistress!)] Rose squeaks in agreement, [rose.speech(That's right!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Brushing down her skirt, Lilaya clears her throat, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ So, have you changed your mind, [pc.name]? You're ready to convince mommy to turn me into a full demon as well, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_ROSE_TOLD_ON_YOU"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Rose hooks her arms around Lilaya's neck and leans back, letting out a deep moan as her owner's fingers continue working away between her legs. She suddenly notices you out of the corner of her eye, and, turning to give you an evil grin, she pointedly grinds down against your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)], before letting out a little eek and jumping to her feet as she feigns surprise. [rose.speech(M-Mistress! [pc.NameIsFull] here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya, upon hearing that, mirrors her maid's movements and jumps out of her chair. [lilaya.speech([pc.Name]! E-Erm, w-we were just... Doing an experiment! Yes! Isn't that right, Rose?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[rose.speech(Yes, Mistress!)] Rose squeaks in agreement, [rose.speech(That's right!)]
	</p>
	<p>
	#IF !lilaya.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc) && !lilaya.getBaseFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative() && lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant()
	#THEN
		#IF lilaya.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(pc.getId())
		#THEN
			As Lilaya brushes down her skirt, you can't help but notice the visible bulge in her belly. As she sees what it is you're looking at, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] clears her throat and confirms, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ Yes, [pc.name], you got me pregnant. As I'm a full demon now, it's really no big deal... As I'm not going to be birthing any imps, I don't mind it at all. But anyway, it's a good job that you came here to see me, [pc.name]. Rose has already told me all about your little adventure in my room with my underwear. So, what do you have to say for yourself?)]
		#ELSE
			As Lilaya brushes down her skirt, you can't help but notice the visible bulge in her belly. As she sees what it is you're looking at, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] clears her throat and confirms, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ Yes, [pc.name], mommy got me pregnant. As I'm a full demon now, it's really no big deal... As I'm not going to be birthing any imps, I don't mind it at all. But anyway, it's a good job that you came here to see me, [pc.name]. Rose has already told me all about your little adventure in my room with my underwear. So, what do you have to say for yourself?)]
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF !lilaya.getBaseFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative() && lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant()
		#THEN
			As Lilaya brushes down her skirt, you can't help but notice that she's still got a very visible bulge in her belly. As she sees what it is you're looking at, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] clears her throat and confirms, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ Yes, [pc.name], I'm still pregnant... But anyway, it's a good job that you came here to see me. Rose has already told me all about your little adventure in my room with my underwear. So, what do you have to say for yourself?)]
		#ELSE
			Brushing down her skirt, Lilaya blushes a little and clears her throat, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ Well, it's a good job that you came here to see me, [pc.name]. Rose has already told me all about your little adventure in my room with my underwear. So, what do you have to say for yourself?)]
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As you're indebted to Lilaya for allowing you to live here, you see no other option but to apologise. Stepping forwards, you make up an excuse and say, [pc.speech(I'm sorry, Lilaya. I don't know what came over me. It must be this arcane aura of mine... or something...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Hmm... Well, if you find yourself feeling like that, there's no need to sneak off into my room. J-Just come back here and I-I can run some tests on you! O-Ok?)] Lilaya responds, trying her best to sound stern and in control, but ultimately failing as her thoughts shift to wanting to do lewd things with you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, Lilaya,)] you respond, much in the same way you always used to with your aunt Lily.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(So, now that that's out of the way, what is it you need?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_BASE_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Rose hooks her arms around Lilaya's neck and leans back, letting out a deep moan as her owner's fingers continue working away between her legs. She suddenly notices you out of the corner of her eye, and, letting out a little eek, she quickly leaps up onto her feet. [rose.speech(M-Mistress! [pc.NamePos] here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya, upon hearing that, mirrors her maid's movements and jumps out of her chair. [lilaya.speech([pc.Name]! E-Erm, w-we were just... Doing an experiment! Yes! Isn't that right, Rose?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[rose.speech(Yes, Mistress!)] Rose squeaks in agreement, [rose.speech(That's right!)]
	</p>
	<p>
	#IF !lilaya.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc) && !lilaya.getBaseFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative() && lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant()
	#THEN
		#IF(lilaya.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(pc.getId()))
			As Lilaya brushes down her skirt, you can't help but notice the visible bulge in her belly. As she sees what it is you're looking at, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] clears her throat and confirms, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ Yes, [pc.name], you got me pregnant. As I'm a full demon now, it's really no big deal... As I'm not going to be birthing any imps, I don't mind it at all. So, what is it you want?)]
		#ELSEIF(lilaya.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(lyssieth.getId()))
			As Lilaya brushes down her skirt, you can't help but notice the visible bulge in her belly. As she sees what it is you're looking at, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] clears her throat and confirms, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ Yes, [pc.name], mommy got me pregnant. As I'm a full demon now, it's really no big deal... As I'm not going to be birthing any imps, I don't mind it at all. So, what is it you want?)]
		#ELSE
			As Lilaya brushes down her skirt, you can't help but notice the visible bulge in her belly. As she sees what it is you're looking at, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] clears her throat and confirms, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ Yes, [pc.name], [daddy.name] got me pregnant. As I'm a full demon now, it's really no big deal... As I'm not going to be birthing any imps, I don't mind it at all. So, what is it you want?)]
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF !lilaya.getBaseFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative() && lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant()
		#THEN
			As Lilaya brushes down her skirt, you can't help but notice that she's still got a very visible bulge in her belly. As she sees what it is you're looking at, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] clears her throat and confirms, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ Yes, I'm still pregnant... So, what is it you need, [pc.name]?)]
		#ELSE
			Brushing down her skirt, Lilaya clears her throat, [lilaya.speech(~Ahem!~ So, what is it you need, [pc.name]?)]
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_ARTHUR_PREGNANCY_BASE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach the door to Lilaya's lab, you hear the distinctive sound of your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s voice getting louder and louder, [lilaya.speech(...and I told you <i>three times</i> already! <i>Don't touch my notes!</i>)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping through the open doorway, you see a rather flustered-looking Arthur sitting down on one of the lab's many chairs, his eyes cast to the floor as he endures your angry [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s furious scolding. [arthur.speech(Sorry, Lilaya, I just thought that-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Be quiet!)] Lilaya shrieks, before suddenly noticing your entry. [lilaya.speech(And now the other asshole's here! [pc.Name]! Come and take a seat, <i>this instant</i>!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_ARTHUR_PREGNANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Looking down at your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s stomach, you see the reason why she's addressing you in such a furious manner; her belly is quite visibly swollen, making it obvious that you've ended up getting her pregnant. Knowing from experience that it's best to just do as you're told when your [lilaya.relation(pc)] is like this, you walk over to the chair next to Arthur and sit down.
	</p>
	<p>
		Addressing you, Lilaya shouts, [lilaya.speech(You <i>know</i> I'm just a half-demon! That means all my kids end up as imps! Do you have any idea of how embarrassing and shameful it is to be called an 'imp-breeder', or 'imp-fucker'?! <i>Do you?!</i>)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not even giving you a chance to answer, she continues in the same furious tone, [lilaya.speech(Once this business with Arthur is sorted out, I don't want to see you anywhere near my lab until my pregnancy is resolved!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_ARTHUR_NOT_PREGNANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing from experience that it's best to just do as you're told when your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s like this, you walk over to the chair next to Arthur and sit down. Looking up at Lilaya's flat stomach, you see that you didn't end up getting her pregnant after all, and, seeing what it is you're glancing at, she firmly says, [lilaya.speech(Yes, luckily for you, I'm not pregnant. You'd have been in so much trouble if I was!)]
	</p>
	<p>
	<p>
		Taking a step back, Lilaya doesn't pause for a moment, and angrily continues, [lilaya.speech(As we only ever give birth to imps, it's extremely embarrassing and shameful for half-demons to get pregnant. Even those who know that I'm the recognised daughter of Lyssieth herself would call me 'imp-breeder' or 'imp-fucker' behind my back... I <i>hate</i> being pregnant!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_ARTHUR_BASE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you approach the door to Lilaya's lab, you hear the distinctive sound of your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s voice getting louder and louder, [lilaya.speech(...and I told you <i>three times</i> already! <i>Don't touch my notes!</i>)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping through the open doorway, you see a rather flustered-looking Arthur sitting down on one of the lab's many chairs, his eyes cast to the floor as he endures your angry [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s furious scolding. [arthur.speech(Sorry, Lilaya, I just thought that-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Be quiet!)] Lilaya shrieks, before suddenly noticing your entry. [lilaya.speech([pc.Name]! Please come in and take a seat!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing from experience that it's best to just do as you're told when your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s like this, you walk over to the chair next to Arthur and sit down.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ENTRY_ARTHUR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Lilaya starts pacing back and forth, her eyes fixed on Arthur as she explains the situation to the two of you, [lilaya.speech(It's just impossible. Absolutely <i>impossible</i>! I might need your help in order to figure out how to return [pc.name] to [pc.her] world, but I simply <i>cannot</i> be around you for longer than five minutes!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[arthur.speech(Lilaya, please, how many times to I have to say I'm sorr-)] Arthur starts, before being cut short by a sudden exclamation from your [lilaya.relation(pc)].
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(You wouldn't have had to say sorry even <i>once</i> if you could have just refrained from fucking my mother! And right here in my lab of all places!)] Lilaya shouts, her cheeks burning red from embarrassment and anger. With a dismissive swipe of her hand, she turns to you and demands, [lilaya.speech([pc.Name], you're going to help Rose clear out my lab's storeroom so that it can be converted into a bedroom for Arthur! I simply can't endure having this insufferable cheating bastard in my presence for more than a few minutes at a time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Finding yourself in an increasingly awkward position, you realise that your only real option is to agree to do as your [lilaya.relation(pc)] asks...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ELLE_HELP_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having forgotten what it was that Lilaya deduced about Elle's location, you ask your [lilaya.relation(pc)] if she can remind you of where you should be looking for her. Letting out an exasperated sigh, Lilaya pushes her glasses up onto the bridge of her nose and sharply states, [lilaya.speech(She's going down into the Bat Caverns, remember?! Just travel down to the west side of Submission to get there!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isSillyMode())
			As you start to thank Lilaya for her help, she steps forwards and bonks you over the head with a rolled-up stack of papers. Frowning at you in disapproval, she states, [lilaya.speech(Please do try to remember what I've said this time!)]
		#ELSE
			Thanking Lilaya for her help, and reassuring her that you'll be careful, you wonder what to do next...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsMinorGood(You can find Elle by searching in the Bat Caverns between [units.time(12)]-[units.time(15)] on a Wednesday!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ELLE_HELP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Struggling to figure out for yourself where Elle could be teleporting to during her long Wednesday lunch breaks, you ask Lilaya if she can help you to figure out where to go. Telling her that the Superintendent apparently takes a pair of night vision goggles with her, and that she returns with wet shoes often coated in some kind of glowing residue, you ask your [lilaya.relation(pc)] if she can figure out what location Elle is visiting.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Hmm, well, if she's taking night vision goggles with her, then she's going somewhere that's dark even in the middle of the day,)] Lilaya muses, before stepping over to a nearby pile of books and retrieving one that appears to be a reference guide on local flora. Flicking through the pages, she quickly finds what she was looking for, and reads out loud, [lilaya.speech(<i>'Bioluminescent fungi are found all throughout Lilith's Realm...'</i> Now where's the section on Dominion... Ah, here it is; <i>'One may be surprised to discover that the subterranean Bat Caverns are home to one of the most diverse fungal ecosystems currently known to exist. In places, vast carpets of bioluminescent fungi can be observed, and it is impossible to take a step without disturbing their vividly-glowing spores...'</i>)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Closing her book and looking up at you with a triumphant look on her face, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] proudly declares, [lilaya.speech(Mystery solved! Your elusive Enforcer must be teleporting down into the Bat Caverns. If you've never been there before, then you should know that you have to travel down to the west side of Submission to get there. Please do be careful if you do decide to follow this 'Elle' character though; the last I heard, the Bat Caverns are quite a dangerous place...)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.isSillyMode())
		<p>
			You start to thank Lilaya for her help, but before you're able to articulate your thoughts, she steps forwards and bonks you on the head with the book that she's still holding. Frowning at you in disapproval, she tuts, [lilaya.speech(You really should have been able to solve this by yourself...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Rubbing your head and feeling more than a little ashamed from your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s words, you wonder what to do next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Thanking Lilaya for her help, and reassuring her that you'll be careful, you wonder what to do next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsMinorGood(You can find Elle by searching in the Bat Caverns between [units.time(12)]-[units.time(15)] on a Wednesday!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LAB_EXIT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing in what appears at first to be a huge library. The walls are covered in shelving, holding what must be hundreds, if not thousands, of ancient-looking leather-bound tomes. Most of the room, however, is occupied by a series of long tables, each covered in strange glass vials, odd-looking instruments, and bottles of glowing liquids.
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya is hovering close by, ready to answer any questions you might have. Her cat-girl maid, Rose, is dutifully standing in one corner of the room, ready to assist with any request her mistress might make.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LAB_EXIT_THROWN_OUT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_EXIT_THROWN_OUT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing outside the door to Lilaya's laboratory. Your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] seemed pretty angry, and you think that it's probably a good idea if you gave her some time to cool off before trying to speak to her again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_PRESENT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_PRESENT_1"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I wanted to get you something for Yuletide, to thank you for everything,)] you say, holding out the wrapped gift towards Lilaya, [pc.speech(so here you go. Happy Yuletide, Lilaya!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Your [lilaya.relation(pc)] gasps as you give her the gift you bought, [lilaya.speech([pc.Name]! Y-You didn't have to do that! Oh my goodness, t-thank you so much!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		She seems completely shocked at the fact that you're giving her a gift, and awkwardly takes the present from out of your hands. [lilaya.speech(S-Should I open it now?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Go on, it'll be fun,)] you reply. [pc.speech(I got it from one of the reindeer-morphs who're working to keep the streets clear of snow. The contents are a surprise, so I guess we'll find out what's in there together!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya sets the present down on the table behind her, before pulling off the ribbon and tearing off the wrapping paper. Opening the top of the box, she gasps as she sees what's inside, and then just a moment later you see it too, as she reaches in and lifts out a beautiful pink [#CT_innoxia_japanese_kanzashi.getName()].
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya turns towards you, a huge smile on her face as she exclaims, [lilaya.speech(Oh, [pc.name]! It's beautiful! Thank you so much!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can react, your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] leaps forwards and pulls you into a loving hug; a gesture that you instantly reciprocate. You feel the warmth of her body as she presses herself tightly against you, squashing her [lilaya.breastSize] breasts into your chest as she sighs, [lilaya.speech(Really, thank you so much.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After a few moments, Lilaya pulls back, placing the [#CT_innoxia_japanese_kanzashi.getName()] to one side and waiting to see what you'd like to discuss next.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_PRESENT_2"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(After I saw how happy you were to receive that [#CT_innoxia_japanese_kanzashi.getName()], I decided to get you another Yuletide gift,)] you say, holding out another wrapped gift towards Lilaya, [pc.speech(so here you go. Happy Yuletide again, Lilaya!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s cheeks flush bright red as you give her another gift. [lilaya.speech([pc.name]! Y-You didn't have to! O-One gift was more than enough!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I know I didn't have to, but I wanted to,)] you smile, handing the gift over to Lilaya, [pc.speech(so go on, open it and let's find out what it is this time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you suggest, Lilaya places the gift down on the table beside her, before pulling off the ribbon and wrapping paper. Taking off the lid, she reaches inside and produces a pair of [#CT_innoxia_japanese_geta.getNamePlural()], before turning and smiling lovingly at you, [lilaya.speech(Thank you, [pc.name]! These will go perfectly with the [#CT_innoxia_japanese_kanzashi.getName()] you got me before!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Now all you need is the kimono itself,)] you reply, [pc.speech(and then you've got the full set!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(P-Please,)] Lilaya stutters a little, [lilaya.speech(don't feel obliged to get me any more gifts! This is already far more than I ever would have dreamed of!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Almost as if to hide her sudden embarrassment, your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] steps forwards and pulls you into another tight hug; her [lilaya.breastSize] breasts pressing up against you as she holds you close. After a moment, she then pulls back, and, placing the [#CT_innoxia_japanese_geta.getNamePlural()] to one side, she waits to see what you'd like to discuss next.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_PRESENT_3"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Seeing as you have the other two parts already, I thought I'd get you one last gift, to see if it contains the kimono to finish the set,)] you say, holding out the wrapped gift towards Lilaya, [pc.speech(so here you go. Happy Yuletide yet again Lilaya!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] cheeks turn a deep shade of scarlet, and she stutters in her embarrassment, [lilaya.speech(P-Please! [pc.Name]! I-I said you'd already given me enough!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I know, I know,)] you laugh, pressing the gift into Lilaya's hands, [pc.speech(but I really wanted to get you the whole set!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(W-Well, these are random gifts, right? S-So it's probably not even going to be a kimono, b-but thank you anyway,)] Lilaya says, placing the gift down on the table beside her, before pulling off the ribbon and wrapping paper. Lifting off the lid, your easily-embarrassed [lilaya.relation(pc)] fails to contain an excited little cry as she sees what's inside. Your suspicions as to what it is are proven correct, as she quickly lifts out a beautiful pink [#CT_innoxia_japanese_kimono.getName()], before turning and beaming at you in delight. [lilaya.speech(Thank you so, so much, [pc.name]! This is the best Yuletide ever!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can say anything, your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] leaps forwards and pulls you into the most loving hug yet; her [lilaya.breastSize] breasts squishing up against your body as she holds you close. After a moment, she then pulls back, and, placing the [#CT_innoxia_japanese_kimono.getName()] to one side, she waits to see what you'd like to discuss next.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LAB_DEMON_TF_AGREE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_DEMON_TF_AGREE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having been convinced by Lilaya's passionate plea, you agree to do as she asks,
		#IF pc.hasFetish(FETISH_INCEST)
		#THEN [pc.speech(Ok, Lilaya, use the resonance stone to contact mommy, and I'll help you to convince her.)]
		#ELSE [pc.speech(Ok, Lilaya, use the resonance stone to contact Lyssieth, and I'll help you to convince her.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_DEMON_TF_AGREE_AFTER_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to let Lilaya know that you've changed your mind, you say,
		#IF pc.hasFetish(FETISH_INCEST)
		#THEN [pc.speech(Go on, use the resonance stone to contact mommy, and I'll help you to convince her to turn you into a full demon.)]
		#ELSE [pc.speech(Go on, use the resonance stone to contact Lyssieth, and I'll help you to convince her to turn you into a full demon.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_DEMON_TF_AGREE_CORE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s eyes light up as you say this, and she quickly rushes over to the other side of her lab where she keeps the resonance stone. Holding it in one hand, you see the dark-purple sphere light up and start to emit a soft pink glow. In a clear voice, Lilaya states, [lilaya.speech(Mommy, I need you to come here. Right now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lyssieth.speech(Yes, dear,)] you hear Lyssieth's voice being projected from out of the arcane device. A moment later, the elder lilin appears before you in a bright purple flash, and although at first she's smiling, her expression turns into one of worry as she sees the angry expression on Lilaya's face. [lyssieth.speech(Oh, sweetheart, what's wrong? You look upse-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Of course I'm upset!)] Lilaya interrupts, [lilaya.speech(You said you'd never turn anyone into a demon ever again, and then you go back on your word the moment you meet [pc.name]! So it turns out that you were just lying to me for all these years! You have no problem at all with turning people into demons, so you've got no reason to leave me as a half-demon for any longer! Tell her, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having already agreed to help Lilaya, you ask your mother,
		#IF pc.hasFetish(FETISH_INCEST)
		#THEN [pc.speech(There'd be no harm in making Lilaya a full demon, would there mommy? It's what she really wants...)]
		#ELSE [pc.speech(There'd be no harm in making Lilaya a full demon, would there? It's what she really wants...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Lyssieth starts to let out a deep, defeated sigh, before suddenly noticing that Rose is present and duly altering her reaction into an unfriendly sneer, [lyssieth.speech(I will only discuss this back in the privacy of my palace. Come here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as your mother says, both you and Lilaya step up next to her, and, wrapping an arm around each of you, she teleports you back to her palace in yet another flash of purple light...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_DEMON_TF_REFUSE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Shaking your head, you reply,
		#IF pc.hasFetish(FETISH_INCEST)
		#THEN [pc.speech(This issue is between you and mommy. I don't want to get between the two of you like this, so I can't do as you ask. Sorry, Lilaya.)]
		#ELSE [pc.speech(This issue is between you and mother. I don't want to get between the two of you like this, so I can't do as you ask. Sorry, Lilaya.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Eugh! You're unbelievable,)] Lilaya crossly states, before turning and pacing back and forth in front of you. [lilaya.speech(I should have known that you and mommy would already have agreed to keep me as a half-demon... Fine! I think you can see how upset I am about being stuck in this half-demon form, so if you want to be a good [pc.sister], then you'll think this over and let me know when you've agreed to help me out.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ok, I'll think about it some more,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(And remember, you're not getting any sex from me until I'm a full demon, just like you!)] Lilaya finally states, and although her voice is still raised, you sense that her initial anger is dying down. Wondering if you'll change your mind after giving this matter some thought, you think about what to ask your [lilaya.relation(pc)] next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!--LAB_TELEPORT_TO_LYSSIETHS_OFFICE-->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_TELEPORT_TO_LYSSIETHS_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to see Lyssieth again, you ask, [pc.speech(Lilaya, could you use the resonance stone to contact Lyssieth? I'd like to talk to her about something.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Of course,)] your [lilaya.relation(pc)] replies, before heading over to the desk in which she keeps the communication device. As she retrieves the small, dark sphere and holds it up in one hand, you see it start to emit a pink glow, and she says, [lilaya.speech(Mommy, [pc.name] would like you to come here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Just a moment later, a flash of purple light fills the lab, and there before you stands the familiar figure of Lyssieth. Smiling at Lilaya, she then turns and steps towards you, before pulling you into a hug and saying, [lyssieth.speech(Let's return to my palace.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the two of you are teleported back into the elder lilin's office, and, releasing you from the hug, Lyssieth smiles at you and asks, [lyssieth.speech(So, what is it you wanted?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_TELEPORT_TO_LYSSIETHS_OFFICE_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to see Lyssieth again, you ask, [pc.speech(Lilaya, could you use the resonance stone to contact Lyssieth? I'd like to talk to her about something.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Of course,)] your [lilaya.relation(pc)] replies, before heading over to the desk in which she keeps the communication device. As she retrieves the small, dark sphere and holds it up in one hand, you see it start to emit a pink glow, and she says, [lilaya.speech(Mommy, [pc.name] would like you to come here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Just a moment later, a flash of purple light fills the lab, and there before you stands the familiar figure of Lyssieth. Smiling at Lilaya, she then turns and steps towards you, before pulling you and [npc.name] into a hug and saying, [lyssieth.speech(Let's return to my palace.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the three of you are teleported back into the elder lilin's office, and, releasing you both from the hug, Lyssieth asks [npc.name] to wait in Meraxis's office. After [npc.sheHas] left, Lyssieth smiles at you and asks, [lyssieth.speech(So, what is it you wanted?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- END_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_END_SEX_CREAMPIE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(lilaya.isAmazonsSecretImpregnation())
		<p>
			Lilaya forcefully shoves you away from her, and with a look of disbelief on her face, clutches her lower abdomen. Looking down at her hot, wet pussy, she angrily shouts, [lilaya.speech(What the fuck?! What the fuck?! I fucking told you to pull back!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Knowing that the effects of your Amazon's Secret potion may very well have led to her being impregnated, she lets out a short, panicked cry. Her face has gone completely scarlet, and as the reality of what you've just done sinks in, she turns on you in a furious rage, [lilaya.speech(What did I say?! Huh?! I fucking told you to get back before you orgasmed! I do <i>not</i> want to be giving birth to a brood of imps! Oh fuck... You'd better fucking hope I don't get pregnant from this!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Lilaya forcefully shoves you away from her, and with a look of disbelief on her face, looks down at the [pc.cum+] dripping out from between her thighs as she shouts, [lilaya.speech(What the fuck?! What the fuck?! I fucking told you to pull out!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Grabbing a tissue from a nearby desk, she starts frantically trying to clean your [pc.cum] out of her creampied pussy. Her face has gone completely scarlet, and as the reality of what you've just done sinks in, she turns on you in a furious rage, [lilaya.speech(What did I say?! Huh?! I fucking told you to pull out! I do <i>not</i> want to be giving birth to a brood of imps! Oh fuck... You'd better fucking hope I don't get pregnant from this!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Continuing to shout and curse, she grabs you by the [pc.arm] and marches you over to the lab's exit. With one last angry cry, she throws you out, before slamming the door behind you. You start to wonder if perhaps you made a mistake, but surely she'll have calmed down in a couple of hours...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_END_SEX_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you disentangle yourself from her clutches, Lilaya lets out a very frustrated sigh. Stepping back, she gives her demonic wings an impatient flutter, before striding back over to her workplace and making several loud tutting sounds. Before you can say anything, she shouts out over her shoulder, [lilaya.speech(I <i>really</i> don't see the point in offering these tests to you, if all you're going to do is <i>that</i>! I didn't even get to cum...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Ignoring your excuses, Lilaya buries herself in preparing yet another of her experiments. Quickly sorting yourself out, you leave her to carry on with her work, knowing that she won't stay angry for long.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_END_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Disentangling herself from your clutches, Lilaya lets out a very satisfied sigh as she stands up and stretches her arms up high. You see her demonic wings and tail following suit, and as she stretches, she turns back to face you. With one last smile and a quick kiss on your cheek, she then rushes back over to her workplace.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Oh, fuck, that was amazing!)] your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] cries out, energetically gathering up papers before starting to frantically write down some notes. [lilaya.speech(With the power of your aura, I'm sure that anyone who you have sex with will feel turned on, even if they're not really into you at first. I-I mean, I'm not advocating anything like <i>that</i>, of course, I just mean that your aura certainly does have some strong effects...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Lilaya buries herself in her work, seemingly forgetting that you're still here. You quickly sort yourself out, and, smiling at the fact that you've given Lilaya a good time, leave her to carry on with her work.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_GEISHA -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_GEISHA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I really want to see how you look wearing that kimono,)] you say, [pc.speech(would you like to try it on and show me?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya's cheeks flush bright red, and, without saying a word, she grabs your hand and starts pulling you towards the door. For a moment, you think she's going to throw you out of the lab, but she instead leads you out into the corridor and over towards the staircase.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(I-I haven't r-really thought about h-how I look in it yet,)] Lilaya stammers out, without turning to look at you, [lilaya.speech(s-so I hope you like it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leading you up the stairs, your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] pulls you along the first-floor corridor, and, without hesitation, into her exceptionally-messy room. Her clothes are scattered all over the floor, and every available surface is littered with beauty products and yet more discarded clothing. You don't have any time to think about the state of your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s room, however, as you're far more concerned with the fact that she's instantly started stripping off in front of you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Either because she's completely indifferent to you seeing her naked, or, more likely, that she's so flustered at the prospect of modelling her kimono for you that she's forgotten you're there, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] quickly pulls off all of her clothes with little regard to your presence. Deciding that it would be best both for her dignity and for the surprise of seeing her wearing her kimono, you turn your back to Lilaya, and allow her to get changed into the clothes that you gifted her.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Aah! I-I forgot you were there!)] Lilaya calls out, proving the second assumption to be true. [lilaya.speech(Y-You can turn around now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning around, you see your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] blushing profusely as she looks to the floor. The elegant pink kimono, delicate kanzashi, and delightful geta that you bought her as a Yuletide gift all work together to accentuate your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s natural beauty. You find yourself gasping at how gorgeous she looks, which makes her look up and smile shyly at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Wow, Lilaya, you look gorgeous!)] you exclaim, causing her cheeks to turn an even deeper shade of red.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(R-Really?)] Lilaya asks, stepping forwards as a huge smile breaks out across her face. [lilaya.speech(W-Well, I have you to thank for giving it to me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The tone of your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s voice changes as she moves closer, and you realise that now she's been assured that she looks good, something other than embarrassment is on her mind. [lilaya.speech(You know, I really do need to show you how thankful I am... While I'm wearing my kimono, perhaps you'd like to have some fun?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_GEISHA_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't resist an offer like that, and, stepping forwards, you pull your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] into your embrace. [pc.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes Lilaya, that sounds good to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to fuck me, make sure you pull out, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant!)] she demands.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_innoxia_amazons_secret) && pc.hasVagina() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to scissor, make sure you pull back before climaxing, ok?)] she demands, before explaining, [lilaya.speech(I'm an arcane researcher, remember? I can tell that you're under the effects of Amazon's Secret, and I'm <b>not</b> going to let you get me pregnant from it.)]
		#ELSE
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes!)] she giggles.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As Lilaya locks her [lilaya.eyes+] onto yours, she throws you a seductive smile, before taking your head in both hands and pressing her lips against your mouth. You reach up and pull her close, passionately making out with one another as you both give in to your lust.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_GEISHA_SUBMISSIVE_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't resist an offer like that, and, stepping forwards, you allow your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] to reach up and pull you into her embrace. [pc.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes Lilaya, that sounds good to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to fuck me, make sure you pull out, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant!)] she demands.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_innoxia_amazons_secret) && pc.hasVagina() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to scissor, make sure you pull back before climaxing, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant from the effects of Amazon's Secret!)] she demands.
		#ELSE
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes!)] she giggles.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As Lilaya locks her [lilaya.eyes+] onto yours, she throws you a seductive smile, before taking your head in both hands and pressing her lips against your mouth. You let out a desperate little whine as she pulls you close to her body, and, passionately making out with one another, you both give in to your lust.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_GEISHA_SEX_REFUSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You really do look amazing, Lilaya, but that might be going a little too far,)] you respond, not liking the idea of having sex with your [lilaya.relation(pc)].
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Aww, well, I understand,)] Lilaya responds, before turning around to get changed back into her regular clothes. [lilaya.speech(Just let me know if you want to see me in this again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reassuring her that you will, you exit your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s bedroom and head back to your own, pleased that your gift looks so good on her.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- END_SEX_GEISHA -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="END_SEX_GEISHA_CREAMPIE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(lilaya.isAmazonsSecretImpregnation())
		<p>
			Lilaya forcefully shoves you away from her, and with a look of disbelief on her face, clutches her lower abdomen. Looking down at her hot, wet pussy, she angrily shouts, [lilaya.speech(What the fuck?! What the fuck?! I fucking told you to pull back!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Knowing that the effects of your Amazon's Secret potion may very well have led to her being impregnated, she lets out a short, panicked cry. Her face has gone completely scarlet, and as the reality of what you've just done sinks in, she turns on you in a furious rage, [lilaya.speech(What did I say?! Huh?! I fucking told you to get back before you orgasmed! Do you know how fucking fertile demons are?! Oh fuck... You'd better fucking hope I don't get pregnant from this!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Lilaya forcefully shoves you away from her, and with a look of disbelief on her face, looks down at the [pc.cum+] dripping out from between her thighs as she shouts, [lilaya.speech(What the fuck?! What the fuck?! I fucking told you to pull out!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Grabbing a tissue from a nearby cabinet, she starts frantically trying to clean your [pc.cum] out of her creampied pussy. Her face has gone completely scarlet, and as the reality of what you've just done sinks in, she turns on you in a furious rage, [lilaya.speech(What did I say?! Huh?! I fucking told you to pull out! Do you know how fucking fertile demons are?! Oh fuck... You'd better fucking hope I don't get pregnant from this!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Continuing to shout and curse, she grabs you by the [pc.arm] and marches you over to her bedroom door. With one last angry cry, she throws you out, before slamming the door behind you. You start to wonder if perhaps you made a mistake, but surely she'll have calmed down in a couple of hours...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="END_SEX_GEISHA_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Lilaya collapses face-first onto her bed, giving her demonic wings an impatient flutter as she sighs in annoyance, [lilaya.speech(As grateful as I am for this outfit, I <i>really</i> don't appreciate being treated like that! You didn't even get me to cum once!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya buries her face in her pillows, ignoring your excuses as she waits for you to leave. Quickly sorting yourself out, you head out of her bedroom, knowing that she won't stay angry for long.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="END_SEX_GEISHA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Lilaya collapses back onto her bed, letting out a very satisfied sigh as she stretches out her arms and wings, [lilaya.speech(That was amazing! We definitely need to do this again some time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reassuring her that you will, you exit your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s bedroom and head back to your own, allowing her to get changed and head back down to her lab.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LAB_JINX_REMOVAL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_JINX_REMOVAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I was wondering if you could help me with my clothes,)] you say, before explaining to Lilaya how you're unable to unseal your clothing due to a 'servitude' enchantment being present on them. 
	</p>
	<p>
		As she hears you explaining your dilemma, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] crosses her arms and tuts in disapproval. Shaking her head as you finish talking, she asks, [lilaya.speech(How did you end up in such a ridiculous situation? Were you just going around Dominion putting on any old piece of clothing you found lying on the ground? No, wait, don't answer. I feel as though I'd regret finding out.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Asking Lilaya if she can help, you're pleased to see the annoyed expression on her face quickly soften as she replies, [lilaya.speech(Yes, I can help. Ordinarily, I'd refuse to help so as to teach you a lesson about being so careless, but seeing as you're completely unable to get yourself out of this mess, I'll remove the servitude enchantments from all of your clothing. Just come and stand over here, please.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving up next to Lilaya, you hold still as she removes the servitude enchantments your clothing. After just a few moments she's done, but as you thank her and then try to remove your clothing, you realise that it's still sealed.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Did you think that I'd waste my essences on unsealing your clothing?)] the [lilaya.race] asks in a disapproving tone. Crossing her arms, she tuts, [lilaya.speech(You can unseal your clothing yourself. Just be grateful that I spent some essences on removing those other enchantments. Now, is there anything else you need from me?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_SCIENTIST_OUTFIT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_SCIENTIST_OUTFIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the look of Lilaya's lab coat, you compliment her on her appearance, before asking if she has a spare lying around which you could have.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Well, in this instance, flattery will get you somewhere after all,)] she responds with a smile on her face. Striding over to a cabinet on the far side of the room, she slides open one of the drawers and retrieves the white lab coat you've asked for. Walking back over to you, she hands you the garment and says, [lilaya.speech(Don't get carried away and start thinking you're a real arcane researcher; it takes years of study to get to that level.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you thank your [lilaya.relation(pc)], she hands you something else which she'd just retrieved from the same drawer, and you look down to see that it's a pair of safety goggles. Flashing you another smile, Lilaya says, [lilaya.speech(If you're trying to get the look right, you'll need these too. Anyway, is there anything else you want?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LAB_LILAYA_HUG -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_LILAYA_HUG"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isQuestProgressGreaterThan(QUEST_LINE_MAIN, QUEST_MAIN_2_D_MEETING_A_LILIN))
			Although she's no longer the same person you knew before Lilith's spell altered this reality, you know that Lilaya is sure to love the same sort of big hug which you used to give her when she was your aunt Lily.
		#ELSE
			Although she's not the same person as the Lily from your world, you know that Lilaya is sure to love the same sort of big hug which you used to give your aunt.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.isShy())
			 Although you're shy around most people, you feel at ease when in the presence of [lilaya.race], and so you don't feel any trepidation in throwing your [pc.arms] around her and pulling her into your loving embrace.
		#ELSE
			 Stepping up to the [lilaya.race], you throw your [pc.arms] around her and pull her into your loving embrace.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Furiously blushing at this sudden display of affection, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] stutters, [lilaya.speech(W-What are you doing?! I-I have important work to be getting on with! I-I don't have time for this!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite her words, the embarrassed [lilaya.race] makes no move to push you off of her, and in fact actually seems to lean into your hug. What's more, you're able to see that her [lilaya.tail+] is excitedly wrapping itself around the leg of the table behind her, and as you continue to hold your [lilaya.relation(pc)] in your embrace, her [lilaya.wings+] suddenly flap out and curl around to return your hug. With her cheeks still flushing a deep shade of scarlet, she mutters, [lilaya.speech(I-I suppose I can spare a minute or two...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After sharing a hug with your [lilaya.relation(pc)] for another couple of minutes, she eventually breaks it off and declares, [lilaya.speech(T-That was nice, thank you, [pc.name]. Now, I really have a lot of important work to get done today, s-so please don't try this again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she made it very clear from her body language that she actually likes being hugged, you're sure that Lilaya would get angry if you were to try and hug her again today. As your [lilaya.relation(pc)] waits to hear if there's anything else you want from her, you think to yourself that you could always do this to her again tomorrow without risk of annoying her... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_EXPLAINS_ESSENCES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_EXPLAINS_ESSENCES"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_jinxedClothingDiscovered))
		#IF(!pc.isAnyEquippedClothingSealed())
			<p>
				[pc.speech(I managed to take it off already, but some clothing that I put on a little while ago sort of stuck onto me,)] you explain. [pc.speech(Every time I tried to take it off, some kind of weird enchantment stopped me. I was wondering if you knew what was causing that?)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[pc.speech(There seems to be something wrong with [#SPECIAL_PARSE_2] [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] I'm wearing,)] you explain. [pc.speech(Every time I try to take [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] off, some kind of weird enchantment stops me. Can you help?)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			Lilaya frowns at you for a moment, then, much to your surprise, she starts scolding you, [lilaya.speech(Well, what did you expect to happen if you're going to start trying on random pieces of clothing like that?!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Well, it's not really my fau-)] you start, but Lilaya quickly interrupts you.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Well then, whose fault is it? Hmm? I can't be running around saving you every time you get in trouble, understood?!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			If it were anyone else, you might have argued back, but Lilaya's stern words sound exactly like the sort of lecture you used to receive from your [lilaya.relation(pc)] Lily. That, combined with the fact that this is a rare display of frustration from Lilaya, leaves you muttering out an apology in the hope that you can calm her down. Thankfully, she lets out one last exasperated sigh before taking in a deep breath and speaking in her normal tone.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Sorry, I didn't mean to be so stern, it's just that I don't want you to get hurt out there... Anyway, if that's all it is, the solution to sealed clothing is actually quite simple!)]
		</p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_essenceOrgasmDiscovered) || game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_essencePostCombatDiscovered))
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Actually, there <i>is</i> something else as well. I recently had this weird experience, where I saw someone's arcane aura. A piece of it broke off and shot <i>into</i> me, and I'm not sure if it needs to be removed or anything...)] your voice trails off as you see an extremely concerned look flash across Lilaya's face.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(Are you sure?! You absorbed someone's essence directly from them?!)] Lilaya asks, failing to conceal the worried tone in her voice.
			</p>
			<p>
				Before you can respond, Lilaya grabs your [pc.arm] and starts pulling you over to the same place where she ran her first test on you. Instructing you to sit on the chair in the middle of the chalk square, she once more starts adjusting the floodlight-like pieces of arcane equipment at each corner.
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Wait, my clothes aren't going to be teleported all over the room or anything again, are they?)] you ask.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(No, don't worry, I fixed that little problem!)] Lilaya responds, and before you get the chance to say anything else, arcane energy suddenly crackles into life around her arm, before shooting out into each of the curious instruments. A familiar bright pink flash illuminates the room, but this time, thankfully, your clothes and sight are unaffected.
			</p>
			<p>
				Once again, you find yourself surrounded by the shimmering pink outline of your arcane aura. This time, however, you see a strange ball of energy orbiting your body, which looks to be the same sort of size as the shard of energy that you remember shooting into you. Looking up at Lilaya, you see that her cheeks have completely drained of colour, and she's looking down at you with an extremely worried expression on her face.
			</p>
		#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_essenceBottledDiscovered))
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Actually, there <i>is</i> something else as well. I had this little bottle with a swirling light in it, and when I took out the stopper, the light sort of shot <i>into</i> me...)] you explain, hoping that Lilaya can tell you what that was all about as well.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(Oh! Of course! I should have mentioned that,)] Lilaya responds. [lilaya.speech(As you've got a demon-strength aura, it's only natural that you'd be able to absorb arcane essences! I really should have tested you for that as well... But we can just do it now!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Before you can respond, Lilaya grabs your [pc.arm] and starts pulling you over to the same place where she ran her first test on you. Instructing you to sit on the chair in the middle of the chalk square, she once more starts adjusting the floodlight-like pieces of arcane equipment at each corner.
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Wait, my clothes aren't going to be teleported all over the room or anything again, are they?)] you ask.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(No, don't worry, I fixed that little problem!)] Lilaya responds, and before you get the chance to say anything else, arcane energy suddenly crackles into life around her arm, before shooting out into each of the curious instruments. A familiar bright pink flash illuminates the room, but this time, thankfully, your clothes and sight are unaffected.
			</p>
			<p>
				Once again, you find yourself surrounded by the shimmering pink outline of your arcane aura. This time, however, you see a strange ball of energy orbiting your body, which looks to be the same sort of size as the shard of energy that you remember shooting into you. Looking up at Lilaya, you see that her cheeks have completely drained of colour, and she's looking down at you with an extremely worried expression on her face.
			</p>
		#ELSEIF(SPECIAL_PARSE_0=="false")
			<p>
				[pc.speech(That's good to hear, so what would I need to do if it happens again?)] you ask.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(Well, as you've got a demon-strength aura, it's only natural that you'd be able to absorb arcane essences too, and then you could channel some of them into clothing to remove seals yourself! I really should have tested you for that as well... But we can just do it now!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Before you can respond, Lilaya grabs your [pc.arm] and starts pulling you over to the same place where she ran her first test on you. Instructing you to sit on the chair in the middle of the chalk square, she once more starts adjusting the floodlight-like pieces of arcane equipment at each corner.
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Wait, my clothes aren't going to be teleported all over the room or anything again, are they?)] you ask.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(No, don't worry, I fixed that little problem!)] Lilaya responds, and before you get the chance to say anything else, arcane energy suddenly crackles into life around her arm, before shooting out into each of the curious instruments. A familiar bright pink flash illuminates the room, but this time, thankfully, your clothes and sight are unaffected.
			</p>
			<p>
				Once again, you find yourself surrounded by the shimmering pink outline of your arcane aura. This time, however, you see a strange ball of energy orbiting your body, which looks to be the same sort of size as the shard of energy that you remember shooting into you. Looking up at Lilaya, you see that her cheeks have completely drained of colour, and she's looking down at you with an extremely worried expression on her face.
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[pc.speech(That's good to hear, so what do I need to do?)] you ask.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(Well, I could just channel some of my absorbed essences into [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] to remove the seal, but...)] Lilaya responds, her sentence trailing off a little as she suddenly thinks of something. [lilaya.speech(As you've got a demon-strength aura, it's only natural that you'd be able to absorb arcane essences too, and then you could remove [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] yourself! I really should have tested you for that as well... But we can just do it now!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Before you can respond, Lilaya grabs your [pc.arm] and starts pulling you over to the same place where she ran her first test on you. Instructing you to sit on the chair in the middle of the chalk square, she once more starts adjusting the floodlight-like pieces of arcane equipment at each corner.
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Wait, my clothes aren't going to be teleported all over the room or anything again, are they?)] you ask.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(No, don't worry, I fixed that little problem!)] Lilaya responds, and before you get the chance to say anything else, arcane energy suddenly crackles into life around her arm, before shooting out into each of the curious instruments. A familiar bright pink flash illuminates the room, but this time, thankfully, your clothes and sight are unaffected.
			</p>
			<p>
				Once again, you find yourself surrounded by the shimmering pink outline of your arcane aura. This time, however, you see a strange ball of energy orbiting your body, which looks to be the same sort of size as the shard of energy that you remember shooting into you. Looking up at Lilaya, you see that her cheeks have completely drained of colour, and she's looking down at you with an extremely worried expression on her face.
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_essenceOrgasmDiscovered) || game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_essencePostCombatDiscovered))
			<p>
				[pc.speech(I wanted to ask you about this weird experience I recently had, where I saw someone's arcane aura. A piece of it broke off and shot <i>into</i> me, and I'm not sure if it needs to be removed or anything...)] your voice trails off as you see an extremely concerned look flash across Lilaya's face.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(Are you sure?! You absorbed someone's essence directly from them?!)] Lilaya asks, failing to conceal the worried tone in her voice.
			</p>
			<p>
				Before you can respond, Lilaya grabs your [pc.arm] and starts pulling you over to the same place where she ran her first test on you. Instructing you to sit on the chair in the middle of the chalk square, she once more starts adjusting the floodlight-like pieces of arcane equipment at each corner.
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Wait, my clothes aren't going to be teleported all over the room or anything again, are they?)] you ask.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(No, don't worry, I fixed that little problem!)] Lilaya responds, and before you get the chance to say anything else, arcane energy suddenly crackles into life around her arm, before shooting out into each of the curious instruments. A familiar bright pink flash illuminates the room, but this time, thankfully, your clothes and sight are unaffected.
			</p>
			<p>
				Once again, you find yourself surrounded by the shimmering pink outline of your arcane aura. This time, however, you see a strange ball of energy orbiting your body, which looks to be the same sort of size as the shard of energy that you remember shooting into you. Looking up at Lilaya, you see that her cheeks have completely drained of colour, and she's looking down at you with an extremely worried expression on her face.
			</p>
			
		#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_essenceBottledDiscovered))
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Well, you see, I had this little bottle with a swirling light in it, and when I took out the stopper, the light sort of shot <i>into</i> me...)] you explain, hoping that Lilaya can tell you what that was all about as well.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(Oh! Of course! I should have mentioned that,)] Lilaya responds. [lilaya.speech(As you've got a demon-strength aura, it's only natural that you'd be able to absorb arcane essences! I really should have tested you for that as well... But we can just do it now!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Before you can respond, Lilaya grabs your [pc.arm] and starts pulling you over to the same place where she ran her first test on you. Instructing you to sit on the chair in the middle of the chalk square, she once more starts adjusting the floodlight-like pieces of arcane equipment at each corner.
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Wait, my clothes aren't going to be teleported all over the room or anything again, are they?)] you ask.
			</p>
			<p>
				[lilaya.speech(No, don't worry, I fixed that little problem!)] Lilaya responds, and before you get the chance to say anything else, arcane energy suddenly crackles into life around her arm, before shooting out into each of the curious instruments. A familiar bright pink flash illuminates the room, but this time, thankfully, your clothes and sight are unaffected.
			</p>
			<p>
				Once again, you find yourself surrounded by the shimmering pink outline of your arcane aura. This time, however, you see a strange ball of energy orbiting your body, which looks to be the same sort of size as the shard of energy that you remember shooting into you. Looking up at Lilaya, you see that her cheeks have completely drained of colour, and she's looking down at you with an extremely worried expression on her face.
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_EXPLAINS_ESSENCES_2 -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_EXPLAINS_ESSENCES_2"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_essenceOrgasmDiscovered) || game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_essencePostCombatDiscovered))
		<p>
			[pc.speech(You look like you've seen a ghost, what's wrong?)] you ask, concerned by Lilaya's reaction.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Ah, well, it's just...)] Lilaya stumbles over her words a little as she responds. [lilaya.speech(You really, <i>really</i> shouldn't be able to do that!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Pointing at the ball of energy that's orbiting your aura, she continues, [lilaya.speech(You see that? You've absorbed a piece of someone's essence! There's something seriously wrong with your aura... Normally only Lilin are able to do that, hell, even demons can't absorb essences directly from people!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Wait, I absorbed their <i>essence</i>? What does that mean?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Well, basically, you absorbed a fragment of someone's aura. Extracting essences isn't harmful to either you or to the other person, and all auras replenish their natural strength very quickly, so don't worry about anything like that,)] Lilaya explains, pacing back and forth. [lilaya.speech(You see, using absorbed essences is the way in which enchantments are infused into objects. Normally, demons have to buy bottled essences in order to absorb them into their aura, but you can <i>somehow</i> absorb them directly from a person, just like a Lilin can! After absorbing an essence, you'll be able to use it to enchant items or remove seals... Look, it's better if I show you...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Lilaya flicks a switch on one of the instruments, and the shimmering pink aura instantly vanishes from sight. Stepping forwards, she takes you by the [pc.arm] once more, and quickly leads you over to another corner of the lab, where a long, sturdy table is covered in all sorts of alchemical-looking apparatus. Large glass bottles filled with brightly coloured liquids bubble away without any apparent source of heat, and all manner of strange looking ingredients lie scattered over the table's surface. Coming to a halt in front of the workspace, Lilaya turns to face you. [lilaya.speech(Right, I can explain as we go...)]
		</p>

	#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_essenceBottledDiscovered))
		<p>
			[pc.speech(You look like you've seen a ghost, what's wrong?)] you ask, concerned by Lilaya's reaction.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Ah, well, it's just...)] Lilaya stumbles over her words a little as she responds. [lilaya.speech(Your aura really, <i>really</i> shouldn't look like that!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Lilaya points up above your head, and you look up to see that there's a ball of energy orbiting your aura. [lilaya.speech(You see that? You've absorbed an essence! I mean, all demonic-strength auras can do that, but there's something seriously wrong with yours... I-It has the exact same characteristics as a Lilin's! With your aura, you'd even be able to absorb essences directly from people! Hell, even demons can't do that!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Wait, what does all of this mean?)] you ask.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Well, basically, you've absorbed an essence, which had been collected directly from someone's aura by a Lilin, and then bottled. Extracting essences isn't harmful to either the Lilin or to the other person, and all auras replenish their natural strength very quickly, so don't worry about anything like that,)] Lilaya explains, pacing back and forth. [lilaya.speech(You see, using absorbed essences is the way in which enchantments are infused into objects. Normally, demons have to buy bottled essences in order to absorb them into their aura, but <i>somehow</i> you'll be able to absorb them directly from a person, just like a Lilin can! After absorbing an essence, you'll be able to use it to enchant items or remove seals... Look, it's better if I show you...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Lilaya flicks a switch on one of the instruments, and the shimmering pink aura instantly vanishes from sight. Stepping forwards, she takes you by the [pc.arm] once more, and quickly leads you over to another corner of the lab, where a long, sturdy table is covered in all sorts of alchemical-looking apparatus. Large glass bottles filled with brightly coloured liquids bubble away without any apparent source of heat, and all manner of strange looking ingredients lie scattered over the table's surface. Coming to a halt in front of the workspace, Lilaya turns to face you. [lilaya.speech(Right, I can explain as we go...)]
		</p>
		
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(You look like you've seen a ghost, what's wrong?)] you ask, concerned by Lilaya's reaction.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Ah, well, it's just...)] Lilaya stumbles over her words a little as she responds. [lilaya.speech(Your aura really, <i>really</i> shouldn't look like that! I-I need to try something, hold still!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as Lilaya asks, you sit still as she turns around and runs over to a nearby desk. As she pulls open the top drawer, you hear the distinctive clink of multiple glass bottles bumping against each other. Lilaya reaches in and grabs something out of the drawer, before running back over to you and holding up what she just retrieved.
		</p>
		<p>
			In her hand, you see a tiny glass bottle, with a flickering purple light swirling around inside of it. Before you can ask what it is you're looking at, Lilaya pulls out the little cork stopper and holds the bottle out towards you. Almost instantly, the light darts out of its glass prison, and you let out a gasp as the curious little wisp shoots straight into your chest. Looking up at Lilaya in alarm, you see her pointing up above your head, and you look up to see that there's now a ball of energy orbiting your aura.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(You see that? You've absorbed an essence! I mean, all demonic-strength auras can do that, but there's something seriously wrong with yours...)] Lilaya says, shaking her head in disbelief. [lilaya.speech(Your aura has the exact same characteristics as a Lilin's! With your aura, you'd even be able to absorb essences directly from people! Hell, even demons can't do that!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Wait, what does all of this mean?)] you ask.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Well, basically, you just absorbed an essence, which had been collected directly from someone's aura by a Lilin, and then bottled. Extracting essences isn't harmful to either the Lilin or to the other person, and all auras replenish their natural strength very quickly, so don't worry about anything like that,)] Lilaya explains, pacing back and forth. [lilaya.speech(You see, using absorbed essences is the way in which enchantments are infused into objects. Normally, demons have to buy bottled essences in order to absorb them into their aura, but <i>somehow</i> you'll be able to absorb them directly from a person, just like a Lilin can! After absorbing an essence, you'll be able to use it to enchant items or remove seals... Look, it's better if I show you...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Lilaya flicks a switch on one of the instruments, and the shimmering pink aura instantly vanishes from sight. Stepping forwards, she takes you by the [pc.arm] once more, and quickly leads you over to another corner of the lab, where a long, sturdy table is covered in all sorts of alchemical-looking apparatus. Large glass bottles filled with brightly coloured liquids bubble away without any apparent source of heat, and all manner of strange looking ingredients lie scattered over the table's surface. Coming to a halt in front of the workspace, Lilaya turns to face you. [lilaya.speech(Right, I can explain as we go...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_EXPLAINS_ESSENCES_3 -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_EXPLAINS_ESSENCES_3"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Ok, so, first thing to know is that these essences are no longer part of the person that they originally came from. It's not as though you're trapping a part of their soul into enchanted items or anything like that!)] Lilaya starts explaining, [lilaya.speech(So don't have any qualms about using these essences to enchant or unseal anything!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she speaks, Lilaya reaches down under the table and produces a bottle of Feline's Fancy, putting it down on the desk before turning back towards you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Right, well I should probably demonstrate enchanting first! I still have a few essences absorbed from some work I was doing earlier, so I might as well use them on this!)] she says, and you notice that her earlier look of worry has been replaced with one of excitement. [lilaya.speech(So, you don't need any special equipment for this, all you need is an item, weapon, or piece of clothing to enchant, and the concentration to draw the essence out from your aura.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya picks up the bottle of Feline's Fancy, before placing a curious little green gem down next to it. [lilaya.speech(So, you have your base ingredient, and that's all well and good, but you can also add elements to an enchantment. Depending on what elements you choose to add, the resulting enchanted item will have different effects. Once you've decided on what ingredient and which elements you're going to use, you just need to focus on combining them...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya closes her eyes and lets out a deep breath, and you gasp as you suddenly see four little balls of purple energy orbiting her body. As you watch, two of the orbs suddenly shoot down into the bottle of Feline's Fancy, and with a bright pink flash and a wisp of odourless smoke, both the bottle and the little green gem disappear. In its place, a curious little bottle of red liquid has materialised out of thin-air.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(You have to sort of feel how much essence you want to pour into the enchantment. The more you put in, the better the resulting item!)] Lilaya picks up the little potion and places it off to one side. [lilaya.speech(And that's all there is to it!)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_jinxedClothingDiscovered) && pc.isAnyEquippedClothingSealed())
		<p>
			Just as your about to thank her for explaining about essences, Lilaya suddenly exclaims, [lilaya.speech(Oh, and this is also how items can be identified, as well as how that sealed clothing of yours needs to be removed! All you need to do is channel some of your absorbed essences into an unidentified item to discover the enchantment, or into sealed clothing to allow you to remove it. Sealed clothing is a major problem for people without demonic-strength auras, as they need to pay demons to remove the seal for them, but for you and I, sealed clothing is no more than a minor inconvenience.)]
		</p>
		
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Just as you're about to thank her for explaining about essences, Lilaya suddenly exclaims, [lilaya.speech(Oh, and this is also how items can be identified, as well as how sealed clothing is removed! All you need to do is channel some of your absorbed essences into an unidentified item to discover the enchantment. Also, if you ever find yourself putting on some clothing, and then it just won't come off, you need to do the same thing, and channel some of your absorbed essences into it to break the seal. Sealed clothing is a major problem for people without demonic-strength auras, as they need to pay demons to remove the seal for them, but for you and I, sealed clothing is no more than a minor inconvenience.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_EXPLAINS_ESSENCES_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thanks, Lilaya, I understand now, but it still seems a little strange.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(The only strange thing about all this is how you're able to absorb essences like a Lilin,)] Lilaya responds, [lilaya.speech(but anyway, I've already got that arcane observation device set up in your room, so hopefully the test results will give me some idea of what's happening.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, hopefully, thanks again, Lilaya.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(You're welcome!)] she answers, before stepping away and giving you some time to think.
	</p>
	<div class='container-full-width' style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>You can now enchant items by selecting them in your inventory, and then pressing the 'Enchant' button.</i><br/>
		<i>In the same way, you're now able to unseal clothing. Simply select the clothing in your inventory, then press the 'Unseal' button.</i>
	</div>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ESSENCE_EXTRACTION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ESSENCE_EXTRACTION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_essenceExtractionKnown))
		<p>
			Turning towards Lilaya, you get her attention before asking, [pc.speech(Is it ok if I extract some more essences?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Of course!)] she responds. [lilaya.speech(Use as many vials as you'd like!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reaching down to pull a few of the little glass containers out from their storage, you wonder which, and how many, of your essences to extract...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(You mentioned that demons absorb essences from bottled sources, so I was wondering if it would be possible to make some of those myself?)] you ask.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Oh, of course that's possible,)] Lilaya happily replies, beckoning you over to one of the many tables in her lab. [lilaya.speech(It's actually one of the easiest things about essence manipulation!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Bending down, Lilaya pulls out a heavy cardboard box, and you hear the high-pitched tinkling sound of countless little glass vials as they knock against each other. Taking one of the empty vessels from out of the box, Lilaya stands up and holds it out towards you. You see that it's no larger than one of her slender fingers, and as you take it from Lilaya's outstretched hand, you see that there's a little cork stopper wedged into the top.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(These are how ordinary arcane users, like me, absorb essences. This one's empty at the moment, so if you take the cork out and concentrate on drawing an essence out from your aura, the vial's special enchantment will do the rest!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Turning the little glass container over in your [pc.hands], you look up at Lilaya. [pc.speech(So <i>all</i> essences that 'ordinary' arcane users have absorbed come from little vials like this?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(That's right,)] Lilaya responds. [lilaya.speech(Well, they come from a Lilin originally, then are extracted into these vials and sold on! Thanks to this unique ability of theirs, and I guess also being given anything they want from Lilith herself, all Lilin are extremely wealthy. I mean, essences are always in high demand, so all a Lilin has to do to earn money is extract some essences and sell them. These empty containers are next to worthless, so if you wanted to extract some essences, please feel free to use as many as you'd like!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You thank Lilaya, and after she moves away to give you a little space, you start to wonder how many of your essences to extract...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ESSENCE_EXTRACTION_BOTTLED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ESSENCE_EXTRACTION_BOTTLED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You pull out the little cork from the top of one of the glass vials, and, closing your [pc.eyes], you concentrate on extracting the arcane essence. Suddenly, you feel a strange little tugging sensation, and, opening your [pc.eyes], you see a pink, swirling glow within the vial in your [pc.hand]. Pushing the cork stopper back in the top, you smile as you realise that you've successfully extracted an essence; something that only a Lilin should be able to do!
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_CURRENT_DATE_TALK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_CURRENT_DATE_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious about the date shown on the calendar in your room, you decide to ask Lilaya about it, [pc.speech(Is the calendar in my room accurate? It's three years into the future from my world...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya frowns as she hears you say that, and leans back against the desk behind her. [lilaya.speech(Well, I can assure you that the year is [#game.getYear()]. Your world was still in [#game.getStartingDate().minusYears(3).getYear()], huh?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You answer in the affirmative, and Lilaya pushes her glasses up to the bridge of her nose, before crossing her arms and sighing, [lilaya.speech(It shouldn't be anything to worry about. There must have been a chain of events in our world's past that led to the year being counted slightly differently to yours. Or maybe you time-travelled when you were teleported into this world!)] As she starts thinking out loud, you can hear the growing excitement in her voice, [lilaya.speech(In fact, it's pretty incredible that your world even uses the same calendar system as ours! And, thinking about it even more, why do we even speak the same language? And how come your customs, clothing, and even your appearance are similar to ours?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You start to chat with Lilaya about the peculiarities of these shared features between your worlds. The more you start to delve into it, however, the more surprised you are at the lack of historical knowledge that Lilaya has. [lilaya.speech(Well, the only history that anyone really knows about is stuff concerning Lilith. She's been ruling this world since before any trace of civilisation even existed, so I guess all of our customs come from her direct influence. I don't think anybody other than Lilith herself really knows much about this world's history. Maybe mommy-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya's cheeks suddenly flush red, and she turns away as she brings a close to the conversation, [lilaya.speech(Anyway! D-Don't worry about anything! Three years into the future is nothing! I-I'll try and investigate a little more, ok?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		It's quite apparent that Lilaya isn't interested in discussing the matter any more...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_CURRENT_DATE_TALK_KNOW_TRUTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to talk to Lilaya about the date shown on the calendar in your room, you observe, [pc.speech(So, not only did Lilith change my old reality, but I also travelled three years into the future...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya sighs as she hears you say that, and leans back against the desk behind her. [lilaya.speech(It would appear so. The year is most definitely [#game.getYear()], but even if it was still [#game.getStartingDate().minusYears(3).getYear()], there still wouldn't be any indication that this is the altered version of reality.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you make an affirmative noise, Lilaya pushes her glasses up to the bridge of her nose, before crossing her arms and sighing, [lilaya.speech(Well, there's nothing that can be done about it now, except continuing with our plan to overthrow the elder lilin. At least now we know why your language, customs, clothing, and even your appearance are similar to those in this reality.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With nothing more to be said on the matter, Lilaya brings a close to the conversation, [lilaya.speech(Anyway, I should get back on with my work, unless there's anything else you needed?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping forwards, you smile at your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)]. [pc.speech(Hi, Lilaya, I'm here for those tests you mentioned.)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.getPlayer().isVisiblyPregnant() && !game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_reactedToPregnancyLilaya))
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Excellent! Let's just... Wait... Are you <i>pregnant</i>?! Well, nevermind, I can help you deal with that later! For now, let's just get these tests done, come over here!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Excellent! Let's get these tests done then, come over here!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		You do as she instructs, and make your way over to where Lilaya's standing. Rose quickly moves out of the way, hurrying over to a corner of the room and blushing as you say hello.
		#IF(!pc.isTaur())
			 Lilaya motions for you to sit down in the chair she just vacated, and as you do so, she grabs a smooth, wand-like instrument from another table.
		#ELSE
			 Lilaya motions for you to stand next to the chair she just vacated, and as you do so, she grabs a smooth, wand-like instrument from another table.
		#ENDIF
		 Moving over to you, the wand suddenly starts giving off a faint pink glow, and she starts swiping it over your body, humming as she does so.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Hmm... Yes... That's what I thought...)] she says, but before you have a chance to ask her what's going on, she steps back and places the wand to one side. [lilaya.speech(Your arcane aura hasn't shown any signs of degradation at all. It looks like it's permanent. If you've been out in Dominion, maybe you've noticed by now, but with an aura that strong, you have the same effect on people that a demon would.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You mean...)] you start, but Lilaya cuts you off.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Yes, I mean that anyone you encounter is going to feel extremely aroused when in your presence,)] she explains, [lilaya.speech(and if you haven't figured it out yet, that's the main power behind the arcane. Sure, it can be harnessed to create all sorts of spells and enchantments, but at its core, it's a primitive force linked very closely to sexual energy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So everyone I meet is going to want to have sex with me?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Sort of, but remember that they have their own, less powerful, auras that shield them from the potency of yours. If they become too weak, whether mentally or physically, they won't be able to control their aura any more, and that's when all they'll be able to think of is... well... A-Anyway, the same applies right back at you!)] she says, starting to blush a little.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So if someone beats me up, my own arcane aura is going to make me want to have sex with them?!)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Well, you'll still be able to summon some resistance, but it's unlikely that you'll be able to put up much of a fight at that stage... Oh, and it'll also happen if you cast too many spells and get mentally fatigued. Anyway, enough of that for now, I need to tell you what I've discovered!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_REPEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping forwards, you smile at your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)]. [pc.speech(Hi, Lilaya, I'm here for some more of those tests...)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && !game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_reactedToPregnancyLilaya))
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Excellent! Let's just... Wait... Are you <i>pregnant</i>?! Well, if you want help with that, all you have to do is ask! For now, let's just get these... Erm... <i>tests</i> done, come over here!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Excellent! Let's get these... Erm... <i>tests</i> done then, come over here!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Rose quickly moves out of the way, hurrying over to a corner of the room and blushing as you say hello.
		#IF(!pc.isTaur())
			 Looking back over to Lilaya, you see her motioning for you to come and sit down in the chair she just vacated.
		#ELSE
			 Looking back over to Lilaya, you see her motioning for you to come and stand next to the chair she just vacated.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_LEAVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You make your excuses to Lilaya, and, while she looks a little sad that you're not going to stay with her, she doesn't openly object.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(If you change your mind, just let me know!)] she says, before backing off a little to give you some space.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_MORE_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_MORE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping forwards, you smile at your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] and ask, [pc.speech(Hi, Lilaya, I was wondering if you wanted to run some more of those... <i>tests</i>?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Ah! Y-Yes! I was hoping for some more of those...)] she responds, fiercely blushing.
	</p>
	<p>
		Rose, understanding what's about to happen, quickly makes her exit, and hurries out of the lab. Lilaya motions for you to come and stand next to the chair she just vacated, smiling seductively as you do as she commands.
	</p>
	<p>
		You look up into her lustful, [lilaya.eyes+], and before you can say anything, she takes your head in both hands and presses her lips against yours. Her tongue slips out of her mouth, and you part your lips as you allow it to slide into yours.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_MORE_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You briefly wonder if it's your aura that's making Lilaya so horny, but whatever it is, you're feeling the same effects. You've never wanted someone as badly as you want her right now, and you feel your heart pounding as her soft, delicate lips press against yours. Before you can make the next move, Lilaya suddenly pulls back and takes the initiative. Pushing you down into the chair she recently vacated, she then throws one leg over yours, before sliding down to sit in your lap, bringing the two of you face-to-face.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to fuck me, make sure you pull out, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant!)] she demands.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_innoxia_amazons_secret) && pc.hasVagina() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to scissor, make sure you pull back before climaxing, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant from the effects of Amazon's Secret!)] she demands.
		#ELSE
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes!)] she giggles.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] throws you a quick, seductive smile, before taking your head in both hands and pressing her lips against yours once more. Reaching up, you pull her in close against your body, passionately making out with one another as you both give in to your lust.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_MORE_SEX_START_TAUR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You briefly wonder if it's your aura that's making Lilaya so horny, but whatever it is, you're feeling the same effects. You've never wanted someone as badly as you want her right now, and you feel your heart pounding as her soft, delicate lips press against yours. Before you can make the next move, Lilaya suddenly pulls back and takes the initiative. Stepping around to one side of your [pc.legRace]-like lower body, she sinks to her knees and reaches up to run her fingers up and over your animalistic groin.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to fuck me, make sure you pull out, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant!)] she demands.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_innoxia_amazons_secret) && pc.hasVagina() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to scissor, make sure you pull back before climaxing, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant from the effects of Amazon's Secret!)] she demands.
		#ELSE
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes!)] she giggles.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply, Lilaya shuffles forwards, moving under your feral body as she prepares to satisfy you with her mouth. Letting out a passionate [pc.moan], you prepare to have some fun with your horny [lilaya.relation(pc)].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_MORE_SEX_STOP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Prying her off of you, you make your excuses to Lilaya as you get up out of the chair. While she's quite clearly upset that you're not going to let her have some fun, she doesn't openly object.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(If you change your mind, just let me know!)] she says, before backing off a little to give you some space.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_ARTHUR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_ARTHUR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Have you found a way to get me back home then?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Sorry, but no. That's what I needed to talk to you about,)] Lilaya answers, [lilaya.speech(The truth is, even though I'm considered one of the top experts in all things related to the arcane, I have no idea how you've ended up here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You can't help but feel completely deflated. Although Lilaya's home isn't exactly the worst place to be living, this whole world still makes you feel uneasy. You were rather hoping that this demonic version of your aunt could have found some way to send you back to where you belong, and as she delivers this bad news, you collapse back in your chair and let out a deep sigh.
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing your reaction, Lilaya lets out a sigh of her own, before offering you a sliver of hope, [lilaya.speech(Well... I suppose there is <i>one</i> way we could find out more... but it means I'd have to talk to <i>him</i> again. There's no way I'm going over there to ask for his help though!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You look up to see Lilaya's face turned up into a scowl as she continues, [lilaya.speech(If you ever want to find a way to go back home, you're going to have to get the help of Arthur... <i>that bastard!</i>)] she spits, before realising how angry she's become. Lilaya closes her eyes for a moment and takes a deep breath, calming herself down before continuing, [lilaya.speech(He and I used to work together, and with the exception of the Lilin themselves, he probably understands more about the arcane than anyone currently living. His apartment's over in Demon Home, but despite the name, people of all races live there. He's actually just a human, which makes his knowledge of the arcane all the more impressive. Here's his address... look for a building called 'Sawlty Towers'. So if you want his help, you're going to have to convince him to stop being such a <i>selfish bastard!</i> He'll need access to my research, and the only way he's going to get it is if he comes crawling to my front door, begging for my forgiveness.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You're quite taken aback at Lilaya's apparent hatred for Arthur. You assume, seeing as he shares the same name, that he's this world's version of your [lilaya.relation(pc)] Lily's colleague from the museum. Back there, they were close friends, and you wonder what's happened in this reality to cause Lilaya to dislike him so much. Seeing how angry she's gotten just at the thought of him, you decide that it would be wise not to press the matter further, and instead you just agree to convince Arthur to apologise.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Good, good... Well, anyway, umm, I guess we're done here,)] Lilaya says, but before you can make a move, she nervously picks up the little wand-like instrument she used to test you earlier, and continues, [lilaya.speech(W-Wait, erm, I mean, t-there's some more tests I could... try on you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya seems to have become quite embarrassed by something, and you find this sudden offer of 'more tests' to be pretty suspicious. She's gripping the wand quite tightly now, and you notice her eyes keep glancing down hungrily at your body. You're almost certain that she's just making an excuse to get you to stay here, and the sudden thought that she's trying to hit on you flashes across your mind...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_ARTHUR_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You make your excuses to Lilaya, and, while she looks a little sad that you're not going to stay with her, she doesn't openly object.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(If you change your mind, just let me know!)] she says, before backing off a little to give you some space.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_HORNY_LILAYA -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_HORNY_LILAYA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Well, if there are more tests you need to run, then sure,)] you say.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Excellent! Now, let me just start up here...)] she happily replies.
	</p>
	<p>
		You remain quite still as Lilaya steps in front of you, holding the wand out to run it over your head.
		#IF(!pc.isTaur())
			 As she does this, she places one hand on your shoulder and leans down, lowering her chest so that her large breasts are directly in front of your face.
		#ELSE
			 As she does this, she places one hand on your shoulder and pushes her chest out, immediately drawing your attention towards her large breasts.
		#ENDIF
		 You can't help but notice that the top few buttons of both her lab coat and her shirt are undone, giving you a clear display of her impressive cleavage.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(I hope you aren't looking anywhere naughty...)] Lilaya softly whispers in your ear, before straightening back up and moving around behind you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(What?! No, I-)] you start, but Lilaya cuts you off as she reaches around to put a finger on your lips.
	</p>
	<p>
		You blush as you feel her free hand press the wand against your inner-thigh, and, still holding her finger over your mouth, she starts to slide the arcane instrument up your body. You can't help but feel aroused as Lilaya presses the wand up and over your chest, while simultaneously trying to push her finger into your mouth.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_HORNY_LILAYA_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not feeling completely comfortable with the way your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] is trying to get you turned on,
		#IF(!pc.isTaur())
			 you quickly stand up and make your excuses as to why you need to leave.
		#ELSE
			 you quickly step back and make your excuses as to why you need to leave.
		#ENDIF
		 While Lilaya looks a little disappointed that you're putting a stop to her advances, she doesn't openly object, and moves back to give you some space, before placing the wand-like instrument back on the table from which it came.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(If you change your mind and want me to try these... erm... <i>tests</i> again, just let me know,)] Lilaya says, clearly hoping that you will.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_HORNY_LILAYA_WANTS_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_HORNY_LILAYA_WANTS_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You part your lips slightly, allowing Lilaya to slip her finger into your mouth. As she slowly starts sliding her digit back and forth past your lips, you notice a faint, salty taste hitting your tongue. As a second finger pushes its way in to join the first, you realise that this is the same hand she was using to finger Rose. Before you can object, you suddenly notice that she's using her free hand to give your groin an experimental squeeze, and, without thinking, you find yourself bucking back against her touch.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Good [pc.girl]...)] she whispers in your ear, [lilaya.speech(And just to think, I was worried that you wouldn't like this...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You've become so caught up in the moment that you haven't even considered putting an end to all this, but as Lilaya draws her fingers from your mouth, you have a sudden moment of clarity in which you find yourself once again thinking of how similar Lilaya looks and sounds to your aunt Lily.
		#IF(pc.hasFetish(FETISH_INCEST))
			 As you've got a serious kink for incestuous sex, you can't help but find this fact immensely arousing, and buck your groin even harder into your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s hand.
		#ELSE
			 Then again, she <i>is</i> [lilaya.a_race] in this reality, so there's no real relation between the two of you... right?
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment, Lilaya leans in to whisper one last thing in your ear,
		#IF(lilaya.getSubspecies()==SUBSPECIES_DEMON)
			 [lilaya.speech(You want to see what my hot little demon pussy looks like, don't you?)]
		#ELSE
			 [lilaya.speech(You know, I'm all-demon where it counts... You want to see what a demon's pussy looks like, don't you?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_HORNY_LILAYA_WANTS_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You briefly wonder if it's your aura that's making Lilaya so horny, but whatever it is, you're feeling the same effects. You've never wanted someone as badly as you want her right now, and you feel your heart pounding as her soft, delicate fingers stroke over your lips. Before you can make the next move, Lilaya suddenly pulls back and takes the initiative. Stepping around to one side, she quickly throws one leg over yours and slides down to sit in your lap, bringing the two of you face-to-face.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to fuck me, make sure you pull out, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant!)] she demands.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_innoxia_amazons_secret) && pc.hasVagina() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to scissor, make sure you pull back before climaxing, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant from the effects of Amazon's Secret!)] she demands.
		#ELSE
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes!)] she giggles.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply, your [lilaya.relation(pc)] throws you a quick, seductive smile, before taking your head in both hands and pressing her lips against yours once more. Reaching up, you pull her in close against your body, passionately making out with one another as you both give in to your lust.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_HORNY_LILAYA_WANTS_SEX_START_TAUR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You briefly wonder if it's your aura that's making Lilaya so horny, but whatever it is, you're feeling the same effects. You've never wanted someone as badly as you want her right now, and you feel your heart pounding as her soft, delicate fingers stroke over your lips. Before you can make the next move, Lilaya suddenly pulls back and takes the initiative. Stepping around to one side of your [pc.legRace]-like lower body, she sinks to her knees and reaches up to run her fingers once again over your animalistic groin.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to fuck me, make sure you pull out, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant!)] she demands.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_innoxia_amazons_secret) && pc.hasVagina() && !lilaya.isVisiblyPregnant() && lilaya.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isNegative())
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes! Just, if you want to scissor, make sure you pull back before climaxing, ok? I'm <b>not</b> getting pregnant from the effects of Amazon's Secret!)] she demands.
		#ELSE
			[lilaya.speech(Mmm, yes!)] she giggles.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply, Lilaya shuffles forwards, moving under your feral body as she prepares to start by using her mouth. Letting out a passionate [pc.moan], you prepare to have some fun with your horny [lilaya.relation(pc)].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUNT_HOME_LABORATORY_TESTING_HORNY_LILAYA_WANTS_SEX_DECLINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not feeling comfortable with the way your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] is fully prepared and eager to have sex with you,
		#IF(!pc.isTaur())
			 you quickly stand up and make your excuses as to why you need to leave.
		#ELSE
			 you quickly step back and make your excuses as to why you need to leave.
		#ENDIF
		 While Lilaya looks more than a little disappointed that you're putting a stop to all of this, she doesn't openly object, and moves back to give you some space, before placing the wand-like instrument back on the table from which it came.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(If you change your mind and want me to try these... erm... <i>tests</i> again, just let me know,)] Lilaya says, clearly hoping that you will.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_FRIEND_ACCOMMODATION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to ask Lilaya about the possibility of inviting guests to come and live here, you take a step towards your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] and ask, [pc.speech(Er, Lilaya, you know all of these empty rooms you've got in your house?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Mmm, what about them?)] she answers, raising one eyebrow as she peers at you over the top of her glasses.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Well, I was wondering if I'd be able to use some of them for guests to stay in.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya lets out a sigh, and, placing her hands on her hips, asks, [lilaya.speech(Who's going to be the one paying for their food and cleaning bills? I trust your judgement, so I don't mind your friends using the spare rooms, but I'm certainly not going to be the one to foot the bill.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'll pay for their rent and expenses,)] you reply. [pc.speech(I'll be able to afford that, don't worry.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Mmm, well, ok then. After all, the more people living here, the more opportunities I'll have to run some background tests on arcane aura fluctuations. You see, I'm very interested in finding out if your demon-strength aura has any sort of long-term impact on those around you. I doubt that it will, but as far as I'm aware, nobody's done research into this before!)] your [lilaya.relation(pc)] replies, giving you her explicit permission to invite your new friend to come and live here with you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thanks, Lilaya! You have no idea how much you're helping them out by doing this,)] you say, smiling fondly at your [lilaya.relation(pc)] as she pushes her glasses back up to the bridge of her nose.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Y-Yes, well, y-you're welcome,)] Lilaya stutters a little, blushing in response to your heartfelt thanks. [lilaya.speech(Just go to whichever room you'd like to use, then call for Rose to prepare it as a guest bedroom. A-And it's not like I'm doing this just for you or your friend, I-I'm just interested in researching the arcane!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ok, thanks again,)] you reply, not wanting to say too much more out of fear of embarrassing your [lilaya.relation(pc)]. Giving her a loving smile, you turn around and head for the lab's exit, determined to return to your friend and invite them to come and live here as soon as possible.
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsGood(You can now invite characters to come and live with you! To do so, you'll need to upgrade one of the empty rooms into a 'Guest Room', before asking the character to move in with you.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_SLAVER_RECOMMENDATION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Lilaya that you're trying to obtain a slaver license, and that during your attempts to acquire one you were informed that you'd need a letter of recommendation from someone who's already got a license. With that, you lead into asking your [lilaya.relation(pc)] if she could write a letter of recommendation for you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya lets out a little sigh and raises her eyebrow as she hears this. Leaning back in her chair, she asks, [lilaya.speech(I'm fine with writing a letter for you, but have you thought about where you're going to keep your slaves?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that you hadn't thought about the logistics of owning slaves, you tell Lilaya that you haven't got a plan for that yet.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(I thought not,)] Lilaya responds, before instructing Rose to bring her a piece of paper and a pen. After the cat-girl maid has quickly carried out this order, Lilaya starts writing your letter, speaking to you as she does so, [lilaya.speech(You're going to need a place to keep your slaves. No doubt they'll tell you all this when you receive your license, but the Slavery Administration is only for holding your new slaves until their relocation. It's <i>not</i> a permanent place to keep them. So, you'll be needing somewhere to house your slaves, won't you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_SLAVER_RECOMMENDATION_SLAVE_ACCOMMODATION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Replying to Lilaya's question in the affirmative, you brace yourself to be on the receiving end of one of your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s scoldings.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Well, luckily for you, I think I can help,)] Lilaya responds, putting your fears of having to endure one of her lectures to rest. Standing up from behind her desk with the completed letter of recommendation in her hand, she states, [lilaya.speech(I'm sure you've noticed, but this house is extremely large, which also means that it's an extremely time-consuming job to keep clean. Isn't that right, Rose?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[rose.speech(Yes, Mistress!)] Rose's voice calls out from one side of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(So, I've got a deal to make. I only ever use my lab and my bedroom, and as you've probably seen, all the other rooms in this house are left empty and unused. I'm willing to let you use those empty rooms as accommodation for your slaves, but only on the condition that you either pay a daily upkeep for each room that you use, or you assign some of your slaves to help with the cleaning. Deal?)] Lilaya offers, tightly holding on to the letter of recommendation as she awaits your answer. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Thinking that her deal sounds fair enough, you nod in agreement and thank Lilaya for her offer.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Great!)] Lilaya responds, beaming at you as she gives you the letter. [lilaya.speech(If you want to use any of the rooms to house slaves, just go into the one you'd like and ring the bell-pull. Rose will handle all the necessary arrangements. Oh, and if you'd like to get Rose to manage your slaves for you, she's more than capable. Just ring the little bell beside her room's door, and she'll come running, won't you, Rose?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[rose.speech(Yes, Mistress! I'd love to help,)] Rose obediently replies.
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] suddenly seems to recall something, and after raising her finger, she states, [lilaya.speech(I've just remembered that we have several books in the library about slavery. You might want to read up on things. Rose, tell [pc.name] exactly where those slavery books are, will you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Rushing forwards to obey, Rose tells you in which of the library's many aisles the books on slavery can be found. After thanking both Rose and Lilaya for their help, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Arthur: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAB_ARTHURS_TALE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling Lilaya that you'll help Rose clear out the lab's storeroom, you hope that your reply will calm your [lilaya.relation(pc)] down.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Thank you, [pc.name]. Rose would be able to manage by herself, but it'll be a lot quicker with your help,)] Lilaya says, before stepping to one side and turning to face Arthur, [lilaya.speech(You should let [pc.name] know how you ended up as Zaranix's slave; after all, [pc.she] was the one who went through all that trouble to free you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[arthur.speech(Yes, Lilaya,)] Arthur responds, before turning to address you. [arthur.speech(We can discuss it a little more some other time, but the basic gist of it is that I decided to do a little research into arcane teleportation.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Which is illegal,)] Lilaya interjects.
	</p>
	<p>
		[arthur.speech(Yes, thank you, Lilaya. Which is illegal. Anyway, thanks to a certain amber-haired demon, who I <i>assumed</i> was no more than a succubus looking to make some quick cash, I ended up creating a teleportation device that actually worked! Well, it sort of worked... It didn't quite take me to where I wanted to go...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You notice Arthur glance across to Lilaya, and the pair of them exchange a slightly worried look, before he continues, [arthur.speech(Anyway, when I returned, I discovered that Amber had already called for the Enforcers. After immediately being enslaved for 'treason', I was quickly shunted through the legal process, and, through a series of bribes, Zaranix quickly gained possession of me. It turned out that he'd been watching me for months, waiting for me to make a mistake so that he could get me enslaved. He was under the rather deluded impression that I'd be able to make a demonic transformative potion, among other things, and that I'd therefore be able to make him rich.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Which could actually be possible, by the way,)] Lilaya interrupts again, leaning back against a desk and crossing her arms.
	</p>
	<p>
		[arthur.speech(Erm, no. It isn't possible. You can harness arcane power to create transformatives for other races, but demonic essence is actually-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Oh please, give me a break. Who was it that said inter-dimensional travel wasn't possible, even when the entire rest of the research community said it was? Oh, that'd be you. And look what's sitting right next to you. Proof that it is possible!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[arthur.speech(L-Lilaya, we can discuss that another time. What I'm talking about it demonic essences being, by their very nature, incompatible with transformative consumables, or indeed items of any sort!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(I honestly can't believe how thick you are sometimes, Arthur. But then again, it is to be expected of someone who'd go behind their lover's back to fuck-)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[arthur.speech(How many times do I have to apologise?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Oh, I'm sorry, I thought <i>I</i> was talking. But that's ok. Seeing as you want to interrupt me, you're obviously very eager to talk about how much you liked fucking her behind my back, so please, do go on!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
