<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- LILAYA_ASSISTS_PREGNANCY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_PREGNANCY_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isShy())
		<p>
			Stepping forwards, you smile at your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)], before looking down and pointedly rubbing your belly. Glancing back up into your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s eyes, you mumble, [pc.speech(Erm... Lilaya...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Wait... Are you <i>pregnant</i>?!)] she asks.
		</p>
		<p>
			You aren't quite sure what to say, and sheepishly look back down at the floor, averting Lilaya's gaze as you hear her footsteps drawing near. Before you know what's happening, her hands are rubbing all over your belly, and you let out a little gasp at the sudden feeling of someone else touching your pregnant bump.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Stepping forwards, you smile at your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)], before glancing down and pointedly rubbing your belly. Looking back up into your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s eyes, you smile and announce, [pc.speech(Hey, Lilaya, I've gone and got pregnant. What should I do now?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(You really should have thought of that before you had unprotected sex,)] she scolds, before stepping up before you and running her hands over your swollen belly. Letting out a sigh, she looks up into your eyes and says, [lilaya.speech(I can help you with this, don't worry...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_PREGNANCY_LILAYA_POSSIBLY_FATHER"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isShy())
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Erm... Lilaya? Just so you know, you <i>might</i> be the one who got me pregnant...)] you explain, nervously shuffling your [pc.feet] once again.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getFertilisationType()==FERTILISATION_NORMAL)
				[lilaya.speech(Well, you're the one who wanted me to grow a cock, remember?)]
			#ELSE
				[lilaya.speech(Well, you're the one who wanted me to drink that bottle of Amazon's Secret, remember?)]
			#ENDIF
			 Lilaya laughs, clearly not at all worried by the fact that she might be the 'father' to your children.
		</p>
		<p>
			You feel very conscious of the fact that you just admitted to having had other sexual partners to Lilaya. As you glance over to the nearby chair that you both had sex on, the feeling of guilt in the back of your mind causes you to start explaining yourself to your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)], [pc.speech(Well... You don't mind that I've been with other partners, do you? I mean, I still like you and everything...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You look up to see Lilaya's cheeks flush red, and she momentarily stops feeling your stomach, leaving her hands to rest on your belly as she stutters a response, [lilaya.speech(O-Oh, no, not at all! D-Don't worry about it! I-I mean... I still like you too... A-And I've kind of got this special sort of relationship with Rose... S-So I didn't think we were exclusive or anything...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Oh, yeah, and it <i>might</i> be you who got me pregnant,)] you explain, thinking that you should probably let Lilaya know that she could be the 'father' of your children.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Well, you seemed to be up for it at the time, remember?)] Lilaya laughs, seemingly not picking up on the fact that you've slept with someone other than her.
		</p>
		<p>
			Wanting to make sure that Lilaya understands what it is you're trying to say, you explain to your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)], [pc.speech(I didn't mean it like that; I meant that the father could be someone else... You don't mind that I've been with other partners, do you? I mean, I still like you and everything...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You look up to see Lilaya's cheeks flush red, and she momentarily stops feeling your stomach, leaving her hands to rest on your belly as she stutters a response, [lilaya.speech(O-Oh, no, not at all! D-Don't worry about it! I-I mean... I still like you too... A-And I've kind of got this special sort of relationship with Rose... S-So I didn't think we were exclusive or anything...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_PREGNANCY_LILAYA_DEFINITELY_FATHER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isShy())
			[pc.speech(Erm... Lilaya? Just so you know, you're definitely the one that got me pregnant...)] you sheepishly explain, looking down at your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s hands as they continue roaming over your swollen stomach.
		#ELSE
			[pc.speech(Oh, and Lilaya? Just so you know, you're definitely the one that got me pregnant.)] you explain, looking down at your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s hands as they continue roaming over your swollen stomach.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getFertilisationType()==FERTILISATION_NORMAL)
			[lilaya.speech(Well, you're the one who wanted me to grow a cock, remember?)]
		#ELSE
			[lilaya.speech(Well, you're the one who wanted me to drink that bottle of Amazon's Secret, remember?)]
		#ENDIF
		 Lilaya laughs, clearly not at all worried by the fact that she's the 'father' to your children.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_PREGNANCY_LILAYA_DEFINITELY_NOT_FATHER"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isShy())
		<p>
			You feel very conscious of the fact that you're presenting clear evidence of having other sexual partners to Lilaya. As you glance over to the nearby chair that you both had sex on, the feeling of guilt in the back of your mind causes you to start explaining yourself to your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)], [pc.speech(So... You don't mind that I've been with other partners, do you? I mean, I still like you and everything...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You look up to see Lilaya's cheeks flush red, and she momentarily stops feeling your stomach, leaving her hands to rest on your belly as she stutters a response, [lilaya.speech(O-Oh, no, not at all! D-Don't worry about it! I-I mean... I still like you too... A-And I've kind of got this special sort of relationship with Rose... S-So I didn't think we were exclusive or anything...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to make sure that Lilaya isn't angry at you for having other sexual partners, you explain, [pc.speech(So... You don't mind that I've been with other partners, do you? I mean, I still like you and everything...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You look up to see Lilaya's cheeks flush red, and she momentarily stops feeling your stomach, leaving her hands to rest on your belly as she stutters a response, [lilaya.speech(O-Oh, no, not at all! D-Don't worry about it! I-I mean... I still like you too... A-And I've kind of got this special sort of relationship with Rose... S-So I didn't think we were exclusive or anything...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_PREGNANCY_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		She suddenly breaks off from fondling your abdomen, before grabbing your wrist and starting to pull you further into her lab. Looking around, you see that Rose has vacated the area, leaving you alone with your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)].
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isPlotDiscovered())
			[lilaya.speech(This is so exciting! I wonder how your body's going to react, what with you having been unaffected by Lilith's spell and everything!)]
		#ELSE
			[lilaya.speech(This is so exciting! I wonder how your body's going to react, what with you coming from another universe and everything!)]
		#ENDIF
		 she exclaims, getting you to sit down on a nearby chair before running off to rummage around in some nearby boxes. As she does so, she shouts back over her shoulder, [lilaya.speech(I'm guessing you're not aware of how pregnancies work here, huh? Well, seeing as the arcane has a massive effect on it, I'm guessing it's pretty different than it is in your world! Hmm... Where did it go?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya stops talking for a moment as she concentrates on searching through the boxes. You aren't given much time to think about what she's saying before you see her straighten up and turn around, and as she starts walking back over towards you, you notice that she's holding another of those wand-like instruments in her right hand.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(So, I'm guessing you've already realised that the arcane has a big influence on pregnancy speed,)] she laughs, stroking your belly once more before stepping back and tinkering with some small dials on the instrument she's just retrieved. [lilaya.speech(I've actually done a fair bit of research on the arcane's influence on pregnancies, so I know that without its presence, pregnancies should really be taking about nine months...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you try to assimilate the information Lilaya's giving you, the instrument in her hand starts giving off a faint pink glow. Letting out a satisfied hum, your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)] brings the little wand down to your pregnant bump, before running it up and down over your swollen belly. Letting out a series of concerned humming sounds, a puzzled expression settles on Lilaya's face, but before you can start to worry about what might be wrong, the instrument suddenly releases a bright flash of pink light, causing Lilaya to let out a happy little cry.
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Well, that's a relief! Oh, right, I need to explain what's going on!)] she says, putting the instrument down on a nearby table before turning back to face you. [lilaya.speech(So, it turns out that your body has completely adapted to this world, and you're going to be obeying the same sort of rules for pregnancy as the rest of us! What that means is that you're not going to be pregnant for the better part of a year; it's going to be more like a few weeks at most. Oh, and also, the races of the children you're going to give birth to will be a split between your race, and the race of the father. Pretty exciting, huh?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isConfident())
			You look down at your pregnant belly, stroking it absent-mindedly as Lilaya's words sink in. As your thoughts turn to the process of bringing up a child in this strange world, you let out a deep sigh and ask, [pc.speech(How do people even bring children up in this world? And of course, what about the whole part of actually giving birth? I guess my life's going to change a lot...)]
		#ELSE
			You look down at your pregnant belly, stroking it absent-mindedly as Lilaya's words sink in. As your thoughts turn to the process of bringing up a child in this strange world, you feel yourself starting to become overwhelmed by emotion, and you blurt out to Lilaya, [pc.speech(B-but what do I do?! How am I meant to raise a child here?! A-And, what about the whole part of actually giving birth?! This is too much!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your surprise, Lilaya's face momentarily scrunches up into a look of confusion, as though she doesn't quite know what you're talking about. Thankfully, after just a moment, she lets out an understanding sigh, and quickly moves to put your fears to rest, [lilaya.speech(Of course, what with the arcane being the thing responsible for rapid growth as well, you'd not know how it works here... I'm sure this will come as a major relief, but you don't have to worry about raising your children; thanks to the arcane, they'll reach full maturity in just a couple of hours. The arcane grants them their mother's general knowledge, without transferring specific memories, so they get all the information they need to make their own way in the world. There's no need for any 'raising' or anything, don't worry. Honestly, I don't even know how people would be able to cope without the arcane!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As Lilaya finishes speaking, a huge wave of relief washes over you. You sink back into the chair, sighing deeply, before you remember your last concern about this whole process; the part about actually giving birth. Before you can ask Lilaya about it again, she continues, 
		#IF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_PREGNANT_3))
				 [lilaya.speech(Oh, and don't worry about the whole giving birth part. I see that your belly has already finished growing, so I can help you to give birth whenever you're ready!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				With your final question answered, you stand up from the chair, and thank Lilaya for all her help. She tells you not to worry about it, and to remember to come back to see her when you're ready to give birth.
		#ELSE
				 [lilaya.speech(Oh, and don't worry about the whole giving birth part. When you're ready, just come back here and I'll talk you through it!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				With your final question answered, you stand up from the chair, and thank Lilaya for all her help. She tells you not to worry about it, and to remember to come back to see her once your belly has finished growing.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_ASSISTS_PREGNANCY_REPEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_PREGNANCY_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isShy())
		<p>
			Stepping forwards, you nervously smile at your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)], before looking down and rubbing your belly, muttering, [pc.speech(Erm... Lilaya...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && !game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_reactedToPregnancyLilaya))
				[lilaya.speech(Wait... Are you pregnant <i>again</i>?!)] she asks.
			#ELSE
				[lilaya.speech(So, you're ready to do something about your little pregnancy problem, huh?)] she asks.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			You aren't quite sure what to say, and look sheepishly at the floor as you hear Lilaya's footsteps drawing near. Before you know what's happening, her hands are rubbing all over your belly, and you let out a little gasp at the sudden feeling of someone else touching your pregnant bump.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_PREGNANT_3))
				[lilaya.speech(I see your belly's already finished growing, so I can help you to give birth whenever you're ready!)] she says, smiling at you as she carries on fondling your swollen bump.
			#ELSE
				[lilaya.speech(You're not quite ready to give birth just yet... Come back when your belly's really nice and round!)] she says, smiling at you as she carries on fondling your swollen bump.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Stepping forwards, you smile at your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)], before looking down and rubbing your belly, saying, [pc.speech(Look, Lilaya, I got pregnant again!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && !game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_reactedToPregnancyLilaya))
				[lilaya.speech(Yes, I can see that!)] she replies, before walking over towards you and placing her hands on your swollen abdomen.
			#ELSE
				[lilaya.speech(So, you're ready to do something about your little pregnancy problem, huh?)] she replies, before walking over towards you and placing her hands on your swollen abdomen.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			You let out a sigh at the feeling of your [lilaya.relation(pc)]'s hands rubbing your pregnant bump, but before you can respond, she continues,
			#IF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_PREGNANT_3))
				 [lilaya.speech(I see your belly's already finished growing, so I can help you to give birth whenever you're ready!)]
			#ELSE
				 [lilaya.speech(You're not quite ready to give birth just yet... Come back when your belly's really nice and round!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(pc.isCharacterPossiblyFather(lilaya))
		<p>
			As nothing's been said on the matter yet, you take this opportunity to tell Lilaya that
			#IF(pc.getPotentialPartnersAsMother().size()==1)
				 she's
			#ELSE
				 she might be
			#ENDIF
			 the one who got you knocked up.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getFertilisationType()==FERTILISATION_NORMAL)
				[lilaya.speech(Well, you're the one who wanted me to grow a cock, remember?)]
			#ELSE
				[lilaya.speech(Well, you're the one who wanted me to drink that bottle of Amazon's Secret, remember?)]
			#ENDIF
			 Lilaya laughs, clearly not at all worried by the fact that she's the 'father' to your children. Taking her hands off your swollen belly, she steps back and finishes by asking, [lilaya.speech(So, is there anything else I can do for you, [pc.name]?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_DETECTS_BIRTHING_TYPE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_DETECTS_BIRTHING_TYPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Cradling your swollen belly with both hands, you look up at Lilaya and say, [pc.speech(I'm ready to give birth now.)]
	</p>
	#IF(!pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_FIRST_TIME_PREGNANCY))
		<p>
			A delighted smile crosses her face, but despite her reassuring look, as well as knowing that you're in competent hands, you're still incredibly nervous about what comes next. Lilaya must have noticed the worried look on your face, as she moves up close to you and makes a soothing hushing sound. Her hands move down to gently stroke over your pregnant bump, and you start blushing at the thought of what's about to happen.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			A delighted smile crosses her face, and despite the fact that you've done this before, you're still pretty nervous about what comes next. She must have noticed the worried look on your face, as she suddenly steps close to you and makes a soothing hushing sound. Her hands stroke over your pregnant bump, and you start blushing at the thought of what's about to happen.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(pc.getBodyMaterial()==BODY_MATERIAL_SLIME)
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Don't worry, I'm here for you,)] she says, pulling you into a loving hug for a moment before stepping back, [lilaya.speech(and anyway, giving birth to slimes is super easy and stress-free. We should do this in the birthing room, follow me!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Don't worry, I'm here for you,)] she says, pulling you into a loving hug for a moment before stepping back, [lilaya.speech(but first, I need to know what sort of race you're going to be giving birth to.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(!pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_VAGINA))
				As she speaks, Lilaya starts stripping off your clothes, and as she gets access to your vagina, she lets out a little humming noise,
			#ELSE
				Your vagina is already exposed, and, after looking down at it for a moment, Lilaya lets out a little humming noise,
			#ENDIF
			#IF(pc.isVaginaEggLayer())
				 [lilaya.speech(Ooh, you're going to be laying #IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()>1)some eggs#ELSEan egg#ENDIF, how exciting! I'm sure you're already feeling it, but some incredibly strong maternal instincts are going to be kicking in pretty soon, and you're only going to feel comfortable doing this in a very personal area. I think using your room would be the best bet, follow me!)]
			#ELSE
				 [lilaya.speech(Ok, so you're going to be giving birth to live young. I've got a room set up for just that purpose, follow me!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_ASSISTS_BIRTHING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ASSIST_BIRTHING_FIRST_TIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your hands in hers, she leads you out of the lab and down the hallway. You soon find yourself standing outside one of the many doors that line the corridor, and Lilaya steps forwards and holds it open for you. Stepping inside, you find yourself in a specially-purposed birthing room. Instead of being carpeted, like most of the other rooms in this house, clean white tiles have been chosen for this room's flooring. A modern-looking birthing bed is sitting against one wall of the room, but apart from that, there isn't much else in the way of medical equipment. A few comfortable chairs have been placed around the edges of the room, but other than those, and a drinks cabinet that's sitting in one corner, the room is devoid of any other furniture.
	</p>
	<p>
		As Lilaya leads you over to the bed, she explains the situation, [lilaya.speech(Ok, so I know you haven't done anything like this before, so I'll quickly explain what's going to happen. In order for you to give birth, I need to focus a special kind of arcane spell into your nice little bump here. Although you won't feel any pain, a lot of the arcane power I'll be using is going to be drawn directly from your aura, and there's a good chance that you're going to pass out from it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You glance across worriedly at Lilaya as she says this, but she squeezes your hand in hers and reassures you, [lilaya.speech(Don't worry, you don't need to stay conscious during this. Now, after I've delivered your children, they're going to grow pretty quickly, so don't be alarmed! They're also going to be pretty hungry, but don't worry if you're not producing any milk, we've got everything they'll need in that cabinet there. Oh, and also, they're probably going to want to leave straight away. All children are born with a strong desire to go out and become independent as soon as possible, so don't take it personally if they've already left by the time you wake up.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(player.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_VAGINA))
			As she's speaking, Lilaya starts stripping off your clothes, and as she gets access to your vagina, she gently pushes you down onto the bed.
		#ELSE
			Your vagina is already exposed, so Lilaya starts by gently pushing you back onto the bed.
		#ENDIF
		 After following a few more of her instructions, you find yourself
		 #IF(pc.hasLegs())
		 	 lying back with your legs held up and spread apart by a pair of sturdy metal supports. Giving you a reassuring smile, Lilaya asks, [lilaya.speech(Ok, all set?)]
		 #ELSE
		 	 lying back with your [pc.pussy+] fully on display to your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)]. Giving you a reassuring smile, she asks, [lilaya.speech(Ok, all set?)]
		 #ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ASSIST_BIRTHING_SLIME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your hands in hers, she leads you out of the lab and down the hallway. You soon find yourself standing outside one of the many doors that line the corridor, and Lilaya steps forwards and holds it open for you. Stepping inside, you find yourself in a specially purposed birthing room. Instead of being carpeted, like most of the other rooms in this house, clean white tiles have been chosen for this room's flooring. A modern-looking birthing bed is sitting against one wall of the room, but apart from that, there isn't much else in the way of medical equipment. A few comfortable chairs have been placed around the edges of the room, but other than those, and a drinks cabinet that's sitting in one corner, the room is devoid of any other furniture.
	</p>
	<p>
		As Lilaya closes the door behind you, she explains the situation, [lilaya.speech(Ok, so I know you haven't done anything like this before, so I'll quickly explain what's going to happen. In order for you to give birth, I need to focus a special kind of arcane spell into your nice little bump here. Slimes, such as yourself, don't give birth like other creatures. Those little cores inside of you don't need a vagina to exit through; instead, they'll simply split off from your body, taking some of your slime with them. Although you won't feel any pain, a lot of the arcane power I'll be using is going to be drawn directly from your aura, and there's a good chance that you're going to pass out from it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You glance across worriedly at Lilaya as she says this, but she squeezes your hand in hers and reassures you, [lilaya.speech(Don't worry, you don't need to stay conscious during this, and I'll make sure to keep feeding you fluids to replenish any slime that your children take with them. I'll do the same with the newly birthed slimes, so they'll quickly get all of the fluid they need to mature to adulthood. Oh, and also, they're probably going to want to leave straight away. All children are born with a strong desire to go out and become independent as soon as possible, so don't take it personally if they've already left by the time you wake up.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Lilaya gets you to lie down on the bed, and, smiling, she asks, [lilaya.speech(You ready?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ASSIST_BIRTHING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your hands in hers, she leads you out of the lab and down the hallway. You soon find yourself standing outside one of the many doors that line the corridor, and Lilaya steps forwards and holds it open for you. Stepping inside, you once again find yourself standing in the specially purposed birthing room. Instead of being carpeted, like most of the other rooms in this house, clean white tiles have been chosen for this room's flooring. A modern-looking birthing bed is sitting against one wall of the room, but apart from that, there isn't much else in the way of medical equipment. A few comfortable chairs have been placed around the edges of the room, but other than those, and a drinks cabinet that's sitting in one corner, the room is devoid of any other furniture.
	</p>
	<p>
		As Lilaya leads you over to the bed, she reminds you of what's about to happen, [lilaya.speech(Ok, so I know you've done this before, but I'll quickly go over what's going to happen. In order for you to give birth, I need to focus a special kind of arcane spell into your nice little bump here. Although you won't feel any pain, a lot of the arcane power I'll be using is going to be drawn directly from your aura, and there's a good chance that you're going to pass out from it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You let out a sigh she says this, but she squeezes your hand in hers and reassures you, [lilaya.speech(Don't worry, remember, you don't need to stay conscious during this. Now, just remember that after I've delivered your children, they're going to grow pretty quickly! They're also going to be hungry, but don't worry if you're not producing any milk, we've got everything they'll need in that cabinet there. Oh, and also, they're probably going to want to leave straight away. All children are born with a strong desire to go out and become independent as soon as possible, so don't take it personally if they've already left by the time you wake up.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(player.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_VAGINA))
			As she's speaking, Lilaya starts stripping off your clothes, and as she gets access to your vagina, she gently pushes you down onto the bed.
		#ELSE
			Your vagina is already exposed, so Lilaya starts by gently pushing you back onto the bed.
		#ENDIF
		 After following a few more of her instructions, you find yourself
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
		 	 lying back with your legs held up and spread apart by a pair of sturdy metal supports. Giving you a reassuring smile, Lilaya asks, [lilaya.speech(Ok, all set?)]
		#ELSE
		 	 lying back with your [pc.pussy+] fully on display to your demonic [lilaya.relation(pc)]. Giving you a reassuring smile, she asks, [lilaya.speech(Ok, all set?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_ASSISTS_BIRTHING_DELIVERS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_BIRTHING_DELIVERS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You nod to Lilaya, [pc.speech(I'm ready...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Right, here we go!)] she says, and you see sparks of purple energy start to run down her arms.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.getBodyMaterial()==BODY_MATERIAL_SLIME)
		<p>
			You strain your neck to look down, and see Lilaya bring her hands up to hover over your pregnant belly. A huge wave of exhaustion crashes over you, and you remember what she said about how she was going to draw out your aura for this. You struggle to keep your eyes open, but as you feel an intense pushing sensation deep with your slimy body, you're almost glad that you can't see what's happening. You start to slip in and out of consciousness, and you find yourself having a strange dream.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			You strain your neck to look down, and see Lilaya bring her hands up to hover over your pregnant belly. A huge wave of exhaustion crashes over you, and you remember what she said about how she was going to draw out your aura for this. You struggle to keep your eyes open, but as you feel an intense pushing sensation deep within your vagina, you're almost glad that you can't see what's happening. You start to slip in and out of consciousness, and you find yourself having a strange dream.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_ASSISTS_BIRTHING_KNOCK_OUT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_BIRTHING_KNOCK_OUT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Have you got anything to drink? You know, so maybe I don't have to be awake for this...)] you ask, looking up at Lilaya hopefully.
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a good-natured laugh, she walks over to the drinks cabinet, saying, [Lilaya.speech(You know, I thought you might ask for that! I prepared this for you earlier!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getBodyMaterial()==BODY_MATERIAL_SLIME)
			She hands you a glass of what looks like ordinary sparkling water, but as you bring it to your lips and quickly down the liquid, you notice that it has a strong taste of peppermint. Almost instantly, you feel your eyelids grow heavy, and as you lie back on the bed, you vaguely see Lilaya bringing her hands up to hover over your pregnant belly. Sparks of purple energy start to run down her arms, and as you start to feel an intense pushing sensation deep within your slimy body, you're glad that you're not going to be awake for this.
		#ELSE
			She hands you a glass of what looks like ordinary sparkling water, but as you bring it to your lips and quickly down the liquid, you notice that it has a strong taste of peppermint. Almost instantly, you feel your eyelids grow heavy, and as you lie back on the bed, you vaguely see Lilaya bringing her hands up to hover over your pregnant belly. Sparks of purple energy start to run down her arms, and as you start to feel an intense pushing sensation deep within your vagina, you're glad that you're not going to be awake for this.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_ASSISTS_EGG_LAYING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_EGG_LAYING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking your hands in hers, Lilaya leads you out of the lab and up to your room. Following her in as she pushes open the door, you see that Rose has laid a soft protective covering over your bed, and a few bottles of milk have been placed on your bedside cabinet.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_FIRST_TIME_PREGNANCY))
			As Lilaya leads you over to the bed, she explains the situation, [lilaya.speech(Ok, so I know you haven't done anything like this before, so I'll quickly explain what's going to happen. In order for you to start laying your #IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()>1)eggs#ELSEegg#ENDIF, I need to focus a special kind of arcane spell into your nice little bump here. This isn't as intense as giving birth to live young, so you're going to stay conscious through all of this.)]
		#ELSE
			As Lilaya leads you over to the bed, she explains the situation, [lilaya.speech(Ok, so I know we've done this before, but I'll just quickly remind you of what's going to happen. In order for you to start laying your #IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()>1)eggs#ELSEegg#ENDIF, I need to focus a special kind of arcane spell into your nice little bump here. This isn't as intense as giving birth to live young, so you're going to stay conscious through all of this.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		You glance across worriedly at Lilaya as she says this, but she squeezes your hand in hers and reassures you, [lilaya.speech(Don't worry, it doesn't hurt or anything! Now, after I've helped you lay your #IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()>1)eggs#ELSEegg#ENDIF, you're probably going to get aggressive if I hang around for too long, so I'll leave as quickly as possible. Oh, and don't worry about your behaviour, I understand that your maternal instinct is going to get pretty intense.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You fidget about uncomfortably a little, but Lilaya makes a soothing shushing noise as she pushes you down into the middle of your bed, before shuffling around to sit behind you. [lilaya.speech(It's alright, don't worry! So, after you've laid your #IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()>1)eggs, you're going to incubate it#ELSEegg, you're going to incubate it#ENDIF for roughly twenty-four hours, during which time you'll find that you'll be unable to sleep or get any rest. Once the #IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()>1)eggs start#ELSEeggs starts#ENDIF hatching, all that built-up tiredness will suddenly wash over you, and you might collapse from exhaustion. I'll be waiting to come in and help your children, so don't worry if you end up passing out! Oh, and remember that they're going to grow pretty rapidly once they've hatched, so they might have already flown the nest by the time you wake up.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she's been speaking, Lilaya has been shuffling around into a comfortable position behind you. Kneeling down on the bed, she presses herself into your back, before reaching around to rub her hands up and down over your belly.
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
		 	 Moving down to apply a gentle pressure to your inner-thighs, Lilaya gets you to spread your legs so that you're ready to start laying your #IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()>1)eggs#ELSEegg#ENDIF. In a gentle voice she then asks, [lilaya.speech(Ok, all set?)]
		 #ELSE
		 	 Moving down to rest her hands on your lower abdomen, Lilaya asks, [lilaya.speech(Ok, you're ready to start laying your #IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().getTotalLitterCount()>1)eggs#ELSEegg#ENDIF, so shall we start?)]
		 #ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_ASSISTS_EGG_LAYING_DELIVERS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_EGG_LAYING_DELIVERS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You nod as you look down at Lilaya's hands resting on your swollen stomach. [pc.speech(I'm ready...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(Right, just try and relax...)] she whispers into your ear, and as she does so, you see a soft pink glow start to run down her arms.
	</p>
	<p>
		Sliding her hands up and down over your pregnant belly, you feel her start to apply a gentle pressure with her thumbs, as though she's trying to push out the #IF(pc.getLastLitterBirthed().getTotalLitterCount()>1)eggs#ELSEegg#ENDIF within you. As she does this, you start to feel an intense pressure building up deep within your vagina, and, collapsing back into Lilaya,
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			 you spread your legs and let out a desperate whine.
		#ELSE
			 you buck your hips and let out a desperate whine.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[lilaya.speech(That's right, now push... Go on, you can do it...)] Lilaya softly speaks into your ear, and, obeying her instructions, you try to push the pressure out from within your womb.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.getLastLitterBirthed().getTotalLitterCount()>1)
		<p>
			Looking down, you see the tip of your first egg peeking out from your vagina, and with a determined cry, you push with all your might. You feel the egg stretching you out as you continue to apply pressure, but just as you feel that you can't keep going any longer, the egg pops free and slides out onto the bed beneath you.
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I did it...)] you sigh, looking down at the egg you've just laid. It looks to be about the same size as an emu's egg, and as you marvel at its pale pink colouring and smooth shell, you feel yourself subconsciously reaching out to pick it up and cradle in your arms.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Good [pc.girl], [pc.name]! But wait, just leave it for a moment, you've still got more to lay!)] Lilaya pulls you back into her, continuing to apply the gentle pressure on your stomach as she makes soothing shushing noises into your ear.
		</p>
		<p>
			Doing as Lilaya says, you allow her to pull you back, but as she does so, a strange feeling suddenly washes over you, and it takes all of your willpower to prevent yourself from pushing Lilaya away and attempting to grab your egg. Almost as though she sensed what you were thinking, Lilaya reminds you to try and overcome your maternal instincts, at least until you've finished laying all your eggs. After promising to do your best, you set about pushing out the rest of your eggs, and within half an hour, you've laid a complete clutch of [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] eggs.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Looking down, you see the tip of your egg peeking out from your vagina, and with a determined cry, you push with all your might. You feel the egg stretching you out as you continue to apply pressure, but just as you feel that you can't keep going any longer, the egg pops free and slides out onto the bed beneath you.
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I did it...)] you sigh, looking down at the egg you've just laid. It looks to be about the same size as an emu's egg, and as you marvel at its pale pink colouring and smooth shell, you feel yourself subconsciously reaching out to pick it up and cradle in your arms.
		</p>
		<p>
			[lilaya.speech(Good [pc.girl], [pc.name]!)] Lilaya exclaims, but as she does so, a strange feeling suddenly washes over you, and it takes all of your willpower to prevent yourself from pushing her away and attempting to grab your egg. Almost as though she sensed what you were thinking, Lilaya reminds you that your maternal instincts are about to take hold...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_ASSISTS_EGG_LAYING_PROTECT_THE_EGGS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_EGG_LAYING_PROTECT_THE_EGGS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.getLastLitterBirthed().getTotalLitterCount()>1)
		<p>
			As you look down at your clutch of eggs, you find yourself burning with an overwhelming need to protect them at all costs. Throwing Lilaya's arms off of you, you collapse forwards, wrapping your [pc.arms] around your precious brood as you turn your head back and shout, [pc.speech(Get away! Don't hurt them!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Lilaya instantly stands up and starts backing off towards the door, [lilaya.speech(Ok, ok, don't worry, I'm leaving. You'll be safe in here...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Still making soothing shushing noises, she opens the door to your room and slips out, before closing it firmly behind her. Having driven off the only possible threat to your nest, you shuffle around into a more comfortable position, pressing the heat of your body up against your eggs as you continue to cover them with your [pc.arms]. You make sure to position yourself so that you're looking at the only entrance to your room, and, once satisfied that you're in a good position, you settle down to your vigilant watch...
		</p>
		<p>
			For the next twenty hours, you barely move a muscle, but despite the fact that you're lying on a warm, comfortable bed, you don't even consider for a moment to get any rest. Your eyes only occasionally drift away from the door, but only to check your surroundings for any sign of danger.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you enter the twenty-first hour of your incubation, you feel one of your eggs start to move. Letting out a delighted cry, you shift position slightly to look down at your clutch. A feeling of overwhelming joy rushes through you as you see each and every one of your eggs trembling and shifting about.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As you look down at your egg, you find yourself burning with an overwhelming need to protect it at all costs. Throwing Lilaya's arms off of you, you collapse forwards, wrapping your [pc.arms] around your precious child as you turn your head back and shout, [pc.speech(Get away! Don't hurt it!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Lilaya instantly stands up and starts backing off towards the door, [lilaya.speech(Ok, ok, don't worry, I'm leaving. You'll be safe in here...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Still making soothing shushing noises, she opens the door to your room and slips out, before closing it firmly behind her. Having driven off the only possible threat to your nest, you shuffle around into a more comfortable position, pressing the heat of your body up against your egg as you continue to cover it with your [pc.arms]. You make sure to position yourself so that you're looking at the only entrance to your room, and, once satisfied that you're in a good position, you settle down to your vigilant watch...
		</p>
		<p>
			For the next twenty hours, you barely move a muscle, but despite the fact that you're lying on a warm, comfortable bed, you don't even consider for a moment to get any rest. Your eyes only occasionally drift away from the door, but only to check your surroundings for any sign of danger.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you enter the twenty-first hour of your incubation, you feel your egg start to move. Letting out a delighted cry, you shift position slightly to look down at it. A feeling of overwhelming joy rushes through you as you see it trembling and shifting about.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_EGG_LAYING_PROTECT_THE_EGGS_FEMININE_HATCHING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getLastLitterBirthed().getTotalLitterCount()>1)
			You watch in awe as the first egg starts to crack. Within moments, a little head bursts through the top, and your eyes open wide as you see a tiny [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] crawling out. A little egg-tooth is still attached to her forehead, but after a quick shake, she drops it off onto the bed beneath her. As all the other eggs start cracking in turn, you feel a wave of exhaustion washing over you, and with what little strength you have left, you feebly call out for Lilaya.
		#ELSE
			You watch in awe as your egg starts to crack. Within moments, a little head bursts through the top, and your eyes open wide as you see a tiny [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] crawling out. A little egg-tooth is still attached to her forehead, but after a quick shake, she drops it off onto the bed beneath her. As you see that your child has safely hatched, you suddenly feel a wave of exhaustion washing over you, and with what little strength you have left, you feebly call out for Lilaya.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_EGG_LAYING_PROTECT_THE_EGGS_MASCULINE_HATCHING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getLastLitterBirthed().getTotalLitterCount()>1)
			You watch in awe as the first egg starts to crack. Within moments, a little head bursts through the top, and your eyes open wide as you see a tiny [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] crawling out. A little egg-tooth is still attached to his forehead, but after a quick shake, he drops it off onto the bed beneath him. As all the other eggs start cracking in turn, you feel a wave of exhaustion washing over you, and with what little strength you have left, you feebly call out for Lilaya.
		#ELSE
			You watch in awe as your egg starts to crack. Within moments, a little head bursts through the top, and your eyes open wide as you see a tiny [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] crawling out. A little egg-tooth is still attached to his forehead, but after a quick shake, he drops it off onto the bed beneath him. As you see that your child has safely hatched, you suddenly feel a wave of exhaustion washing over you, and with what little strength you have left, you feebly call out for Lilaya.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_EGG_LAYING_PROTECT_THE_EGGS_END"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.getLastLitterBirthed().getTotalLitterCount()>1)
		<p>
			As your head collapses down onto the bed, you vaguely see Lilaya rushing into the room. A delighted smile breaks out across her face as she sees that your eggs are hatching, and just before you pass out, you see her bending down in order to start taking care of your children.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.getBreastRawMilkStorageValue()>0 && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_NIPPLES, true) && pc.getNippleShape()==NIPPLE_SHAPE_NORMAL && game.isLactationContentEnabled())
				Some time later, you drift back into consciousness for a moment as you feel a desperate suckling at your nipples, and you're vaguely aware that it's your children who are eagerly drinking down mouthfuls of your [pc.milk]. Letting your eyelids close again, you soon drift off into an exhausted sleep.
			#ELSE
				Some time later, you drift back into consciousness for a moment as you feel a weight on your chest, and you're vaguely aware of cradling your children in your arms as they eagerly drink down bottle after bottle of the milk that Lilaya has provided for you. Letting your eyelids close again, you soon drift off into an exhausted sleep.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As your head collapses down onto the bed, you vaguely see Lilaya rushing into the room. A delighted smile breaks out across her face as she sees that your egg has hatched, and just before you pass out, you see her bending down in order to start taking care of your child.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.getBreastRawMilkStorageValue()>0 && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_NIPPLES, true) && pc.getNippleShape()==NIPPLE_SHAPE_NORMAL && game.isLactationContentEnabled())
				Some time later, you drift back into consciousness for a moment as you feel a desperate suckling at your nipples, and you're vaguely aware that it's your child who's eagerly drinking down mouthfuls of your [pc.milk]. Letting your eyelids close again, you soon drift off into an exhausted sleep.
			#ELSE
				Some time later, you drift back into consciousness for a moment as you feel a weight on your chest, and you're vaguely aware of cradling your child in your arms as they eagerly drink down bottle after bottle of the milk that Lilaya has provided for you. Letting your eyelids close again, you soon drift off into an exhausted sleep.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LILAYA_ASSISTS_BIRTHING_FINISHED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LILAYA_ASSISTS_BIRTHING_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You wake up some time later, lying in your bed. With a groan, you sit up, pushing the covers back as you rub sleep from your eyes.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasVagina())
		<p>
			The first thing you notice is how easy it is to move, and you let out a little gasp as you start running your hands over your now-flat stomach. As you do so, an unexpected twinge of sadness runs through you, and for a moment you find yourself deeply missing the reassuring feeling of having a big swollen belly.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you move, you discover the second thing that's changed, and you let out a surprised gasp at the feeling #IF(pc.hasLegs())between your legs#ELSEin your groin#ENDIF. Quickly moving your fingers down to your groin, you discover that your vagina has been stretched out considerably, and you let out an uncomfortable groan as you become aware of the dull ache within your [pc.vaginaCapacity] pussy.
		</p>
		<p>
			Glancing across to your bedside cabinet, the final thing you discover is a note from Lilaya. Picking it up, you glance over the contents:
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			You notice how easy it is to move, and you let out a little gasp as you start running your hands over your now-flat stomach. As you do so, an unexpected twinge of sadness runs through you, and for a moment you find yourself deeply missing the reassuring feeling of having a big swollen belly.
		</p>
		<p>
			Glancing across to your bedside cabinet, you discover a note from Lilaya. Picking it up, you glance over the contents:
		</p>
	   #ENDIF
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
	<i>
		Hey [pc.name], congratulations! Everything went perfectly!
		<br/>
		I hope you don't mind, but I collected a lot of data about your aura while we were doing this! I had to start analysing it straight away, and you were fast asleep anyway, so I hope you don't mind me leaving you there to rest.
		<br/><br/>
		If you need anything, or perhaps if you'd like some more 'tests', then you know where to find me!
		<br/><br/>
		#IF(pc.getLastLitterBirthed().getTotalLitterCount() > 1)
			P.S. I managed to get your kids together for a picture before they left, it's under this note!
		#ELSE
			P.S. I got a picture of your kid before they left, it's under this note!
		#ENDIF
	</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		You put down the piece of paper and see the picture lying where Lilaya said it would be. Picking it up, you feel tears welling up in your eyes as you see the result of your pregnancy smiling back at you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
