<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BADGER_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although they're an extremely rare sight in Dominion, badger-morphs are one of the more common morphs which can be found in the Foloi Fields. A furry body, with distinctive striped black-and-white hair or facial fur, is usually enough to identify someone as a badger-morph.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="BADGER_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While the personality of badger-morphs can vary greatly on an individual basis, they are typically very intelligent and highly social, and will not shy away from a fight if it's to protect their territory or loved ones. While male badger-morphs are known to be a lot more territorial than their female counterparts, badger-girls will still often choose to fiercely defend their homes instead of fleeing from intruders.
	</p>
	<p>
		A large portion of the badger-morph population live in underground burrows, referred to as setts, which can be found throughout the Foloi Fields. These homes are as different from a feral badger's sett as you could imagine, for instead of consisting of pitch-black, muddy tunnels, a badger-morph's home will be clean, well-lit, and furnished in a homely, rustic manner. Badger-morphs typically share these often-sprawling underground homes with relatives and close friends, which together form clans. It's not uncommon to find clans of twenty badger-morphs all living under one roof, with the largest clan being known to have reached a population of over fifty.
	</p>
	<p>
		Possessing sturdy, strong bodies, badger-morphs are excellent physical labourers. Although badger clans are largely self-sufficient, badger-morphs will often work on farms or do seasonal construction jobs, especially digging, in order to earn the flames to purchase items which they don't grow or make themselves.
	</p>
	<p>
		Badger-morphs, like the other common races, get heavily affected by arcane storms. Being exposed to arcane thunder will make badger-boys seek out a partner to mate with, while badger-girls will go into heat.
	</p>
	<p>
		A badger-morph's offspring will be a mixture of badger-morphs and offspring of their partner's race.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</bookText>
