<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	
	<!-- RAT_WARREN_INITIAL_ENTRY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE_WHORE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Telling the guards that you'd like to come inside again, you patiently wait as they activate the mechanism to shut the doors behind you, before opening the interior ones to grant you access to the Rat Warrens. As you step inside, the rats move up on either side of you and [npc.name], before [npc2.name] asks, [npc2.speech(So, you two 'ere ta fuck Vengar again, huh?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isLewd())
				#IF(pc.hasVagina())
					#IF(npc.hasVagina())
						[pc.speech(Well, our little pussies <i>are</i> crying out for a good pounding from your leader,)] you lewdly tease, [pc.speech(What's it to you?)]
					#ELSE
						[pc.speech(Well, my little pussy <i>is</i> crying out for a good pounding from your leader,)] you lewdly tease, [pc.speech(What's it to you?)]
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					[pc.speech(Well, I can't say that the two of us would mind getting a taste of your leader's fat cock,)] you lewdly tease, [pc.speech(What's it to you?)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				[pc.speech(Maybe,)] you coyly tease, [pc.speech(What's it to you?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Unable to keep their hands to themselves, the pair of rats step closer and reach around to grope both your and [npc.namePos] asses. Leaning in to grind up against your companion, [npc3.name] growls, [npc3.speech(Wot's it ta us is that we want a piece o' this sweet ass! Ya goin' ta let us get ya warmed up fer Vengar, ain't ya?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Telling the guards that you'd like to come inside again, you patiently wait as they activate the mechanism to shut the doors behind you, before opening the interior ones to grant you access to the Rat Warrens. As you step inside, the rats move up on either side of you, before [npc.name] asks, [npc.speech(So, you 'ere ta fuck Vengar again, huh?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isLewd())
				#IF(pc.hasVagina())
					[pc.speech(Well, my little pussy <i>is</i> crying out for a good pounding from your leader,)] you lewdly tease, [pc.speech(What's it to you?)]
				#ELSE
					[pc.speech(Well, I can't say that I'd mind getting a taste of your leader's fat cock,)] you lewdly tease, [pc.speech(What's it to you?)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				[pc.speech(Maybe,)] you coyly tease, [pc.speech(What's it to you?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Unable to keep their hands to themselves, the pair of rats step closer and reach around to grope your [pc.ass+]. Leaning in to grind up against you, [npc2.name] slips [npc2.her] down to give your crotch a squeeze, before growling into your [pc.ear], [npc2.speech(Wot's it ta us is that we want a piece o' your sweet ass! Yer goin' ta let us get ya warmed up fer Vengar, ain't ya?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Telling the guards that you do indeed have more business with Vengar, you patiently wait as they activate the mechanism to shut the doors behind you, before opening the interior ones to grant you and your companion access to the Rat Warrens.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you step inside, the rats quickly move around in front of you and [npc.name], blocking the way forwards. Narrowing [npc2.her] eyes, [npc2.name] sneers and suspiciously asks, [npc2.speech(So, wot business ya got with Vengar, huh?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Telling the guards that you do indeed have more business with Vengar, you patiently wait as they activate the mechanism to shut the doors behind you, before opening the interior ones to grant you access to the Rat Warrens.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you step inside, the rats quickly move around in front of you, blocking the way forwards. Narrowing [npc.her] eyes, [npc.name] sneers and suspiciously asks, [npc.speech(So, wot business ya got with Vengar, huh?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE_INITIAL"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Telling the guards that you have business with Vengar, you patiently wait as they step back from the hatches and start whispering to one another.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(The boss did say 'e was expectin' visitors,)] [npc2.name] hisses, completely failing to keep [npc2.her] voice low enough to not be overheard, [npc2.speech(An' if these ain't the ones, we can deal with 'em easily enough.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc3.speech(Yeah, I ain't wantin' ta get on the boss's bad side if we end up turnin' away people 'e was waitin' for,)] [npc3.name] replies, [npc3.speech(Let's let 'em in.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reappearing at the hatch, [npc2.name] growls out, [npc2.speech(Right, we's goin' ta let yer in. Just stay there; these inner doors can't open unless them outer ones are shut first. It's security. Ya wouldn't understand, so don' ya be questionin' it.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Convinced that these two guards don't have the mental capacity to trap you in this hallway, you allow them to activate the mechanism which shuts the doors behind you, and, sure enough, once they're firmly closed, the interior ones slowly open to grant you and your companion access to the Rat Warrens.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you step inside, the rats quickly move around in front of you and [npc.name], blocking the way forwards. Narrowing [npc2.her] eyes, [npc2.name] sneers and suspiciously asks, [npc2.speech(So, before we let ya get any further, exactly wot business is it ya got with Vengar, huh?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Telling the guards that you have business with Vengar, you patiently wait as they step back from the hatches and start whispering to one another.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(The boss did say 'e was expectin' a visitor,)] [npc.name] hisses, completely failing to keep [npc.her] voice low enough to not be overheard, [npc.speech(An' if [pc.she] ain't the one, we can deal with [pc.herHim] easily enough.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Yeah, I ain't wantin' ta get on the boss's bad side if we end up turnin' away people 'e was waitin' for,)] [npc2.name] replies, [npc2.speech(Let's let [pc.herHim] in.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reappearing at the hatch, [npc.name] growls out, [npc.speech(Right, we's goin' ta let yer in. Just stay there; these inner doors can't open unless them outer ones are shut first. It's security. Ya wouldn't understand, so don' ya be questionin' it.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Convinced that these two guards don't have the mental capacity to trap you in this hallway, you allow them to activate the mechanism which shuts the doors behind you, and, sure enough, once they're firmly closed, the interior ones slowly open to grant you access to the Rat Warrens.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you step inside, the rats quickly move around in front of you, blocking the way forwards. Narrowing [npc.her] eyes, [npc.name] sneers and suspiciously asks, [npc.speech(So, before we let ya get any further, exactly wot business is it ya got with Vengar, huh?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE_REPEAT_ACCESSED"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			[pc.speech(That's confidential,)] you reply, [pc.speech(you wouldn't want your boss knowing that you'd been asking about his private affairs, would you?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(You's better not be lyin' ta me,)] [npc2.name] sneers, before taking a step back and waving you on, [npc2.speech(We's got our eyes on the two o' you, so ya betta watch yerselves in 'ere...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Following [npc3.her] superior's lead, [npc3.name] steps aside, allowing you and [npc.name] to freely enter the Rat Warrens...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(That's confidential,)] you reply, [pc.speech(you wouldn't want your boss knowing that you'd been asking about his private affairs, would you?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(You's better not be lyin' ta me,)] [npc.name] sneers, before taking a step back and waving you on, [npc.speech(We's got our eyes on you, so ya betta watch yerself in 'ere...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Following [npc2.her] superior's lead, [npc2.name] steps aside, allowing you to freely enter the Rat Warrens...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE_INTITIAL_ENTRY_AXEL"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Dropping the name 'Axel', you tell the two guards that you're here to discuss the handling of protection money payments.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Axel, huh... You's better not be lyin' ta me,)] [npc2.name] sneers, before taking a step back and waving you on, [npc2.speech(We's got our eyes on the two o' you, so ya betta watch yerselves in 'ere...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Following [npc3.her] superior's lead, [npc3.name] steps aside, allowing you and [npc.name] to freely enter the Rat Warrens...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Dropping the name 'Axel', you tell the two guards that you're here to discuss the handling of protection money payments.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Axel, huh... You's better not be lyin' ta me,)] [npc.name] sneers, before taking a step back and waving you on, [npc.speech(We's got our eyes on you, so ya betta watch yerself in 'ere...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Following [npc2.her] superior's lead, [npc2.name] steps aside, allowing you to freely enter the Rat Warrens...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE_INTITIAL_ENTRY_FIGHT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isBrave())
				Feeling supremely confident in your combat abilities, you tell the rats that you're here to put an end to their criminal activities, before readying yourself for a fight. [npc.Name] follows your lead, and similarly prepares [npc.herself] to join you in combat.
			#ELSE
				Wanting to take the direct route, you tell the rats that you're here to put an end to their criminal activities, before readying yourself for a fight. [npc.Name] follows your lead, and similarly prepares [npc.herself] to join you in combat.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(You's 'ere ta do wot?!)] [npc2.name] exclaims, before turning [npc2.her] head back to the tunnels behind [npc2.herHim] and bellowing at the top of [npc2.her] voice, [npc2.speech(Everyone! Get in 'ere! We need 'elp!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Within seconds, half a dozen rat-morphs are dashing into the area as backup, but as they see that there's a fight afoot, a couple of them turn around and run off, abandoning their comrades. Looking around, you count six gang members in front of you and [npc.name], including the two who granted you entry.
		</p>
		<p>
			Caught up in the moment, [npc2.name] yanks on a nearby lever so hard that it breaks off in [npc2.her] hand. Behind you, you hear a heavy lock slam shut, sealing the doors and dashing any hopes you might have had of attempting to escape. With a wild grin on [npc2.her] face, [npc2.name] gleefully shouts, [npc2.speech(There ain't no escape fer ya now! Let's do this!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isBrave())
				Feeling supremely confident in your combat abilities, you tell the rats that you're here to put an end to their criminal activities, before readying yourself for a fight.
			#ELSE
				Wanting to take the direct route, you tell the rats that you're here to put an end to their criminal activities, before readying yourself for a fight.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(You's 'ere ta do wot?!)] [npc.name] exclaims, before turning [npc.her] head back to the tunnels behind [npc.herHim] and bellowing at the top of [npc.her] voice, [npc.speech(Everyone! Get in 'ere! We need 'elp!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Within seconds, half a dozen rat-morphs are dashing into the area as backup, but as they see that there's a fight afoot, a couple of them turn around and run off, abandoning their comrades. Looking around, you count six gang members in front of you, including the two who granted you entry.
		</p>
		<p>
			Caught up in the moment, [npc.name] yanks on a nearby lever so hard that it breaks off in [npc.her] hand. Behind you, you hear a heavy lock slam shut, sealing the doors and dashing any hopes you might have had of attempting to escape. With a wild grin on [npc.her] face, [npc.name] gleefully shouts, [npc.speech(There ain't no escape fer ya now! Let's do this!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- RAT_WARREN_INITIAL_ENTRY_WHORE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAT_WARREN_INITIAL_ENTRY_WHORE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isLewd())
				#IF(pc.hasVagina() && npc.hasVagina())
					Deciding that it would be easiest to pretend that you're whores here to see Vengar, you lewdly tease, [pc.speech(The business we have with Vengar concerns our hot little pussies and how the two of us are going to get a good pounding from his fat cock.)]
				#ELSE
					Deciding that it would be easiest to pretend that you're whores here to see Vengar, you lewdly tease, [pc.speech(The business we have with Vengar concerns how the two of us are going to get a good pounding from his fat cock.)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				Deciding that it would be easiest to pretend that you're whores here to see Vengar, you coyly tease, [pc.speech(You could say that the business we have with Vengar is of a very <i>intimate</i> nature...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking across at one another, the pair of rats let devious smiles settle on their faces, and as one, they step forwards and reach around to grope both your and [npc.namePos] asses. Leaning in to grind up against your companion, [npc3.name] growls, [npc3.speech(The boss is real lucky, gettin' ta plough such a sweet ass! Ya goin' ta let us get ya warmed up fer him, ain't ya?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isLewd())
				#IF(pc.hasVagina())
					Deciding that it would be easiest to pretend that you're a whore here to see Vengar, you lewdly tease, [pc.speech(The business I have with Vengar concerns my hot little pussy and how it's going to get a good pounding from his fat cock.)]
				#ELSE
					Deciding that it would be easiest to pretend that you're a whore here to see Vengar, you lewdly tease, [pc.speech(The business I have with Vengar concerns his fat cock and how he's going to use it to give me a good pounding.)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				Deciding that it would be easiest to pretend that you're a whore here to see Vengar, you coyly tease, [pc.speech(You could say that the business we have with Vengar is of a very <i>intimate</i> nature...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking across at one another, the pair of rats let devious smiles settle on their faces, and as one, they step forwards and reach around to grope your [pc.ass+]. Leaning in to grind up against you, [npc2.name] growls, [npc2.speech(The boss is real lucky, gettin' ta plough such a sweet ass! Ya goin' ta let us get ya warmed up fer him, ain't ya?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAT_WARREN_INITIAL_ENTRY_WHORE_NO_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Not wanting to have sex with these guards, you step out of their grasp and turn to pout at them, explaining, [pc.speech(Sorry, but we've already been paid for, and your boss might not take too kindly to finding out that his purchases have been tampered with in transit...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Fine,)] [npc2.name] huffs, stepping back and leaning heavily against a nearby wall, [npc2.speech(But if yer still feelin' horny after the boss has had 'is fun, then ya just come back 'ere, ok? The two o' us will show ya a real good time.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at the rats, you turn your back on them and prepare to head off into the tunnels with [npc.name], letting out a sigh of relief under your breath as you reflect on the fact that your ruse was successful...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Not wanting to have sex with these guards, you step out of their grasp and turn to pout at them, explaining, [pc.speech(Sorry, but I've already been paid for, and your boss might not take too kindly to finding out that his purchase has been tampered with in transit...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Fine,)] [npc.name] huffs, stepping back and leaning heavily against a nearby wall, [npc.speech(But if yer still feelin' horny after the boss has had 'is fun, then ya just come back 'ere, ok? The two o' us will show ya a real good time.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at the rats, you turn your back on them and prepare to head off into the tunnels, letting out a sigh of relief under your breath as you reflect on the fact that your ruse was successful...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAT_WARREN_INITIAL_ENTRY_WHORE_SOLO"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Thinking that it might be fun to get fucked by these guards, you bite your lip and explain, [pc.speech(You know, that does sound like fun, but at least one of us needs to be unspoiled for Vengar... [npc.Name], you just stand back and watch, ok?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Ok,)] your companion replies, stepping away from the two rats before turning to watch.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(What a horny little slut,)] [npc2.name] groans into your [pc.ear], [npc2.speech(Ya gonna love the feelin' o' my cock!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc3.speech(This is gonna be good!)] [npc3.name] [npc3.moans], groping your [pc.ass+] as [npc3.she] grinds up against you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a horny [pc.moan], you tell the two guards that they can do whatever they want with you...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Thinking that it might be fun to get fucked by these guards, you bite your lip and tease, [pc.speech(You know, that does sound like fun... I'm sure Vengar wouldn't mind sharing me with the two of you...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(What a horny little slut,)] [npc.name] groans into your [pc.ear], [npc.speech(Ya gonna love the feelin' o' my cock!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(This is gonna be good!)] [npc2.name] [npc2.moans], groping your [pc.ass+] as [npc2.she] grinds up against you.
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a horny [pc.moan], you tell the two guards that they can do whatever they want with you...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAT_WARREN_INITIAL_ENTRY_WHORE_BOTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it might be fun to get fucked by these guards, you bite your lip and tease, [pc.speech(You know, that does sound like fun... I'm sure Vengar wouldn't mind sharing the two of us with his hard-working guards...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!npc.isAttractedTo(npc2))
			[npc.speech(Eugh... As if you're going to make me do this...)] [npc.name] sighs, reluctantly allowing [npc3.name] to start fondling [npc.herHim].
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Mmm, that's right, don't be shy now,)] [npc.name] sensually sighs, encouraging [npc3.name] to start fondling [npc.herHim].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(What a horny little slut,)] [npc2.name] groans into your [pc.ear], [npc2.speech(Ya gonna love the feelin' o' my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(This is gonna be good!)] [npc3.name] [npc3.moans], groping your companion's [npc.ass+] as [npc3.she] grinds up against [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a horny [pc.moan], you tell the two guards that they can do whatever they want with the two of you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RAT_WARREN_INITIAL_ENTRY_WHORE_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it might be fun to watch your companion being fucked by these guards, you bite your lip and explain, [pc.speech(You know, that does sound like fun, but at least one of us needs to be unspoiled for Vengar... [npc.Name], you don't mind letting these two have some fun with you, do you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!npc.isAttractedTo(npc2))
			[npc.speech(Eugh... As if you're going to make me do this...)] [npc.name] sighs, reluctantly allowing [npc2.name] to start fondling [npc.herHim].
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Mmm, that's right, don't be shy now,)] [npc.name] sensually sighs, encouraging [npc2.name] to start fondling [npc.herHim].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(You horny little slut,)] [npc2.name] groans into your companion's [npc.ear], [npc2.speech(Ya gonna love the feelin' o' my cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(This is gonna be good!)] [npc3.name] [npc3.moans], groping [npc.namePos] [npc.ass+] as [npc3.she] grinds up against [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an excited [pc.moan], you tell the two guards that they can do whatever they want with [npc.name], before stepping abck and preparing to watch the show...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_ENTRANCE_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_ENTRANCE_SEX_COMPANION_WATCHING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had their fun, the two guards step back, leaving you panting and [pc.moaning] as you try to quickly recover your breath.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Not bad,)] [npc2.name] growls, grinning at you as [npc2.she] gets [npc2.her] clothing back in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(Yeah, come back at any time an' we can give yer a real good fuckin' again!)] [npc3.name] laughs, clearly happy with how things turned out.
	</p>
	<p>
		Copying the two rats, you get your things back in order, before stepping over to your companion. Looking across at you, [npc.name] asks, [npc.speech(So, feeling satisfied?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			[pc.speech(For now...)] you reply, before preparing to set off into the tunnels...
		#ELSE
			[pc.speech(Not really,)] you whine, before preparing to set off into the tunnels...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_ENTRANCE_SEX_PLAYER_WATCHING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had their fun, the two guards step back, leaving [npc.name] panting and [npc.moaning] as [npc.she] tries to quickly recover [npc.her] breath.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Not bad,)] [npc2.name] growls, grinning at your companion as [npc2.she] gets [npc2.her] clothing back in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(Yeah, come back at any time an' we can give yer a real good fuckin' again!)] [npc3.name] laughs, clearly happy with how things turned out.
	</p>
	<p>
		Copying the two rats, [npc.name] gets [npc.her] things back in order, before stepping over to you. Looking across at your companion, you ask, [pc.speech(So, feeling satisfied?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(npc.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
			[npc.speech(Yes...)] [npc.she] sighs, before preparing to follow you off into the tunnels...
		#ELSE
			[npc.speech(Not really,)] [npc.she] whines, before preparing to follow you off into the tunnels...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_ENTRANCE_SEX_BOTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had their fun, the two guards step back, leaving you and [npc.name] panting and [pc.moaning] as you try to quickly recover your breath.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Not bad,)] [npc2.name] growls, grinning at the two of you as [npc2.she] gets [npc2.her] clothing back in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(Yeah, come back at any time an' we can give yer a real good fuckin' again!)] [npc3.name] laughs, clearly happy with how things turned out.
	</p>
	<p>
		Copying the two rats, you and [npc.name] get your things back in order, before preparing to set off into the tunnels...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_ENTRANCE_SEX_SOLO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had their fun, the two guards step back, leaving you panting and [pc.moaning] as you try to quickly recover your breath.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Not bad,)] [npc.name] growls, grinning at you as [npc.she] gets [npc.her] clothing back in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Yeah, come back at any time an' we can give yer a real good fuckin' again!)] [npc2.name] laughs, clearly happy with how things turned out.
	</p>
	<p>
		Copying the two rats, you get your things back in order, before preparing to set off into the tunnels...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			You and [npc.name] watch as the last of the rats staggers back, before collapsing to the floor alongside the other five. First making sure that there are no other combatants ready to spring a trap, you and your companion lower your guard and step forwards towards your vanquished foes.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			You watch as the last of the rats staggers back, before collapsing to the floor alongside the other five. First making sure that there are no other combatants ready to spring a trap, you lower your guard and step forwards towards your vanquished foes.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Eugh...)] [npc2.name] groans, before raising [npc2.her] [npc2.ass] and whining, [npc2.speech(What ya waitin' for? Come an' fuck us already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Ignoring [npc2.her] moans for a moment, you reflect on the fact that the surrounding tunnels will most likely now be clear of hostile rats, but you can be sure that the areas deeper into the Rat Warrens will be alert and getting ready to fight you. Before you can deal with that situation, however, you need to decide what to do with the six defeated, horny gang members in front of you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_SCARE_OFF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting these rats to recover their courage and return to fight you all over again, you put on your most intimidating tone of voice and tell them that you'll have them all enslaved if they dare come back to challenge you again. Having already been made well aware of the fact that you're far stronger than them, the rats immediately scurry to get out of your sight. As the front entrance is temporarily sealed off, they rush off deeper into the Rat Warrens, no doubt to warn Vengar of your approach.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			With little else to do now but prepare yourself for your next fight, you and [npc.name] get ready to follow in the fleeing rat's footsteps and head further into the Rat Warrens yourselves...
		#ELSE
			With little else to do now but prepare yourself for your next fight, you get ready to follow in the fleeing rat's footsteps and head further into the Rat Warrens yourself...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Feeling more than a little turned on by the sight of the defeated rats before you, you can't help but let out a horny whine as you advance on them with lewd thoughts in your mind. Turning back to address your companion, you say, [pc.speech(You just stand back and keep watch, [npc.name]. I wouldn't want any surprises to interrupt my fun!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Nodding in confirmation, [npc.name] steps back and watches as you step up to [npc2.name] and [pc.moan], [pc.speech(You're hoping to get fucked, huh? I think I can help you with that...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out excited moans of their own, the defeated gang members submissively shuffle closer to you and each start begging to be the one who's fucked first...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling more than a little turned on by the sight of the defeated rats before you, you can't help but let out a horny whine as you advance on them with lewd thoughts in your mind. Stepping up to [npc2.name], you [pc.moan], [pc.speech(You're hoping to get fucked, huh? I think I can help you with that...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out excited moans of their own, the defeated gang members submissively shuffle closer to you and each start begging to be the one who's fucked first...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Feeling more than a little turned on by the sight of the defeated rats before you, you can't help but let out a horny whine as you advance on them with lewd thoughts in your mind. Turning back to address your companion, you say, [pc.speech(You just stand back and keep watch, [npc.name]. I wouldn't want any surprises to interrupt my fun!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Nodding in confirmation, [npc.name] steps back and watches as you step up to [npc2.name] and softly [pc.moan], [pc.speech(You want some nice gentle fun, hmm? I think I can help you with that...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out excited moans of their own, the defeated gang members submissively shuffle closer to you and each start begging to be the one who's fucked first...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling more than a little turned on by the sight of the defeated rats before you, you can't help but let out a horny whine as you advance on them with lewd thoughts in your mind. Stepping up to [npc2.name], you softly [pc.moan], [pc.speech(You want some nice gentle fun, hmm? I think I can help you with that...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out excited moans of their own, the defeated gang members submissively shuffle closer to you and each start begging to be the one who's fucked first...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_ROUGH"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Feeling more than a little turned on by the sight of the defeated rats before you, you can't help but let out a predatory growl as you advance on them with lewd thoughts in your mind. Turning back to address your companion, you say, [pc.speech(You just stand back and keep watch, [npc.name]. I wouldn't want any surprises to interrupt my fun!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Nodding in confirmation, [npc.name] steps back and watches as you step up to [npc2.name] and snarl, [pc.speech(You want to be fucked like a bitch, huh? I'll give you what you want alright!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out excited moans of their own, the defeated gang members submissively shuffle closer to you and each start begging to be the one who's fucked first...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling more than a little turned on by the sight of the defeated rats before you, you can't help but let out a predatory growl as you advance on them with lewd thoughts in your mind. Stepping up to [npc2.name], you snarl, [pc.speech(You want to be fucked like a bitch, huh? I'll give you what you want alright!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out excited moans of their own, the defeated gang members submissively shuffle closer to you and each start begging to be the one who's fucked first...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_SUBMIT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Looking down at the defeated gang members sprawled across the floor, you start to feel a desperate desire to let them reverse the situation and have their way with you. Not wanting your companion to get involved in your scheme, you turn to face [npc.herHim] and say, [pc.speech(I'm going to let these rats have a little fun with me, so you just step back and keep watch until they're finished...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(If you're sure about this...)] [npc.name] replies, before stepping back and doing as [npc.sheIs] told.
		</p>
		<p>
			Stepping forwards, you kneel down beside the group of rats, before asking [npc2.name], [pc.speech(I bet you're feeling frustrated after being defeated like this, aren't you? If it'd make you feel better, you can use me however you'd like...)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			Quick to take advantage of your suggestion, [npc2.name] pushes [npc2.herself] up onto [npc2.her] feet, before asking, [npc2.speech(Are ya fer real? Ya gonna let us fuck ya after beatin' us like that?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Making a show of looking small and submissive, you confirm to [npc2.name] that [npc2.she] and the rest of the rats can fuck you any way they want. Letting out a chorus of lewd comments, the group immediately advances on you, and after pulling you up onto your feet, they set about groping you and preparing to give you what you want...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Looking down at the defeated gang members sprawled across the floor, you start to feel a desperate desire to let them reverse the situation and have their way with you. Stepping forwards, you kneel down beside the group of rats, before asking [npc2.name], [pc.speech(I bet you're feeling frustrated after being defeated like this, aren't you? If it'd make you feel better, you can use me however you'd like...)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			Quick to take advantage of your suggestion, [npc2.name] pushes [npc2.herself] up onto [npc2.her] feet, before asking, [npc2.speech(Are ya fer real? Ya gonna let us fuck ya after beatin' us like that?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Making a show of looking small and submissive, you confirm to [npc2.name] that [npc2.she] and the rest of the rats can fuck you any way they want. Letting out a chorus of lewd comments, the group immediately advances on you, and after pulling you up onto your feet, they set about groping you and preparing to give you what you want...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_GROUP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling more than a little turned on by the sight of the defeated rats before you, you can't help but let out a horny whine as you advance on them with lewd thoughts in your mind. Turning back to address your companion, you tell [npc.herHim] to join you in having dominant sex with them.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!npc.isAttractedToGroup(game.getNonCompanionCharactersPresent()))
			Letting out an exasperated sigh, [npc.name] mutters, [npc.speech(I don't really have a choice, do I...)]
		#ELSE
			Letting out an eager [npc.moan], [npc.name] enthusiastically replies, [npc.speech(This is going to be good!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping up in front of the defeated gang members, you and your companion smirk as they submissively shuffle closer and start begging to be the one who's fucked first...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_GROUP_SUBMIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Looking down at the defeated gang members sprawled across the floor, you start to feel a desperate desire to let them reverse the situation and have their way with you and your companion. Turning to face [npc.name], you reveal your plan and tell [npc.herHim] to join you in submitting to them.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!npc.isAttractedToGroup(game.getNonCompanionCharactersPresent()))
			Letting out an exasperated sigh, [npc.name] mutters, [npc.speech(I don't really have a choice, do I...)]
		#ELSE
			Letting out an eager [npc.moan], [npc.name] enthusiastically replies, [npc.speech(This is going to be good!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Joined by your companion, you step forwards and kneel down beside the group of rats, before asking [npc2.name], [pc.speech(I bet you're feeling frustrated after being defeated like this, aren't you? If it'd make you feel better, you can use the two of us however you'd like...)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Quick to take advantage of your suggestion, [npc2.name] pushes [npc2.herself] up onto [npc2.her] feet, before asking, [npc2.speech(Are ya fer real? Ya gonna let us fuck ya after beatin' us like that?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Making a show of looking small and submissive, you confirm to [npc2.name] that [npc2.she] and the rest of the rats can fuck you and [npc.name] any way they want. Letting out a chorus of lewd comments, the group immediately advances on the two of you, and after pulling you and [npc.name] up onto your feet, they set about groping you and preparing to give you what you want...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_GIVE_TO_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling more than a little turned on by the sight of the defeated rats before you, you can't help but let out a horny whine as a particularly lewd thought enters your mind. Turning to address your companion, you tell [npc.herHim], [pc.speech(Go on, [npc.name], have sex with them while I watch...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!npc.isAttractedToGroup(game.getNonCompanionCharactersPresent()))
			Letting out an exasperated sigh, [npc.name] mutters, [npc.speech(I don't really have a choice, do I...)]
		#ELSE
			Letting out an eager [npc.moan], [npc.name] enthusiastically replies, [npc.speech(This is going to be good!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping up in front of the defeated gang members, your companion smirks as they submissively shuffle closer and start begging to be the one who's fucked first. Stepping back a little, you can't help but let out a [pc.moan] as you prepare to watch [npc.name] fuck all of them at once...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_OFFER_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling more than a little turned on by the sight of the defeated rats before you, you can't help but let out a horny whine as a particularly lewd thought enters your mind. Turning to address your companion, you tell [npc.herHim], [pc.speech(Go on, [npc.name], submit to them and let them fuck you while I watch...)]
	</p>
	#IF(!npc.isAttractedToGroup(game.getNonCompanionCharactersPresent()))
		<p>
			Letting out an exasperated sigh, [npc.name] mutters, [npc.speech(I don't really have a choice, do I...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Stepping up in front of the defeated gang members, your companion reluctantly informs the rats that they can do whatever they want to [npc.herHim]. Letting out a chorus of lewd comments, the group immediately advances on [npc.name], and you can't help but let out a [pc.moan] as you prepare to watch [npc.herHim] get fucked by all of them at once...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Letting out an eager [npc.moan], [npc.name] enthusiastically replies, [npc.speech(This is going to be good!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Stepping up in front of the defeated gang members, your companion lets out a submissive whine before informing the rats that they can do whatever they want to [npc.herHim]. Letting out a chorus of lewd comments, the group immediately advances on [npc.name], and you can't help but let out a [pc.moan] as you prepare to watch [npc.herHim] get fucked by all of them at once...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_AFTER_SEX_BOTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough fun for now, you and [npc.name] disentangle yourselves from the group of rats, before stepping back and getting your things in order. A moment later, and the two of you are ready to continue on your way through the Rat Warrens. First, however, you need to decide what to do with the rats panting on the floor before you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_AFTER_SEX_SOLO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough fun for now, you disentangle yourself from the group of rats, before stepping back and getting your things in order. A moment later, and you're ready to continue on your way through the Rat Warrens. First, however, you need to decide what to do with the rats panting on the floor before you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_VICTORY_AFTER_SEX_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough fun for now, [npc.name] disentangles [npc.herself] from the group of rats, before stepping back and getting [npc.her] things in order. A moment later, and the two of you are ready to continue on your way through the Rat Warrens. First, however, you need to decide what to do with the rats panting on the floor before you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_NO_NON_CON"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Unable to continue fighting any longer, you and [npc.name] slump to the ground, utterly defeated. A chorus of mocking laughter causes you to wearily look up, only to see the six rats looming over you with wicked grins on their faces.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Ya fucked with the wrong gang!)] [npc2.name] sneers, [npc2.speech(There ain't no chance a couple as pathetic as the two o' ya could ever beat us!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Another round of mocking laughter accompanies this statement, and before you can think of what to do next, [npc2.name] turns to [npc2.her] subordinates and orders, [npc2.speech(Throw 'em out into the tunnels! I ain't wastin' any more time on these losers!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Unable to continue fighting any longer, you slump to the ground, utterly defeated. A chorus of mocking laughter causes you to wearily look up, only to see the six rats looming over you with wicked grins on their faces.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Ya fucked with the wrong gang!)] [npc.name] sneers, [npc.speech(There ain't no chance someone as pathetic as ya could ever beat us!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Another round of mocking laughter accompanies this statement, and before you can think of what to do next, [npc.name] turns to [npc.her] subordinates and orders, [npc.speech(Throw this trash out into the tunnels! I ain't wastin' any more time on 'em!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Unable to continue fighting any longer, you and [npc.name] slump to the ground, utterly defeated. A chorus of mocking laughter causes you to wearily look up, only to see the six rats looming over you with wicked grins on their faces.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Ya fucked with the wrong gang!)] [npc2.name] sneers, [npc2.speech(There ain't no chance a couple as pathetic as the two o' ya could ever beat us, an' ya ain't ever gonna get the chance ta try again!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Another round of mocking laughter accompanies this statement, and before you can think of what to do next, [npc2.name] turns to [npc2.her] subordinates and orders, [npc2.speech(The four o' ya, go let the others know the situation's dealt with! An' you, help me drag these two to Murk! I'm gonna trade 'em with 'im to write off me debt.)]
		</p>
		#IF(!game.isInvoluntaryNTREnabled())
			<p>
				<i>You feel as though you might be able to summon just enough energy to fight the rats off long enough to buy [npc.name] time to escape. [style.italicsSex(This will be your only opportunity to prevent your companion from being used without your consent!)]</i>
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Unable to continue fighting any longer, you slump to the ground, utterly defeated. A chorus of mocking laughter causes you to wearily look up, only to see the six rats looming over you with wicked grins on their faces.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Ya fucked with the wrong gang!)] [npc.name] sneers, [npc.speech(There ain't no chance someone as pathetic as ya could ever beat us, an' ya ain't ever gonna get the chance ta try again!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Another round of mocking laughter accompanies this statement, and before you can think of what to do next, [npc.name] turns to [npc.her] subordinates and orders, [npc2.speech(Yous lot, go let the others know the situation's dealt with! I'm gonna drag this 'un to Murk, so's I can trade [pc.herHim] with 'im to write off me debt.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_THROWN_OUT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Hurrying to obey [npc2.namePos] command, the gang members roughly grab hold of you and [npc.name], and after a short wait while the door release mechanism is fixed, the two of you are dragged back out into Submission's tunnels. Hurled to the hard ground with no concern for your safety or comfort, the rats tell you that if you ever dare to show your faces back here again, they'll be ready to give you another sound beating.
		</p>
		<p>
			Making sure that [npc.name] is not hurt, the two of you spend a moment getting your breath back, before brushing yourselves off and preparing to continue on your way once again...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Hurrying to obey [npc.namePos] command, the gang members roughly grab hold of you, and after a short wait while the door release mechanism is fixed, you find yourself being dragged back out into Submission's tunnels. Hurled to the hard ground with no concern for your safety or comfort, the rats tell you that if you ever dare to show your face back here again, they'll be ready to give you another sound beating.
		</p>
		<p>
			You take a moment to get your breath back while the doors to the Rat Warrens creak shut behind you, before brushing yourself off and preparing to continue on your way once again...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS_COMPANION_ESCAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Desperately wanting to avoid an unpleasant fate for your companion, you summon the last of your energy and push the rats back, before turning to [npc.name] and shouting, [pc.speech(Get out of here, now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising the desperate state you're both in, [npc.name] does as you command, and manages to rush away to safety while you hold the rats off. Only once you feel confident that you've bought enough time for your companion to make a getaway, do you allow your fatigue to wash over you, and, collapsing to the ground ocne more, you're soon grabbed by the rats and pinned to the floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Ya gonna pay fer that!)] [npc2.name] angrily shouts at you, before turning once again to [npc2.her] subordinates and ordering, [npc2.speech(Yous lot, go let the others know the situation's really been dealt with this time! I'm gonna drag this 'un to Murk! We may have lost [pc.her] friend, but this 'un's gonna be more than enough ta trade with Murk in order to write off me debt.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Hurrying to do as they're told, four of the rats run off into the tunnels to tell the rest of the gang that you and [npc.name] have been dealt with, while the two which remain roughly grab hold of you and your companion and start dragging you off in a different direction. Letting out cruel laugh, [npc2.name] sneers, [npc2.speech(You's gonna love havin' Murk as yer master! I's seen it 'appen a couple o' times now; he's gonna transform the two o' ya into milkin' bitches, an' get yer broken in an' worshippin' 'is cock!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc3.speech(That's right,)] [npc3.name] joins in, laughing at the thought of what's going to happen to you, [npc3.speech(Once yer both nothin' but 'is obedient sluts, he'll start rentin' yer out, so all o' us in the gang can come an' 'ave a go fuckin' ya!)]
		</p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkIntroduced))
			<p>
				The rats' taunts and mocking laughter fills the twisting passageways as they continue dragging you and your companion towards your fate at the hands of Murk. Knowing all too well the sort of vile character he is, you know that what the gang members are saying is true, but you aren't given too long to think about your future, as the rats suddenly come to a stop and throw the two of you down to the hard ground.
			</p>
			<p>
				Looking up, you see that you're once again in the milk storage room, with dozens of metal pails stacked up against the walls. Sitting on his tatty old red sofa, you see Murk staring at you and [npc.name] with a wicked gleam in his eye. Just like the last time you were here, the rat-boy's massive, sheathed cock and huge balls are fully on display, and as he stands up and walks towards you, his disproportionately-large testicles swing ponderously from side to side.
			</p>
			<p>
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Fancy seein' the two o' yer 'ere again!)] Murk sneers in a slovenly tone as he comes to a halt in front of you. Reaching up to scratch his chubby belly, the foul-mannered rat-boy lets out a loud belch, before throwing the empty can in his other hand over to one side of the room. Moving his hungry gaze up from you to look at the rat which dragged you into this place, he snarls, [murk.speechNoEffects(Took ya long enough ta get 'em subdued! So, ya 'ere ta 'and 'em over ta me then, are ya?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(If ya write off me debt, then sure,)] [npc2.name] responds, [npc2.speech(or else I'll go throw 'em out into Submission an' ya can miss out on gettin' this pair o' new toys.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Spitting on the ground, Murk sneers once again, [murk.speechNoEffects(Let's get 'em stripped an' I'll consider it. Y'know I's trained ta remove any jinxed clothin', but you're gonna owe me fer the cost o' any essences I 'ave ta spend!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				The rats' taunts and mocking laughter fills the twisting passageways as they continue dragging you and your companion towards your fate at the hands of this 'Murk' character, whoever he may be. You aren't sure whether the gang members are making all of this up to scare you, but you aren't given too long to think about it, as the rats suddenly come to a stop and throw the two of you down to the hard ground.
			</p>
			<p>
				Looking up, you see that you're in a relatively small, well-lit room, with the most striking feature being dozens of metal milk-pails stacked up against the walls. Over on the far side of the earth-packed floor, directly ahead of you, there's a collection of old, tatty-looking furniture arrayed next to an old wooden door. A couple of worn, wooden tables are haphazardly surrounded by half a dozen stools and chairs, while pushed up against the far wall are several crates and cabinets. Finishing off this assortment of furnishings is an old, faded, red sofa, which catches your eye both due to its splash of colour, as well as due to there being a greater rat-boy sitting in the middle of it.
			</p>
			<p>
				This resident gang member, who you assume must be 'Murk' looks over at you and [npc.name] with a wicked gleam in his shifty yellow eyes. Reaching up to scratch the dark-brown fur covering his exposed, chubby belly, he lets out an evil snicker before sliding off the sofa and starting to stroll towards you. Due to his short stature, being only around [murk.heightValue] tall, his lower half was obscured behind one of the chairs while he was slouched on the sofa, but as he walks towards you and [npc.name], you see that he's wearing a pair of black, crotchless chaps, leaving his genitals totally exposed.
			</p>
			<p>
				Although it's sheathed, and so impossible to know the erect length of it, the circumference of the rat-boy's withdrawn, pale-pink cock is absolutely huge. The pair of massive, heavy balls hanging down between his legs are also disproportionately large in relation to his height, and you can't help but glance at them as they ponderously swing from side to side in pace with his short stride.
			</p>
			<p>
				[murk.speechNoEffects('Ungry fer me fat cock, are ya?)] Murk sneers at you in a slovenly tone as he catches you looking at his massive genitals. Reaching up to scratch his chubby belly once again, the foul-mannered rat-boy lets out a loud belch, before throwing the empty can in his other hand over to one side of the room. Moving his hungry gaze up from you to look at the rat which dragged you into this place, Murk snarls, [murk.speechNoEffects(I 'eard there were a couple o' troublemakers runnin' around in 'ere. Took ya long enough ta get 'em subdued, didn't it?! So, ya 'ere ta 'and 'em over ta me then, are ya?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(If ya write off me debt, then sure,)] [npc2.name] responds, [npc2.speech(or else I'll go throw 'em out into Submission an' ya can miss out on gettin' this pair o' new toys.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Spitting on the ground, Murk sneers once again, [murk.speechNoEffects(Let's get 'em stripped an' I'll consider it. Y'know I's trained ta remove any jinxed clothin', but you're gonna owe me fer the cost o' any essences I 'ave ta spend!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Hurrying to do as they're told, all of the other rats run off into the tunnels to tell the rest of the gang that you've been dealt with, while the leader who remains roughly grabs hold you and starts dragging you off in a different direction. Letting out cruel laugh, [npc.name] sneers, [npc.speech(You's gonna love havin' Murk as yer master! I's seen it 'appen a couple o' times now; he's gonna transform ya into an 'orny milkin' bitch, an' get yer broken in an' worshippin' 'is cock! Then once yer nothin' but 'is obedient slut, he'll start rentin' yer out, so all o' us in the gang can come an' 'ave a go fuckin' ya!)]
		</p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkIntroduced))
			<p>
				The rat's taunts and mocking laughter fills the twisting passageways as [npc.she] continues dragging you towards your fate at the hands of Murk. Knowing all too well the sort of vile character he is, you know that what your captor is saying is true, but you aren't given too long to think about your future, as [npc.she] suddenly comes to a stop and throws you down to the hard ground.
			</p>
			<p>
				Looking up, you see that you're once again in the milk storage room, with dozens of metal pails stacked up against the walls. Sitting on his tatty old red sofa, you see Murk staring at you with a wicked gleam in his eye. Just like the last time you were here, the rat-boy's massive, sheathed cock and huge balls are fully on display, and as he stands up and walks towards you, his disproportionately-large testicles swing ponderously from side to side.
			</p>
			<p>
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Fancy seein' ya 'ere again!)] Murk sneers in a slovenly tone as he comes to a halt in front of you. Reaching up to scratch his chubby belly, the foul-mannered rat-boy lets out a loud belch, before throwing the empty can in his other hand over to one side of the room. Moving his hungry gaze up from you to look at the rat which dragged you into this place, he snarls, [murk.speechNoEffects(Took ya long enough ta get [pc.herHim] subdued! So, ya 'ere ta 'and [pc.herHim] over ta me then, are ya?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.speech(If ya write off me debt, then sure,)] [npc.name] responds, [npc.speech(or else I'll go throw [pc.herHim] out into Submission an' ya can miss out on gettin' yerself a new toy.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Spitting on the ground, Murk sneers once again, [murk.speechNoEffects(Let's get [pc.herHim] stripped an' I'll consider it. Y'know I's trained ta remove any jinxed clothin', but you're gonna owe me fer the cost o' any essences I 'ave ta spend!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				The rat's taunts and mocking laughter fills the twisting passageways as [npc.she] continues dragging you towards your fate at the hands of this 'Murk' character, whoever he may be. You aren't sure whether your captor is making all of this up to scare you, but you aren't given too long to think about it, as [npc.she] suddenly comes to a stop and throws you down to the hard ground.
			</p>
			<p>
				Looking up, you see that you're in a relatively small, well-lit room, with the most striking feature being dozens of metal milk-pails stacked up against the walls. Over on the far side of the earth-packed floor, directly ahead of you, there's a collection of old, tatty-looking furniture arrayed next to an old wooden door. A couple of worn, wooden tables are haphazardly surrounded by half a dozen stools and chairs, while pushed up against the far wall are several crates and cabinets. Finishing off this assortment of furnishings is an old, faded, red sofa, which catches your eye both due to its splash of colour, as well as due to there being a greater rat-boy sitting in the middle of it.
			</p>
			<p>
				This resident gang member, who you assume must be 'Murk' looks over at you with a wicked gleam in his shifty yellow eyes. Reaching up to scratch the dark-brown fur covering his exposed, chubby belly, he lets out an evil snicker before sliding off the sofa and starting to stroll towards you. Due to his short stature, being only around [murk.heightValue] tall, his lower half was obscured behind one of the chairs while he was slouched on the sofa, but as he walks towards you, you see that he's wearing a pair of black, crotchless chaps, leaving his genitals totally exposed.
			</p>
			<p>
				Although it's sheathed, and so impossible to know the erect length of it, the circumference of the rat-boy's withdrawn, pale-pink cock is absolutely huge. The pair of massive, heavy balls hanging down between his legs are also disproportionately large in relation to his height, and you can't help but glance at them as they ponderously swing from side to side in pace with his short stride.
			</p>
			<p>
				[murk.speechNoEffects('Ungry fer me fat cock, are ya?)] Murk sneers at you in a slovenly tone as he catches you looking at his massive genitals. Reaching up to scratch his chubby belly once again, the foul-mannered rat-boy lets out a loud belch, before throwing the empty can in his other hand over to one side of the room. Moving his hungry gaze up from you to look at the rat which dragged you into this place, Murk snarls, [murk.speechNoEffects(I 'eard there were a troublemaker runnin' around in 'ere. Took ya long enough ta get [pc.herHim] subdued, didn't it?! So, ya 'ere ta 'and [pc.herHim] over ta me then, are ya?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(If ya write off me debt, then sure,)] [npc2.name] responds, [npc2.speech(or else I'll go throw [pc.herHim] out into Submission an' ya can miss out on gettin' yerself a new toy.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Spitting on the ground, Murk sneers once again, [murk.speechNoEffects(Let's get [pc.herHim] stripped an' I'll consider it. Y'know I's trained ta remove any jinxed clothin', but you're gonna owe me fer the cost o' any essences I 'ave ta spend!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS_STRIPPED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS_STRIPPED"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Still completely exhausted from your fight, neither you nor [npc.name] are able to put up an effective resistance as the rats set about stripping each of you of all your clothes and belongings. Setting about their task with much enthusiasm, the horny gang members take full advantage of the situation to grope and squeeze every part of your naked bodies. Their lewd comments and hungry growls are broken only by Murk reminding them that all of your possessions are now his, and to place them in a nearby storage crate which he's opened specially for this occasion.
		</p>
		<p>
			Once you and your companion have been completely stripped of all of your flames, clothing, and other belongings, Murk securely locks the crate into which they were placed, before turning to your captors and snarling, [murk.speechNoEffects(Don't think fer a moment that this is goin' towards payin' off yer debts! I ain't gonna be touchin' this stuff we took 'til I get the chance ta discuss it with Vengar, and seein' as me and 'im ain't on the best o' terms right now, that might be a while. Anyways, yous lot just watch over these two while I get their new 'outfits'... Heh-heh-heh...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Chuckling to himself, Murk walks off to the other crates stacked up against the far side of the room, before opening the nearest one and starting to rummage about inside of it. After a moment of being forced to wait down on your knees beside the four rats, you watch as Murk pulls something out of the crate, and as he starts walking back over towards you and [npc.name], you're able to see that he's holding a matching pair of heavy metal collars, each of which is coloured in a very feminine shade of light pink.
		</p>
		<p>
			Dealing with your companion first, the chubby rat-boy locks one of these collars in place around [npc.namePos] neck, before stepping over to you and doing the same. As the jinxed item of clothing locks into place, you feel the effects of the collar's powerful enchantment seeping into your mind and making you unable to bring yourself to either attempt to unjinx it, or use any self-transformative powers you might possess in order to slip out of it.
		</p>
		<p>
			[murk.speechNoEffects(Hmm, yeah, these two are gonna do nicely,)] Murk muses to himself, before addressing [npc2.name] and continuing, [murk.speechNoEffects(I'll write off yer debts if ya let me keep the two o' 'em. I'm doin' ya a favour 'ere; I'm sure I don't need ta remind ya 'ow much ya owe me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(These two is worth way more than wot I owe's ya,)] [npc2.name] replies, [npc2.speech(But if ya let us fuck 'em, we can call it even, agreed?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[murk.speechNoEffects(Ya can use their mouths, sure,)] Murk replies, [murk.speechNoEffects(but their other 'oles are reserved fer my fat cock.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Deal,)] [npc2.name] says, spitting on [npc2.her] hand and holding it out to Murk. The chubby rat-boy likewise spits on the palm of his hand, before the two rats shake on their deal.
		</p>
		<p>
			[murk.speechNoEffects(Bring 'em through into the milkin' room,)] Murk finally says, [murk.speechNoEffects(I want the two o' 'em chained up and locked into their new 'omes before ya let 'em get intimate with wot's between ya legs.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Still completely exhausted from your fight, you aren't able to put up an effective resistance as Murk and [npc.name] set about stripping you of all your clothes and belongings. Setting about their task with much enthusiasm, the horny rats take full advantage of the situation to grope and squeeze every part of your naked body. [npc.NamePos] lewd comments and hungry growls are broken only by Murk occasionally reminding [npc.herHim] that all of your possessions are now his, and to place them in a nearby storage crate which he's opened specially for this occasion.
		</p>
		<p>
			Once you've been completely stripped of all of your flames, clothing, and other belongings, Murk securely locks the crate into which they were placed, before turning to your captors and snarling, [murk.speechNoEffects(Don't think fer a moment that this is goin' towards payin' off yer debts! I ain't gonna be touchin' this stuff we took 'til I get the chance ta discuss it with Vengar, and seein' as me and 'im ain't on the best o' terms right now, that might be a while. Anyways, yous lot just watch over [pc.herHim] while I get [pc.her] new 'outfit'... Heheheh...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Chuckling to himself, Murk walks off to the other crates stacked up against the far side of the room, before opening the nearest one and starting to rummage about inside of it. After a moment of being forced to wait down on your knees beside [npc.name], you watch as Murk pulls something out of the crate, and as he starts walking back over towards you, you're able to see that he's holding a heavy metal collar, which is coloured in a very feminine shade of light pink.
		</p>
		<p>
			Stepping up to you, the chubby rat-boy reaches down and roughly locks the heavy collar into place around your neck. The very moment that it seals shut, you feel the effects of the collar's powerful enchantment seeping into your mind and making you unable to bring yourself to either attempt to unjinx it, or use any self-transformative powers you might possess in order to slip out of it.
		</p>
		<p>
			[murk.speechNoEffects(Hmm, yeah, this 'un's gonna do nicely,)] Murk muses to himself, before addressing [npc.name] and continuing, [murk.speechNoEffects(I'll write off yer debts if ya let me keep [pc.herHim]. I'm doin' ya a favour 'ere; I'm sure I don't need ta remind ya 'ow much ya owe me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech([pc.SheIs] worth way more than wot I owe's ya,)] [npc.name] replies, [npc.speech(But if ya let me fuck [pc.herHim], we can call it even, agreed?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[murk.speechNoEffects(Ya can use [pc.her] mouth, sure,)] Murk replies, [murk.speechNoEffects(but [pc.her] other 'oles are reserved fer my fat cock.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Deal,)] [npc.name] says, spitting on [npc.her] hand and holding it out to Murk. The chubby rat-boy likewise spits on the palm of his hand, before the two rats shake on their deal.
		</p>
		<p>
			[murk.speechNoEffects(Bring [pc.herHim] through into the milkin' room,)] Murk finally says, [murk.speechNoEffects(I want [pc.herHim] chained up and locked into [pc.her] new 'ome before ya let [pc.herHim] get intimate with wot's between ya legs.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS_STRIPPED_END -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS_STRIPPED_END"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Grabbing hold of you and [npc.name] one last time, the gang members drag the two of you over to the old wooden door on the other side of the room. Stepping in front of you, Murk twists the handle and opens the door, before leading you into the room beyond.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				Having already seen your 'new home' before, you're already familiar with the sight of the long series of metal-framed stalls. Just like the last time you were here, out of the six wall-facing stalls which you count, the four furthest from the door are currently occupied by busty human females, who all start desperately crying out for Murk as they hear you enter.
			#ELSE
				As you step into your 'new home', the first thing that you immediately notice is that this room's proportions are more akin to a wide corridor than a conventional square or rectangular shape. The very next thing you register is that running down alongside the left-hand wall, there are a series of metal-framed stalls, each consisting of a padded bench plus surrounding supports to which an occupant's legs or arms can be chained. Out of the six wall-facing stalls which you count, the four furthest from the door are currently occupied by busty human females, who all start desperately crying out for Murk as they hear you enter.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc4.speech(Master! Please, fill my pussy!)] one of them whines.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc6.speech(Please, master! I need your cock!)] the one beside the first cries out.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Ain't none o' yous milker sluts gonna get a feel o' me cock if ya don't shut up!)] Murk shouts out, causing the four milkers to quieten down. They don't completely stop making a noise, however, as each one of them settles into letting out a series of subdued, horny moans. As the gang members start dragging you and [npc.name] towards the nearby vacant stalls, you see the cause of the milkers' lewd background noise taking the familiar form of an arcane-powered milking machine positioned beside each one of them.
			#ELSE
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Ain't none o' yous milker sluts gonna get a feel o' me cock if ya don't shut up!)] Murk shouts out, causing the four 'milkers' to quieten down. They don't completely stop making a noise, however, as each one of them settles into letting out a series of subdued, horny moans. As the gang members start dragging you and [npc.name] towards the nearby vacant stalls, you see the cause of the milkers' lewd background noise taking the form of an arcane-powered milking machine positioned beside each one of them.
			#ENDIF
			 Leading back into these machines via a long tube, steadily-pumping suction cups have been attached over each of the milkers' puffy, milk-dripping nipples,
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
					 while a pair of fat, rhythmically-vibrating dildos have been firmly inserted into each of their dripping, stretched-out pussies and assholes.
				#ELSE
					 while a pair of thick, rhythmically-vibrating dildos have been firmly inserted into each of their dripping pussies and assholes.
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
					 while a fat, rhythmically-vibrating dildo has been firmly inserted into each of their dripping, stretched-out pussies.
				#ELSE
					 while a thick, rhythmically-vibrating dildo has been firmly inserted into each of their dripping pussies.
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				[murk.speechNoEffects(I's bettin' ya never thought yer were gonna end up bein' in the milker's position, did ya?)]
			#ELSE
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Ya like the look o' yer new home?)]
			#ENDIF
			 Murk asks you and [npc.name] in a mocking tone. Not waiting for an answer, he motions the rats to push the two of you stomach-down onto the vacant benches, and once that's done, he locks each of your collars to metal chains welded to the stalls' frames. Wanting to make sure that you can't stand up and attempt to resist, the rats use a nearby series of secondary chains and locks to firmly secure your arms and legs to the cold metal frame, resulting in each of you having very little room in which to move around, while simultaneously leaving your rear ends completely exposed to the room.
		</p>
		<p>
			[murk.speechNoEffects(So go on, gets ta usin' their mouths already. The sooner yer done with 'em, the sooner I can get on with startin' their trainin'!)] Murk scowls, before stepping back and keeping a close watch to ensure that the rats only make use of your mouths...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Grabbing hold of you one last time, [npc.name] drags you over to the old wooden door on the other side of the room. Stepping in front of you, Murk twists the handle and opens the door, before leading you into the room beyond.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				Having already seen your 'new home' before, you're already familiar with the sight of the long series of metal-framed stalls. Just like the last time you were here, out of the six wall-facing stalls which you count, the four furthest from the door are currently occupied by busty human females, who all start desperately crying out for Murk as they hear you enter.
			#ELSE
				As you step into your 'new home', the first thing that you immediately notice is that this room's proportions are more akin to a wide corridor than a conventional square or rectangular shape. The very next thing you register is that running down alongside the left-hand wall, there are a series of metal-framed stalls, each consisting of a padded bench plus surrounding supports to which an occupant's legs or arms can be chained. Out of the six wall-facing stalls which you count, the four furthest from the door are currently occupied by busty human females, who all start desperately crying out for Murk as they hear you enter.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc4.speech(Master! Please, fill my pussy!)] one of them whines.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc6.speech(Please, master! I need your cock!)] the one beside the first cries out.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Ain't none o' yous milker sluts gonna get a feel o' me cock if ya don't shut up!)] Murk shouts out, causing the four milkers to quieten down. They don't completely stop making a noise, however, as each one of them settles into letting out a series of subdued, horny moans. As the gang members start dragging you towards the nearby vacant stalls, you see the cause of the milkers' lewd background noise taking the familiar form of an arcane-powered milking machine positioned beside each one of them.
			#ELSE
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Ain't none o' yous milker sluts gonna get a feel o' me cock if ya don't shut up!)] Murk shouts out, causing the four 'milkers' to quieten down. They don't completely stop making a noise, however, as each one of them settles into letting out a series of subdued, horny moans. As [npc.name] starts dragging you towards the nearest vacant stall, you see the cause of the milkers' lewd background noise taking the form of an arcane-powered milking machine positioned beside each one of them.
			#ENDIF
			 Leading back into these machines via a long tube, steadily-pumping suction cups have been attached over each of the milkers' puffy, milk-dripping nipples,
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
					 while a pair of fat, rhythmically-vibrating dildos have been firmly inserted into each of their dripping, stretched-out pussies and assholes.
				#ELSE
					 while a pair of thick, rhythmically-vibrating dildos have been firmly inserted into each of their dripping pussies and assholes.
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
					 while a fat, rhythmically-vibrating dildo has been firmly inserted into each of their dripping, stretched-out pussies.
				#ELSE
					 while a thick, rhythmically-vibrating dildo has been firmly inserted into each of their dripping pussies.
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				[murk.speechNoEffects(I's bettin' ya never thought yer were gonna end up bein' in the milker's position, did ya?)]
			#ELSE
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Ya like the look o' yer new home?)]
			#ENDIF
			 Murk asks you in a mocking tone. Not waiting for an answer, he motions [npc.name] to push you stomach-down onto the vacant bench, and once that's done, he locks your collar to a heavy metal chain welded to the stall's frame. Wanting to make sure that you can't stand up and attempt to resist, Murk uses a nearby series of secondary chains and locks to firmly secure your arms and legs to the cold metal frame, resulting in you having very little room in which to move around, while simultaneously leaving your rear end completely exposed to the room.
		</p>
		<p>
			[murk.speechNoEffects(So go on, gets ta usin' [pc.her] mouth already. The sooner yer done with [pc.herHim], the sooner I can get on with startin' [pc.her] trainin'!)] Murk scowls, before stepping back and keeping a close watch to ensure that [npc.name] only makes use of your mouth...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Seeing the futility of trying to resist in your current situation, you stay still as [npc2.name] steps around in front of you and starts fiddling with [npc2.her] clothing in order to expose [npc2.her] groin. Just a moment more, and you find yourself
			#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
				 staring at [npc2.namePos] [npc2.cockSize], [npc2.cockGirth] [npc2.cock], which is rapidly hardening right in front of your face.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(Open wide, slut,)] [npc2.name] orders, and, not seeing any point in disobeying, you submissively open your mouth and prepare to take [npc2.her] [npc2.cock+] down your throat.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in! [pc.SheIs] already 'ungry fer rat cock!)] [npc2.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc2.her] hips forwards and sliding [npc2.her] throbbing cock past your waiting lips.
				</p>
				<p>
					Off to one side, you hear [npc3.name] similarly starting to receive oral from [npc.name], but with the [npc2.cock+] pushing its way down your throat, you've got other things to be focusing on...
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(npc2.hasVagina())
				 staring at [npc2.namePos] [npc2.fingers+] teasing their way up and down over [npc2.her] [npc2.pussy+].
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(Open wide, bitch, an' get ready ta use yer tongue!)] [npc2.name] orders, and, not seeing any point in disobeying, you submissively open your mouth and prepare to start performing cunnilingus on your captor.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in! [pc.SheIs] already 'ungry fer the taste o' rat cunt!)] [npc2.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc2.her] hips forwards and pressing [npc2.her] [npc2.pussy+] against your waiting lips.
				</p>
				<p>
					Off to one side, you hear [npc3.name] similarly starting to receive oral from [npc.name], but as you push your [pc.tongue] out past [npc2.namePos] [npc2.labia+], you find yourself with other things to be focusing on...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				 staring at [npc2.namePos] [npc2.fingers+] teasing their way up and down over [npc2.her] smooth, doll-like groin.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(Open wide, bitch, an' get ready ta use yer tongue!)] [npc2.name] orders, and, not seeing any point in disobeying, you submissively open your mouth and prepare to start performing oral on your captor.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in!)] [npc2.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc2.her] hips forwards and pressing [npc2.her] smooth crotch against your waiting lips.
				</p>
				<p>
					Off to one side, you hear [npc3.name] similarly starting to receive oral from [npc.name], but you quickly find yourself with other things to be focusing on...
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Seeing the futility of trying to resist in your current situation, you stay still as [npc.name] steps around in front of you and starts fiddling with [npc.her] clothing in order to expose [npc.her] groin. Just a moment more, and you find yourself
			#IF(npc.hasPenis())
				 staring at [npc.namePos] [npc.cockSize], [npc.cockGirth] [npc.cock], which is rapidly hardening right in front of your face.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(Open wide, slut,)] [npc.name] orders, and, not seeing any point in disobeying, you submissively open your mouth and prepare to take [npc.her] [npc.cock+] down your throat.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in! [pc.SheIs] already 'ungry fer rat cock!)] [npc.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc.her] hips forwards and sliding [npc.her] throbbing cock past your waiting lips...
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(npc.hasVagina())
				 staring at [npc.namePos] [npc.fingers+] teasing their way up and down over [npc.her] [npc.pussy+].
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(Open wide, bitch, an' get ready ta use yer tongue!)] [npc.name] orders, and, not seeing any point in disobeying, you submissively open your mouth and prepare to start performing cunnilingus on your captor.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in! [pc.SheIs] already 'ungry fer the taste o' rat cunt!)] [npc.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc.her] hips forwards and pressing [npc.her] [npc.pussy+] against your waiting lips...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				 staring at [npc.namePos] [npc.fingers+] teasing their way up and down over [npc.her] smooth, doll-like groin.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(Open wide, bitch, an' get ready ta use yer tongue!)] [npc.name] orders, and, not seeing any point in disobeying, you submissively open your mouth and prepare to start performing oral on your captor.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in!)] [npc.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc.her] hips forwards and pressing [npc.her] smooth crotch against your waiting lips...
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS_SEX_EAGER"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Your current situation has got you incredibly turned on, and you can't help but let out an eager [pc.moan] as [npc2.name] steps around in front of you and starts fiddling with [npc2.her] clothing. Just a moment later, and you find yourself hungrily
			#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
				 staring at [npc2.namePos] [npc2.cockSize], [npc2.cockGirth] [npc2.cock], which is rapidly hardening right in front of your face. Desperate to get a taste, you open your mouth and let out a pleading whine.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in! [pc.SheIs] already 'ungry fer rat cock!)] [npc2.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc2.her] hips forwards and rubbing the head of [npc2.her] throbbing cock against your waiting lips. Letting out a sneer, [npc2.she] teases, [npc2.speech(Go on, beg fer it, slut!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[pc.speech(Please! Let me suck your cock!)] you desperately whine, craning your neck forwards and trying to take [npc2.namePos] [npc2.cock+] into your mouth.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(That's a good slut,)] [npc2.name] says, before stepping forwards and sliding [npc2.her] throbbing cock past your waiting lips.
				</p>
				<p>
					Off to one side, you hear [npc3.name] similarly starting to receive oral from [npc.name], but with the [npc2.cock+] pushing its way down your throat, you've got other things you'd rather be focusing on...
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(npc2.hasVagina())
				 staring at [npc2.namePos] [npc2.fingers+] teasing their way up and down over [npc2.her] [npc2.pussy+]. Desperate to get a taste, you open your mouth and let out a pleading whine.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in! [pc.SheIs] already 'ungry fer the taste o' rat cunt!)] [npc2.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc2.her] hips forwards bringing [npc2.her] [npc2.pussy+] closer towards your waiting lips. Letting out a sneer, [npc2.she] teases, [npc2.speech(Go on, beg fer it, slut!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[pc.speech(Please! Let me lick your pussy!)] you desperately whine, craning your neck forwards and trying to lick [npc2.namePos] [npc2.pussy+].
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(That's a good slut,)] [npc2.name] says, before stepping forwards and letting you slide your tongue into [npc2.her] [npc2.pussy].
				</p>
				<p>
					Off to one side, you hear [npc3.name] similarly starting to receive oral from [npc.name], but as you push your [pc.tongue] past [npc2.namePos] [npc2.labia+], you find yourself with other things you'd rather be focusing on...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				 staring at [npc2.namePos] [npc2.fingers+] teasing their way up and down over [npc2.her] smooth, doll-like groin. Desperate to please [npc2.herHim], you open your mouth and let out a pleading whine.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(Open wide, bitch, an' get ready ta use yer tongue!)] [npc2.name] orders, and, not seeing any point in disobeying, you submissively open your mouth and prepare to start performing oral on your captor.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in!)] [npc2.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc2.her] hips forwards and pressing [npc2.her] smooth crotch against your waiting lips.
				</p>
				<p>
					Off to one side, you hear [npc3.name] similarly starting to receive oral from [npc.name], but you quickly find yourself with other things to be focusing on...
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Your current situation has got you incredibly turned on, and you can't help but let out an eager [pc.moan] as [npc.name] steps around in front of you and starts fiddling with [npc.her] clothing. Just a moment later, and you find yourself hungrily
			#IF(npc.hasPenis())
				 staring at [npc.namePos] [npc.cockSize], [npc.cockGirth] [npc.cock], which is rapidly hardening right in front of your face. Desperate to get a taste, you open your mouth and let out a pleading whine.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in! [pc.SheIs] already 'ungry fer rat cock!)] [npc.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc.her] hips forwards and rubbing the head of [npc.her] throbbing cock against your waiting lips. Letting out a sneer, [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(Go on, beg fer it, slut!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[pc.speech(Please! Let me suck your cock!)] you desperately whine, craning your neck forwards and trying to take [npc.namePos] [npc.cock+] into your mouth.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(That's a good slut,)] [npc.name] says, before stepping forwards and sliding [npc.her] throbbing cock past your waiting lips...
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(npc.hasVagina())
				 staring at [npc.namePos] [npc.fingers+] teasing their way up and down over [npc.her] [npc.pussy+]. Desperate to get a taste, you open your mouth and let out a pleading whine.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in! [pc.SheIs] already 'ungry fer the taste o' rat cunt!)] [npc.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc.her] hips forwards bringing [npc.her] [npc.pussy+] closer towards your waiting lips. Letting out a sneer, [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(Go on, beg fer it, slut!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[pc.speech(Please! Let me lick your pussy!)] you desperately whine, craning your neck forwards and trying to lick [npc.namePos] [npc.pussy+].
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(That's a good slut,)] [npc.name] says, before stepping forwards and letting you slide your tongue into [npc.her] [npc.pussy]...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				 staring at [npc.namePos] [npc.fingers+] teasing their way up and down over [npc.her] smooth, doll-like groin. Desperate to please [npc.herHim], you open your mouth and let out a pleading whine.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(Open wide, bitch, an' get ready ta use yer tongue!)] [npc.name] orders, and, not seeing any point in disobeying, you submissively open your mouth and prepare to start performing oral on your captor.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech(Ya ain't gonna need ta do much ta break this 'un in!)] [npc.name] gleefully shouts out to Murk, before pushing [npc.her] hips forwards and pressing [npc.her] smooth crotch against your waiting lips...
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS_SEX_RESIST"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Finally starting to recover enough energy to resist, you start to struggle against your restraints, shouting, [pc.speech(Stop this! Let me go!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a mocking laugh, but otherwise ignoring your protests, [npc2.name] steps around in front of you and starts fiddling with [npc2.her] clothing. Just a moment later, and you find yourself trying to wriggle backwards as
			#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
				 [npc2.namePos] [npc2.cockSize], [npc2.cockGirth] [npc2.cock] flops free right in front of your face.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech('Ain't no use in strugglin', slut! Ya gonna be chokin' on me fat cock in a moment, an' there ain't nothin' ya can do about it!)] [npc2.name] sneers, while reaching down to start stroking [npc2.her] cock to full erectness. While you continue squirming and struggling against your restraints, [npc2.name] pushes [npc2.her] hips forwards and forcefully rubs the head of [npc2.her] throbbing cock against your lips. Letting out a mocking laugh, [npc2.she] teases, [npc2.speech(If ya say please, I'll think about leavin' ya alone!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Seeing no other option but to take a chance on doing what [npc2.name] asks, you open your mouth to say please, but the moment you do, [npc2.name] thrusts forwards and rams [npc2.her] [npc2.cock+] into your mouth. Pushing [npc2.her] throbbing shaft deep down your throat, [npc2.name] sneers, [npc2.speech(That's me good dumb slut! Yer gonna learn ta love rat cock soon enough!)] 
				</p>
				<p>
					Off to one side, you hear [npc3.name] similarly starting to receive oral from [npc.name], but with the [npc2.cock+] pushing its way down your throat, you've got other things you'd rather be focusing on and trying to resist...
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(npc2.hasVagina())
				 [npc2.namePos] [npc2.pussy+] hovers right in front of your face.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech('Ain't no use in strugglin', slut! Ya gonna be eatin' me out in a moment, an' there ain't nothin' ya can do about it!)] [npc2.name] sneers, while reaching down to tauntingly spread [npc2.her] [npc2.labia+]. While you continue squirming and struggling against your restraints, [npc2.name] pushes [npc2.her] hips forwards and forcefully rubs [npc2.her] clit against your lips. Letting out a mocking laugh, [npc2.she] teases, [npc2.speech(If ya say please, I'll think about leavin' ya alone!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Seeing no other option but to take a chance on doing what [npc2.name] asks, you open your mouth to say please, but the moment you do, [npc2.name] thrusts forwards and firmly presses [npc2.her] [npc2.pussy+] over your mouth. Grinding [npc2.her] [npc2.labia] over your face, [npc2.name] sneers, [npc2.speech(That's me good dumb slut! Yer gonna learn ta love rat pussy soon enough!)] 
				</p>
				<p>
					Off to one side, you hear [npc3.name] similarly starting to receive oral from [npc.name], but you find yourself with other things you'd rather be focusing on and trying to resist...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				 [npc2.namePos] smooth, doll-like groin hovers right in front of your face.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc2.speech('Ain't no use in strugglin', slut! Ya gonna be servicin' me in a moment, an' there ain't nothin' ya can do about it!)] [npc2.name] sneers. While you continue squirming and struggling against your restraints, [npc2.name] pushes [npc2.her] hips forwards and forcefully rubs [npc2.her] doll-like crotch against your lips. Letting out a mocking laugh, [npc2.she] teases, [npc2.speech(If ya say please, I'll think about leavin' ya alone!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Seeing no other option but to take a chance on doing what [npc2.name] asks, you open your mouth to say please, but the moment you do, [npc2.name] thrusts forwards and firmly presses [npc2.her] mound over your mouth. Grinding up and down over your face, [npc2.she] sneers, [npc2.speech(That's me good dumb slut! Yer gonna learn ta love this soon enough!)] 
				</p>
				<p>
					Off to one side, you hear [npc3.name] similarly starting to receive oral from [npc.name], but you find yourself with other things you'd rather be focusing on and trying to resist...
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Finally starting to recover enough energy to resist, you start to struggle against your restraints, shouting, [pc.speech(Stop this! Let me go!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a mocking laugh, but otherwise ignoring your protests, [npc.name] steps around in front of you and starts fiddling with [npc.her] clothing. Just a moment later, and you find yourself trying to wriggle backwards as
			#IF(npc.hasPenis())
				 [npc.namePos] [npc.cockSize], [npc.cockGirth] [npc.cock] flops free right in front of your face.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech('Ain't no use in strugglin', slut! Ya gonna be chokin' on me fat cock in a moment, an' there ain't nothin' ya can do about it!)] [npc.name] sneers, while reaching down to start stroking [npc.her] cock to full erectness. While you continue squirming and struggling against your restraints, [npc.name] pushes [npc.her] hips forwards and forcefully rubs the head of [npc.her] throbbing cock against your lips. Letting out a mocking laugh, [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(If ya say please, I'll think about leavin' ya alone!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Seeing no other option but to take a chance on doing what [npc.name] asks, you open your mouth to say please, but the moment you do, [npc.name] thrusts forwards and rams [npc.her] [npc.cock+] into your mouth. Pushing [npc.her] throbbing shaft deep down your throat, [npc.name] sneers, [npc.speech(That's me good dumb slut! Yer gonna learn ta love rat cock soon enough!)] 
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(npc.hasVagina())
				 [npc.namePos] [npc.pussy+] hovers right in front of your face.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech('Ain't no use in strugglin', slut! Ya gonna be eatin' me out in a moment, an' there ain't nothin' ya can do about it!)] [npc.name] sneers, while reaching down to tauntingly spread [npc.her] [npc.labia+]. While you continue squirming and struggling against your restraints, [npc.name] pushes [npc.her] hips forwards and forcefully rubs [npc.her] clit against your lips. Letting out a mocking laugh, [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(If ya say please, I'll think about leavin' ya alone!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Seeing no other option but to take a chance on doing what [npc.name] asks, you open your mouth to say please, but the moment you do, [npc.name] thrusts forwards and firmly presses [npc.her] [npc.pussy+] over your mouth. Grinding [npc.her] [npc.labia] over your face, [npc.name] sneers, [npc.speech(That's me good dumb slut! Yer gonna learn ta love rat pussy soon enough!)] 
				</p>
			#ELSE
				 [npc.namePos] smooth, doll-like groin hovers right in front of your face.
				</p>
				<p>
					[npc.speech('Ain't no use in strugglin', slut! Ya gonna be servicin' me in a moment, an' there ain't nothin' ya can do about it!)] [npc.name] sneers. While you continue squirming and struggling against your restraints, [npc.name] pushes [npc.her] hips forwards and forcefully rubs [npc.her] doll-like crotch against your lips. Letting out a mocking laugh, [npc.she] teases, [npc.speech(If ya say please, I'll think about leavin' ya alone!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Seeing no other option but to take a chance on doing what [npc.name] asks, you open your mouth to say please, but the moment you do, [npc.name] thrusts forwards and firmly presses [npc.her] mound over your mouth. Grinding up and down over your face, [npc.she] sneers, [npc.speech(That's me good dumb slut! Yer gonna learn ta love this soon enough!)] 
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARD_COMBAT_DEFEAT_STOCKS_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Having had their fun, the two rats step back from you and your companion, bringing an end to your oral sex session. While [npc3.name] is quick to get [npc3.her] clothing back in place and take [npc3.her] leave, [npc2.name] takes a moment to mock you one last time, [npc2.speech(This is wot ya deserve fer tryin' ta fight us! Murk's gonna get ya turned into an obedient bitch beggin' fer 'is fat cock soon enough! I's give ya no more than five days before ya just like the rest o' these milkers; callin' Murk ya master an' pleading fer 'im ta rut ya all day long! Heh-heh-heh!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, [npc2.name] follows [npc2.her] subordinate out of the milking room, leaving you and [npc.name] alone with Murk...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having had [npc.her] fun, [npc.name] steps back, bringing an end to your oral sex session. Before [npc.she] takes [npc.her] leave, however, your captor takes a moment to mock you one last time, [npc.speech(This is wot ya deserve fer tryin' ta fight us! Murk's gonna get ya turned into an obedient bitch beggin' fer 'is fat cock soon enough! I's give ya no more than five days before ya just like the rest o' these milkers; callin' Murk ya master an' pleading fer 'im ta rut ya all day long! Heh-heh-heh!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, [npc.name] heads out of the milking room, leaving you alone with Murk...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ENTRANCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The entrance to the Rat Warrens is secured by two sets of sturdy wooden doors, separated by a small inner chamber. The opening and closing of both sets of these doors is handled by means of two crude levers, located near to where you're currently standing. Small hatches are located on either side of the inner pair of doors, allowing any guards stationed here to shoot into the inner chamber.  
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensClearedCentre))
		<p>
			Having already beaten the rats guarding the entrance, there are no gang members present in this area right now. What's more, the levers which control the door's operation seem to be broken, trapping
			#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
				 you and [npc.name] inside. If you want to get out of here, the two of you will have to venture further into the gang's den and confront Vengar...
			#ELSE
				 you inside. If you want to get out of here, you'll have to venture further into the gang's den and confront Vengar...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
				#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensEntryWhore))
					Having been told that you and [npc.name] are whores, the two rats give you lustful looks as you enter the area. Hungrily licking [npc2.her] lips, [npc2.name] asks, [npc2.speech(Surely ya ain't gonna leave without 'avin' quick fuck with the two o' us, are ya?)]
				#ELSE
					The two rats on guard duty eye you and [npc.name] suspiciously as you enter the area. Spitting on the ground, [npc2.name] asks, [npc2.speech(You's wantin' ta leave? Or ya just 'angin' around 'ere fer the fun o' it?)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensEntryWhore))
					Having been told that you're a whore, the two rats give you lustful looks as you enter the area. Hungrily licking [npc2.her] lips, [npc2.name] asks, [npc2.speech(Surely ya ain't gonna leave without 'avin' quick fuck with the two o' us, are ya?)]
				#ELSE
					The two rats on guard duty eye you suspiciously as you enter the area. Spitting on the ground, [npc.name] asks, [npc.speech(You's wantin' ta leave? Or ya just 'angin' around 'ere fer the fun o' it?)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CORRIDOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CHECKPOINT_FIGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that the inhabitants of the Rat Warrens must be alerted to your hostile presence by now, you make sure to stay alert as you travel down the twisting passageways. Just as you expected, when you turn the next corner, you see six rat-morphs waiting to confront you.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Seeing you and [npc.name] at the same time as you see them, the rats let out a shout and prepare to fight you. As they advance on the two of you, their leader calls out, [npc2.speech(Yer gonna pay fer this! I 'ope yer ready fer a beatin'!)]
		#ELSE
			Seeing you at the same time as you see them, the rats let out a shout and prepare to fight you. As they advance on you, their leader calls out, [npc.speech(Yer gonna pay fer this! I 'ope yer ready fer a beatin'!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR_CLEARED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Just like the one you find yourself walking through right now, the vast majority of the space inside the Rat Warrens consists of twisting, poorly-lit passageways. In places passing through cavernous, naturally-formed chambers, and in others so narrowly carved through solid rock that two people would struggle to walk abreast, these tunnels are invariable only in the crudity of their construction and maintenance. Here and there, old wooden pillars and boards are holding up the walls and ceiling, while piled up against the edges of the earth-packed floor are piles of crumbled stone mixed with all manner of rubbish.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			With the inhabitants of the Rat Warrens now alerted to your hostile presence, you and [npc.name] don't run into any gang members on your way through the tunnels. The lack of any sign of life gives the whole place a very eerie atmosphere, and you can't shake the feeling that someone's silently watching the two you from the shadows...
		#ELSE
			With the inhabitants of the Rat Warrens now alerted to your hostile presence, you don't run into any gang members on your way through the tunnels. The lack of any sign of life gives the whole place a very eerie atmosphere, and you can't shake the feeling that someone's silently watching you from the shadows...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Just like the one you find yourself walking through right now, the vast majority of the space inside the Rat Warrens consists of twisting, poorly-lit passageways. In places passing through cavernous, naturally-formed chambers, and in others so narrowly carved through solid rock that two people would struggle to walk abreast, these tunnels are invariable only in the crudity of their construction and maintenance. Here and there, old wooden pillars and boards are holding up the walls and ceiling, while piled up against the edges of the earth-packed floor are piles of crumbled stone mixed with all manner of rubbish.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Although rare, you and [npc.name] sometimes encounter one or two rat-morphs, either travelling in the opposite direction, or getting intimate with one another in a dimly-lit hollow. While the ones not too busy with one another sometimes take a moment to question who the two of you are, they don't really seem to care what answer you give, and quickly scurry off on their business. 
		#ELSE
			Although rare, you sometimes encounter one or two rat-morphs, either travelling in the opposite direction, or getting intimate with one another in a dimly-lit hollow. While the ones not too busy with one another sometimes take a moment to question who you are, they don't really seem to care what answer you give, and quickly scurry off on their business. 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DORMITORY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Located at the end of a long, twisting tunnel, there's a relatively spacious, well-lit room carved out of solid rock. Lacking any sort of door to partition the interior from the Rat Warren's gloomy passageways, you're able to step right into what turns out to be some kind of dormitory for the resident gang members. Looking around, you see that there are several wooden bunk beds lining the walls, each with a ragged cloth curtain which can be drawn to afford the occupants a small amount of privacy. Next to each bunk bed, there are a couple of wooden chests for personal belongings, but apart from those, the only other pieces of furniture present are a few tables and chairs haphazardly placed in the middle of the room.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_OCCUPIED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			As it's not time for the gang members to be making use of these sleeping quarters, the bunk beds are all currently empty. The place isn't completely deserted, however, as a few rats are sitting around one of the tables gambling with some dice. Although they turn to see who's entered the room, none of them bother to ask who you are, and after shooting you suspicious glares, they quickly turn back to their game.
		#ELSE
			As it's currently night time, several of the bunk beds are currently occupied by sleeping gang members, whose loud snores fill the otherwise deserted room.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_CLEARED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you've already cleared out this section of the Rat Warrens, the dormitory is completely deserted. Although there's nobody here to stop you from pilfering through the wooden chests beside each bunk bed, you can tell that there's absolutely nothing of value in them, and so there's nothing for you to do in here except turn around and head back into the tunnels...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_FIGHT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			<p>
				Deciding that this is the right time to get started on clearing out the Rat Warrens, you step up to the occupied table and tell the gambling rats that you're here to put an end to their criminal activities. As the gang members jump to their feet, you and [npc.name] ready yourselves for combat.
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(You's 'ere ta do wot?!)] [npc2.name] exclaims, before bellowing at the top of [npc2.her] voice, [npc2.speech(Everyone! Get in 'ere! We need 'elp!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Within seconds, more than half a dozen rat-morphs are dashing into the dormitory as backup, but as they see that there's a fight afoot, a few of them turn around and run off, abandoning their comrades. At the end of all this, you count six gang members left in front of you and [npc.name].
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Deciding that this is the right time to get started on clearing out the Rat Warrens, you shout out that you're here to put an end to all of the rats' criminal activities. Angry at being woken from their slumber, the gang members quickly jump out of their bunk-beds while you and [npc.name] ready yourselves for combat.
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(You's 'ere ta do wot?!)] the nearest gang member exclaims, [npc2.speech(Come on you's lot! 'Elp me give these two a beatin'!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Although they greatly outnumber you, a few of the rats don't seem to like their odds, and quickly dash past you and run off into the tunnels, abandoning their comrades. Once they're gone, you count six gang members left in front of you and [npc.name].
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			With a wild snarl, [npc2.name] shouts to the remaining rats, [npc2.speech(We'll deal with them cowardly scum later! Fer now, let's give these two a real good beatin'!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			<p>
				Deciding that this is the right time to get started on clearing out the Rat Warrens, you step up to the occupied table and tell the gambling rats that you're here to put an end to their criminal activities. As the gang members jump to their feet, you ready yourself for combat.
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.speech(You's 'ere ta do wot?!)] [npc.name] exclaims, before bellowing at the top of [npc.her] voice, [npc.speech(Everyone! Get in 'ere! We need 'elp!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Within seconds, more than half a dozen rat-morphs are dashing into the dormitory as backup, but as they see that there's a fight afoot, a few of them turn around and run off, abandoning their comrades. At the end of all this, you count six gang members left in front of you.
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Deciding that this is the right time to get started on clearing out the Rat Warrens, you shout out that you're here to put an end to all of the rats' criminal activities. Angry at being woken from their slumber, the gang members quickly jump out of their bunk-beds while you ready yourself for combat.
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.speech(You's 'ere ta do wot?!)] the nearest gang member exclaims, [npc.speech(Come on you's lot! 'Elp me give this 'un a beatin'!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Although they greatly outnumber you, a few of the rats don't seem to like their odds, and quickly dash past you and run off into the tunnels, abandoning their comrades. Once they're gone, you count six gang members left in front of you.
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			With a wild snarl, [npc.name] shouts to the remaining rats, [npc.speech(We'll deal with them cowardly scum later! Fer now, let's give this 'un a real good beatin'!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DICE_DEN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DICE_DEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		At the end of one of the many tunnels which snake their way through the Rat Warrens, there's a large, naturally-formed grotto, and it's within this underground hollow that you currently find yourself standing. A few small, barred holes in the high ceiling allow both natural light and a steady stream of water to flow down into this area, filling the cave with the sound of murmuring, echoing splashes. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Running through the middle of the floor, a shallow channel has been half-dug, half-eroded into the solid rock, diverting the water down and away into a metal pipe, which no doubt leads into Submission's main waterways. Positioned all around the rest of this cavern, there are about two dozen old wooden tables, each surrounded with four or so chairs. Running along part of the left-hand wall, there's an open bar, consisting of a long counter-top positioned in front of numerous bottle-filled shelves and cabinets.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DICE_DEN_ENTRY"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensHostile))
		<p>
			Having already cleared the gang members out of this area, the entire place is completely deserted...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
				#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
					You see that several rats are currently sitting around a few of the tables, either chatting with one another or playing some kind of dice game. Standing behind the bar, there's [npc2.a_race], who leans forwards on the counter-top and calls out to you and [npc.name], [npc2.speech(Ya lookin' ta buy a drink? Or maybe ya want ta play some dice poker? Come over 'ere an' let me know if ya are.)]
				#ELSE
					Despite the unsociable hour, you see that several rats are currently sitting around a few of the tables, either chatting with one another or playing some kind of dice game. Standing behind the bar, there's [npc2.a_race], who leans forwards on the counter-top and calls out to you and [npc.name], [npc2.speech(Ya can't sleep either, huh? So long as ya awake, ya might as well come an' buy a drink, right? Or maybe ya want ta play some dice poker? Come over 'ere an' let me know if ya are.)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
					You see that several rats are currently sitting around a few of the tables, either chatting with one another or playing some kind of dice game. Standing behind the bar, there's [npc2.a_race], who leans forwards on the counter-top and calls out to you, [npc.speech(Ya lookin' ta buy a drink? Or maybe ya want ta play some dice poker? Come over 'ere an' let me know if ya are.)]
				#ELSE
					Despite the unsociable hour, you see that several rats are currently sitting around a few of the tables, either chatting with one another or playing some kind of dice game. Standing behind the bar, there's [npc2.a_race], who leans forwards on the counter-top and calls out to you, [npc.speech(Ya can't sleep either, huh? So long as ya awake, ya might as well come an' buy a drink, right? Or maybe ya want ta play some dice poker? Come over 'ere an' let me know if ya are.)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DICE_DEN_CHALLENGE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Deciding that this is the right time to get started on clearing out the Rat Warrens, you step step forwards and call out to the gambling rats that you're here to put an end to their criminal activities. As the gang members jump to their feet, you and [npc.name] ready yourselves for combat.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc7.speech(You's 'ere ta do wot?!)] [npc7.name] exclaims, before rushing around from behind the bar and calling out, [npc7.speech(Come on everyone! Let's show 'em wot we do ta troublemakers!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Although many of the gang members join [npc7.name] in getting ready to fight you, many more of them dash past you and run off into the tunnels, abandoning their comrades. All in all, you count six gang members, including [npc7.name], left in front of you and [npc.name].
		</p>
		<p>
			With a wild snarl, [npc2.name] makes [npc2.herself] known as the leader of this group, and shouts to the remaining rats, [npc2.speech(We'll deal with them cowardly scum later! Fer now, let's give these two a real good beatin'!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Deciding that this is the right time to get started on clearing out the Rat Warrens, you step step forwards and call out to the gambling rats that you're here to put an end to their criminal activities. As the gang members jump to their feet, you ready yourself for combat.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc6.speech(You's 'ere ta do wot?!)] [npc6.name] exclaims, before rushing around from behind the bar and calling out, [npc6.speech(Come on everyone! Let's show 'em wot we do ta troublemakers!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Although many of the gang members join [npc6.name] in getting ready to fight you, many more of them dash past you and run off into the tunnels, abandoning their comrades. All in all, you count six gang members, including [npc6.name], left in front of you.
		</p>
		<p>
			With a wild snarl, [npc.name] makes [npc.herself] known as the leader of this group, and shouts to the remaining rats, [npc.speech(We'll deal with them cowardly scum later! Fer now, let's give this 'un a real good beatin'!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DICE_DEN_LOOT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DICE_DEN_LOOT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Having cleared out this part of the Rat Warrens, there's nobody left to stop you from heading behind the bar and searching it for anything worth taking. Telling [npc.name] to keep watch in case anyone turns up, you set about looting the shelves and cabinets situated behind the bar's long counter. Although most of the bottles are either half-empty or in such a filthy state that they're not worth taking, you're still able to procure a decent amount of alcohol...
		#ELSE
			Having cleared out this part of the Rat Warrens, there's nobody left to stop you from heading behind the bar and searching it for anything worth taking. Taking one last look around the cavern to make sure that there's nobody waiting to ambush you, you then set about looting the shelves and cabinets situated behind the bar's long counter. Although most of the bottles are either half-empty or in such a filthy state that they're not worth taking, you're still able to procure a decent amount of alcohol...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DICE_DEN_RULES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DICE_DEN_RULES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Wanting to know the rules of dice poker before starting a game, you walk up to the bar and ask [npc2.name] to explain them to you. Letting out a devious laugh, [npc2.she] reaches down under the counter to grab something, before straightening up and placing a slightly-rusted metal sign down on the surface before you. Grinning in a mischievous manner, [npc2.she] says, [npc2.speech(One o' me mates pilfered this from that Gamblin' Den a few months back. Ya can read the rules on 'ere, an' if ya wantin' ta do a game, let me know an' I'll find ya an opponent.)]
		#ELSE
			Wanting to know the rules of dice poker before starting a game, you walk up to the bar and ask [npc.name] to explain them to you. Letting out a devious laugh, [npc.she] reaches down under the counter to grab something, before straightening up and placing a slightly-rusted metal sign down on the surface before you. Grinning in a mischievous manner, [npc.she] says, [npc.speech(One o' me mates pilfered this from that Gamblin' Den a few months back. Ya can read the rules on 'ere, an' if ya wantin' ta do a game, let me know an' I'll find ya an opponent.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at the sign, you read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<b>[axel.name]'s Rules For Dice Poker</b><br/>
		1. Both players place the buy-in amount to start a game.<br/><i>Some of the text has been etched out here, and replaced with crude writing:</i><br/>If ya wont to play, you haz to pay up [style.moneyFormat(500, span)]. No reefundz, no arrguinn if ya looses.<br/>
		2. Both players roll five dice each.<br/>
		3. Players can choose to increase the bet (referred to as a 'raise'), or leave the bet at the buy-in amount (referred to as a 'call').<br/>
		4. After betting is done, each player selects as many of their dice as they want to re-roll.<br/>
		5. The players re-roll their chosen dice.<br/>
		6. The ranking of each player's dice is compared to find the winner, who then takes all of the money in the pot.
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<b>Results ranking (from winning to losing)</b><br/>
		1. Five of a kind: Five dice of the same value. (e.g. 33333)<br/>
		2. Four of a kind: Four dice of the same value. (e.g. 55551)<br/>
		3. High straight: Consecutive numbers starting at two. (e.g. 23456)<br/>
		4. Full house: Two dice of the same value, plus three dice of a different, same value. (e.g. 22666)<br/>
		5. Three of a kind: Three dice of the same value. (e.g. 44415)<br/>
		6. Low straight: Consecutive numbers starting at one. (e.g. 12345)<br/>
		7. Two pair: Two dice of the same value, plus two dice of a different, same value. (e.g. 55331)<br/>
		8. Pair: Two dice of the same value. (e.g. 22415)<br/>
		9. Runt: All dice of different values. (e.g. 13456)<br/><br/>
		
		If both players have the same ranking, the total value of the dice that make up their rank are compared. For example:<br/>
		Player A: 33661<br/>
		Player B: 22115<br/>
		Although both players have 'Two pair', player A wins, as the total of their ranking dice is 18 (3+3+6+6), compared to player B's 6 (2+2+1+1).<br/><br/>
		
		If both players have the same ranking, and the same value, the game is a draw, and the money in the pot is returned to each player's hand.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DICE_DEN_POST_GAMBLING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DICE_DEN_POST_GAMBLING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Having finished your game, you leave the table and walk back over to the bar. Seeing you and [npc.name] approach, [npc2.name] calls out, [npc2.speech(Ya want another opponent, just ask me! Or if ya want a drink ta quench ya thirst, I's got the best rum you's ever gonna taste!)]
		#ELSE
			Having finished your game, you leave the table and walk back over to the bar. Seeing you approach, [npc.name] calls out, [npc.speech(Ya want another opponent, just ask me! Or if ya want a drink ta quench ya thirst, I's got the best rum you's ever gonna taste!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DICE_DEN_RUM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DICE_DEN_RUM"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Feeling thirsty and with the temptation of the bar right in front of you, you ask [npc2.name] for a glass of rum, before handing over the flames [npc2.she] asks for. Grinning at you, the [npc2.race] leaves the flames sitting on the counter as [npc2.she] reaches under the counter to grab a glass. Turning around and picking up a half-empty bottle of rum, [npc2.she] pours your drink and then steps back, still leaving the money untouched on the counter-top.
		</p>
		<p>
			Picking up the glass, you quickly drink down the rum, before placing the now-empty vessel back down on the counter and preparing to move off. Before you can go, however, [npc2.name] calls out for you stay, [npc2.speech(Hey, why don't ya 'ang around a little longer? I's bettin' ya'd like ta earn that money o' yours back, wouldn't ya?)]
		</p>
		#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
			<p>
				Looking down at the money still sitting on the counter, you ask [npc2.name] what it is you'd have to do. Leaning forwards and grinning at you, [npc2.she] says, [npc2.speech(Well, wot with 'avin' ta work behind this 'ere bar all day long, I don't get much time fer gettin' me dick wet. If ya want yer money back, all ya 'ave ta do is come round 'ere an' get down on yer knees, then wrap yer pretty little mouth 'round me cock an' get ta suckin'. Let me blow a load down yer throat or over ya face, an' ya can 'ave yer money back.)]
			</p>
			#IF(game.isVoluntaryNTREnabled())
				<p>
					As you're thinking of what to say in response to this offer, [npc2.name] continues, [npc2.speech(I'll even let yer friend 'ere watch me fuck yer throat! Or maybe [npc.she]'d like ta be the one suckin' me cock an' ya can watch us!)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Looking down at the money still sitting on the counter, you ask [npc2.name] what it is you'd have to do. Leaning forwards and grinning at you, [npc2.she] says, [npc2.speech(Well, wot with 'avin' ta work behind this 'ere bar all day long, me cunt don't get much attention. If ya want yer money back, all ya 'ave ta do is come round 'ere an' get down on yer knees, then open wide an' get ta eatin' me out. Once I've 'ad enough fun with yer tongue, ya can 'ave yer money back.)]
			</p>
			#IF(game.isVoluntaryNTREnabled())
				<p>
					As you're thinking of what to say in response to this offer, [npc2.name] continues, [npc2.speech(I'll even let yer friend 'ere watch! Or maybe [npc.she]'d like ta be the one servicin' me pussy an' ya can watch us!)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling thirsty and with the temptation of the bar right in front of you, you ask [npc.name] for a glass of rum, before handing over the flames [npc.she] asks for. Grinning at you, the [npc.race] leaves the flames sitting on the counter as [npc.she] reaches under the counter to grab a glass. Turning around and picking up a half-empty bottle of rum, [npc.she] pours your drink and then steps back, still leaving the money untouched on the counter-top.
		</p>
		<p>
			Picking up the glass, you quickly drink down the rum, before placing the now-empty vessel back down on the counter and preparing to move off. Before you can go, however, [npc.name] calls out for you stay, [npc.speech(Hey, why don't ya 'ang around a little longer? I's bettin' ya'd like ta earn that money o' yours back, wouldn't ya?)]
		</p>
		#IF(npc.hasPenis())
			<p>
				Looking down at the money still sitting on the counter, you ask [npc.name] what it is you'd have to do. Leaning forwards and grinning at you, [npc.she] says, [npc.speech(Well, wot with 'avin' ta work behind this 'ere bar all day long, I don't get much time fer gettin' me dick wet. If ya want yer money back, all ya 'ave ta do is come round 'ere an' get down on yer knees, then wrap yer pretty little mouth 'round me cock an' get ta suckin'. Let me blow a load down yer throat or over ya face, an' ya can 'ave yer money back.)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Looking down at the money still sitting on the counter, you ask [npc.name] what it is you'd have to do. Leaning forwards and grinning at you, [npc.she] says, [npc.speech(Well, wot with 'avin' ta work behind this 'ere bar all day long, me cunt don't get much attention. If ya want yer money back, all ya 'ave ta do is come round 'ere an' get down on yer knees, then open wide an' get ta eatin' me out. Once I've 'ad enough fun with yer tongue, ya can 'ave yer money back.)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DICE_DEN_RUM_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
			<p>
				Deciding that you're willing to suck [npc2.namePos] cock in order to get your flames back, you agree to do as [npc2.she] asks. Letting out a triumphant laugh, [npc2.she] says, [npc2.speech(Get round 'ere then an' drop down onto ya knees. Yer friend 'ere can come round an' watch as well!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Walking around to the end of the bar, you and [npc.name] step around behind it and move up to [npc2.name]. Doing as you're told, you drop down onto your knees in front of [npc2.herHim], while [npc.name] keeps [npc.her] distance and watches.
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(Get it out then, slut,)] [npc2.name] commands, and you obediently displace [npc2.her] clothing in order to allow [npc2.her] [npc2.cock+] to flop free in front of your face. Impatiently thrusting [npc2.her] hips forwards a little, [npc2.name] continues, [npc2.speech(Get me hard with yer tongue, slut, then ya can take me cock down yer throat.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Leaning in to [npc2.her] groin, you start licking [npc2.namePos] cock, and are rewarded for your efforts as it quickly stiffens to full erectness. Opening wide, you then wrap your [pc.lips+] around the head, before taking [npc2.her] throbbing length into your mouth and down your throat. As you start giving [npc2.name] a blowjob, [npc2.she] [npc2.moans], [npc2.speech(Good slut. Keep this up an' I'll be bustin' a nut down yer throat in no time!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Deciding that you're willing to perform cunnilingus on [npc2.name] in order to get your flames back, you agree to do as [npc2.she] asks. Letting out a triumphant laugh, [npc2.she] says, [npc2.speech(Get round 'ere then an' drop down onto ya knees. Yer friend 'ere can come round an' watch as well!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Walking around to the end of the bar, you and [npc.name] step around behind it and move up to [npc2.name]. Doing as you're told, you drop down onto your knees in front of [npc2.herHim], while [npc.name] keeps [npc.her] distance and watches.
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc2.speech(Get to it then, slut,)] [npc2.name] commands, and you obediently displace [npc2.her] clothing in order to gain access to [npc2.her] [npc2.pussy+]. Impatiently thrusting [npc2.her] hips forwards a little, [npc2.name] continues, [npc2.speech(Use yer tongue a bit first, slut, then ya can get tucked in an' start eatin' me out proper.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Leaning in to [npc2.her] groin, you do as you're instructed and start licking [npc2.namePos] [npc2.labia+], before teasing [npc2.her] clit with the tip of your tongue. Quickly wanting more than what you're giving to [npc2.herHim], [npc2.name] suddenly grabs the back of your head and pulls you into [npc2.her] groin. Finding your lips pressed up against [npc2.namePos] [npc2.pussy+], you start enthusiastically eating [npc2.herHim] out, causing [npc2.herHim] to [npc2.moanVerb] out from above, [npc2.speech(That's it, slut! Keep this up an' I'll be squirtin' all over ya face in no time!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF(npc.hasPenis())
			<p>
				Deciding that you're willing to suck [npc.namePos] cock in order to get your flames back, you agree to do as [npc.she] asks. Letting out a triumphant laugh, [npc.she] says, [npc.speech(Get round 'ere then an' drop down onto ya knees!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Walking around to the end of the bar, you step around behind it and move up to [npc.name]. Doing as you're told, you then drop down onto your knees in front of [npc.herHim].
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.speech(Get it out then, slut,)] [npc.name] commands, and you obediently displace [npc.her] clothing in order to allow [npc.her] [npc.cock+] to flop free in front of your face. Impatiently thrusting [npc.her] hips forwards a little, [npc.name] continues, [npc.speech(Get me hard with yer tongue, slut, then ya can take me cock down yer throat.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Leaning in to [npc.her] groin, you start licking [npc.namePos] cock, and are rewarded for your efforts as it quickly stiffens to full erectness. Opening wide, you then wrap your [pc.lips+] around the head, before taking [npc.her] throbbing length into your mouth and down your throat. As you start giving [npc.name] a blowjob, [npc.she] [npc.moans], [npc.speech(Good slut. Keep this up an' I'll be bustin' a nut down yer throat in no time!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Deciding that you're willing to perform cunnilingus on [npc.name] in order to get your flames back, you agree to do as [npc.she] asks. Letting out a triumphant laugh, [npc.she] says, [npc.speech(Get round 'ere then an' drop down onto ya knees!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Walking around to the end of the bar, you step around behind it and move up to [npc.name]. Doing as you're told, you then drop down onto your knees in front of [npc.herHim].
			</p>
			<p>
				[npc.speech(Get to it then, slut,)] [npc.name] commands, and you obediently displace [npc.her] clothing in order to gain access to [npc.her] [npc.pussy+]. Impatiently thrusting [npc.her] hips forwards a little, [npc.name] continues, [npc.speech(Use yer tongue a bit first, slut, then ya can get tucked in an' start eatin' me out proper.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Leaning in to [npc.her] groin, you do as you're instructed and start licking [npc.namePos] [npc.labia+], before teasing [npc.her] clit with the tip of your tongue. Quickly wanting more than what you're giving to [npc.herHim], [npc.name] suddenly grabs the back of your head and pulls you into [npc.her] groin. Finding your lips pressed up against [npc.namePos] [npc.pussy+], you start enthusiastically eating [npc.herHim] out, causing [npc.herHim] to [npc.moanVerb] out from above, [npc.speech(That's it, slut! Keep this up an' I'll be squirtin' all over ya face in no time!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DICE_DEN_RUM_ORAL_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
		<p>
			Thinking that it would be a good idea for [npc.name] to help you get your flames back, you turn to your companion and say, [pc.speech(Go on, [npc.name]. Suck [npc2.her] cock so that I can get those flames back.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(!npc.isAttractedTo(npc2))
				[npc.speech(Eugh... I really don't want to do this,)] [npc.name] protests, [npc.speech(but I guess I've got no choice, have I?)]
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Mmm, that sounds like fun,)] [npc.name] replies, [npc.speech(I wonder how big [npc2.she] is...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a triumphant laugh as [npc2.she] hears what it is the two of you are saying, [npc2.name] looks [npc.name] and commands, [npc2.speech(Get round 'ere then an' drop down onto ya knees. Yer friend 'ere can come round an' watch as well!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Walking around to the end of the bar, you and [npc.name] step around behind it and move up to [npc2.name]. Doing as [npc.sheIs] told, your companion drops down onto [npc.her] knees in front of the [npc2.race] while you keep your distance and watch.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Get it out then, slut,)] [npc2.name] commands. Doing as [npc.sheIs] told, [npc.name] quickly displaces [npc2.namePos] clothing, and after just a moment, [npc2.her] [npc2.cock+] flops free in front of your companion's face. Impatiently thrusting [npc2.her] hips forwards a little, [npc2.name] continues, [npc2.speech(Get me hard with yer tongue, slut, then ya can take me cock down yer throat.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Leaning in to [npc2.her] groin, [npc.name] starts licking [npc2.namePos] cock, and is rewarded for [npc.her] efforts as it quickly stiffens to full erectness. Opening wide, [npc.she] then wraps [npc.her] [npc.lips+] around the head, before taking the [npc2.race]'s throbbing length into [npc.her] mouth and down [npc.her] throat. As your companion starts giving [npc2.name] a blowjob, the [npc2.race] [npc2.moans], [npc2.speech(Good slut. Keep this up an' I'll be bustin' a nut down yer throat in no time!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Thinking that it would be a good idea for [npc.name] to help you get your flames back, you turn to your companion and say, [pc.speech(Go on, [npc.name]. Eat [npc2.herHim] out so that I can get those flames back.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(!npc.isAttractedTo(npc2))
				[npc.speech(Eugh... I really don't want to do this,)] [npc.name] protests, [npc.speech(but I guess I've got no choice, have I?)]
			#ELSE
				[npc.speech(Mmm, that sounds like fun,)] [npc.name] replies, [npc.speech(I can't wait to get a taste of [npc2.her] pussy...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a triumphant laugh as [npc2.she] hears what it is the two of you are saying, [npc2.name] looks [npc.name] and commands, [npc2.speech(Get round 'ere then an' drop down onto ya knees. Yer friend 'ere can come round an' watch as well!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Walking around to the end of the bar, you and [npc.name] step around behind it and move up to [npc2.name]. Doing as [npc.sheIs] told, your companion drops down onto [npc.her] knees in front of the [npc2.race] while you keep your distance and watch.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Get it out then, slut,)] [npc2.name] commands. Doing as [npc.sheIs] told, [npc.name] quickly displaces [npc2.namePos] clothing in order to gain access to [npc2.her] [npc2.pussy+]. Impatiently thrusting [npc2.her] hips forwards a little, [npc2.name] continues, [npc2.speech(Use yer tongue a bit first, slut, then ya can get tucked in an' start eatin' me out proper.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Leaning in to the [npc2.race]'s groin, [npc.name] does as [npc.sheIs] instructed and starts licking [npc2.namePos] [npc2.labia+], before teasing [npc2.her] clit with the tip of [npc.her] tongue. Quickly wanting more than what your companion is giving to [npc2.herHim], [npc2.name] suddenly grabs the back of [npc.namePos] head and pulls [npc.herHim] into [npc2.her] groin. Finding [npc.her] lips pressed up against [npc2.namePos] [npc2.pussy+], [npc.name] starts eating [npc2.herHim] out, causing the [npc2.race] to [npc2.moanVerb] out from above, [npc2.speech(That's it, slut! Keep this up an' I'll be squirtin' all over ya face in no time!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_DICE_DEN_ORAL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_DICE_DEN_ORAL_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
		<p>
			Letting out a satisfied sigh, [npc2.name] makes your companion lick the head of [npc2.her] [npc2.cock+] one last time before pushing [npc.herHim] away and sneering, [npc2.speech(Ya know how ta please a rat's cock, I'll give yer that!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Letting out a satisfied sigh, [npc2.name] makes your companion lick [npc2.her] sopping-wet pussy one last time before pushing [npc.herHim] away and sneering, [npc2.speech(Ya know how ta please a rat's cunt, I'll give yer that!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		As [npc.name] cleans [npc.herself] up a little, you walk around to the other side of the bar and collect the money which you paid for the glass of rum. After just a moment more, your companion walks around to return to your side, and after throwing [npc.her] a lustful grin, [npc2.name] turns to you and says, [npc2.speech(Ya welcome ta buy another drink whenever ya want! Perhaps next time yer gonna be the one who's down on yer knees, eh?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the [npc2.race]'s cackling laughter ringing out over the counter-top, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_DICE_DEN_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
			<p>
				Letting out a satisfied sigh, [npc2.name] makes you lick the head of [npc2.her] [npc2.cock+] one last time before pushing you away and sneering, [npc2.speech(Ya know how ta please a rat's cock, I'll give yer that!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Letting out a satisfied sigh, [npc2.name] makes you lick [npc2.her] sopping-wet pussy one last time before pushing you away and sneering, [npc2.speech(Ya know how ta please a rat's cunt, I'll give yer that!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			After cleaning yourself up a little, you walk around to the other side of the bar with [npc.name] and collect the money which you paid for the glass of rum. As you do this, [npc2.name] throws you a lustful grin and says, [npc2.speech(Ya welcome ta buy another drink whenever ya want!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With the [npc2.race]'s cackling laughter ringing out over the counter-top, you wonder what to do next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(npc.hasPenis())
			<p>
				Letting out a satisfied sigh, [npc.name] makes you lick the head of [npc.her] [npc.cock+] one last time before pushing you away and sneering, [npc.speech(Ya know how ta please a rat's cock, I'll give yer that!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Letting out a satisfied sigh, [npc.name] makes you lick [npc.her] sopping-wet pussy one last time before pushing you away and sneering, [npc.speech(Ya know how ta please a rat's cunt, I'll give yer that!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			After cleaning yourself up a little, you walk around to the other side of the bar and collect the money which you paid for the glass of rum. As you do this, [npc.name] throws you a lustful grin and says, [npc.speech(Ya welcome ta buy another drink whenever ya want!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With the [npc.race]'s cackling laughter ringing out over the counter-top, you wonder what to do next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MILKING_STORAGE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_STORAGE_CLEARED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Branching off from a twist in a particularly damp and dingy section of the Rat Warren's tunnels, you follow a narrow passageway which ends up leading into a relatively small, well-lit room. Judging by the fact that the high ceiling is home to many naturally-formed stalactites, while the walls and floor form a uniform rectangular shape, this area seems to have been carved out from a smaller pre-existing cave.
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking a look at your surroundings, you find that the most striking feature of this area is the dozens of metal milk-pails stacked up on shelving units against the walls. Over on the far side of the earth-packed floor, directly ahead of you, there's also an odd collection of old, tatty-looking furniture arrayed next to an old wooden door. A couple of worn, wooden tables are haphazardly surrounded by half a dozen stools and chairs, while pushed up against the far wall are several crates and cabinets. Finishing off this assortment of furnishings is an old, faded, red sofa, which, like the rest of the room, is absent of any sign of life.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you've cleared out the gang members from this section of the Rat Warrens, there's nothing stopping you from opening the old wooden door and heading through into the room beyond...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_STORAGE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkIntroduced))
		<p>
			Branching off from a twist in a particularly damp and dingy section of the Rat Warren's tunnels, you follow a narrow passageway which ends up leading into a relatively small, well-lit room. Judging by the fact that the high ceiling is home to many naturally-formed stalactites, while the walls and floor form a uniform rectangular shape, this area seems to have been carved out from a smaller pre-existing cave.
		</p>
		<p>
			Taking a look at your surroundings, you find that the most striking feature of this area is the dozens of metal milk-pails stacked up on shelving units against the walls. Over on the far side of the earth-packed floor, directly ahead of you, there's also an odd collection of old, tatty-looking furniture arrayed next to an old wooden door. A couple of worn, wooden tables are haphazardly surrounded by half a dozen stools and chairs, while pushed up against the far wall are several crates and cabinets. Finishing off this assortment of furnishings is an old, faded, red sofa, which catches your eye both due to its splash of colour, as well as due to there being a greater rat-boy sitting in the middle of it.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you catch sight of this resident gang member, you see that he's staring at you with an opportunistic gleam in his shifty yellow eyes. Reaching up to scratch the dark-brown fur covering his exposed, chubby belly, he lets out a loud belch before sliding off the sofa and starting to stroll towards you. Now standing fully upright, you see that this rat-boy is only around [murk.heightValue] tall, but as he walks towards you, you find yourself thinking not of his short stature, but instead of the fact that his black, crotchless chaps are leaving his genitals totally exposed.
		</p>
		<p>
			Although it's sheathed, and so impossible to know the erect length of it, the circumference of the rat-boy's withdrawn, pale-pink cock is absolutely huge. The pair of massive, heavy balls hanging down between his legs are also disproportionately large in relation to his height, and you can't help but glance at them as they ponderously swing from side to side in pace with his short stride.
		</p>
		<p>
			[murk.speechNoEffects('Ungry fer me fat cock, are ya?)] the rat-boy sneers at you in a slovenly tone as he catches you looking at his massive genitals. Looking you up and down, he lets out a tutting noise before continuing, [murk.speechNoEffects(I's gonna 'ave ta disappoint ya; me cock's reserved fer me milkers, so's I ain't gonna fuck ya no matter 'ow much ya beg.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Your 'milkers'?)] you ask, ignoring the foul-mannered rat-boy's other comments.
		</p>
		<p>
			[murk.speechNoEffects(Wot, ya ain't 'eard 'bout me milkers? Then I's guessin' ya don't know that me name's 'Murk' either, does ya?)] 'Murk' replies, but before you can answer, he continues, [murk.speechNoEffects(Well, ain't no issue if ya don't know who I is; this way ain't no cunt's gone an' given' ya the wrong impression o' me.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Wondering just how anyone could possibly be given a worse impression of Murk than how he is in reality, you continue to listen as he turns around and strolls back over to his sofa, shouting behind him as he goes, [murk.speechNoEffects(I's known 'round 'ere as bein' the guy ya need when ya wantin' ta 'ave a quick fuck but there ain't no rat sluts willin' ta do it with ya. I's got a collection o' humans who're willin' ta do anything I's tell 'em ta do, ya see, an' they're wot I call me milkers. Rats come 'ere, pay me, an' I let 'em fuck one o' me milkers.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Reaching his sofa, Murk spits on the ground before turning around and motioning to the milk pails stacked up against the walls. [murk.speechNoEffects(Me milkers provide a good income fer me; their milk sells fer a pretty penny up in the city. They's also real good at doin' milkin' themselves; milkin' me balls into their cunts that is! Heh-heh-heh!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Before you can think of what to say in response to this, the rat-boy jumps back up onto his sofa, and, leaning back and scratching his chubby belly once again, he says, [murk.speechNoEffects(It's five 'undred flames ta fuck one o' me milkers. They's through that door behind me, an' you's got ta pay up before ya gets ta see 'em. I's let ya choose which one ya want ta fuck, but there ain't no refunds if ya don't like any o' 'em, an' I's got a rule that only one o' you's can be fuckin' 'em at once, so yer friend 'ere is gonna 'ave ta watch. So, ya gonna pay up, or ya gonna go back the way ya came?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Branching off from a twist in a particularly damp and dingy section of the Rat Warren's tunnels, you once again follow the narrow passageway which leads into Murk's relatively small, well-lit milking storage room. Judging by the fact that the high ceiling is home to many naturally-formed stalactites, while the walls and floor form a uniform rectangular shape, you remark to yourself how this area seems to have been carved out from a smaller pre-existing cave.
		</p>
		<p>
			Taking a look at your surroundings, you find that the most striking feature of this area is the dozens of metal milk-pails stacked up on shelving units against the walls. Over on the far side of the earth-packed floor, directly ahead of you, there's also an odd collection of old, tatty-looking furniture arrayed next to an old wooden door. A couple of worn, wooden tables are haphazardly surrounded by half a dozen stools and chairs, while pushed up against the far wall are several crates and cabinets. Finishing off this assortment of furnishings is an old, faded, red sofa, which catches your eye both due to its splash of colour, as well as due to the fact that Murk is currently sitting in the middle of it.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you catch sight of the crass gang member, you see that he's staring at you with an opportunistic gleam in his shifty yellow eyes. Reaching up to scratch the dark-brown fur covering his exposed, chubby belly, he lets out a loud belch before spreading his legs a little and once again revealing that his black, crotchless chaps are leaving his disproportionately-huge balls and sheathed cock totally exposed.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
					Before you can say anything, the rat-boy calls out, [murk.speechNoEffects(It's gonna be five 'undred flames if ya want ta see me milkers again. Just as before, you's got ta pay up before ya gets ta see 'em. I's let ya choose which one ya want ta fuck, but there ain't no refunds if ya don't like any o' 'em, an' I's got a rule that only one o' you's can be fuckin' 'em at once, so yer friend 'ere is gonna 'ave ta watch. So, ya gonna pay up, or ya gonna go back the way ya came?)]
				#ELSE
					Before you can say anything, the rat-boy calls out, [murk.speechNoEffects(It's gonna be five 'undred flames if ya want ta see me milkers again. Just as before, you's got ta pay up before ya gets ta see 'em. I's let ya choose which one ya want ta fuck, but there ain't no refunds if ya don't like any o' 'em. So, ya gonna pay up, or ya gonna go back the way ya came?)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
					Before you can say anything, the rat-boy calls out, [murk.speechNoEffects(It's still gonna be five 'undred flames ta fuck one o' me milkers. They's through that door behind me, an' you's got ta pay up before ya gets ta see 'em. I's let ya choose which one ya want ta fuck, but there ain't no refunds if ya don't like any o' 'em, an' I's got a rule that only one o' you's can be fuckin' 'em at once, so yer friend 'ere is gonna 'ave ta watch. So, ya gonna pay up, or ya gonna go back the way ya came?)]
				#ELSE
					Before you can say anything, the rat-boy calls out, [murk.speechNoEffects(It's still gonna be five 'undred flames ta fuck one o' me milkers. They's through that door behind me, an' you's got ta pay up before ya gets ta see 'em. I's let ya choose which one ya want ta fuck, but there ain't no refunds if ya don't like any o' 'em. So, ya gonna pay up, or ya gonna go back the way ya came?)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_STORAGE_CAPTIVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thanks to your bedding being closest to the door to the milking storage room, you find that you're able to get quite close to it before the solid chain binding your collar to your milking stall reaches its furthest extent. As you're not actually able to reach the door, however, all you can do for now is return to your bedding...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_STORAGE_CHALLENGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not willing to endure Murk's offensive presence for a single moment longer than you have to, you step forwards and tell him that you're here to put an end to his evildoings.
	</p>
	<p>
		As the rat-boy realises that you intend to fight him, the smirk is instantly wiped off his face, and with eyes wide in fear, he jumps off his sofa and bolts over to one of the larger cabinets placed up against the wall. Not expecting the chubby rat-boy to be capable of such a burst of speed, you're taken a little off-guard and aren't able to stop him in time before he grabs one side of the cabinet and pulls it crashing to the ground. Murk's unexpected move reveals the entrance to a hidden tunnel, and it's into this cramped, dark passageway that he frantically bolts.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Rushing over to try and catch him before he's able to get too far, you and [npc.name] quickly cross the room and prepare to enter the tunnel yourselves.
		#ELSE
			Rushing over to try and catch him before he's able to get too far, you quickly cross the room and prepare to enter the tunnel yourself.
		#ENDIF
		 Just as you get there, however, a metallic clang suddenly rings out from behind you. Spinning around, you see a couple of milk pails rolling across the floor, followed quickly by Murk as he hastily exits through yet another concealed entrance to his escape tunnel.
	</p>
	<p>
		Rushing off into the Rat Warrens, Murk half-shouts, half-screams at the top of his lungs, [murk.speechNoEffects('Elp! 'Elp! Get over 'ere an' 'elp me!)] 
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Although you and [npc.name] are able to quite quickly catch up with him, Murk's cries end up attracting the attention of numerous rats who, fortuitously for the chubby rat-boy, must have been loitering nearby. As you and your companion come to halt in the passageway and prepare to defend yourselves, Murk cries out, [murk.speechNoEffects(You's lot! These two cunts are tryin' ta attack me! Beat 'em down an' I'll give yer all a free fuck with me milkers!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Obviously liking the sound of Murk's offer, the rats quickly advance on you and [npc.name]. With this new threat demanding all of your attention, Murk shows his cowardly nature once again by slipping past and running off into the tunnels, leaving his comrades to deal with the two of you without his help...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Although you're able to quite quickly catch up with him, Murk's cries end up attracting the attention of numerous rats who, fortuitously for the chubby rat-boy, must have been loitering nearby. As you come to halt in the passageway and prepare to defend yourself, Murk cries out, [murk.speechNoEffects(You's lot! This cunt is tryin' ta attack me! Beat 'em down an' I'll give yer all a free fuck with me milkers!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Obviously liking the sound of Murk's offer, the rats quickly advance on you. With this new threat demanding all of your attention, Murk shows his cowardly nature once again by slipping past and running off into the tunnels, leaving his comrades to deal with you without his help...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	
	<!-- MILKING_ROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_ROOM"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				Wanting to gain access to the milking room again, you tell Murk that you and [npc.name] would like to have some fun with his milkers. The rat-boy's face turns up into a grin as he hears you say this, and after rudely spitting on the floor, he sneers, [murk.speechNoEffects(Ya gots the five 'undred flames then, huh? You's two ain't gettin any o' me milkers' pussy without payin' me first!)]
			#ELSE
				Wanting to find out who these 'milkers' are, you tell Murk that you and [npc.name] would like to see them. The rat-boy's face turns up into a grin as he hears you say this, and after rudely spitting on the floor, he sneers, [murk.speechNoEffects(Ya gots the five 'undred flames then, huh? You's two ain't gettin any o' me milkers' pussy without payin' me first!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Producing the money which Murk is asking for, you hand over the five hundred flames. Snatching the coins and hurrying over to put them away in a nearby chest, the rat-boy then walks over to the nearby wooden door, before pushing it open and stepping through. Calling over his shoulder, he shouts, [murk.speechNoEffects(Come on then, you's two! I ain't got all day!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				Following the chubby rat-boy into the narrow room beyond, you're greeted by the familiar sight of the long series of metal-framed stalls running down the left-hand wall. Just like the last time you were here, out of the six wall-facing stalls which you count, the four furthest from the door are currently occupied by busty human females, who all start desperately crying out for Murk as they hear you enter.
			#ELSE
				Following the rat-boy through the doorway, the first thing which you immediately notice about the room beyond is that its proportions are more akin to a wide corridor than a conventional square or rectangular shape. The very next thing you register is that running down alongside the left-hand wall, there are a series of metal-framed stalls, each consisting of a padded bench plus surrounding supports to which an occupant's legs or arms can be chained. Out of the six wall-facing stalls which you count, the four furthest from the door are currently occupied by busty human females, who all start desperately crying out for Murk as they hear you enter.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Master! Please, fill my pussy!)] one of them whines.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc4.speech(Please, master! I need your cock!)] the one beside the first cries out.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Shut it, ya milker sluts! One o' you's is gonna be fucked by someone else this time!)] Murk shouts out, causing the four milkers to quieten down. They don't completely stop making a noise, however, as each one of them settles into letting out a series of subdued, horny moans. As Murk leads you and [npc.name] towards the occupied stalls, you see the cause of the milkers' lewd background noise taking the familiar form of an arcane-powered milking machine positioned beside each one of them.
			#ELSE
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Shut it, ya milker sluts! One o' you's is gonna be fucked by someone else this time!)] Murk shouts out, causing the four 'milkers' to quieten down. They don't completely stop making a noise, however, as each one of them settles into letting out a series of subdued, horny moans. As Murk leads you and [npc.name] towards the occupied stalls, you see the cause of the milkers' lewd background noise taking the form of an arcane-powered milking machine positioned beside each one of them.
			#ENDIF
			 Leading back into these machines via a long tube, steadily-pumping suction cups have been attached over each of the milkers' puffy, milk-dripping nipples,
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
					 while a pair of fat, rhythmically-vibrating dildos have been firmly inserted into each of their pussies and assholes. Making his way from one milker to another, Murk pulls these dildos out and drops them to the floor, revealing that every one of the milkers' holes are not only dripping wet, but have also been permanently stretched open.
				#ELSE
					 while a pair of thick, rhythmically-vibrating dildos have been firmly inserted into each of their dripping pussies and assholes. Making his way from one milker to another, Murk pulls these dildos out and drops them to the floor, revealing that every one of the milkers' holes are dripping wet and ready for penetration.
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
					 while a fat, rhythmically-vibrating dildo has been firmly inserted into each of their dripping, stretched-out pussies. Making his way from one milker to another, Murk pulls these dildos out and drops them to the floor, revealing that every one of the milkers' cunts are not only dripping wet, but have also been permanently stretched open.
				#ELSE
					 while a thick, rhythmically-vibrating dildo has been firmly inserted into each of their dripping pussies. Making his way from one milker to another, Murk pulls these dildos out and drops them to the floor, revealing that every one of the milkers' cunts are dripping wet and ready for penetration.
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
				Quickly finishing his task of freeing up all their holes, Murk pushes several of his fingers into the loose pussy of the nearest milker, causing her to let out a desperate moan. Pulling his now-wet fingers back, the rat-boy delivers a sharp slap on the her rear end, before turning towards you and sneering, [murk.speechNoEffects(I 'ope ya don't mind 'ow I've gone an' gaped their 'oles so as ta fit me fat cock! So, which one o' these sluts  ya lookin' ta fuck? Remember, I's got the rule that on;y one o' ya can be fuckin' 'em at once, so decide between ya which one o' ya is gonna be watchin' the other doin' the fuckin'. Oh, an' if ya change yer mind an' think these 'oles ain't tight enough ta satisfy ya, then just ya remember that there ain't no refunds!)]
			#ELSE
				Quickly finishing his task of freeing up all their holes, Murk pushes several of his fingers into the dripping-wet pussy of the nearest milker, causing her to let out a desperate moan. Pulling his now-wet fingers back, the rat-boy delivers a sharp slap on the her rear end, before turning towards you and sneering, [murk.speechNoEffects(I 'ope ya don't mind knowin' that I've fucked these 'oles more time than I's able ta count! So, which one o' these sluts ya lookin' ta fuck? Remember, I's got the rule that on;y one o' ya can be fuckin' 'em at once, so decide between ya which one o' ya is gonna be watchin' the other doin' the fuckin'. Oh, an' if ya change yer mind an' think these 'oles ain't appealin' to ya, then just ya remember that there ain't no refunds!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				Wanting to gain access to the milking room again, you tell Murk that you'd like to have some fun with his milkers. The rat-boy's face turns up into a grin as he hears you say this, and after rudely spitting on the floor, he sneers, [murk.speechNoEffects(Ya gots the five 'undred flames then, huh? Ya ain't gettin any o' me milkers' pussy without payin' me first!)]
			#ELSE
				Wanting to find out who these 'milkers' are, you tell Murk that you'd like to see them. The rat-boy's face turns up into a grin as he hears you say this, and after rudely spitting on the floor, he sneers, [murk.speechNoEffects(Ya gots the five 'undred flames then, huh? Ya ain't gettin any o' me milkers' pussy without payin' me first!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Producing the money which Murk is asking for, you hand over the five hundred flames. Snatching the coins and hurrying over to put them away in a nearby chest, the rat-boy then walks over to the nearby wooden door, before pushing it open and stepping through. Calling over his shoulder, he shouts, [murk.speechNoEffects(Come on then! I ain't got all day!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				Following the chubby rat-boy into the narrow room beyond, you're greeted by the familiar sight of the long series of metal-framed stalls running down the left-hand wall. Just like the last time you were here, out of the six wall-facing stalls which you count, the four furthest from the door are currently occupied by busty human females, who all start desperately crying out for Murk as they hear you enter.
			#ELSE
				Following the rat-boy through the doorway, the first thing which you immediately notice about the room beyond is that its proportions are more akin to a wide corridor than a conventional square or rectangular shape. The very next thing you register is that running down alongside the left-hand wall, there are a series of metal-framed stalls, each consisting of a padded bench plus surrounding supports to which an occupant's legs or arms can be chained. Out of the six wall-facing stalls which you count, the four furthest from the door are currently occupied by busty human females, who all start desperately crying out for Murk as they hear you enter.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Master! Please, fill my pussy!)] one of them whines.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc4.speech(Please, master! I need your cock!)] the one beside the first cries out.
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Shut it, ya milker sluts! One o' you's is gonna be fucked by someone else this time!)] Murk shouts out, causing the four milkers to quieten down. They don't completely stop making a noise, however, as each one of them settles into letting out a series of subdued, horny moans. As Murk leads you and [npc.name] towards the occupied stalls, you see the cause of the milkers' lewd background noise taking the familiar form of an arcane-powered milking machine positioned beside each one of them.
			#ELSE
				[murk.speechNoEffects(Shut it, ya milker sluts! One o' you's is gonna be fucked by someone else this time!)] Murk shouts out, causing the four 'milkers' to quieten down. They don't completely stop making a noise, however, as each one of them settles into letting out a series of subdued, horny moans. As Murk leads you and [npc.name] towards the occupied stalls, you see the cause of the milkers' lewd background noise taking the form of an arcane-powered milking machine positioned beside each one of them.
			#ENDIF
			 Leading back into these machines via a long tube, steadily-pumping suction cups have been attached over each of the milkers' puffy, milk-dripping nipples,
			#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
				#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
					 while a pair of fat, rhythmically-vibrating dildos have been firmly inserted into each of their pussies and assholes. Making his way from one milker to another, Murk pulls these dildos out and drops them to the floor, revealing that every one of the milkers' holes are not only dripping wet, but have also been permanently stretched open.
				#ELSE
					 while a pair of thick, rhythmically-vibrating dildos have been firmly inserted into each of their dripping pussies and assholes. Making his way from one milker to another, Murk pulls these dildos out and drops them to the floor, revealing that every one of the milkers' holes are dripping wet and ready for penetration.
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
					 while a fat, rhythmically-vibrating dildo has been firmly inserted into each of their dripping, stretched-out pussies. Making his way from one milker to another, Murk pulls these dildos out and drops them to the floor, revealing that every one of the milkers' cunts are not only dripping wet, but have also been permanently stretched open.
				#ELSE
					 while a thick, rhythmically-vibrating dildo has been firmly inserted into each of their dripping pussies. Making his way from one milker to another, Murk pulls these dildos out and drops them to the floor, revealing that every one of the milkers' cunts are dripping wet and ready for penetration.
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
				Quickly finishing his task of freeing up all their holes, Murk pushes several of his fingers into the loose pussy of the nearest milker, causing her to let out a desperate moan. Pulling his now-wet fingers back, the rat-boy delivers a sharp slap on the her rear end, before turning towards you and sneering, [murk.speechNoEffects(I 'ope ya don't mind 'ow I've gone an' gaped their 'oles so as ta fit me fat cock! So, which one o' these sluts ya lookin' ta fuck? Oh, an' if ya change yer mind an' think these 'oles ain't tight enough ta satisfy ya, then just ya remember that there ain't no refunds!)]
			#ELSE
				Quickly finishing his task of freeing up all their holes, Murk pushes several of his fingers into the dripping-wet pussy of the nearest milker, causing her to let out a desperate moan. Pulling his now-wet fingers back, the rat-boy delivers a sharp slap on the her rear end, before turning towards you and sneering, [murk.speechNoEffects(I 'ope ya don't mind knowin' that I've fucked these 'oles more time than I's able ta count! So, which one o' these sluts ya lookin' ta fuck? Oh, an' if ya change yer mind an' think these 'oles ain't appealin' to ya, then just ya remember that there ain't no refunds!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_ROOM_CLEARED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensSeenMilkers))
			Heading through the old wooden door into the 'milking room', you're once again greeted by the familiar sight of the long series of metal-framed stalls running down the left-hand wall. Just like the last time you were here, out of the six wall-facing stalls which you count, the four furthest from the door are currently occupied by busty human females, who all start desperately crying out for
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkIntroduced))
				 Murk
			#ELSE
				 their 'master'
			#ENDIF
			 as they hear you enter.
		#ELSE
			Curious to see what exactly is behind the wooden door on the far side of the room, you head over to it and push it open. Stepping through into the room beyond, the first thing which you immediately notice is that its proportions are more akin to a wide corridor than a conventional square or rectangular shape. The very next thing you register is that running down alongside the left-hand wall, there are a series of metal-framed stalls, each consisting of a padded bench plus surrounding supports to which an occupant's legs or arms can be chained. Out of the six wall-facing stalls which you count, the four furthest from the door are currently occupied by busty human females, who all start desperately crying out for
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkIntroduced))
				 Murk
			#ELSE
				 their 'master'
			#ENDIF
			 as they hear you enter.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Master! Please, fill my pussy!)] one of them whines.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc3.speech(Please, master! I need your cock!)] the one beside the first cries out.
	</p>
	<p>
		Craning their necks to see why their master hasn't replied to their cries, the four 'milkers' start to quieten down as they see#IF(pc.hasCompanions()) you and [npc.name]#ELSE you#ENDIF standing there instead. They don't completely stop making a noise, however, as each one of them settles into letting out a series of subdued, horny moans. As you start to move towards the occupied stalls, you see the cause of the milkers' lewd background noise taking the familiar form of an arcane-powered milking machine positioned beside each one of them. Leading back into these machines via a long tube, steadily-pumping suction cups have been attached over each of the milkers' puffy, milk-dripping nipples,
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
				 while a pair of fat, rhythmically-vibrating dildos have been firmly inserted into each of their pussies and assholes.
			#ELSE
				 while a pair of thick, rhythmically-vibrating dildos have been firmly inserted into each of their dripping pussies and assholes.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
				 while a fat, rhythmically-vibrating dildo has been firmly inserted into each of their dripping, stretched-out pussies.
			#ELSE
				 while a thick, rhythmically-vibrating dildo has been firmly inserted into each of their dripping pussies.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		With nobody here to stop you,#IF(pc.hasCompanions()) you and [npc.name]#ELSE you#ENDIF could quite easily have some fun with one or more of these milkers. Then again, you could always just turn around and leave, or even try to free them...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_ROOM_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Deciding that you want to fuck [npc2.name], you step up behind [npc2.herHim] and give [npc2.her] [npc2.ass+] a squeeze, causing [npc2.herHim] to let out [npc2.a_moan+]. Seeing which of his milkers you've chosen, Murk steps back and remarks, [murk.speechNoEffects(Ya gonna enjoy fuckin' this 'un; she always squeals the loudest when I's fillin' 'er with me fat cock!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Telling [npc.name] to stand back and watch, you prepare to start getting your money's worth out of [npc2.name]...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Deciding that you want to fuck [npc.name], you step up behind [npc.herHim] and give [npc.her] [npc.ass+] a squeeze, causing [npc.herHim] to let out [npc.a_moan+]. Seeing which of his milkers you've chosen, Murk steps back and remarks, [murk.speechNoEffects(Ya gonna enjoy fuckin' this 'un; she always squeals the loudest when I's fillin' 'er with me fat cock!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Ignoring Murk's comment, you prepare to start getting your money's worth out of [npc.name]...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_ROOM_SEX_AFTER_CLEARED"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Deciding that you want to fuck [npc2.name], you step up behind [npc2.herHim] and give [npc2.her] [npc2.ass+] a squeeze, causing [npc2.herHim] to let out [npc2.a_moan+]. Telling [npc.name] to stand back and watch, you prepare to start having some fun with [npc2.name]...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Deciding that you want to fuck [npc.name], you step up behind [npc.herHim] and give [npc.her] [npc.ass+] a squeeze, causing [npc.herHim] to let out [npc.a_moan+]. With nobody here to stop you, you prepare to start having some fun with [npc.herHim]...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_ROOM_SEX_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you want to watch [npc.name] fuck [npc2.name], you move into a position from which you can see everything that's going to be going on and then tell your companion to get to it.
		#IF(!npc.isAttractedTo(npc2))
			 Letting out a disgruntled sigh, [npc.name] reluctantly moves forwards, muttering, [npc.speech(I suppose I don't have a choice...)]
		#ELSE
			 Letting out an eager [npc.moan], [npc.name] quickly moves forwards, exclaiming, [npc.speech(Oh, this is going to be fun!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing which of his milkers [npc.name] is about to fuck, Murk steps back and remarks, [murk.speechNoEffects(Ya gonna enjoy playin' with this 'un; she always squeals the loudest when I's fillin' 'er with me fat cock!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_ROOM_SEX_COMPANION_AFTER_CLEARED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you want to watch [npc.name] fuck [npc2.name], you move into a position from which you can see everything that's going to be going on and then tell your companion to get to it.
		#IF(!npc.isAttractedTo(npc2))
			 Letting out a disgruntled sigh, [npc.name] reluctantly moves forwards, muttering, [npc.speech(I suppose I don't have a choice...)]
		#ELSE
			 Letting out an eager [npc.moan], [npc.name] quickly moves forwards, exclaiming, [npc.speech(Oh, this is going to be fun!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_ROOM_SEX_BOTH_AFTER_CLEARED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you want [npc.name] to join you in fucking [npc2.name], you move into a position behind the moaning milker and then tell your companion to move around to [npc2.her] front.
		#IF(!npc.isAttractedTo(npc2))
			 Letting out a disgruntled sigh, [npc.name] reluctantly moves forwards, muttering, [npc.speech(I suppose I don't have a choice...)]
		#ELSE
			 Letting out an eager [npc.moan], [npc.name] quickly moves forwards, exclaiming, [npc.speech(Oh, this is going to be fun!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Reaching down to give [npc2.namePos] [npc2.ass+] a squeeze, you smile as [npc2.she] responds by letting out [npc2.a_moan+]. As soon as [npc.name] gets into position, you get started on using the horny milker...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_ROOM_CHALLENGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not willing to endure Murk's offensive presence for a single moment longer than you have to, you step forwards and tell him that you're here to put an end to his evildoings.
	</p>
	<p>
		As the rat-boy realises that you intend to fight him, the smirk is instantly wiped off his face, and with eyes wide in fear, he bolts past you and dashes towards the door through which you entered. Not expecting the chubby rat-boy to be capable of such a burst of speed, you're taken a little off-guard and aren't able to stop him in time before he manages to escape back out into the milk storage room.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Rushing to try and catch him before he's able to get too far, you and [npc.name] pursue Murk past his tatty old red sofa, across the room, and into the Rat Warren's tunnels.
		#ELSE
			Rushing to try and catch him before he's able to get too far, you pursue Murk past his tatty old red sofa, across the room, and into the Rat Warren's tunnels.
		#ENDIF
		 Despite his initial burst of speed, Murk turns out to be not nearly as fast as you are, and as he realises that you're about to catch him, he half-shouts, half-screams at the top of his lungs, [murk.speechNoEffects('Elp! 'Elp! Get over 'ere an' 'elp me!)] 
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Murk's cries end up attracting the attention of numerous rats who, fortuitously for the chubby rat-boy, must have been loitering nearby. As you and your companion come to halt in the passageway and prepare to defend yourselves, Murk cries out, [murk.speechNoEffects(You's lot! These two cunts are tryin' ta attack me! Beat 'em down an' I'll give yer all a free fuck with me milkers!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Obviously liking the sound of Murk's offer, the rats quickly advance on you and [npc.name]. With this new threat demanding all of your attention, Murk shows his cowardly nature once again by slipping past and running off into the tunnels, leaving his comrades to deal with the two of you without his help...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Murk's cries end up attracting the attention of numerous rats who, fortuitously for the chubby rat-boy, must have been loitering nearby. As you come to halt in the passageway and prepare to defend yourself, Murk cries out, [murk.speechNoEffects(You's lot! This cunt is tryin' ta attack me! Beat 'em down an' I'll give yer all a free fuck with me milkers!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Obviously liking the sound of Murk's offer, the rats quickly advance on you. With this new threat demanding all of your attention, Murk shows his cowardly nature once again by slipping past and running off into the tunnels, leaving his comrades to deal with you without his help...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_MILKER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_MILKER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		If orgasmed, then when stop you see Murk finish fucking one of the other milkers. Their tongue lolling out, they are completely lost in bliss as Murk fills their gaping pussy with cum. Gets off them and plugs their pussy with the vibrating dildo again.
		You finish with [npc.name], and step away from [npc.herHim]. Murk approaches and says he'll have to fuck [npc.herHim] later so that [npc.she] remembers who [npc.her] real owner is. Tells you to follow him back into the storage room.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_MILKER_SEX_CLEARED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You finish with [npc.name], and step away from [npc.herHim]. As you've cleared this section of the Rat Warrens out, there's nothing stopping you from choosing another milker to fuck next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_MILKER_SEX_CHALLENGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Murk that these girls are yours now, and move to attack him. He calls for help, and some rats come charging in.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_MILKER_SEX_FINISHED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_MILKER_SEX_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You follow Murk back into the storage room. He says if you want another fuck, you know how much it is.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MILKING_ROOM_BACKGROUND -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_ROOM_BACKGROUND"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Shows how loyal they all are (if non-con enabled, make reference of how he kidnapped them as humans and transformed them into his milking sluts). If gape content is on, he says you'll have to deal with their loose holes; his cock has stretched them out nicely to his size...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MILKING_ROOM_FREE_ATTEMPT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKING_ROOM_FREE_ATTEMPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You try to free the captives, but they don't want to be freed, and just keep asking to be milked and fucked. You'll have to deal with them later...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Huge stone hall. A dozen long, wooden tables. At the far end, a raised dais, with a throne sitting atop it.
	</p>
	<p>
		If hostile, the rats you beat are here (and Murk, if introduced), they throw insults at you, but are too scared to fight. Vengar calls out that you're going to see what they do to busybodies like you.<br/>
		If not hostile, Vengar calls out for you to come forwards.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You approach the throne.
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_ratWarrensHostile))
		<p>
			Vengar says he thinks after you're beaten, he'll turn you into his rat-girl fucktoy. Introduce Silence, with Vengar saying she'll be more than enough to deal with you.
			#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
				#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_OBSERVANT))
					 You see Shadow sneaking up behind you, and manage to prevent her from launching a surprise attack.
				#ELSEIF(npc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_OBSERVANT))
					 [npc.Name] sees Shadow sneaking up behind you, and manages to prevent her from launching a surprise attack.
				#ELSE
					 Shadow sneaks up behind [npc.name] and stabs [npc.herHim] in the back with her ethereal poison blades!
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_OBSERVANT))
					 You see Shadow sneaking up behind you, and manage to prevent her from launching a surprise attack.
				#ELSE
					 Shadow sneaks up behind you and stabs you in the back with her ethereal poison blades!
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Vengar calls out to ask who you are and what you want. You see Shadow and Silence lurking to one side of the room near Vengar.
		</p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_vengarIntroduced))
			<p>
				#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_axelSissified))
					He asks if you'd like to join him in his private bed-chambers, or perhaps the two of you could go and visit Lexa together.
				#ELSE
					He asks if you'd like to join him in his private bed-chambers.
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_FIGHT_SURPRISED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You manage to twist out of Shadow's grip. She sadistically laughs and says how she loves it when people scream. Stepping over to Silence, she says that the two of them will destroy you. Silence just nods.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_FIGHT_SURPRISED_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You move to help your companion get out of Shadow's grip. She twists away, sadistically laughing, and says how she loves it when people scream. Stepping over to Silence, she says that the two of them will destroy you. Silence just nods.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_FIGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping over to Silence, Shadow says that the two of them will destroy you. Silence just nods.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_CHALLENGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Vengar that you're here to fight him. He says you'll have to get through his bodyguards first.
	</p>
	<p>
		Shadow and Silence step forwards. Shadow says that the two of them will destroy you. Silence just nods.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You try to convince Vengar to stop extorting Submission's honest businessfolk. He asks why he should listen to someone who clearly doesn't know their place. Demands that you either pay [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames to keep your dignity, or kneel before him (with companion, if applicable) to show everyone that you're submissive to him.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_REFUSE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You refuse to do either. Enraged, Vengar says that you're going to submit whether you like it or not. Bodyguards step forwards to fight you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_PAY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_PAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to take the non-violent approach, and unwilling to kneel to him, you pay Vengar the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames. He reveals that he was intending to stop illegal activities and focus on the rum distillery business that he 'acquired' a few months ago.
	</p>
	<p>
		Says that before he can do this, he needs the more powerful shop keepers to come and show their submission, otherwise his gang members will lose respect. Now that you've decided on this course of action, you suppose that convincing Axel to come and do this is acceptable.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_PAY_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Vengar that you'll do as he asks, before leaving the hall.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_KNEEL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_KNEEL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You (and companion) step up in front of Vengar and kneel down before him. Grinning in delight, he demands that you get down on all fours and act as his footrest.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_KNEEL_REFUSE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You refuse to do something so humiliating, and tell him no. Enraged, Vengar says that you're going to submit whether you like it or not. Bodyguards step forwards to fight you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_KNEEL_SUBMIT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_KNEEL_SUBMIT_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You (and companion) kneel down before Vengar. He demands that you turn to face the hall, so he can look at your ass.
	</p>
	<p>
		Puts his feet up on you (and companion) while rats in hall laugh and jeer at you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_BOTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After a while of being humiliated like this, Vengar takes his feet off, before leaning forwards and grabbing your and companion's asses. Rubbing his thumb over your asshole/pussy, he says that he can tell you want to really show your submission. Orders you both to expose yourselves and raise your asses so that he can fuck you in front of everyone.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_COMPANION_WATCHING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After a while of being humiliated like this, Vengar takes his feet off, before leaning forwards and grabbing your ass. Annoyed that your companion cannot be exposed. Rubbing his thumb over your asshole/pussy, he says that he can tell you want to really show your submission. Orders you to expose yourself and raise your ass so that he can fuck you in front of everyone. Says to your companion that [npc.she] can watch.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_SOLO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After a while of being humiliated like this, Vengar takes his feet off, before leaning forwards and grabbing your ass. Rubbing his thumb over your asshole/pussy, he says that he can tell you want to really show your submission. Orders you to expose yourself and raise your ass so that he can fuck you in front of everyone.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_PLAYER_WATCHING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After a while of being humiliated like this, Vengar takes his feet off, before leaning forwards and grabbing your companion's ass. Annoyed that you cannot be exposed. Rubbing his thumb over [npc.namePos] asshole/pussy, he says that he can tell [npc.she] wants to really show [npc.her] submission. Orders [npc.herHim] to expose [npc.herself] and raise [npc.her] ass so that he can fuck [npc.her] in front of everyone. Says to you that you can watch.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_NO_ACCESS_NO_NTR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After a while of being humiliated like this, Vengar takes his feet off, before saying that he's annoyed you can't be fucked.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_NO_ACCESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After a while of being humiliated like this, Vengar takes his feet off, before saying that he's annoyed that neither of you can be fucked.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_NO_ACCESS_SOLO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After a while of being humiliated like this, Vengar takes his feet off, before saying that he's annoyed you can't be fucked.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_NO_ACCESS_FINISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Vengar tells you (and companion, if applicable) to get up, before revealing that he was intending to stop illegal activities and focus on the rum distillery business that he 'acquired' a few months ago.
	</p>
	<p>
		Says that before he can do this, he needs the more powerful shop keepers to come and show their submission, otherwise his gang members will lose respect. Now that you've decided on this course of action, you suppose that convincing Axel to come and do this is acceptable.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_PLAYER_WATCHING_REFUSE_FINISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Vengar that you're not going to let him fuck [npc.name] in front of everyone, and that you've already done what he asked of you. He laughs but doesn't press the issue. Reveals that he was intending to stop illegal activities and focus on the rum distillery business that he 'acquired' a few months ago.
	</p>
	<p>
		Says that before he can do this, he needs the more powerful shop keepers to come and show their submission, otherwise his gang members will lose respect. Now that you've decided on this course of action, you suppose that convincing Axel to come and do this is acceptable.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_PLAYER_WATCHING_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't bring yourself to object.
		<br/>If companion attracted to Vengar: From the speed and enthusiasm which [npc.name] exposes [npc.herself] to Vengar, [npc.she] also doesn't seem opposed to the idea.
		<br/>If not, [npc.she] reluctantly goes along with it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Vengar exposes his rapidly-hardening cock, before taunting you and starting to fuck your companion. All you can do is join the rest of the hall's occupants in watching...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_REFUSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Vengar that you're not going to let him fuck you (and companion, if applicable) in front of everyone, and that you've already done what he asked of you. He laughs but doesn't press the issue. Reveals that he was intending to stop illegal activities and focus on the rum distillery business that he 'acquired' a few months ago.
	</p>
	<p>
		Says that before he can do this, he needs the more powerful shop keepers to come and show their submission, otherwise his gang members will lose respect. Now that you've decided on this course of action, you suppose that convincing Axel to come and do this is acceptable.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_SOLO_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		If companion dialogue, get companion to stand back and watch. Expose yourself to Vengar as he ordered.
	</p>
	<p>
		Vengar exposes his rapidly-hardening cock, before (taunting companion, if applicable, and) starting to fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_PLAYER_OFFER_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You say that he can fuck your companion, but not you.
		<br/>If companion attracted to Vengar: From the speed and enthusiasm which [npc.name] exposes [npc.herself] to Vengar, [npc.she] also doesn't seem opposed to the idea.
		<br/>If not, [npc.she] reluctantly goes along with it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Vengar exposes his rapidly-hardening cock, before taunting you and starting to fuck your companion. All you can do is join the rest of the hall's occupants in watching...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_SEX_DOUBLE_CHOICE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_SEX_DOUBLE_CHOICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell your companion to go along with it, and expose yourself to Vengar.
		<br/>If companion attracted to Vengar: From the speed and enthusiasm which [npc.name] exposes [npc.herself] to Vengar, [npc.she] also doesn't seem opposed to the idea.
		<br/>If not, [npc.she] reluctantly goes along with it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Vengar exposes his rapidly-hardening cock, before rubbing it over your ass/pussy and then your companion's. Says that you can eat [npc.name] out while he fucks you, getting [npc.her] ready for his second load, or the other way around (factoring in mouth access).
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_BOTH_PLAYER_FIRST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You push back against Vengar's cock, signalling that you want to be fucked first. If able, he tells your companion to receive oral from you. Makes you beg, then starts fucking you. If available, companion gets you to start oral on [npc.herHim].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_BOTH_COMPANION_FIRST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You shuffle away from Vengar's cock, signalling that you want to be fucked second. If able, he tells your companion to perform oral on you. Makes [npc.her] beg, then starts fucking [npc.herHim]. If available, companion starts oral on you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_AFTER_SEX_DOUBLE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_AFTER_SEX_DOUBLE_PLAYER_NEXT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having been prepared by your companion, Vengar slides his fingers into you, before declaring you ready for his cock. If able, companion is told to present you with Vengar's creampie. If not, they watch.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_AFTER_SEX_DOUBLE_COMPANION_NEXT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having been prepared by your tongue, Vengar slides his fingers into your companion, before declaring [npc.herHim] ready for his cock. If able, you are told to present your companion with Vengar's creampie. If not, you watch.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_BOTH_PLAYER_SECOND_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Vengar teases, then slides into you. If able, companion is set about receiving oral from you, eating out Vengar's creampie. If not, they watch.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_SUB_SEX_BOTH_COMPANION_SECOND_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Vengar teases, then slides into [npc.name]. If able, you are set about receiving oral from your companion, eating out Vengar's creampie. If not, you watch.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Vengar is finished. Makes derogatory comments about your submission. Tells you to stand up.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_AFTER_SEX_FINISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You stand up. Vengar reveals that he was intending to stop illegal activities and focus on the rum distillery business that he 'acquired' a few months ago.
	</p>
	<p>
		Says that before he can do this, he needs the more powerful shop keepers to come and show their submission, otherwise his gang members will lose respect. Now that you've decided on this course of action, you suppose that convincing Axel to come and do this is acceptable.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_FINISH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_PERSUADE_FINISH_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You agree to do as Vengar asks. Leave the hall.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN_CHUUNI"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You make ridiculous chuuni threats. The rats actually seem nervous. Vengar tries to call you out on your nonsense (but you actually believe your own words). If companion (who is not chuuni), they cringe.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN_DEMON"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You use the fact that you're a demon to intimidate and threaten Vengar. The rats actually seem nervous.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You use the fact that you know that you're a lot more powerful than Vengar to intimidate and threaten him. The rats actually seem nervous.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Vengar stands up and says that he'll give you one chance to make amends. Reveals that he was intending to stop illegal activities and focus on the rum distillery business that he 'acquired' a few months ago.
	</p>
	<p>
		Says that before he can do this, he needs the more powerful shop keepers to come and show their submission, otherwise his gang members will lose respect. Vengar strides towards you, ready to press you on the issue.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN_AGREE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You agree to do as Vengar asks. He returns to his throne. You leave.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN_FIGHT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Vengar that if it's a fight he wants, you'll give it to him.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN_KNOCK_OUT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN_KNOCK_OUT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You use your unarmed skills to effortlessly throw Vengar to the floor, knocking him out. A large commotion breaks out, with some rats starting to fight each other as they argue about if Vengar is still the leader. You notice that the two rat-girl bodyguards have disappeared.
	</p>
	<p>
		A large explosion is suddenly heard throughout the Warrens.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN_KNOCK_OUT_SWORD_RAID -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_THREATEN_KNOCK_OUT_SWORD_RAID"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		SWORD bursts in, shooting and arresting rats. Thankfully, Claire is with them, and recognises you. She stops SWORD from arresting you and tells you to follow her.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- SWORD_RAID_EXIT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SWORD_RAID_EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You go with Claire back to the nearest Enforcer outpost. You have to stay there for 6 hours while paperwork is sorted out. Claire says that Vengar and Murk are being enslaved and given to Axel as compensation. Shadow and Silence cooperated, and apparently Claire received orders from higher up to let them go without any charge.
	</p>
	<p>
		Claire apologises for how long it took, and you're finally allowed to go.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE_TELEPATHY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You seduce Vengar by using your telepathic abilities. Convince him to take you to his bedroom.
	</p>
	<p>
		You enter his bedroom, leaving behind companion (if applicable).
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You seduce Vengar. Convince him to take you to his bedroom.
	</p>
	<p>
		You enter his bedroom, leaving behind companion (if applicable).
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE_SEX_SUBMISSIVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You submit to Vengar, allowing him to fuck you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE_SEX_DOMINANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Vengar that you're in charge. He's so horny that he accepts, allowing you to dom him.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE_NO_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE_NO_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You continue to lead Vengar on, but don't allow him to get physical with you. You get him to reveal that he was intending to stop illegal activities and focus on the rum distillery business that he 'acquired' a few months ago.
	</p>
	<p>
		Says that before he can do this, he needs the more powerful shop keepers to come and show their submission, otherwise his gang members will lose respect. Vengar strides towards you, ready to press you on the issue.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE_NO_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You agree to do as Vengar asks, before leaving.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You finish having sex. Vengar reveals that he was intending to stop illegal activities and focus on the rum distillery business that he 'acquired' a few months ago.
	</p>
	<p>
		Says that before he can do this, he needs the more powerful shop keepers to come and show their submission, otherwise his gang members will lose respect. Vengar strides towards you, ready to press you on the issue.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_APPROACH_SEDUCE_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You agree to do as Vengar asks, before leaving.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_HALL_RESONANCE_STONE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_RESONANCE_STONE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seeing that Vengar is here, you activate the resonance stone which Claire gave to you. Now to stall for time until the SWORD Enforcers show up...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_HALL_RESONANCE_STONE_RAID"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You stall for time. There is a loud explosion, before moments later SWORD enters.
	</p>
	<p>
		Claire is with them, tells you to follow her out.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BODYGUARDS_COMBAT_SHADOW_DEFEATED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BODYGUARDS_COMBAT_SHADOW_DEFEATED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As Shadow falls to the ground, Silence staggers back, looking like she's about to collapse as well. She goes into a trance and summons an air elemental, which speaks for her and says she will destroy you. Her eyes glow with increased intensity as she attacks you once again.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BODYGUARDS_COMBAT_SILENCE_DEFEATED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BODYGUARDS_COMBAT_SILENCE_DEFEATED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As Silence falls to the ground, Shadow lets out a furious scream. Seemingly filled with a renewed vigour, she launches back into combat alone.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BODYGUARDS_COMBAT_VICTORY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BODYGUARDS_COMBAT_VICTORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having defeated both Shadow and Silence, you look up at Vengar to see that he's advancing on you. With no time to prepare, you must now defend yourself against his attacks!
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BODYGUARDS_COMBAT_DEFEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BODYGUARDS_COMBAT_DEFEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You are defeated by the rat-girls. If non-con disabled, explosion in heard before anyone can make a move on you. If non-con is on, Shadow strips you (Silence strips companion, if applicable) in front of everyone in the hall.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BODYGUARDS_COMBAT_DEFEAT_COMPANION_ESCAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You manage to hold off the rats long enough for [npc.name] to escape.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGAR_COMBAT_VICTORY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGAR_COMBAT_VICTORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You have defeated the rats. A large commotion breaks out, with some rats starting to fight each other as they argue about if Vengar is still the leader. You notice that the two rat-girl bodyguards have disappeared.
	</p>
	<p>
		A large explosion is suddenly heard throughout the Warrens.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGAR_COMBAT_DEFEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGAR_COMBAT_DEFEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You are defeated by Vengar. If non-con disabled, explosion in heard before anyone can make a move on you. If non-con is on, Shadow recovers and strips you (Silence strips companion, if applicable) in front of everyone in the hall. Essence extraction somehow.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- FINAL_COMBAT_VICTORY_SWORD_RAID -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FINAL_COMBAT_VICTORY_SWORD_RAID"><![CDATA[
	
	<p>
		SWORD squad enters. Claire is with them, tells you to follow her out.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_BEDROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_BEDROOM_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Accepting Vengar's offer (and leaving your companion with Shadow and Silence), you soon once again find yourself in his bedroom with him. Kissing one another, you wonder if you should take the lead or let Vengar dom...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_BEDROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Accepting Vengar's offer (and leaving your companion with Shadow and Silence), you find yourself in his bedroom with him. Kissing one another, you wonder if you should take the lead or let Vengar dom...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_BEDROOM_SEX_SUBMISSIVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You submit to Vengar.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_BEDROOM_SEX_DOMINANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You dominate Vengar.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- VENGARS_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You finish having sex.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="VENGARS_BEDROOM_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You head back into the Rat Warrens.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LEXA_VISIT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LEXA_VISIT_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You and Vengar go to the Gambling den to pay Lexa another visit. Upon arriving, she once again shows the two of you into her office (companion waits outside).
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LEXA_VISIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You and Vengar go to the Gambling den to pay Lexa a visit. Upon arriving, she shows the two of you into her office (companion waits outside).
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LEXA_VISIT_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You and Vengar move to start having sex with Lexa
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LEXA_VISIT_WATCH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You decide against having sex with Lexa, and instead stand back and watch Vengar fuck her.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LEXA_VISIT_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You decide against having sex with Lexa, and instead leave Vengar to fuck her.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LEXA_VISIT_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LEXA_VISIT_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finish sex and step back out into entrance of the gambling den.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- POST_CAPTIVITY_SWORD_RAID -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="POST_CAPTIVITY_SWORD_RAID"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Shadow leaves you with Silence while she makes sure the way is clear. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="POST_CAPTIVITY_SWORD_RAID_FINISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Shadow returns and leads you out of the Warrens. To your surprise, SWORD squad is there with Claire. They start their raid and Claire tells you to go with her. Shadow and Silence seem to vanish while this is happening. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- POST_DEFEAT_SWORD_RAID -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="POST_DEFEAT_SWORD_RAID"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		SWORD raids the Warrens. They seem to recognise or at least know who Silence is (random rat says they betrayed them). She stops SWORD from taking you into custody. The officer says he'll wait for the one who can actually talk.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="POST_CAPTIVITY_SWORD_RAID_FINISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Shadow returns with Claire, who tells you to go with her. Shadow and Silence seem to vanish while this is happening.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
