<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
    <htmlContent tag="START"><![CDATA[
    <p>
        A strange little shop appears in the walkway. It's little more than a ramshackle tent like structure made of
        gauzy cloth. Flickering fire light from inside casts erotically writing shadows against the deceptively thin
        cloth. You can't quit make out what's going on, but the subtle gasps and moans drifting in the air are enough
        to tell you it has to be an intense experience.
    </p>
    <p>
        There's a strange symbol, cast in gold, mounted above the door. It's not a symbol you recognize, and the more
        you look at it the more your eyes seem to slide off it.

        #IF(pc.isAbleToOrgasm())
            You find yourself unable to move any closer to the shop and get the feeling that you would not be welcome
            inside if you could. You can almost hear it telling you to return only when you seek that which is denied.
        #ELSE
            Somehow, the shape is strangely inviting, as though it wants you to come inside. It hints at a release to
            your yearning, if you're willing to pay the price.
        #ENDIF
    </p>
    ]]></htmlContent>

    <htmlContent tag="BLOCKED"><![CDATA[
        <p>
            As you force your way closer to the shop, a female lion-morph bursts through the shop's door with purple
            sparks of arcane power crackling around her body. [deniedDollMaker_TheDollMaker.speech(You would dare
            cross this barrier?)] Her eyes scan the alley way and lock with your own.
        </p>
        <p>
            [deniedDollMaker_TheDollMaker.speech(You!)] The word comes out a more of a roar than human speech.
        </p>
    ]]></htmlContent>

    <htmlContent tag="DOLLMAKER_WON"><![CDATA[
        <p>
            [deniedDollMaker_TheDollMaker.speech(If I needed another slave, I'd collar you right now. It so happens I
            don't. On the other hand, I can't leave your insolence unpunished either.)] She looks at your for a moment,
            contemplating her options.
        </p>
        <p>
            [deniedDollMaker_TheDollMaker.speech(Perhaps a taste of what you're missing.)] There's a little blue pill
            in her hand that you realizes se is about to force you to swallow.
        </p>
    ]]></htmlContent>

    <htmlContent tag="DOLLMAKER_WON_RESISTED"><![CDATA[
        <p>[deniedDollMaker_TheDollMaker.speech(A pitty)] She growls and disappears, along with her shop, in a puff of
        purple smoke.</p>
    ]]></htmlContent>

    <htmlContent tag="DOLLMAKER_WON_SWALLOWED"><![CDATA[
        <p>
            The little blue pill easily slides down your throat, and after only a few moments you [pc.verb(feel)] a
            pulsing warmth taking root deep within your loins. An arcane glow surrounds you for a moment crotch and then
            fades away. You have the feeling that you've lost something that was very important to you.</p>
        <p>
            [deniedDollMaker_TheDollMaker.speech(Now that that's over with, you're welcome to come inside and look
            around!)]
        </p>
    ]]></htmlContent>

    <!-- TODO: Expand on this -->
    <htmlContent tag="DOLLMAKER_LOST"><![CDATA[
        <p>
            [deniedDollMaker_TheDollMaker.speech(You're a better fighter than I expected, but it doesn't matter.)]
            She growls as The Doll Maker and her shop disappear in a puff of purple smoke.
        </p>
    ]]></htmlContent>

    <!-- TODO: Need a real description of the interior -->
    <htmlContent tag="INSIDE"><![CDATA[
        <p>
            [deniedDollMaker_TheDollMaker.speech(Welcome to my humble little shop! Please do have a look around.)]
        </p>
    ]]></htmlContent>

</dialogue>
