<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	
	<!-- You can define an author name to be shown in-game by setting the 'author' attribute.
		I advise using a lore-friendly name so as to not break immersion, although of course you're free to use whatever name you like in your mod. -->
	<htmlContent tag="HYENA_BASIC" author="Professor Webster"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Hyena-morphs are almost exclusively found in the savannah and desert in the south of Lilith's Realm, although the odd individual may sometimes be seen wandering the streets of Dominion. Rounded ears, predatory eyes, and their distinctive spotted or striped fur is usually enough to identify a person as a hyena-morph.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HYENA_ADVANCED" author="Professor Webster"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldHyena(Spotted Hyenas)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Spotted hyena-morphs are nomadic dwellers of the savannah and desert. While it's not unheard of to see one make a living in the city of Dominion, they for the most part tend to stick to their tribal encampments. Occasionally armed bands may venture beyond their usual homes in the wastes in search of travellers or undefended villages to raid.
	</p>
	<p>
		Often of larger build and height, females have the unusual physical feature of an enlarged clitoris that they use as a pseudo penis. Male spotted hyenas in comparison are often shorter and less physically imposing than the females of their species, though are still slightly taller than the average human.
	</p>
	<p>
		Spotted hyena society is one based on strength, and due to their biology, often matriarchal. The strongest warrior rules each tribe, advised by a shaman gifted in the arcane. Customarily a chieftain is a woman, however it is not unheard of for a male to lead a tribe, though this is a rare occurrence. The stronger, often female, warrior class treats the weaker, usually male, members of the tribe as a servant class. These weaker tribal members in turn lord over the captives of the tribe, be they slaves or an individual held for ransom. Unless a warrior or shaman takes personal guardianship over one of these captives, they can expect to be used as an outlet for the sexual frustration of the tribe's lessers. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Like most morphs, arcane storms inspire a deep rut in hyenas, and they will aggressively seek out a partner to dominate. Thankfully most hyenas live far from the storms' epicentre in Dominion, and as such one rarely has to worry about falling victim to one of these affected individuals.
	</p>
	<p>
		Like most morphs, a spotted hyena's offspring will be a mix of the hyena and the partner's race. Children gifted in the arcane are especially prized in hyena society and because of this, raiding parties are always on the lookout for morphs who are gifted in the arcane travelling through their territory. While raiding parties dare not to accost full demons for fear of retribution, there have been some reports of half-demons, youkos, and others gifted in the arcane being approached by raiding parties with an amicable offer of protection or trade given in exchange for fathering or mothering children. More often than not however, hyena raiding parties will attempt to take what they want by force, including mates.
	</p>
	<br/>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.boldHyena(Striped Hyenas)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Striped hyena-morphs are a settled people among the wastes, who make their living through subsistence farming and herding. Their kind values the laws and proper behaviour of a civilized society so they are a far more common sight in Dominion than their spotted cousins. Unfortunately, their nature as homebodies means it is still rare that one will actually make the trek to the city. Although they are for the most part an independent people who value their privacy, they group up in large numbers to travel the wastes, due to the threat posed by their rival subspecies, spotted hyena-morphs.
	</p>
	<p>
		Male and female striped hyenas tend to be of the same height as one another. Unlike spotted hyenas, they do not have any major deviations in genital arrangement and both are equally physically adept, that is to say, very. The pride of a striped hyena can easily be said to be their long, luxurious mohawks. Both males and females sport them and much personal pride is put into their appearance. Jewellery is not an uncommon feature among more affluent members of the race but the most common embellishment among them is to simply dye it in colours which are important to the individual.
	</p>
	<p>
		Being a society based on independence, their desire for privacy means they will often make their homes in the various rural communities that dot the savannah and desert. While not as physically intimidating as their spotted cousins, physical achievement is still highly prized in striped hyena society, and thus contact sports form the usual pastime in their communities. Their desire to cement their individuality often times expresses itself via an intense competitive spirit. Due to this, the striped hyenas within Dominion can often times can be found near a gym, especially the boxing ring.
	</p>
	<p>
		Striped hyenas' competitive nature also manifests in their relationship with their spotted cousins. Despite their penchant for independence, groups of striped hyenas regularly patrol between towns in the wastes for the chance of happening on a patrol of spotted raiders to best in combat. For a price, merchants and other travellers seeking to navigate the wastes can usually enlist the aid of striped hyenas, or bargain their way into being allowed to accompany one of these vigilante groups.
	</p>
	<p>
		Arcane storms inspire a deep rut in striped hyenas, though unlike spotted hyenas, they aren't nearly as aggressive and are just as likely to submit to a willing partner as force themselves on an unwilling one. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Like most morphs, a striped hyena's offspring will be a mix of the hyena and the partner's race. Striped hyenas have a family structure that consists only of themselves and their romantic partner. Children are expected to work towards acquiring their own home as soon as possible though their parents will usually lend what aid they can. After the child acquires a home they will tend to look for a mate. Striped hyenas are usually monogamous though more urbanized individuals will usually be more promiscuous than the rural members of their kind.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</bookText>
