<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	
	<!-- EISEK_ENCOUNTER_INITIAL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_ENCOUNTER_INITIAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you stroll through the market, you notice a small mob gathered around one of the stalls. It is composed of all sorts of plainly dressed animal morphs and a few are carrying simple wooden signs. They are angrily shouting or chanting something, but you can't quite make out what it is above the general hubbub and music around you. Those not in the mob are giving the area a wide berth, perhaps you should do the same.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_ENCOUNTER_BACK_OFF -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_ENCOUNTER_BACK_OFF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You decide not to get any closer to the stall or the crowd around it.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_ENCOUNTER_APPROACH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_ENCOUNTER_APPROACH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious to see what the mob is so angry about, you decide to approach the stall. As you get closer, the crowd's shouting becomes clearer and you can make out a few phrases.
	</p>
	<p>
		[test.speechMasculine(Get out of our town!)] shouts a portly rabbit-boy.
	</p>
	<p>
		[test.speechFeminine(We're not here as plunder!)] bleets the sheep-girl next to him.
	</p>
	<p>
		Fortunately, they are not packed in so close together that you cannot squeeze through and after a bit of effort you are able to make your way to the front. The object of the crowd's ire is a [eisek.raceFull(true)] [eisek.materialDescriptor] [eisek.skinFullDescription(true)] who seems to be a bit oversized for his stall. His clothing looks primitive and hard-worn, but the produce on display before him almost glows with health. You can tell from his expression that he's trying very hard to look unperturbed by the crowd and he hasn't said a word so far, but the puffs of steam occasionally emitting from his nostrils must surely mean he's very close to breaking point.
	</p>
	<p>
		Perhaps spurred on by your intense visual study, his [eisek.eyeColour(true)] eyes lock with yours.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Ah, you again! Would you like the usual?)] he asks, his rumbling baritone cutting across the din, [eisek.speech(They are all fresh in today.)] His face has brightened somewhat, but you recognise the pleading look in his eyes.
	</p>
	<p>
		It's obvious he wants you to play along, but should you? Perhaps the angry mob is right. After all, you don't know anything about this [eisek.race], what if all this is just a front? With all the shouting about plunder that the crowd is doing, he could be back tonight to raze and loot the place.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_ENCOUNTER_BANISHMENT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_ENCOUNTER_BANISHMENT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPersonalityTrait(PERSONALITY_TRAIT_SELFISH))
			You tell the [eisek.race] that you're neither a fool nor a friend of his. Before you can say anything else, a tough looking horse-girl interjects. [test.speechFeminine(Yeah! We're not fools and we don't want you in our town! Get out!)] she shouts.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasPersonalityTrait(PERSONALITY_TRAIT_SHY))
			You break eye contact with the [eisek.race] and simply look away, saying nothing in response. An awkward moment passes before a tough looking horse-girl breaks the silence. [test.speechFeminine(You can't fool us! We don't want you in our town! Get out!)] she shouts.
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasPersonalityTrait(PERSONALITY_TRAIT_CYNICAL))
			You tell the [eisek.race] that to find some other patsy. Before you can say anything else, a tough looking horse-girl interjects. [test.speechFeminine(Yeah! And find some other town while you're at it! Get out!)] she shouts.
		#ELSE
			You hesitate, not wanting to play a part in this mass deception. Before you can say anything else, a tough looking horse-girl interjects.
		#ENDIF
		 Her words are accompanied by a rotten tomato that tints part of the stall red as it splatters against the wood. The mob takes this as a cue to start throwing rotten produce as well, and when they run out, rubbish and small rocks start flying.
	</p>
	<p>
		Finally at the limit of his patience, the [eisek.race] charges up his breath weapon and [style.boldIce(you are momentarily blinded by a bright blue flash!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isImmuneToDamageType(DAMAGE_TYPE_ICE) || pc.getAttributeValue(ATTRIBUTE_RESISTANCE_ICE) >= 300)
			You feel a slight chill as an icy cloud envelops the immediate area. Although you are unaffected, the mob is unable to continue its bombardment as all of its members have been frozen in place from the neck down by a thin glazing of ice.
			[##pc.addStatusEffect(SE_FREEZING_FOG, 10)]
		#ELSE
			When your vision clears, you find yourself feeling very cold as an icy cloud envelops the immediate area. You want to cover yourself for warmth but when you try, you find that you're unable to do anything except shiver from the neck down.
			[##npc.addStatusEffect(SE_FROZEN, 10)]
		#ENDIF
		The cloud obstructs your vision but you can hear the flapping of large wings, prompting you to look up just in time to see the [eisek.race] flying off to parts unknown. Soon, the ice melts and the cloud dissipates, leaving behind the empty, defenceless stall. 
	</p>
	<p>
		The mob, evidently not content with driving off the [eisek.race] and not deterred by being partially frozen, rushes forward to demolish the stall and destroy its contents. By the time they are satisfied, nothing is left except splinters of wood, shreds of fabric, and a worthless paste of ruined produce. Cheering at having achieving its goal, the mob then slowly disperses, leaving you standing alone before empty space where the stall had been.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_ENCOUNTER_DISPERSE_CROWD -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_ENCOUNTER_DISPERSE_CROWD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPersonalityTrait(PERSONALITY_TRAIT_SHY))
			With every ounce of courage you can muster, you greet the [eisek.race]
		#ELSEIF (pc.hasPersonalityTrait(PERSONALITY_TRAIT_CONFIDENT))
			Confidently striding forward, you greet the [eisek.race] like an old friend
		#ELSE
			You greet the [eisek.race] on familiar terms
		#ENDIF
		and respond affirmatively to his question. To really make it look convincing, you also ask if he has a new crop in today as you close the distance with the stall and casually lean on the counter.
	</p>
	<p>
		It's subtle, but relief washes across the [eisek.race]'s face as he continues the charade, [eisek.speech(You have a keen eye, [pc.sir], it is indeed a new crop.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The mob, having been stunned into silence by your friendly exchange with what by all accounts should be a violent creature of unequal greed, regains its composure.
	</p>
	<p>
		[test.speechMasculine(Hey! What's wrong with you?)] a scrawny donkey-boy asks indignantly, [test.speechMasculine(He's a looting, plundering animal!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You look back towards the angry mob and, looking as disinterested in their arguments as possible, tell them that the that if they're here to buy they should get in line or else you are going to call in the Enforcers. You don't catch what the donkey-boy's long-winded response is, preferring to make banter about the weather with the [eisek.race] instead.
	</p>
	<p>
		Finding themselves ignored in favor of the most mundane of topics, most of the mob awkwardly disperses, leaving only the still-rambling donkey-boy behind. Eventually realizing he's alone, the donkey-boy points in the general direction of the stall and brays [test.speechMasculine(This isn't over!)] before trotting off.
	</p>
	<p>
		With the mob now gone, the [eisek.race] bows his head slightly and lets out a long sigh of relief. [eisek.speech(Thank you,)] he says in the first bit of genuine conversation between the two of you, [eisek.speech(If you had not shown up, I do not know what I might have done. Somebody could have gotten hurt. Here, for your trouble.)] He gives you a small pouch that jingles with the sound of flames before continuing. [eisek.speech(The name is Eisek, Eisek Seawings, by the way...I do not believe I know yours, or else I would have used it in our little subterfuge.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You stash away the money and, seeing no reason to keep your name from the [eisek.race], introduce yourself. He acknowledges you with a nod. [eisek.speech([pc.Name]...I will remember you. Now then, can interest I you in some fine fruits and vegetables?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_STALL_BANISHED -->
	<!-- TODO: Merge all stall descriptions -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_STALL_BANISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The space previously occupied by that [eisek.race]'s stall still hasn't found a new occupant, but at least the ruins and the pile of pulverized produce have been cleared away.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_STALL_VACANT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_STALL_VACANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The space normally occupied by Eisek's stall is empty, he must not be around. You recall that he's only in town between the first and third of each month.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_STALL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_STALL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Eisek's stall is constructed in much the same way as all the others lining the avenue although it does look comparatively dull and shabby. Stretched over the wooden counter is some sort of rough fabric, you guess burlap, stitched together into a crude cover and there's not even shade to keep the occupant out of the sun. The counter is split into a flat table area and an angled display area with a small chalkboard affixed to a post above it for displaying prices. The thin wooden placard hanging over the front is unpainted with the words "FRESH PRODUCE" simply burned into it.
	</p>
	<p>
		It is presently being manned by Eisek and the display area is filled with a sampling of this month's product. His movements are careful and deliberate as the stall seems to be just slightly too small for him. Every once in a while, you see him blowing a gentle stream of frosty air over both the produce on display and in the crates behind him.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_STALL_FANCY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Eisek's stall now looks much more colourful and inviting. The counter is now covered in bright orange fabric much like the new awning it now sits under. Sewn to the front of the counter is the tapestry-like sign you had made, depicting a gust of wind descending from snow-capped mountains, carrying fruits and vegetables down the slopes while swirling blue letters proclaim "FRESH PRODUCE, MOUNTAIN GROWN". As before, the counter is split into a flat table area and an angled display area with a small chalkboard affixed to a post above it for displaying prices.
	</p>
	<p>
		It is presently being manned by Eisek and the display area is filled with a sampling of this month's product. His movements are careful and deliberate as the stall seems to be just slightly too small for him. Every once in a while, you see him blowing a gentle stream of frosty air over both the produce on display and in the crates behind him.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_MENU -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_MENU"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QuestLine.SIDE_EISEK_MOB) && flags.hasFlag(FLAG_dsg_elis_eisek_mob_quest_persuade) && !flags.hasFlag(FLAG_dsg_elis_eisek_talk_post_mob_quest))
		<p>
			As you approach the stall, you notice a sheep-girl speaking with Eisek. A pang of adrenaline rushes through you as you recognise her from the same mob that had been trying to drive him out. Fearing the worst, you quicken your pace, but she leaves before you can do or say anything.
		</p>
		<p>
			Catching sight of you, a smile grows across Eisek's face. [eisek.speech(Greetings, [pc.name],)] he says, [eisek.speech(The strangest thing happened just before you got here. Some members of that mob stopped by and...actually apologised to me. I assume you had something to do with that.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eisek chuckles when you mention that you didn't expect any of them to actually return. [eisek.speech(So, what can I do for my favourite doer of good deeds?)]
		</p>
		[##flags.setFlag(FLAG_dsg_elis_eisek_talk_post_mob_quest, true)]
	#ELSEIF(eisek.getAffection(pc) >= 15)
		<p>
			Catching sight of you as you approach, a smile grows across Eisek's face as he greets you. [eisek.speech(Ah, and what can I do for my favourite customer?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Catching sight of you as you approach, a faint smile creeps across Eisek's face. [eisek.speech(Greetings, [pc.name],)] he says, [eisek.speech(What can I do for you?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_DRAGONFALL_SPECIFIC -->
	<!-- TODO: Break up this wall of text -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_DRAGONFALL_SPECIFIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A puff of steam leaves Eisek's nostrils as you broach the subject again. He closes his eyes for a moment, thinking, before finally giving his response.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Alright,)] he says, somewhat dejectedly, [eisek.speech(I suppose you have already heard something of it from that mob. There's no harm in telling you the truth of the matter.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(We dragons were not always as we are now, a scattered and isolated people wringing our survival from the land. Once, the dragons of old were proud servants of Lisophia. For her Glistering Hoard they performed all sorts of brute tasks, extorted the peasants on her land, plundered countless villages, and in return she made them strongest creatures in the land. They were proud of their lot in life, so proud that they could not see the winds of change blowing.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(When Lisophia decided there were better ways of growing her hoard, they no longer needed and were cast aside. Of course, the dragons of old were angry, they fought back, and for that Lisophia's retribution was swift and terrible. My ancestors said very little about what happened and wrote down even less, so great was their shame, but I know that at the end of a great battle almost all the dragons of old were left with only a fraction of their former strength. What Lisopha gave she could just as easily take away, you see.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(No longer afraid, society rejected them for the crimes they committed in Lisophia's service, and the Lilin hated them for their arrogance. They and their children down the generations were forced to become outcasts. That is the Dragonfall. A millennia-long punishment for the hubris of my forefathers and why those who know about it wish for us to remain outcasts.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_HIMSELF -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_HIMSELF"><![CDATA[
	#IF(eisek.getAffection(pc) >= 15)
		<p>
			Having earned his trust, the [eisek.race] opens up a little. [eisek.speech(I come from Cimryth's Crag, a rocky little valley high in the mountains far to the west of here. My family has farmed there for a hundred years.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Expressing surprise that his farm is in the mountains, you ask Eisek how he can grow anything up there and how he can carry enough to sell all the way down. Trying not to sound too proud, he explains [eisek.speech(Cimryth chose well when she decided where to settle my ancestors. Heat rises from the earth there, and ice never touches the ground. She brought soil from the foothills with her, and the greenhouses she designed took care of the rest. It is for this reason the Crag is named after her, and it is my honour to carry on in her tradition.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eisek flexes his wings slightly before continuing, [eisek.speech(It is easy enough to carry my weight in goods on a downward glide from the Crag, and after three days in the thick air down here the return trip is much easier.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			From the sounds of things, the [eisek.race] is doing much or even all of this on his own. When you ask him if he's got anyone helping him, his face darkens. [eisek.speech(No,) he answers tersely.  You decide not to pry further.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Eisek opens his mouth to respond, but shuts it again just as quickly. A brief look of hesitation flashes across his face before he answers your question. [eisek.speech(My product comes from the mountains,)] he says carefully, [eisek.speech(On the first day of each month I bring it here and on the third day I leave.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			When you ask how he can grow anything in the mountains, his answer is only a cryptic [eisek.speech(There are ways.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			From the way he dodged your questions he evidently doesn't trust you enough yet.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_BUSINESS -->
	<!-- TODO: Merge variants -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_BUSINESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		He ponders your question for a moment, looking off into the distance, before answering [eisek.speech(Well enough, I suppose. I never planned to succeed through volume. Although...) the [eisek.race] pauses as he surveys the other stalls up and down the avenue. [eisek.speech(My stall could use some work. There is nothing I can do about the size, I need to fly with it...although I would not mind an awning for some shade. It is definitely not as eye-catching compared with the others. If only I could get some better fabric and a better sign...hmm, but I cannot leave my stall undefended. I would come back to it in ruins for sure.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As if suddenly aware that he's been thinking aloud, he snaps out of his trance and looks back at you, doing his best to hide his embarrassment. [eisek.speech(Ah, but I am sure you that did not come to hear me ramble. I am fortunate that not all of the locals are thick-skulled. They are not talkative like you, but they buy what I have to sell, and that is good enough for me.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_BUSINESS_FANCY_STALL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_BUSINESS_FANCY_STALL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(You have done me a great service with this new stall,)] he says, trying not to sound too excited, [eisek.speech(I am on more equal footing with the others now, and I have even seen a few new customers.)] He scratches his chin in thought before flashing you a cheeky grin. [eisek.speech(Though, you still talk the most.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_BUSINESS_POST_QUEST -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_BUSINESS_POST_QUEST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		His eyes light up at the question. [eisek.speech(I cannot thank you enough, [pc.name]. Without that crowd of hooligans around I can focus on running this stall, for which I also owe you. Sales have really started to pick up and I have seen many new faces among my customers.)] He studies you intently for a brief instant before continuing with a warm smile. [eisek.speech(Don't worry, you will always be my favourite.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_FAMILY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_FAMILY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You ask Eisek about the family he mentioned. The question seems to hit him off-balance and he initially pretends that he didn't hear it as his expression darkens. When he finally does respond, he stares at the counter and says only [eisek.speech(I don't want to talk about that,)] in a barely audible whisper.
	</p>
	<p>
		Probably not a good idea to push further.
	</p>
	[##game.getDialogueFlags().incrementSavedLong("elis_eisek_talk_score", 1)]
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_WHY_ELIS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_WHY_ELIS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From what you know about dragons, they dislike strangers. How did Eisek come to run a stall in a town full of them, especially when some of them are so hostile?
	</p>
	<p>
		The [eisek.race] lets out a rumbling chuckle. [eisek.speech(Ah yes, ironic, isn't it? Well as much as we dragons value our solitude, there are some things we must rely on traders for. About three years ago, they stopped coming to the Crag and after a bad storm smashed up a few greenhouses last winter I had little other choice.)] He pauses for a moment, looking you over with a small smile before continuing, [eisek.speech(Thanks to you, my little gamble on civilisation has worked out better than I could have hoped for.)]
	</p>
	[##game.getDialogueFlags().incrementSavedLong("elis_eisek_talk_score", 1)]
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_OTHER_DRAGONS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_OTHER_DRAGONS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Met? Only one. A family friend of sorts hailing from the desert. She was a skilled glassfromer who once helped me repair a greenhouse. We have not spoken in...a long time,)], he replies, looking slightly misty-eyed at the recall of some private memory, [eisek.speech(As for others, I only know about the existence of others from the sight of their fields in bloom during the day and the glow of the their kilns during the night. They were not so desperate as I was to make contact with strangers, however, and you would be wise to leave them alone should you encounter them in the wilds.)]
	</p>
	[##game.getDialogueFlags().incrementSavedLong("elis_eisek_talk_score", 1)]
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_VENDOR -->
	<!-- TODO: Check if this is even necessary -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_VENDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(The cream of the crop. You will not find better in the whole of this market.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_ASK_ABOUT_MOB -->
	<!-- TODO: Variants for quest completion -->
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_ASK_ABOUT_MOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Something about the crowd you dispersed when you first met Eisek bothers you. They seemed rather organized for a random bunch of thugs, and to their credit, they did at least leave without a fight. What did they hope to gain by driving him out?
	</p>
	<p>
		Eisek meets your question with a steaming snort. [eisek.speech(Oh them. The first one showed up maybe three months ago. I ignored him and he came back with friends. The Enforcers came two or three times, but harassment is hardly a serious crime. The ones that got arrested would be absent for the next day or so, but they'd always come back, none the worse for wear. They were a nuisance more than anything and I was mostly concerned that they were scaring away customers. Well, that was before their friends came back with more friends...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As he trails off, you get the impression that the [eisek.race] is avoiding your question. Eisek leans against the counter when you try to steer the conversation back to the crowd's motivation. [eisek.speech(You heard them as well as I did. They think that I am like the dragons of old, from before the Dragonfall,)] he says quietly.
	</p>
	<p>
		You're not really sure what the "dragons of old" really means or what a "Dragonfall" is. Do you press him for more information, focus on the matter at hand, or drop the subject entirely?
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_DRAGONFALL_VAGUE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_DRAGONFALL_VAGUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		When you ask Eisek what he means by "dragons of old", he dodges your gaze. [eisek.speech(My ancestors did things to their ancestors. Things I am not proud of,)] he answers, as quietly as before.
	</p>
	<p>
		He's obviously hiding something but it's unlikely you'll get any more out of him without earning his trust.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_MOB_QUEST_START -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_MOB_QUEST_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From the sound of things, it is the mob will return sooner or later and you're not sure a verbal telling off will be enough next time. They did appear to be common townsfolk, however, and a search around town could reveal more about them. You tell Eisek as much.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(So, if you find them, what will you do?)] he asks, trying to hide his doubt, [eisek.speech(If you harm them for my sake, you will have proven their point.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You reassure the [eisek.race] that <i>when</i> you find them, it need not come to that. There may yet be other options. Although your words do not seem to have much effect, Eisek grudgingly agrees.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Very well...)] he pauses and looks down at the counter as if thinking of what to say next, [eisek.speech(But please be careful. I will await news of your...success.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_FAREWELL -->
	<!-- TODO: Low and medium affection variants -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_FAREWELL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The [eisek.race] nods his head slightly as you bid him farewell. [eisek.speech(Thank you for stopping by.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_TALK_STALL_QUEST_START -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_TALK_STALL_QUEST_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking back to what Eisek accidentally let slip about improvements to his stall, you ask him what he'd like on a sign representing his business. The [eisek.race] tilts his head slightly at you. [eisek.speech(...Why do you ask? The details of an object out of my grasp matter little.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You evade his suspicion and reframe the question as wanting to know what qualities his goods posses that are so important that he'd put them on a sign if he had one, hypothetically. [eisek.speech(Hmm...)] he rumbles, leaning forward slightly on the counter, [eisek.speech(They are brought down from the mountains, yes, from the clear air. And I keep them cold while I am here, they stay fresh that way.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		While his guard is still down, you slip in another question about his favourite colour to which he responds [eisek.speech(Orange. Is there...an aim behind this?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You don't bother trying to worm your way out with a grand explanation and admit to only being curious. With this new information, it seems you have some shopping to do. Perhaps there's a store in town that deals in fabric?
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_STALL_QUEST_COMPLETE -->
	<!-- Add variants for different PC personalities and body types-->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_STALL_QUEST_COMPLETE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Eisek's eyes widen as his gaze catches the materials you have triumphantly brought back.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(So that strange line of questions earlier was for this?)] he asks as you set down the bolts of cloth and wooden poles down on the counter. His tone is reserved, but the way his tail twitches when he examines the new sign gives away his excitement.
	</p>
	<p>
		With your objective within sight, you come clean. Yes, those strange questions about signs and favourite colours were about getting him the improvements to his stall that he wanted, and there is nothing he can do to stop them now.
	</p>
	<p>
		The next half hour is spent helping Eisek put up the awning and replace the fabric and signage covering the counter. When the two of you are done, the transformation is total and the stall stands on equal footing with all of its neighbours.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Why did you do all this for me?)] Eisek asks, in a much quieter voice than usual.
	</p>
	<p>
		You tell him simply that after everything that's happened, he deserves to win for once. The [eisek.race] is silent, speechless for a few long minutes before he presses a hefty pouch-full of flames into one of your hands and grips the other in a firm handshake.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(I am glad that I chose to come to this town. I met you in it. You have my sincerest thanks, [pc.name].)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_MOB_QUEST_ENCOUNTER -->
	<!-- TODO: Set exact conditions for each path and warn player if they do not meet at least one of them -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_MOB_QUEST_ENCOUNTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you walk down the street, a flyer plastered to a nearby building. In bright, bold letters it proclaims
	</p>
	<p>
		
	</p>
	<p>
		This must be from that group that's been harassing Eisek. At the bottom there are directions to the building's cellar and you note that the meeting started a few minutes ago. If you want to confront the mob now, you'll need to head into the cellar right away. On the other hand, if they are printing flyers they're probably holding these meetings regularly all over town. You could find another place and time.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_MOB_QUEST_DISCARD_FLYER -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_MOB_QUEST_DISCARD_FLYER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You don't want to confront the mob right now, but you decide to rip the flyer off and toss it in the nearest rubbish bin. Next time, you tell yourself.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_MOB_QUEST_MEET_MOB -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_MOB_QUEST_MEET_MOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You descend the steps into the building's cellar, following the sound of voices. It is surprisingly well lit and spacious inside. Unmarked crates and barrels line the walls, providing most of the seating, but there are some chairs upon which you see some familiar faces. One of those familiar faces is the long-winded donkey-boy who takes notice of you the instant to you enter the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		[test.speechMasculine(You,)] he says, his face twisted in disgust as he extends an accusatory digit, [test.speechMasculine(Come to settle the score? You don't know anything about that [eisek.race] and what his kind is really like, what they did before they fell from favour.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You tell the donkey-boy, who you assume to be a leader of sorts, that you want them to leave Eisek alone. Your request is met by derisive laughter.
	</p>
	<p>
		[test.speechMasculine(And why would we do that? We will not stand by while our homes are in danger!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		What will do you to convince the mob?
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_MOB_QUEST_INTIMIDATE -->
	<!-- TODO: Merge variants -->
	<!-- TODO: Add variants for ferals who don't have hands (use teeth/hooves/horns/etc) and slimes -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_MOB_QUEST_INTIMIDATE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You crack your knuckles menacingly and explain that if they don't honour your request, the next time you see them anywhere near Eisek you'll give them a thrashing they'll never forget. And with their history with the Enforcers, somehow you don't think you're going to be the one getting arrested.
	</p>
	<p>
		A murmur travels around the room. Your show of strength seems to have had quite the effect and the donkey-boy for his part is visibly intimidated.
	</p>
	<p>
		[test.speechMasculine(V-very well. But I hope you understand that you've doomed this town and everyone in it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Satisfied, you turn around and leave without another word. Somehow you doubt that the donkey-boy's prophecy of doom will come to pass.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_MOB_QUEST_INTIMIDATE_ARCANE -->
	<!-- TODO: Add variants for different spells that the player has (Fireball/Ice Shard/Poison Vapours/Slam)-->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_MOB_QUEST_INTIMIDATE_ARCANE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You cast a ball of fire that flies right between the donkey-boy's legs and scorches the floor beneath his chair. You explain that if your request isn't honoured, the next time you see any of them anywhere near Eisek you won't miss. And with their history with the Enforcers, somehow you don't think you're going to be the one getting arrested.
	</p>
	<p>
		A murmur travels around the room. Your show of arcane prowess seems to have had quite the effect and the donkey-boy for his part is visibly intimidated.
	</p>
	<p>
		[test.speechMasculine(V-very well. But I hope you understand that you've doomed this town and everyone in it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Satisfied, you turn around and leave without another word. Somehow you doubt that the donkey-boy's prophecy of doom will come to pass.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_MOB_QUEST_INTIMIDATE_FAIL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_MOB_QUEST_INTIMIDATE_FAIL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You explain that if they don't honour your request, the next time you see them anywhere near Eisek they'll be sorry.
	</p>
	<p>
		More derisve laughter meets your threat. [test.speechFeminine(We'll be sorry?)] says a tough-looking horse-girl as she walks up to you, [test.speechFeminine(No, I think <i>you'll</i> be sorry.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she grabs hold of you and starts shoving you towards the exit. Despite your struggling and protestations, you cannot overpower her iron grip before you find yourself back out on the street, slightly worse for wear.
	</p>
	<p>
		You'd better tell Eisek the bad news...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_MOB_QUEST_PERSUADE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_MOB_QUEST_PERSUADE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You explain that the mob's fears are baseless. Eisek isn't anything like his ancestors. If he really was going to burn and pillage the place, running a stall in the market is an awfully strange way to go about it. They have talked so much about what his kind is like and yet not one of them has tried to get to know him and find out what he's really like. Yet you have. The Eisek you know is a humble produce farmer who took a big gamble in coming down from the mountains. If any member of this twisted little group had actually taken the time as you did, they would have found out the same thing.
	</p>
	<p>
		The mob is silent as a stone in response to your impassioned speech. After what seems like an eternity, the donkey-boy speaks again. [test.speechMasculine(Alight, you've made your point. Perhaps...we have been too quick to judge. Let us verify these claims.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Confident that they will come to the same conclusion as you have, you thank the townsfolk and leave without another word. 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_MOB_QUEST_SEDUCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_MOB_QUEST_SEDUCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		EISEK_MOB_QUEST_SEDUCE
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_MOB_QUEST_AFTERMATH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_MOB_QUEST_SEDUCE_AFTERMATH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		EISEK_MOB_QUEST_AFTERMATH
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- EISEK_MOB_QUEST_COMPLETE -->
	<!-- TODO: Variants based on how the player resolved the confrontation -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EISEK_MOB_QUEST_COMPLETE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Eisek that the mob won't be returning but he doesn't look convinced.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Is that so? And how did you manage such a feat?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You explain that since you'd learned so much about him, you were able to convince the townsfolk that Eisek wasn't anything like his ancestors.
	</p>
	<p>
		The [eisek.race]'s eyes widen slightly in surprise. He speaks haltingly, each word carefully chosen, [eisek.speech(I admit, I did not think you actually cared. Forgive me for doubting you.)] He then reaches under the counter and retrieves something. [eisek.speech(I have little in the way of rewarding you but perhaps these will do,)] he says as he places three bright pink fruit covered in green, scale-like leaves on the counter, [eisek.speech(My orchards can produce very few of these now, but if you would like to...empathize with my kind further, they will help you. If you need more, I can keep some on hand, just for you.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
