<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The link between this shopping precinct and the rest of Elis takes the form of a wide gap between a couple of residential buildings. A large sign proudly names this precinct as 'Wall's End', with an additional touristy-looking information board situated right in the middle of the path.
	</p>
	<p>
		Large wooden plant boxes line the sides of this entranceway, and are filled with a dazzling array of brightly-coloured flowers.
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=9 && game.getHourOfDay()<17)
			 With the information board quite clearly listing the standard opening times of the precinct's stores as [units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)], it's no wonder that there are a considerable amount of people passing through this entrance.
		#ELSE
			 Despite the information board quite clearly listing the standard opening times of the precinct's stores as [units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)], there's still the occasional person passing through this entrance.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		From here you have the limited options of heading into Wall's End, exiting back out into Elis, or reading the information board...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT_INFO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to take a moment to read the touristy-looking information board, you [pc.walk] over to it and scan over the following:
	</p>
	<hr/>
	<i>
		<p style='text-align:center; font-size:1.1em'>
			<b>Wall's End</b>
			<br/>
			Standard Opening Times: [units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)]
		</p>
		<p>
			<b>History</b>
			<br/>
			How did this shopping precinct come into being? Why is it called 'Wall's End'? And why is it needed when the farmer's market already exists? Woah, so many questions! Thankfully, all three can be answered by recounting a little of our wonderful town's history!
			<br/><br/>
			As you might already know, in the past our town was just a village, although a village that was destined to grow into the best town in all of Lilith's Realm. Of course, as with any growing population, Elis soon had need of commercial premises which couldn't be accommodated by simple market stalls. As such, our wonderful mayor, Minotallys, decreed that a shopping precinct needed to be created.
			<br/><br/>
			This decision coincided with the most ambitious construction project Elis has ever seen. Known to the locals as 'the northern expansion', a portion of the defensive walls needed to be torn down and rebuilt so as to accommodate an entirely new district. Where you're standing right now is where that northern wall once stood, hence it was agreed that this shopping precinct should honour that history by being called 'Wall's End'!
			<br/><br/>
			I hope that answers your questions, and now you can get to shopping! Make sure to spend lots of money to help keep our economy ticking!
		</p>
		<br/>
		<p>
			<b>Businesses</b>
			<br/>
			Here at Wall's End we've got a convenience store, a place for clothes shopping, and even a massage parlour! Who needs to go to Dominion when you've got everything you could ever need right here?!
			<br/><br/>
			Most businesses are open six days a week, between [units.time(9)]-[units.time(17)]. The convenience store is open 24/7, however, so even if it's the middle of the night there's no reason for you not to come in and take a look around!
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center; font-size:0.75em'>
			This information has been provided by the Elis tourism board. For complaints or queries, please inquire at the town hall.
		</p>
	</i>
	<hr/>
	<p>
		Having read through all of the information the sign contains, there's little else for you to do except [pc.step] back and decide where to go next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having concluded your business at Wall's End, you head out of the exit and find yourself back in the streets of Elis once again... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FOUNTAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In the very middle of Wall's End, facing the entrance, there's a large statue of the town's mayor, Minotallys. Expertly carved from white marble, this depiction of the town's favourite minotauress is wearing nothing except the jewellery which adorns her horns, fingers, and tail.
	</p>
	<p>
		With a playful grin on her face, this marble mimicry of Minotallys is using one hand to cover her pussy, while her other arm is crossed over beneath her huge breasts. Dual streams of water are being expelled from her large, puffy nipples, which fall down into the pool beneath her with a gentle splashing sound.
	</p>
	<p>
		A bronze plaque attached to the plinth upon which this statue stands reads: 'Funds for the creation and installation of this fountain were donated by the residents of Elis. Long may Minotallys guide us to prosperity!'
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=9 && game.getHourOfDay()<17)
			#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()!=WEATHER_RAIN)
				Other than a few people who have decided to make use of the raised edge of the pool to sit down and take a rest,
			#ELSE
				With most of the people in the precinct hurrying from one shop to another in order to avoid the rain,
			#ENDIF
			 nobody seems to be paying the fountain much attention, and with your interest similarly not being held for too long, you prepare to continue on your way...
		#ELSE
			Out of the very few people who are in the precinct at this hour, none of them are paying the fountain much attention, and with your interest similarly not being held for too long, you prepare to continue on your way...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GENERIC_SHOP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		For every one of the stores which are of interest to you, there are one or two that offer goods or services which are of no use to you whatsoever. Ranging from furniture stores to first-floor accountants offices, you pass by these businesses without giving them so much of a second glance.
	</p>
	<p>
		It's in front of one of these generic shops which you currently find yourself standing, and other than offering a place for you to stand and look around Wall's End, there's nothing for you to do here...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LAWN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A long, rectangular strip of grass sits in the middle of Wall's End,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_hasSnowedThisWinter) && game.getSeason()==SEASON_WINTER)
			 and despite the fact that the roofs and tops of the nearby lampposts are covered in snow, the lawn has somehow been kept clear, allowing you to admire its vivid green, perfectly-cut appearance.
		#ELSE
			 and from its vivid green, perfectly-cut appearance, looks to be very well maintained.
		#ENDIF
		 Several small signs have been placed along the lawn's edge, but instead of ordering people to keep off, they instead declare that walking over or sitting upon the grass is encouraged.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=9 && game.getHourOfDay()<17)
			#IF(game.getSeason()==SEASON_WINTER)
				Despite the signs' message, there aren't many people willing to sit out in the cold, and other than the few people who are walking over it to reach the other side of the precinct, the lawn is completely deserted.
			#ELSEIF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_RAIN)
				Despite the signs' message, there aren't many people willing to sit out in the rain, and other than the few people who are hurrying over it to reach the other side of the precinct, the lawn is completely deserted.
			#ELSE
				Perhaps due in part to the signs' message, there are quite a few people lounging around and even picnicking on the grass, and you have to adjust your path several times to avoid these groups.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Due to the fact that there are very few people in the precinct at this hour, the lawn is completely deserted.
		#ENDIF
		 Not having much to do here, you continue on your way across the lawn to the other side of the shopping precinct...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STREET"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Running around the shopping precinct in a circular fashion, this cobblestone street is very similar to the ones found throughout the rest of Elis. While the arcane street lamps are slightly different to the others in the town, they're still of an old, ornate design which adds to the surrounding timber-framed buildings' appearance to give this area a late-medieval aesthetic.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=9 && game.getHourOfDay()<17)
			Thanks to the hour of day,
			#IF(game.getDayOfWeek()!=DOW_SUNDAY)
				 all
			#ELSE
				 some
			#ENDIF
			 of the shops here are currently open, and there are a great deal of people either walking around with shopping bags in their hands or
			#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_RAIN)
				 standing beneath the shops' canvas awnings so as to be protected from the rain.
			#ELSE
				 sitting on one of the many wooden benches which line the sides of the street.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Due to the current hour, almost all of the shops here are currently closed, although there are still some people to be seen either out taking a walk around the precinct or heading to or from the convenience store.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wherever there's a concentration of members of the public, there exists the need for offering restroom facilities. Wall's End is no exception to this, and has met this need by converting the ground floor of one of the timber-framed buildings into public toilets.
	</p>
	<p>
		A sign next to the entrance informs you that these facilities are open 24/7 and are cleaned at least once per hour, in addition to asking members of the public to please treat the toilets with respect. An additional sign has been attached beneath this one at what you assume to be a later date, and reminds the reader that the creation of glory holes in the stalls is considered to be vandalism, and is punishable by a fine of up to one hundred flames.
	</p>
	<p>
		If you wanted to, you could head inside the public toilets and make use of them, or instead turn around and head back into Wall's End...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS_INTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you want to make use of the public toilets, you head inside and take a look around. While the stalls and sinks are of the usual public restroom quality, everything looks to be very well maintained, with the entire interior being nothing short of spotlessly clean. The steady hum of arcane-powered ventilation shafts produces a slightly-unpleasant monotonous background noise, but it's a minor discomfort worth paying to ensure that the air is kept fresh and odour-free.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getHourOfDay()>=9 && game.getHourOfDay()<17)
			A few of the stalls are currently occupied, while a couple of members of the public are making use of the sinks before heading back out into Wall's End to continue their shopping. As you walk past these people,
		#ELSE
			Due to the current time, these toilets are completely deserted. As you walk down the entire length of the restroom,
		#ENDIF
		#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_toilets_hole_ever_made))
			 you notice that there's not a single glory hole between any of the stalls, and you wonder if the exterior sign's threat of a fine has put people off making one, or if the local population just aren't into that sort of thing...
		#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_toilets_hole_made))
			 you see that the glory hole which you previously made hasn't yet been repaired, and you wonder if it's worth the risk of being discovered and fined to make use of it...
		#ELSE
			 you notice that the glory hole which you previously made has been flawlessly repaired, and you wonder if it's worth the risk of being discovered and fined to make another one...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having finished with the public restrooms, you head back out into the shopping precinct...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS_USE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] into one of the empty stalls, you turn and lock the door behind you, before making use of the toilet. After you've finished, you flush the toilet before making your way over to one of the sinks and washing your [pc.hands]. Grabbing a paper towel from the nearby dispenser, you quickly dry yourself off, before turning to face the room and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS_WASH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling like you could do with having a quick clean, you step over to the sinks and thoroughly wash your [pc.hands], before splashing some water on your [pc.face]. Grabbing a paper towel from the nearby dispenser, you quickly dry yourself off, before turning to face the room and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TOILETS_MAKE_HOLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Looking around to make sure that there's no member of the cleaning staff or an Enforcer in the restroom, you enter one of the stalls and take out your bladed weapon. Slicing it into the thin wooden wall of the stall, you swiftly slice it around in a small circle, before popping out the round piece of wood and admiring the glory hole you've just made.
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeling turned on at the thought of being the one responsible for the lewd acts which will undoubtedly be performed in this stall's immediate future, you put away your blade and take a look through to the stall that's connected to this one. Nobody's in there right now, but it's only a matter of time before your act of vandalism is discovered, and you wonder whether it's time for you to leave or to risk the chance of being fined in order to dominantly use the glory hole or submissively service it...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>