<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="TRANSACTION_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After you've informed her that you're thinking of purchasing some jewellery, Penelope leads you a short way over to the display cabinet in which she keeps such items, before politely saying in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(Please let me know if you'd like to try anything on.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="BUY_TRANSACTION_COMPLETE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Informing Penelope that you'd like to purchase the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0], you hand over [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] flames and wait for her to retrieve it from the display cabinet. Presenting you with your purchase, Penelope smiles and asks, [penelope.speech(Will that be all for today, [pc.sir], or do you have another transaction in mind?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SELL_TRANSACTION_COMPLETE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Asking Penelope if she'd like to buy your [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0], you wait as she thinks for a moment, before offering you [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] flames for it. Agreeing to the sale, you hand over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] in exchange for the agreed upon price, after which Penelope politely asks, [penelope.speech(Is there anything else I can do for you today, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- All of these are linked to the 'dialogue/innoxia/places/fields/elis/shops/spa.xml' dialogue nodes. -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Over in one of the far corners of the shopping precinct, a sign hanging from the upper floor of a timber-framed building shows a stylised pair of sheep-girls holding up the words 'Woolly Heaven'. Blinds have been half-closed over most of the windows on the ground floor, and the spots which aren't concealed in this manner are home to shelves stacked full of potted plants and cosmetics products, making it all but impossible to see into the building's interior. Thankfully for potential customers, the nature of this business is revealed from the writing that's etched into the glass of its front door. [pc.Stepping] forwards to take a closer look, you read: 'Woolly Heaven: Spa, Massage Parlour, & Beauticians'
	</p>
	<p>
		Beneath this brief overview, you see that the business's opening hours are 
		#IF(game.isHourBetween(9, 24))
			'[style.colourMinorGood([units.time(9)]-[units.time(0)])]', meaning that it's currently [style.colourGood(open)]. If you wanted to make use of any of the three services which this business provides, there's nothing stopping you from heading inside... 
		#ELSE
			'[style.colourMinorBad([units.time(9)]-[units.time(0)])]', meaning that it's currently [style.colourBad(closed)]. If you wanted to make use of any of the three services which this business provides, then you'll have to come back during its opening hours...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTER"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_elis_spa_visited))
		<p>
			Wanting to find out what's inside this 'Woolly Heaven' establishment, you push open the front door and [pc.step] inside. Within, you find yourself standing in a large, modern-looking reception area, with polished wooden floorboards underfoot and trendy oversized light bulbs hanging from the high ceiling. Standing behind a long, tall counter that's been roughly hewn from the trunk of a large tree and topped with frosted glass, a border collie-girl is giving you a warm smile. As the door swings shut behind you, she calls out in a very posh accent, [penelope.speech(Good [style.afternoon], [pc.sir], and welcome to 'Woolly Heaven'. My name is Penelope Fear, and I'm the manager and owner of this establishment.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As you return her greeting, you see that Penelope is wearing a very suggestive, burgundy 'virgin-killer' sweater, and is sporting several pieces of gold jewellery. While this eye-catching outfit would undoubtedly look too daring on most people, Penelope's beautiful features and perfectly proportioned body allow her to carry it off. Her anthropomorphic, border collie-like face is absolutely gorgeous, and as she bats her large, [penelope.eyeColour] eyes at you, she leans forwards a little in order to flaunt her [penelope.cupSize]-cup breasts.
		</p>
		<p>
			Her effortless beauty grants her the same sort of aura that's radiated by the harpy matriarch, Helena, and just like that swan-harpy, Penelope also appears to have spent some time pursuing a career in modelling. Posters and pages from fashion magazines have been framed and hung all over the walls of this reception area, with each one showing Penelope posing in a different outfit. There are even a couple from what look to be soft-core pornography publications, in which the border collie-girl is baring her naked breasts and making suggestive expressions at the viewer.
		</p>
		<p>
			[penelope.speech(Unless I'm mistaken, I haven't had the pleasure of meeting you before. May I ask for your name?)] Penelope asks, before resting her chin on her interlaced hands and giving you a delightful smile.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Deciding to once again pay a visit to this 'Woolly Heaven' establishment, you push open the front door and [pc.step] inside. Within, you find yourself standing in a large, modern-looking reception area, with polished wooden floorboards underfoot and trendy oversized light bulbs hanging from the high ceiling. Standing behind a long, tall counter that's been roughly hewn from the trunk of a large tree and topped with frosted glass, the familiar, beautiful figure of Penelope is giving you a warm smile. As the door swings shut behind you, the border collie-girl calls out in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(Good [style.afternoon], [pc.sir], and welcome once again to 'Woolly Heaven'.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As you return her greeting, you see that Penelope is wearing a very suggestive, burgundy 'virgin-killer' sweater, and is sporting several pieces of gold jewellery. While this eye-catching outfit would undoubtedly look too daring on most people, Penelope's beautiful features and perfectly proportioned body allow her to carry it off. Her anthropomorphic, border collie-like face is absolutely gorgeous, and as she bats her large, [penelope.eyeColour] eyes at you, she leans forwards a little in order to flaunt her [penelope.cupSize]-cup breasts.
		</p>
		<p>
			Her effortless beauty grants her the same sort of aura that's radiated by the harpy matriarch, Helena, and just like that swan-harpy, Penelope also appears to have spent some time pursuing a career in modelling. Posters and pages from fashion magazines have been framed and hung all over the walls of this reception area, with each one showing Penelope posing in a different outfit. There are even a couple from what look to be soft-core pornography publications, in which the border collie-girl is baring her naked breasts and making suggestive expressions at the viewer.
		</p>
		<p>
			As you approach her counter, Penelope states in her posh voice, [penelope.speech(Please let me know which of our services you require, [pc.sir]. Oh, and remember that my sheep-girls and I all have prostitution licenses, so paying for sex once you're in a massage room is all completely legal and above board.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="COSMETICS_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You tell Penelope that you'd like to make use of her services as an arcane beautician. Guiding you over to one side of the large reception area, she asks you to take a seat in front of a stylish mirror, before asking, [penelope.speech(So, what'll it be, [pc.sir]? Would you like to try a new hair style, or were you thinking of something a little more adventurous than that?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Gesturing over to a jewellery display cabinet situated a short distance from where you're sitting, the beautiful border collie-girl reminds you, [penelope.speech(I also have several items of jewellery for sale, so please don't hesitate to ask if you'd like to try anything on.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_POSTERS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Gesturing to the framed posters and pages from fashion magazines which have been hung on the surrounding walls, you ask Penelope if she's still pursuing a career in modelling.
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(Oh, no, I left all of that behind me when I departed from Dominion,)] she replies. Taking a moment to look around at the posters, she smiles and reveals, [penelope.speech(I was a model for almost ten years, and by the end I'd had enough of it. Don't get me wrong, it was a lot of fun to be doing all of that travelling around and getting to model all of the latest designer outfits, but after almost a decade of doing it I really felt like I needed a change.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Penelope pauses for a moment, allowing you to ask if that's when she decided to move here to Elis.
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(That's right,)] she says, [penelope.speech(I'd always wanted to have my own spa, and thanks to the money I'd made from being a top model, I was able to purchase this building and have it converted into 'Woolly Heaven'. I'd actually always planned to open this place in the middle of Dominion, but I felt like I had to leave the city to get away from my twin sister, Pix. I don't know if you've ever had the pleasure of meeting her; she runs a gym in Dominion's Shopping Arcade.)]
	</p>
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_pix_introduced))
		<p>
			Having visited Pix's gym, you tell Penelope that you have indeed met her, but you don't recall her mentioning that she had a twin sister.
		</p>
		<p>
			[penelope.speech(Oh, that'd be because we didn't part on the best of terms,)] Penelope sighs, [penelope.speech(No matter how many times I told her that I had no interest in such an arrangement, she kept on insisting that I come and work at her gym. When I told her that I'd be leaving Dominion to set up a business in Elis, she started ranting about me betraying her... Oh, pardon me, I didn't mean to bore you with my silly family feud. Is there anything else I can do for you today, [pc.name]?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having not visited Pix's gym in Dominion, you tell Penelope that you haven't met her twin sister.
		</p>
		<p>
			[penelope.speech(Ah, well if you do meet her, it might be best to not mention me. We didn't part on the best of terms, and she might get annoyed if you ask her about me,)] Penelope sighs, before continuing, [penelope.speech(You see, no matter how many times I told her that I had no interest in such an arrangement, she kept on insisting that I come and work at her gym. When I told her that I'd be leaving Dominion to set up a business in Elis, she started ranting about me betraying her... Oh, pardon me, I didn't mean to bore you with my silly family feud. Is there anything else I can do for you today, [pc.sir]?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_SHEEP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious to find out why all of Penelope's employees are sheep-morphs, you ask her if that was a conscious choice to fit with the name of her spa, or if it came about naturally and the name 'Woolly Heaven' was chosen afterwards.
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(I'd always planned to hire only sheep-morphs,)] Penelope reveals, before stating, [penelope.speech(I find sheep-girls to be particularly easy to manage and control, and clients seem to really love their woolly bodies. Unlike feral sheep, the wool which covers a sheep-morph is soft and luxurious to the touch, doubly so after it's been treated with the right shampoo and conditioner.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wondering why she finds sheep-morphs easy to manage, you ask Penelope what the reason for this is.
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(I honestly couldn't say,)] she replies, before taking a moment to think and then ponder out loud, [penelope.speech(I suppose it must be due to my instincts as a border collie-morph... Every time I see a sheep-morph I get this strong desire to tell them what to do... Well, whatever the case may be, having sheep-morphs as my employees makes it very easy for me to manage my spa. Now, can I interest you in any of our services, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Saying goodbye to Penelope, you exit Woolly Heaven and find yourself [pc.stepping] back out into Wall's End...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="INTRODUCTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] up to the counter, you give Penelope your name, to which she happily replies in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(It's a pleasure to meet you, [pc.name]. Would you like to hear what services we offer here at Woolly Heaven?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Replying in the positive, you listen as the border collie-girl reels off a sales pitch that she's no doubt repeated many dozens of times before, [penelope.speech(Our main attraction is our indoor spa; we have steam rooms, saunas, a pool, and both cold and heated baths. Entry to the spa costs one hundred and fifty flames. I'm also trained and fully qualified as an arcane beautician, so I can alter almost any aspect of your appearance, including applying, removing, and even enchanting tattoos. I also have several items of jewellery for sale at our cosmetics station, if you're interested in that.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she's not yet finished with her recitation of offered services, Penelope pauses for a moment to flash you a flirtatious grin. Slightly altering the tone of her voice so as to grant her posh accent an air of seduction, she continues, [penelope.speech(We also offer massages, which start at two hundred and fifty flames for a session with one of my sheep-girls. For an extra seven hundred and fifty flames, I'll personally give you your massage. If you choose to receive a massage, then once it's started you'll be able to purchase some more... <i>exciting</i> services from your masseuse.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you take a moment to think about what services, if any, you'd like to use, Penelope smirks and bluntly states in her posh voice, [penelope.speech(Just so that I've made myself clear, my sheep-girls and I all have prostitution licenses, so you can pay for sex once you're in a massage room. So, what'll it be, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="POST_COSMETICS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having got everything you wanted from Penelope's arcane cosmetics service, you tell her that you're happy with how you look, and that you don't need anything more from her. Flashing you a warm smile, the border collie-girl leads you back over to her desk, before asking, [penelope.speech(Is there anything else I can do for you today, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RELAX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling as though you're in need of some time in which to relax and unwind, you tell Penelope that you'd like to have a session in the spa. After you've handed over the one hundred and fifty flames which she asks for, Penelope leads you over to a doorway on the far side of the reception area. Standing to one side, she gestures towards it and says, [penelope.speech(You'll find the changing rooms and lockers in the room beyond. Please spend as much time as you'd like in the spa, and if there's any issue please don't hesitate to report it to a member of staff.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking Penelope, you [pc.step] forwards through the doorway, and after turning a corner, find yourself in a large, unisex changing room. A politely-worded sign fixed to a nearby wall informs you that there's no dress code, and so you're free to wear as much or as little as you like while in the spa. Stripping out of your clothes, you make use of one of the lockers in which to store your personal belongings, before proceeding into the showers beyond.
	</p>
	<p>
		A quick wash later, and you're [pc.stepping] out into the main area of the spa, which contains a couple of large pools surrounded by dozens of loungers. Signs around the edge of this cavernous interior offer directions to the steam rooms, saunas, and baths. Looking around, you see that there are several clients making use of the spa facilities, and a sheep-girl member of staff is watching over the area to make sure that everything remains calm and under control. None of the people who are present show any sign of being interested in anything other than quietly relaxing, and so with your only real option being to follow their example, you prepare to spend some alone time in which to relax and unwind...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RELAX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		For the next couple of hours you make your way around the spa, using all of the facilities which it has to offer. Eventually, having had your fill of the pool, steam room, sauna, and baths, you feel like you're as relaxed and calm as you've ever been. Deciding that you've had enough of the spa for now, you head on back to the changing rooms.
	</p>
	<p>
		Retrieve your belongings from your locker, you get dressed and return to the reception area, where you see the beautiful border collie-girl, Penelope, standing behind the counter. Looking over at you as you [pc.step] over towards her, she smiles and asks in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(I trust everything was to your satisfaction in the spa, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Responding in the positive, you tell Penelope that you enjoyed using the facilities, and that you're now feeling well and truly relaxed and refreshed. Leaning forwards over her counter, the border collie-girl pushes out her chest to show off her [penelope.cupSize]-cup breasts and teases, [penelope.speech(Perhaps after that you're feeling in the mood for fucking one of my sheep-girls? Or perhaps even myself? How about you have a nice massage and see where it leads...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Playfully winking at you, Penelope waits to hear if you'll take her up on her offer, or perhaps ask for something else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have the tension worked out of your muscles, you tell Penelope that you'd like to have a massage, and then proceed to give her the two hundred and fifty flames which she asks for. Giving you a warm smile, she states, [penelope.speech(I have many sheep-girls who work for me, but there are three who are undoubtedly my best. As it so happens, all three are available at the moment, so you'll be free to choose any one of them.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the border collie-girl reaches down under her counter and presses three buttons, one after the other. As each of these buttons are pressed, you hear three faint chimes – each one of which having a slightly different pitch – ring out from down the corridor which leads off from behind where Penelope is standing. Just a moment later, and one of the corridor's many doors swings open. After looking back to see who's the first sheep-girl to appear, Penelope turns to smile at you and say in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(It seems as though the first masseuse to arrive is Belle...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking past Penelope, you see a beautiful, white-woollen sheep-girl, who looks to be in her late teens, excitedly skipping down the corridor towards you. As she approaches, you see that her light-pink outfit consists of a microskirt, crotchless thong, and a conspicuously-untied croptop. As such, this sheep-girl's tight pussy and small, [belle.cupSize]-cup breasts are completely exposed. Coming to a halt in front of you, she lewdly squeezes her tits, before teasing her fingers over her exposed pussy and giggling, [belle.speech(Heya! You lookin' for a massage, or are you here to fuck this hot little cunt of mine?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can respond to this blunt question, Belle leans forwards and reaches up to her neck, drawing your attention to the restraints around her wrists and ankles as she does so. Taking hold of the metal tag that's fixed to the front of her leather choker, she lifts it up so that you can see that it bears the words 'Worthless Cunt'. Letting out another giggle, she moves her hands to start playfully tugging on the silver rings which have been fitted to her large, pierced nipples, before locking her light blue eyes on yours and moaning, [belle.speech(As a special service, I let my clients tie me up and punish me like the dirty slut that I am! I want you to make me scream like a filthy whore!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment, another door down the corridor swings open, and Penelope sharply orders Belle to quieten down before announcing, [penelope.speech(It looks as though Daphne is the second masseuse to answer her summons...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_INTRO_NEXT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again looking past Penelope, you see that this Daphne takes the form of a brown-woollen sheep-girl, who looks to be in her early thirties. Equally as attractive as Belle, although in a more mature way, this masseuse is wearing a dark brown outfit, which consists of a microskirt, crotchless panties, and an unzipped leather jacket. Just like with Belle, these items of clothing leave her slightly-loose pussy and [daphne.cupSize]-cup breasts completely exposed. The bell collar which is fitted around her neck softly jingles as she comes to a halt beside her younger co-worker, and after submissively batting her eyelids at you, she teases, [daphne.speech(I'm not into the rough stuff like Belle, but I do enjoy being dominated... After your massage, I'd like it if you'd give me a good fuck.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[belle.speech(No way, Daph! [pc.SheIs] going to pick me!)] Belle objects.
	</p>
	<p>
		[daphne.speech(Well, that's only if [pc.sheIs] not interested in a sheep-girl who has some real assets,)] Daphne teases as she steps forwards and presses her comparatively huge breasts against Belle's. The younger sheep-girl lets out an annoyed huff in response to Daphne's move, which the brown-woollen masseuse takes as a sign of surrender. Patronisingly patting Belle on the head, she states, [daphne.speech(Besides, not everybody's into the sort of masochism which you love.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping back from the muttering Belle, Daphne reaches down to tease her fingers over her dark labia, before moving up beside you and lowering her voice to whisper into your ear, [daphne.speech(I've got a very special service for my clients. I love doing a little pet-play, you see, and so if you choose me, I can pretend to be a dumb sheep as you fuck me like an animal...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment a third door down the corridor begins to slowly swing open, and Penelope issues yet another sharp order to silence both Belle and Daphne before saying, [penelope.speech(The last masseuse which I have for you is our dear Farah...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_INTRO_FINAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		For the final time, you look past Penelope to see a black-woollen sheep-girl, who looks to be in her late forties, walking down the corridor towards you. Just like the other two sheep-girls, she's very attractive, although in a much more mature way than Belle or Daphne. The only items of clothing which she's wearing are some gold jewellery and a black corset, which she might have chosen to wear to help conceal the fact that she's a little on the chubby side. Swaying her womanly hips as she advances to stand in front of you, this mature sheep-girl smiles and says in a soft voice, [farah.speech(Hello there, sugar. If you're looking for an experienced masseuse, then I'm the one for you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Jealously glancing at Farah's exposed, [farah.cupSize]-cup breasts, Daphne mutters, [daphne.speech(You don't let the clients have any fun though...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[farah.speech(That's not true at all,)] Farah responds, before dominantly stepping forwards and pressing her huge breasts up against your torso. Locking her big, hazel eyes onto yours, she gently strokes one of her hands up your [pc.leg(true)] and reveals, [farah.speech(What Daphne means is that I insist on always being the one in charge. We can have plenty of gentle fun together, but I'm not going to be your submissive little fuck-toy. Choose one of these younger girls if you want that sort of thing.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As if to demonstrate her commitment to being the dominant partner, Farah takes hold of your [pc.hand] and gets you to tease your fingers over her [farah.labia+] as she leans forwards to softly moan, [farah.speech(If you like risky sex or trying to get girls pregnant, then my special service is for you. After giving you your massage, I'll be willing to take a fertility pill and give you the chance to knock me up...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With Farah having completed her introduction, Penelope sharply orders her to step back. Letting out a soft sigh, the black-woollen sheep-girl does as she's told and falls back to stand in line with Belle and Daphne, allowing Penelope to move forwards and address you once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_INTRO_FINAL_PENELOPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(So there you have it,)] the border collie-girl states, [penelope.speech(Belle's into being used and abused, Daphne loves being a submissive little sheep, and Farah always demands to be in charge. If you've got an extra seven hundred and fifty flames, then you can always pay to personally receive a massage from me instead. If you've got the cash, then we can fuck after your massage as well, but first you should see what you'll be in for...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Penelope quickly steps around to your side of the counter, before suddenly hiking up the bottom of her virgin-killer sweater and hooking her thumbs into her lacy panties. A moment later, and she's pulled down her underwear so as to fully expose her genitals to you. Looking down, you see that this border collie-girl not only has the dog-pussy that you expected between her legs, but she also has a sheathed canine cock. Teasing her fingers over her hermaphroditic groin, Penelope lewdly sighs, [penelope.speech(I like having both my cock and pussy used, so whatever you're into will be fine with me. Oh, and I'm a bit of a switch, so if you want me to submit or take charge, then I'm happy to do either.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[belle.speech(Her cock feels amazing,)] Belle teases.
	</p>
	<p>
		[daphne.speech(Yeah, taking her knot makes me orgasm every time,)] Daphne confirms.
	</p>
	<p>
		[farah.speech(I prefer her pussy, myself,)] Farah states, letting you know that all three of these sheep-girls have had sex with Penelope.
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling her underwear back up and moving her sweater back down into its previous position, Penelope ignores her masseuses' comments and addresses you once again, [penelope.speech(I offer a couple of special post-massage services. I can either dress up in one of my old outfits and do a little fashion show for you, or I can use both my cock and pussy to give you what I like to call a 'double facial'. So, what would you like for your first massage, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Penelope joins the three sheep-girls in waiting to hear who you'll choose for your first massage...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have the tension worked out of your muscles, you tell Penelope that you'd like to have a massage, and then proceed to give her the two hundred and fifty flames which she asks for. Giving you a warm smile, she states, [penelope.speech(Belle, Daphne, and Farah are once again available at the moment. Please wait one moment while I call them here for you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the border collie-girl reaches down under her counter and presses three buttons, one after the other. As each of these buttons are pressed, you hear three faint chimes – each one of which having a slightly different pitch – ring out from down the corridor which leads off from behind where Penelope is standing. Just a moment later, and three of the corridor's many doors swing open, one after the other. Looking past Penelope, you see the familiar figures of Belle, Daphne, and Farah walking towards you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[belle.speech(Heya, [pc.name]!)] the white-woollen Belle teases calls out as she rushes up to where you're standing. Drawing your attention to the words 'Worthless Cunt' which are stamped on the metallic tag of her choker, she grins and teases, [belle.speech(After your massage, you can tie me up and fuck me as hard as you want!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[daphne.speech(If you fancy something a little gentler than what Belle has in mind, then we could do a bit of pet-play together,)] Daphne suggests as she steps up beside Belle, before seductively pinching her exposed nipples and biting her lip.
	</p>
	<p>
		[farah.speech(I'll leave those submissive games to the younger sheep,)] Farah says with a smirk as she approaches.
		#IF(farah.isPregnant())
			 Rubbing her hands over her
			#IF(farah.isVisiblyPregnant())
				 visibly-pregnant
			#ENDIF
			 belly, she winks at you and teases, [farah.speech(As you've already got me knocked up, my special service obviously isn't available, but we can still have a nice, gentle fuck after your massage.)]
		#ELSE
			 Placing one hand on her hip, she uses her other to stroke her pussy as she teases, [farah.speech(Remember that I'll be the one who's in charge if you want a nice, gentle fuck with me.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(So there you have it,)] Penelope states, [penelope.speech(Belle's into being used and abused, Daphne loves being a submissive little sheep, and Farah always demands to be in charge. If you've got an extra seven hundred and fifty flames, then you can always pay to personally receive a massage from me instead. If you've got the cash, then we can fuck after your massage as well, but just remember that I'm packing a cock as well as a cunt, so if that's not your thing then don't waste my time.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Penelope joins the three sheep-girls in waiting to hear who you'll choose for your first massage...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Changing your mind, you tell Penelope that you don't want a massage after all. The three sheep-girls each let out disappointed whines and sighs as they hear this, before turning around and walking off back to their rooms. Giving you a polite smile, Penelope hands you back your flames and states, [penelope.speech(Very well, [pc.sir]. Here's your two hundred and fifty flames. Please let me know if there's anything else I can do for you today.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking the border collie-girl, you wonder what to ask of her next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Belle massage: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_BELLE_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a massage from Belle, you tell the young, white-woollen sheep-girl that you've chosen her. Happily jumping up and down on the spot, she exclaims, [belle.speech(Hooray! Hey, after your massage, you're gonna want to wreck my hot little cunt, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(There'll be plenty of time to discuss that once you've started giving [pc.name] [pc.her] massage,)] Penelope reprimands her excitable employee, before addressing you in her calm, posh accent, [penelope.speech(Please follow Belle to her massage room, and I hope that you'll enjoy your time with her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With Penelope's admonishment having done very little to calm the excitable sheep-girl, Belle eagerly grabs hold of your [pc.hand] and impatiently pulls you along after her as she leads you down the corridor to her room. A moment later, and she's closing the door behind you as you take a look around the room in which you're to receive your massage. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like the reception area, this massage room has been furnished in a modern, trendy style. The floor consists of the same polished wooden floorboards which are found throughout the rest of the establishment, and on all four sides the pale pink walls are illuminated via oversized light bulbs which hang down from the high ceiling. Industrial-style shelving covers one wall, and is filled with all manner of potted plants, miscellaneous ornaments, and beauty products. Wooden blinds cover the window that's set into the opposite wall, granting you and Belle total privacy for what's about to happen on the large, modular massage table that's located right in the centre of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			[belle.speech(Hold on one moment; I'll just adjust the table to fit your body type,)]
		#ELSE
			[belle.speech(Hold on one moment; I'll just adjust the table to fit your height,)]
		#ENDIF
		 Belle happily says, before skipping over to the massage table and adjusting some of its padded surfaces. After she's finished, she gestures to the table and smiles at you as she says, [belle.speech(If you'll just strip naked and then lie down on here, I'll begin your massage straight away!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as Belle asks, you strip naked for her, and after you've lain down on the massage table, she places her soft hands on your torso and starts to give you a firm, enthusiastic massage. Despite her young age, she's extremely proficient at her job, and you find yourself melting in pleasure under the pressure which she applies to every part of your body.
	</p>
	<p>
		After almost ten minutes have flown by in this manner, your masseuse lets out a cheeky little giggle, before asking, [belle.speech(So, would you like me to continue with the rest of your massage, or would you prefer one of my special services? I can give you a nice groin 'massage' for a hundred flames, an oral 'massage' for two hundred and fifty, or we can get right on to fucking for five hundred. If you'd like to indulge me in my favourite fetish, then for seven hundred and fifty flames you can tie me up to this table and fuck me senseless... So, what'll it be?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_BELLE_HANDS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of having Belle's hands focused on your
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 cock and pussy,
			#ELSE
				 cock,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 pussy,
		#ENDIF
		 you tell her that you want her special groin 'massage', before handing over the hundred flames which she's asked for. Letting out an excited squeal, the sheep-girl quickly stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before hastily returning to kneel down before your groin. Teasing her fingers down towards your genitals, she bites her lip and lustfully moans, [belle.speech(I'll make you cum in no time... Just lie back and enjoy this...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				Gripping your hard cock in one hand, the sheep-girl starts to slide her fingers up and down around your throbbing length, letting out hungry little moans as she does so. After a few strokes, she starts to move her free hand towards your pussy, and once it's there, she quickly slides her fingers into your cunt and starts to finger you while simultaneously continuing to give you a handjob. With both of your sexual organs being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Belle, who teases, [belle.speech(That's it, let yourself go! ~Mmm!~ You'll be climaxing soon enough...)]
			#ELSE
				Gripping your hard cock in one hand, the sheep-girl starts to slide her fingers up and down around your throbbing length, letting out hungry little moans as she does so. With your [pc.cock+] being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Belle, who teases, [belle.speech(That's it, let yourself go! ~Mmm!~ You'll be cumming soon enough...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			After teasing her fingers up and down over your [pc.labia+], the sheep-girl pauses for a moment to play with your clit, before suddenly sliding her fingers into your cunt and starting to finger you. With your [pc.pussy+] being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Belle, who teases, [belle.speech(That's it, let yourself go! ~Mmm!~ You'll be climaxing soon enough...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_BELLE_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of having Belle continue her massage with her mouth, you tell her that you want her special oral 'massage', before handing over the two hundred and fifty flames which she's asked for. Letting out an excited squeal, the sheep-girl quickly stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before hastily returning to kneel down before your groin. Leaning forwards so that you can feel her hot breath on your
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 cock and pussy, Belle bites her lip and lustfully moans, [belle.speech(I'll make you cum in no time... Just lie back and enjoy this... Oh, and just let me know whenever you want me to switch to eating you out...)]
			#ELSE
				 cock, Belle bites her lip and lustfully moans, [belle.speech(I'll make you cum in no time... Just lie back and enjoy this...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 pussy, Belle bites her lip and lustfully moans, [belle.speech(I'll make you climax in no time... Just lie back and enjoy this...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			Parting her lips, the sheep-girl darts out her tongue and delivers a long, wet lick up the underside of your hard cock, before opening wide and taking your [pc.cockHead+] into her mouth. Letting out hungry, muffled moans, she starts enthusiastically bobbing her head up and down as she gives you a blowjob. As you feel your [pc.cock+] being taken deep down the sheep-girl's tight, wet throat, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], which encourages Belle to suddenly deepthroat you. After gazing longingly up into your eyes for a moment, she pulls her head up and wetly sucks the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+], before continuing to give you head...
		#ELSE
			After leaning in to plant a big, wet kiss on your [pc.clit+], the sheep-girl darts out her tongue and delivers a series of long, wet licks to your [pc.labia+]. Letting out hungry, muffled moans, she then presses her face into your groin and starts enthusiastically darting her tongue into your [pc.pussy+]. As the sheep-girl starts to perform cunnilingus, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], which encourages Belle to grind her face into your cunt and thrust her tongue as deep as possible into your hot, wet pussy. After gazing longingly up into your eyes for a moment, she pulls back and lifts her head up to wetly suck on your [pc.clit+], before continuing to eat you out...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_BELLE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have a session of full-on sex with Belle, you give her five hundred flames and tell her that you're going to fuck her. Letting out an excited squeal, the sheep-girl quickly stores your money in a nearby cabinet as you get up from the massage table and prepare to get started.
	</p>
	<p>
		[belle.speech(You can fuck me like this if you want,)] Belle teases as she lies back on the table that you've just vacated. Spreading her legs, she reaches down to her exposed pussy and uses two of her digits to spread her [belle.labia+]. Lewdly presenting her tight cunt to you, she bites her lip and whines, [belle.speech(I love getting a good, hard fuck, so be as rough with me as you want! I'll be your good little bitch!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] forwards and preparing to take advantage of Belle's submissive position, you wonder how best to start...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_BELLE_BONDAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of getting to tie Belle to the table and fuck her as hard as you want, you give her seven hundred and fifty flames and tell her that you're going to bind her up tight. Letting out an excited squeal, the sheep-girl quickly stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before producing a length of rope and instructing you to trade places with her.
	</p>
	<p>
		[belle.speech(Tie it up nice and tight around my legs and arms,)] Belle tells you as she hands you the rope and lies back on the massage table. Spreading her legs, she reaches down to her exposed pussy and uses two of her digits to spread her [belle.labia+]. Lewdly presenting her tight cunt to you, she bites her lip and whines, [belle.speech(Tie me up and then show my dirty little pussy no mercy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to do as she asks, you start by tying Belle's legs to the massage table, and thanks to the leather restraints which she's wearing around her ankles, you're able to tightly bind her lower limbs to the table's legs. Moving up, you then take hold of the sheep-girl's arms, and one after the other, you securely tie them down to a pair of metal struts which seem to have been added to the table for just such a binding. Finding herself now securely tied down, Belle pouts at you and struggle a little to show that she's unable to escape, before passionately moaning, [belle.speech(Yes! ~Mmm!~ Come on, give me a hard, rough fuck! Abuse me as much as you want! ~Aah!~ I'm your good little fuck-toy! Break me!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] forwards and preparing to take advantage of Belle's immobility, you wonder how best to start...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_BELLE_CONTINUE_MASSAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting this massage session to turn into anything sexual, you tell Belle that you don't want to purchase any of her special services. Letting out a disappointed whine, she teases, [belle.speech(Aww, fine... Well, maybe next time you'll be in the mood for something fun!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the sheep-girl lets out a little laugh, before pressing her hands down into your torso and continuing to give you your massage. Working her hands all over your body, she once again demonstrates her proficiency at her job, and within just a matter of moments you find yourself letting out a steady stream of satisfied hums and sighs...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_BELLE_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ten minutes later, and with your body feeling well and truly relaxed, Belle steps back and happily announces, [belle.speech(There we go, we're all finished for this session!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Getting up off the massage table and getting dressed, you thank Belle for her service and tell her what an excellent job she's done. Giving you a big grin as she hears your praise, the sheep-girl happily claps her hands together and replies, [belle.speech(You're welcome! Maybe next time you'll be in the mood for some other services as well, and then you can see how good I am at those, too!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_BELLE_FINISHED_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With that, Belle asks you to accompany her back to reception, and so after exiting the room, you follow her down the corridor and find yourself once again standing before Penelope's counter. Smiling at the two of you, the border collie-girl asks, [penelope.speech(I trust that Belle was able to satisfy you, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've responded in the positive, Penelope tells Belle that she's done a good job, before dismissing the sheep-girl and turning her attention back to you. Leaning forwards over her counter and playfully pushing her large, [penelope.cupSize]-cup breasts towards you, she asks in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(Is there anything else which I can do for you today, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_BELLE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having finished giving you her special service, Belle lets out one last passionate moan, before informing you that the fun's over. Disentangling yourself from the panting sheep-girl, you set about getting your things back in order while Belle proceeds to clean herself up.
	</p>
	<p>
		[belle.speech(That was a lot of fun! Thanks for choosing me, [pc.name], and for buying one of my special services,)] Belle says as she steps over to unlock the door. Telling her that you had a lot of fun too, you make sure that you've retrieved all of your possessions before preparing to head back to reception...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Daphne massage: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_DAPHNE_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a massage from Daphne, you tell the brown-woollen sheep-girl that you've chosen her. Letting out a happy little laugh, she flashes you a submissive smile and says, [daphne.speech(Thank you for choosing me. If you'll please follow me to my room, we can get started on your massage right away... And then after that, you can fuck me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Gesturing for you to follow her, Daphne sets off down the corridor, and you fall in behind her as she leads you to her room. A moment later, and she's closing the door behind you as you take a look around the room in which you're to receive your massage. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like the reception area, this massage room has been furnished in a modern, trendy style. The floor consists of the same polished wooden floorboards which are found throughout the rest of the establishment, and on all four sides the pale pink walls are illuminated via oversized light bulbs which hang down from the high ceiling. Industrial-style shelving covers one wall, and is filled with all manner of potted plants, miscellaneous ornaments, and beauty products. Wooden blinds cover the window that's set into the opposite wall, granting you and Daphne total privacy for what's about to happen on the large, modular massage table that's located right in the centre of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			[daphne.speech(Please wait for just one moment; I'll just adjust the table to fit your body type,)]
		#ELSE
			[daphne.speech(Please wait for just one moment; I'll just adjust the table to fit your height,)]
		#ENDIF
		 Daphne says, before hurrying over to the massage table and adjusting some of its padded surfaces. After she's finished, she gestures to the table and smiles at you as she says, [daphne.speech(If you'll just strip naked and then lie down on here, I'll begin your massage straight away!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as Daphne asks, you strip naked for her, and after you've lain down on the massage table, she places her soft hands on your torso and starts to firmly massage your muscles. It very quickly becomes apparent that Daphne is exceptionally proficient at her job, as you soon find yourself melting in pleasure under the pressure which she applies to every part of your body.
	</p>
	<p>
		After almost ten minutes have flown by in this manner, your masseuse lets out a quiet, hungry moan, before asking, [daphne.speech(Should I continue with the rest of your massage, or would you prefer one of my special services? I can offer you a groin 'massage' for a hundred flames, an oral 'massage' for two hundred and fifty, or you can dominantly fuck me for five hundred. If you'd like to indulge me in my favourite fetish, then for seven hundred and fifty flames I'll pretend to be a dumb, horny little sheep for you to fuck... So, what'll it be?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_DAPHNE_HANDS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of having Daphne's hands focused on your
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 cock and pussy,
			#ELSE
				 cock,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 pussy,
		#ENDIF
		 you tell her that you want her special groin 'massage', before handing over the hundred flames which she's asked for. Letting out an excited moan, the sheep-girl quickly stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before hastily returning to kneel down before your groin. Teasing her fingers down towards your genitals, she bites her lip and lustfully sighs, [daphne.speech(I'll be a good girl and make you cum... Please lie back and enjoy this...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				Gripping your hard cock in one hand, the sheep-girl starts to slide her fingers up and down around your throbbing length, letting out hungry little moans as she does so. After a few strokes, she starts to move her free hand towards your pussy, and once it's there, she quickly slides her fingers into your cunt and starts to finger you while simultaneously continuing to give you a handjob. With both of your sexual organs being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Daphne, who happily pants, [daphne.speech(That's it, let your good little sheep pleasure you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be climaxing soon enough...)]
			#ELSE
				Gripping your hard cock in one hand, the sheep-girl starts to slide her fingers up and down around your throbbing length, letting out hungry little moans as she does so. With your [pc.cock+] being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Daphne, who happily pants, [daphne.speech(That's it, let your good little sheep pleasure you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be cumming soon enough...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			After teasing her fingers up and down over your [pc.labia+], the sheep-girl pauses for a moment to play with your clit, before suddenly sliding her fingers into your cunt and starting to finger you. With your [pc.pussy+] being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Daphne, who happily pants, [daphne.speech(That's it, let your good little sheep pleasure you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be climaxing soon enough...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_DAPHNE_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of having Daphne continue her massage with her mouth, you tell her that you want her special oral 'massage', before handing over the two hundred and fifty flames which she's asked for. Letting out an excited moan, the sheep-girl quickly stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before hastily returning to kneel down before your groin. Leaning forwards so that you can feel her hot breath on your
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 cock and pussy, Daphne bites her lip and lustfully moans, [daphne.speech(I'll be a good little sheep and make you cum in no time... Please lie back and enjoy this... Oh, and please let me know whenever you want me to switch to eating you out...)]
			#ELSE
				 cock, Daphne bites her lip and lustfully moans, [daphne.speech(I'll be a good little sheep and make you cum in no time... Please lie back and enjoy this...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 pussy, Daphne bites her lip and lustfully moans, [daphne.speech(I'll be a good little sheep and make you climax in no time... Please lie back and enjoy this...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			Parting her lips, the sheep-girl darts out her tongue and delivers a long, wet lick up the underside of your hard cock, before opening wide and taking your [pc.cockHead+] into her mouth. Letting out hungry, muffled moans, she starts enthusiastically bobbing her head up and down as she gives you a blowjob. As you feel your [pc.cock+] being taken deep down the sheep-girl's tight, wet throat, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], which encourages Daphne to suddenly deepthroat you. After gazing longingly up into your eyes for a moment, she pulls her head up and wetly sucks the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+], before continuing to give you head...
		#ELSE
			After leaning in to plant a big, wet kiss on your [pc.clit+], the sheep-girl darts out her tongue and delivers a series of long, wet licks to your [pc.labia+]. Letting out hungry, muffled moans, she then presses her face into your groin and starts enthusiastically darting her tongue into your [pc.pussy+]. As the sheep-girl starts to perform cunnilingus, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], which encourages Daphne to grind her face into your cunt and thrust her tongue as deep as possible into your hot, wet pussy. After gazing longingly up into your eyes for a moment, she pulls back and lifts her head up to wetly suck on your [pc.clit+], before continuing to eat you out...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_DAPHNE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have a session of full-on sex with Daphne, you give her five hundred flames and tell her that you're going to dominantly fuck her. Letting out an excited squeal, the sheep-girl quickly stores your money in a nearby cabinet as you get up from the massage table and prepare to get started.
	</p>
	<p>
		[daphne.speech(I'll be your good little sheep,)] Daphne moans as she lies back on the table that you've just vacated. Spreading her legs, she reaches down to her exposed pussy and uses two of her digits to spread her [daphne.labia+]. Lewdly presenting her [daphne.pussyCapacity] cunt to you, she bites her lip and whines, [daphne.speech(Come on... ~Mmm!~ Dominate me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] forwards and preparing to take advantage of Daphne's submissive position, you wonder how best to start...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_DAPHNE_PET_PLAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of getting Daphne to engage in a little pet-play, you stand up, hand over seven hundred and fifty flames, and tell her that you want to fuck her while she's pretending to be a dumb sheep. Your masseuse's eyes light up as she hears what it is that you want, and after letting out an extremely horny moan, she hurries to store your money in a nearby cabinet. Rushing to take off all of her clothing and jewellery, with the exception of the bell collar around her neck, Daphne bites her lip and breathlessly sighs, [daphne.speech(Yes... I'll be your good, horny little sheep...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the sheep-girl drops down onto all fours and slowly crawls forwards, before turning around and presenting her rear-end to you. Submissively raising her ass, she turns back to give you an innocent look and lets out a surprisingly-convincing, [daphne.speech(~Baa!~)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Finding yourself quickly getting aroused at the sight of Daphne's commitment to acting like a dumb sheep, you [pc.step] forwards and prepare to fuck her. Turning her head back once more to watch your approach, Daphne spreads her legs a little and pushes her ass even further up into the air, and as she presents you with her
		#IF(game.isAnalContentEnabled())
			 [daphne.pussy+] and [daphne.asshole+],
		#ELSE
			 [daphne.pussy+],
		#ENDIF
		 she allows her sheep impersonation to take on a more lustful tone as she bleats once more, [daphne.speech(~Baa!~ ~Baa!~)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_DAPHNE_CONTINUE_MASSAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting this massage session to turn into anything sexual, you tell Daphne that you don't want to purchase any of her special services. Letting out a disappointed sigh, she states, [daphne.speech(As you wish... Maybe next time you'll be in the mood for something a little more fun...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the sheep-girl flashes you a warm smile, before pressing her hands down into your torso and continuing to give you your massage. Working her hands all over your body, she once again demonstrates her proficiency at her job, and within just a matter of moments you find yourself letting out a steady stream of satisfied hums and sighs...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_DAPHNE_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ten minutes later, and with your body feeling well and truly relaxed, Daphne steps back and announces with a slight note of satisfaction in her voice, [daphne.speech(Your massage is complete. I trust that it was enjoyable for you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Getting up off the massage table and getting dressed, you thank Daphne for her service and tell her what an excellent job she's done. Giving you a big smile as she hears your praise, the sheep-girl happily bows her head a little and replies, [daphne.speech(You're very welcome. Maybe next time you'll be in the mood for some other services as well, and then you can really see what a good, submissive little sheep I am...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_DAPHNE_FINISHED_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With that, Daphne asks you to accompany her back to reception, and so after exiting the room, you follow her down the corridor and find yourself once again standing before Penelope's counter. Smiling at the two of you, the border collie-girl asks, [penelope.speech(I trust that Daphne was able to satisfy you, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've responded in the positive, Penelope tells Daphne that she's done a good job, before dismissing the sheep-girl and turning her attention back to you. Leaning forwards over her counter and playfully pushing her large, [penelope.cupSize]-cup breasts towards you, she asks in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(Is there anything else which I can do for you today, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_DAPHNE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having finished giving you her special service, Daphne lets out one last passionate moan, before informing you that the fun's over. Disentangling yourself from the panting sheep-girl, you set about getting your things back in order while Daphne proceeds to clean herself up.
	</p>
	<p>
		[daphne.speech(That was a lot of fun... Thank you for choosing me, [pc.name], and for buying one of my special services,)] Daphne says as she steps over to unlock the door. Telling her that you had a lot of fun too, you make sure that you've retrieved all of your possessions before preparing to head back to reception...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Farah massage: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like a massage from Farah, you tell the mature, black-woollen sheep-girl that you've chosen her.
		#IF(farah.isPregnant())
			#IF(farah.isVisiblyPregnant())
				 Letting out an amused chuckle, she strokes her swollen belly and teases, [farah.speech(You just want me to fuck you while I'm pregnant, don't you, sugar?)]
			#ELSE
				 Letting out an amused chuckle, she strokes her belly and teases, [farah.speech(You just want me to fuck you while knowing that I'm pregnant, don't you, sugar?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 Letting out a soft chuckle, she flashes you a sly grin and teases, [farah.speech(What are you really wanting, sugar? A massage, or for to me to fuck you?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(There'll be plenty of time to discuss whether or not [pc.name] wants sex after you've started [pc.her] massage,)] Penelope reprimands her employee, before addressing you in her calm, posh accent, [penelope.speech(Please follow Farah to her massage room, and I hope that you'll enjoy your time with her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly not wanting to get into Penelope's bad books, Farah offers the border collie-girl a polite nod, before gesturing for you to follow along after her. Doing as she instructs, you tag along behind the black-woollen sheep-girl, and can't help but watch her exposed ass sway from side to side as she slowly struts down the corridor to her room. A moment later, and she's closing the door behind you as you take a look around the room in which you're to receive your massage. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like the reception area, this massage room has been furnished in a modern, trendy style. The floor consists of the same polished wooden floorboards which are found throughout the rest of the establishment, and on all four sides the pale pink walls are illuminated via oversized light bulbs which hang down from the high ceiling. Industrial-style shelving covers one wall, and is filled with all manner of potted plants, miscellaneous ornaments, and beauty products. Wooden blinds cover the window that's set into the opposite wall, granting you and Farah total privacy for what's about to happen on the large, modular massage table that's located right in the centre of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			[farah.speech(I know you were staring at my ass just now, sugar. You be a good [pc.girl] and keep watching while I adjust the table to fit your body type,)]
		#ELSE
			[farah.speech(I know you were staring at my ass just now, sugar. You be a good [pc.girl] and keep watching while I adjust the table to fit your height,)]
		#ENDIF
		 Farah teases, before sauntering over to the massage table and pushing her ass out towards you as she bends over to adjust some of its padded surfaces. After she's finished, she gestures to the table and smiles at you as she softly orders, [farah.speech(Strip naked and then lie down on here, sugar. I'm as keen to get this massage started as you are.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as Farah asks, you strip naked for her, and after you've lain down on the massage table, she places her soft hands on your torso and starts to firmly massage your muscles. It very quickly becomes apparent that Farah is absolutely exceptional at her job, as you almost immediately find yourself melting in pleasure under the pressure which she applies to every part of your body.
	</p>
	<p>
		After almost ten minutes have flown by in this manner, your masseuse lets out a soft, horny moan, before asking, [farah.speech(Should I continue with the rest of your massage, sugar, or would you prefer one of my special services? I can offer you a groin 'massage' for a hundred flames, an oral 'massage' for two hundred and fifty, or I can fuck you for five hundred.
		#IF(farah.isPregnant())
			 Seeing as you've already got me pregnant, I can't offer you my fertile sex special, so it'll have to be one of the other options if you're looking for some fun.
		#ELSE
			 If you were looking for something a little extra, and if you've got a thing for risky sex or knocking girls up, then for seven hundred and fifty flames I'll take a breeder pill and give you a shot at getting me pregnant.
		#ENDIF
		 So, what'll it be?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_HANDS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of having Farah's hands focused on your
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 cock and pussy,
			#ELSE
				 cock,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 pussy,
		#ENDIF
		 you tell her that you want her special groin 'massage', before handing over the hundred flames which she's asked for. Letting out a soft moan, the sheep-girl takes her time as she safely stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before stepping back towards you and kneeling down before your groin. Teasing her fingers down towards your genitals, she gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [farah.speech(Be a good [pc.girl] for me and relax... I'll make this good for you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				Dominantly taking hold of your hard cock in one hand, the sheep-girl starts to slide her fingers up and down around your throbbing length, letting out deep, quiet moans as she does so. After a few strokes, she starts to move her free hand towards your pussy, and once it's there, she slowly slides her fingers into your cunt and starts to gently finger you while simultaneously continuing to give you a handjob. With both of your sexual organs being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Farah, who happily teases, [farah.speech(That's it, sugar, let me take care of you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be climaxing for me soon enough...)]
			#ELSE
				Dominantly taking hold of your hard cock in one hand, the sheep-girl starts to gently slide her fingers up and down around your throbbing length, letting out deep, quiet moans as she does so. With your [pc.cock+] being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Farah, who happily teases, [farah.speech(That's it, sugar, let me take care of you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be cumming soon enough...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			After dominantly teasing her fingers up and down over your [pc.labia+], the sheep-girl pauses for a moment to play with your clit, before slowly sliding her fingers into your cunt and starting to gently finger you. With your [pc.pussy+] being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Farah, who happily teases, [farah.speech(That's it, sugar, let me take care of you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be climaxing soon enough...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of having Farah continue her massage with her mouth, you tell her that you want her special oral 'massage', before handing over the two hundred and fifty flames which she's asked for. Letting out a soft moan, the sheep-girl takes her time as she safely stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before stepping back towards you and kneeling down before your groin. Leaning forwards so that you can feel her hot breath on your
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 cock and pussy, Farah gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [farah.speech(Be a good [pc.girl] for me and relax... I'll make this good for you, sugar... Oh, and do let me know if you want me to switch to eating you out...)]
			#ELSE
				 cock, Farah gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [farah.speech(Be a good [pc.girl] for me and relax... I'll make this good for you, sugar...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 pussy, Farah gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [farah.speech(Be a good [pc.girl] for me and relax... I'll make this good for you, sugar...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			Parting her lips, the sheep-girl darts out her tongue and delivers a long, wet lick up the underside of your hard cock, before opening wide and taking your [pc.cockHead+] into her mouth. Letting out soft, muffled moans, she starts slowly bobbing her head up and down as she gives you a dominant blowjob. As you feel your [pc.cock+] being taken deep down the sheep-girl's tight, wet throat, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], which encourages Farah to suddenly deepthroat you. After gazing lovingly up into your eyes for a moment, she pulls her head up and wetly sucks the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+], before continuing to give you head...
		#ELSE
			After leaning in to plant a big, wet kiss on your [pc.clit+], the sheep-girl darts out her tongue and delivers a series of long, wet licks to your [pc.labia+]. Letting out soft, muffled moans, she then presses her face into your groin and starts slowly pushing her tongue into your [pc.pussy+]. As the sheep-girl starts to dominantly perform cunnilingus, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], which encourages Farah to press her face into your cunt and slide her tongue as deep as possible into your hot, wet pussy. After gazing lovingly up into your eyes for a moment, she pulls back and lifts her head up to wetly suck on your [pc.clit+], before continuing to eat you out...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have a session of full-on sex with Farah, you give her five hundred flames and tell her that you want to fuck her. Letting out a soft moan, the sheep-girl safely stores your money in a nearby cabinet as you get up from the massage table and prepare to get started.
	</p>
	<p>
		[farah.speech(Remember, sugar, I'm the one in charge here,)] Farah confidently states as she steps over to lie back on the table that you've just vacated. Spreading her legs, she reaches down to her exposed pussy and uses two of her digits to spread her [farah.labia+]. Lewdly presenting her [farah.pussyCapacity] cunt to you, she flashes you a sly smirk and says, [farah.speech(Come here, sugar. This pussy's been getting hot and wet at the thought of getting you to fuck it...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] forwards and prepare to follow Farah's further instructions as she starts to dominantly have sex with you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_FERTILE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have a session of full-on sex with Farah, and eager to have the chance to get her pregnant, you give her seven hundred and fifty flames and tell her that you want to knock her up. Letting out a soft moan, the sheep-girl safely stores your money in a nearby cabinet as you get up from the massage table and prepare to get started.
	</p>
	<p>
		[farah.speech(Remember, sugar, I'm the one in charge here,)] Farah confidently states as she steps over to lie back on the table that you've just vacated. Producing a breeder pill, she pops it out of its protective packaging and swallows it, before spreading her legs she's reaching down to use two of her digits to spread her [farah.labia+]. Lewdly presenting her [farah.pussyCapacity] cunt to you, she flashes you a sly smirk and says, [farah.speech(Come here, sugar. This pussy's getting hot and wet at the thought of being fertile and ready to receive a big creampie...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] forwards and prepare to follow Farah's further instructions as she starts to dominantly have sex with you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_CONTINUE_MASSAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting this massage session to turn into anything sexual, you tell Farah that you don't want to purchase any of her special services. Letting out a disappointed sigh, she states, [farah.speech(Suit yourself, sugar... Maybe next time you'll be in the mood for something a little more fun...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the sheep-girl flashes you a warm smile, before pressing her hands down into your torso and continuing to give you your massage. Working her hands all over your body, she once again demonstrates her proficiency at her job, and within just a matter of moments you find yourself letting out a steady stream of satisfied hums and sighs...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ten minutes later, and with your body feeling well and truly relaxed, Farah steps back and announces with a soft sigh, [farah.speech(Your massage is complete, sugar. Did you enjoy it?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Getting up off the massage table and getting dressed, you thank Farah for her service and tell her what an excellent job she's done. Giving you a warm smile as she hears your praise, the sheep-girl replies, [farah.speech(You're very welcome, sugar. Maybe next time you'll be in the mood for some other services as well...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_FINISHED_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With that, Farah asks you to accompany her back to reception, and so after exiting the room, you follow her down the corridor and find yourself once again standing before Penelope's counter. Smiling at the two of you, the border collie-girl asks, [penelope.speech(I trust that Farah was able to satisfy you, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've responded in the positive, Penelope tells Farah that she's done a good job, before dismissing the sheep-girl and turning her attention back to you. Leaning forwards over her counter and playfully pushing her large, [penelope.cupSize]-cup breasts towards you, she asks in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(Is there anything else which I can do for you today, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having finished giving you her special service, Farah lets out one last soft moan, before informing you that the fun's over. Disentangling yourself from the panting sheep-girl, you set about getting your things back in order while Farah proceeds to clean herself up.
	</p>
	<p>
		[farah.speech(Thanks for the fun, sugar,)] Farah says as she steps over to unlock the door. Telling her that you had a lot of fun too, you make sure that you've retrieved all of your possessions before preparing to head back to reception...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_AFTER_SEX_FERTILE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(farah.hasStatusEffect(SE_PREGNANT_0))
		<p>
			Having finished giving you her special service, Farah lets out one last soft moan, before informing you that the fun's over. Disentangling yourself from the panting sheep-girl, you set about getting your things back in order while Farah produces an arcane pregnancy tester and declares, [farah.speech(I'm not one to wait around and find out if I'm pregnant or not. Hold on a moment, sugar, and I'll let you know if you've gone and made me a mother...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Not giving you any chance to object, the sheep-girl quickly swipes the pregnancy tester down over her belly...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having finished giving you her special service, Farah lets out one last soft moan, before informing you that the fun's over. Disentangling yourself from the panting sheep-girl, you set about getting your things back in order while Farah proceeds to clean herself up.
		</p>
		<p>
			[farah.speech(Thanks for the fun, sugar, although I'm a little disappointed that you didn't even try to get me pregnant,)] Farah says as she steps over to unlock the door. Telling her that you had a lot of fun too, you make sure that you've retrieved all of your possessions before preparing to head back to reception...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_FARAH_AFTER_SEX_FERTILE_RESULT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(farah.isPregnant())
		<p>
			[farah.speech(Well, how about that, sugar? You've gone and got me pregnant,)] Farah states with a big grin on her face. Rubbing her hands over her slightly-chubby belly, she says, [farah.speech(I don't bother using any arcane tricks to speed up my pregnancies, so there'll be plenty of time for you to come back and fuck me while I'm pregnant, if that's something you're into. Oh, and before you ask, no, I don't need anything from you; this isn't the first time I've had kids, and I can handle myself just fine.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With Farah telling you that she doesn't need any help with the pregnancy, all there is for you to do is wish her well and prepare to leave. Telling you to come back and see her again soon, the sheep-girl helps to make sure that you've retrieved all of your possessions before preparing to lead you back to reception...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[farah.speech(Well, sugar, looks like you didn't manage to get me pregnant,)] Farah states. Rubbing her hands over her slightly-chubby belly, she says, [farah.speech(There's always next time, I suppose... You will come back and try again, won't you?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Telling Farah that you'll come back if you get the chance, you make sure that you've retrieved all of your possessions before preparing to head back to reception...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Penelope massage: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to personally receive a massage from Penelope herself, you hand the beautiful border collie-girl the seven hundred and fifty flames which she's asked for and tell her that you've chosen her. Telling Daphne to take over at the reception desk, Penelope dismisses the other two sheep-girls with a wave of her paw-like hand, before smiling at you and teasing, [penelope.speech(You've got a thing for girls with cocks, huh? Or maybe it's my pussy you're after...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not giving you a chance to respond, the border collie-girl turns around and sets off down the corridor behind the counter, gesturing for you to follow along after her as she does so. [pc.Stepping] past Penelope, you tag along behind the spa's owner, and can't help but watch her ass and tail sway from side to side as she struts down the corridor to her room. A moment later, and she's closing the door behind you as you take a look around the room in which you're to receive your massage. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like the reception area, this massage room has been furnished in a modern, trendy style. The floor consists of the same polished wooden floorboards which are found throughout the rest of the establishment, and on all four sides the pale pink walls are illuminated via oversized light bulbs which hang down from the high ceiling. Industrial-style shelving covers one wall, and is filled with all manner of potted plants, miscellaneous ornaments, and beauty products. Wooden blinds cover the window that's set into the opposite wall, granting you and Penelope total privacy for what's about to happen on the large, modular massage table that's located right in the centre of the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			[penelope.speech(Please wait for one moment while I adjust the table to fit your body type,)]
		#ELSE
			[penelope.speech(Please wait for one moment while I adjust the table to fit your height,)]
		#ENDIF
		 Penelope asks, before stepping over to the massage table and bending over to adjust some of its padded surfaces. After she's finished, she gestures to the table and smiles at you as she instructs, [penelope.speech(If you'll please strip naked and lie down on here, then I'll start your massage right away.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as Penelope asks, you strip naked for her, and after you've lain down on the massage table, she places her soft hands on your torso and starts to firmly massage your muscles. It very quickly becomes apparent that Penelope is an outstanding masseuse, as you almost immediately find yourself melting in pleasure under the pressure which she applies to every part of your body.
	</p>
	<p>
		After almost ten minutes have flown by in this manner, the border collie-girl lets out a quiet, horny moan, before asking, [penelope.speech(So, do you want the rest of your massage, or would you prefer to purchase one of my special services instead? I can offer you a groin 'massage' for two hundred flames, an oral 'massage' for five hundred, or we can fuck for a thousand. I'm a bit of a switch, so just let me know if you'd prefer me to be submissive or to take control...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pausing your massage for a moment, Penelope playfully teases her paw-like fingers over your body and offers, [penelope.speech(I can also give you one of my other very special services, both of which cost one thousand five hundred flames. One of these is where I give you what I like to call a double facial; I get you to eat me out then suck my cock, and then I cum and squirt all over your face...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a playful laugh as she pointedly traces her fingers down over the growing bulge that's poking out beneath the bottom of her virgin-killer sweater, the border collie-girl finishes by explaining, [penelope.speech(The final thing I offer is to give you a little mock fashion show. I've got five of my favourite outfits from my time working as a model, and I can show one of these off to you before letting you fuck me while I'm still wearing it... So, what'll it be?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting this massage session to turn into anything sexual, you tell Penelope that you don't want to purchase any of her special services. Professionally nodding as she hears you say this, she states, [penelope.speech(Very good, [pc.sir]. Now please relax while I give you the rest of your massage...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the beautiful border collie-girl flashes you a warm smile, before pressing her hands down into your torso and continuing to give you your massage. Working her hands all over your body, she once again demonstrates her proficiency at her job, and within just a matter of moments you find yourself letting out a steady stream of satisfied hums and sighs...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_HANDS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of having Penelope's hands focused on your
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 cock and pussy,
			#ELSE
				 cock,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 pussy,
		#ENDIF
		 you tell her that you want her to give you a submissive groin 'massage', before handing over the two hundred flames which she's asked for. Letting out a horny moan, the beautiful border collie-girl safely stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before stepping back towards you and kneeling down before your groin. Teasing her fingers down towards your genitals, she gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [penelope.speech(Please relax and enjoy this, [pc.sir]... I'll make this good for you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				Taking hold of your hard cock in one hand, Penelope starts to slide her fingers up and down around your throbbing length, letting out erotic moans as she does so. After a few strokes, she starts to move her free hand towards your pussy, and once it's there, she eagerly slides her fingers into your cunt and starts to finger you while simultaneously continuing to give you a handjob. With both of your sexual organs being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of the border collie-girl, who happily teases, [penelope.speech(That's it, let me take care of you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be climaxing for me soon enough...)]
			#ELSE
				Taking hold of your hard cock in one hand, Penelope starts to eagerly slide her fingers up and down around your throbbing length, letting out erotic moans as she does so. With your [pc.cock+] being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of the border collie-girl, who happily teases, [penelope.speech(That's it, let me take care of you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be cumming soon enough...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			After teasing her fingers up and down over your [pc.labia+], Penelope pauses for a moment to play with your clit, before sliding her fingers into your cunt and starting to eagerly finger you. With your [pc.pussy+] being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of the border collie-girl, who happily teases, [penelope.speech(That's it, let me take care of you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be climaxing soon enough...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of having Penelope continue her massage with her mouth, you tell her that you want her to give you a submissive oral 'massage', before handing over the five hundred flames which she's asked for. Letting out an excited moan, the beautiful border collie-girl safely stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before stepping back towards you and kneeling down before your groin. Leaning forwards so that you can feel her hot breath on your
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 cock and pussy, Penelope gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [penelope.speech(Please relax and enjoy this, [pc.sir]... I'll make this good for you... Oh, and do let me know if you want me to switch to eating you out...)]
			#ELSE
				 cock, Penelope gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [penelope.speech(Please relax and enjoy this, [pc.sir]... I'll make this good for you...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 pussy, Penelope gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [penelope.speech(Please relax and enjoy this, [pc.sir]... I'll make this good for you...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			Parting her lips, Penelope darts out her tongue and delivers a long, wet lick up the underside of your hard cock, before opening wide and taking your [pc.cockHead+] into her mouth. Letting out horny, muffled moans, she starts rapidly bobbing her head up and down as she gives you a submissive blowjob. As you feel your [pc.cock+] being taken deep down the beautiful border collie-girl's tight, wet throat, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], which encourages her to suddenly deepthroat you. After gazing lovingly up into your eyes for a moment, she pulls her head up and wetly sucks the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+], before continuing to give you head...
		#ELSE
			After leaning in to plant a big, wet kiss on your [pc.clit+], Penelope darts out her tongue and delivers a series of long, wet licks to your [pc.labia+]. Letting out horny, muffled moans, she then presses her face into your groin and starts greedily pushing her tongue into your [pc.pussy+]. As the beautiful border collie-girl starts to submissively perform cunnilingus, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], which encourages her to press her face into your cunt and slide her tongue as deep as possible into your hot, wet pussy. After gazing lovingly up into your eyes for a moment, she pulls back and lifts her head up to wetly suck on your [pc.clit+], before continuing to eat you out...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have a session of full-on sex with Penelope, you give her a thousand flames and tell her that you're going to dominantly fuck her. Letting out a hungry moan, the beautiful border collie-girl safely stores your money in a nearby cabinet as you get up from the massage table and prepare to get started.
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(I'll be a good girl for you,)] Penelope moans as she lies back on the table that you've just vacated. Spreading her legs, she reaches down to her exposed pussy and uses two of her digits to spread her [penelope.labia+]. Lewdly presenting her [penelope.pussyCapacity] cunt to you, she uses her other hand to tease her rapidly-hardening dog-cock, before biting her lip and submissively whining, [penelope.speech(My pussy's getting hot and wet at the thought of getting you to fuck it... ~Mmm!~ My cock's desperate to be used as well... Please, [pc.sir], fuck me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] forwards and preparing to take advantage of Penelope's submissive position, you wonder how best to start...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_CONTINUE_REVERSAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to submit to Penelope, you tell her that you want the massage to continue, but that you want to reverse the roles and be the one massaging her. Smirking as she hears this, the beautiful border collie-girl teases, [penelope.speech(You want to feel me up, huh? Sure, that's fine with me. Get up then, so that we can swap places.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hurrying to obey, you stand up and vacate the massage table, allowing Penelope to take your place and lie down on the padded surface. Letting out a soft sigh, she dominantly commands, [penelope.speech(Get started then; I don't have all day.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Once more hastening to carry out Penelope's orders, you press your [pc.hands] down on her furry body and start to give her a massage...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_HANDS_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of having Penelope's hands focused on your
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 cock and pussy,
			#ELSE
				 cock,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 pussy,
		#ENDIF
		 you tell her that you want her to give you a dominant groin 'massage', before handing over the two hundred flames which she's asked for. Letting out a horny moan, the beautiful border collie-girl safely stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before stepping back towards you and kneeling down before your groin. Teasing her fingers down towards your genitals, she gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [penelope.speech(Please relax and enjoy this, [pc.sir]... I'll make this good for you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				Dominantly taking hold of your hard cock in one hand, the sheep-girl starts to slide her fingers up and down around your throbbing length, letting out erotic moans as she does so. After a few strokes, she starts to move her free hand towards your pussy, and once it's there, she eagerly slides her fingers into your cunt and starts to finger you while simultaneously continuing to give you a handjob. With both of your sexual organs being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Penelope, who happily teases, [penelope.speech(That's it, let me take care of you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be climaxing for me soon enough...)]
			#ELSE
				Dominantly taking hold of your hard cock in one hand, the sheep-girl starts to eagerly slide her fingers up and down around your throbbing length, letting out erotic moans as she does so. With your [pc.cock+] being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Penelope, who happily teases, [penelope.speech(That's it, let me take care of you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be cumming soon enough...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			After dominantly teasing her fingers up and down over your [pc.labia+], the sheep-girl pauses for a moment to play with your clit, before eagerly sliding her fingers into your cunt and starting to finger you. With your [pc.pussy+] being stimulated in this manner, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], much to the delight of Penelope, who happily teases, [penelope.speech(That's it, let me take care of you... ~Mmm!~ You'll be climaxing soon enough...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_ORAL_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of having Penelope continue her massage with her mouth, you tell her that you want her to give you a dominant oral 'massage', before handing over the five hundred flames which she's asked for. Letting out an excited moan, the beautiful border collie-girl safely stores your money in a nearby cabinet, before stepping back towards you and kneeling down before your groin. Leaning forwards so that you can feel her hot breath on your
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				 cock and pussy, Penelope gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [penelope.speech(Please relax and enjoy this, [pc.sir]... I'll make this good for you... Oh, and do let me know if you want me to switch to eating you out...)]
			#ELSE
				 cock, Penelope gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [penelope.speech(Please relax and enjoy this, [pc.sir]... I'll make this good for you...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 pussy, Penelope gives you a sly look and lustfully sighs, [penelope.speech(Please relax and enjoy this, [pc.sir]... I'll make this good for you...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasPenisIgnoreDildo() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_PENIS, true))
			Parting her lips, Penelope darts out her tongue and delivers a long, wet lick up the underside of your hard cock, before opening wide and taking your [pc.cockHead+] into her mouth. Letting out horny, muffled moans, she starts rapidly bobbing her head up and down as she gives you a dominant blowjob. As you feel your [pc.cock+] being taken deep down the beautiful border collie-girl's tight, wet throat, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], which encourages her to suddenly deepthroat you. After gazing lovingly up into your eyes for a moment, she pulls her head up and wetly sucks the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+], before continuing to give you head...
		#ELSE
			After leaning in to plant a big, wet kiss on your [pc.clit+], Penelope darts out her tongue and delivers a series of long, wet licks to your [pc.labia+]. Letting out horny, muffled moans, she then presses her face into your groin and starts greedily pushing her tongue into your [pc.pussy+]. As the beautiful border collie-girl starts to dominantly perform cunnilingus, you quickly find yourself letting out a series of [pc.moans+], which encourages her to press her face into your cunt and slide her tongue as deep as possible into your hot, wet pussy. After gazing lovingly up into your eyes for a moment, she pulls back and lifts her head up to wetly suck on your [pc.clit+], before continuing to eat you out...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_SEX_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have a session of full-on sex with Penelope, you give her a thousand flames and tell her that you want her to dominantly fuck you. Letting out a hungry moan, the beautiful border collie-girl safely stores your money in a nearby cabinet as you get up from the massage table and prepare to get started.
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(Don't forget that I'm the one in charge now,)] Penelope confidently states as she strips out of her clothing and steps over to lie back on the table that you've just vacated. Spreading her legs, she reaches down to her exposed pussy and uses two of her digits to spread her [penelope.labia+]. Lewdly presenting her [penelope.pussyCapacity] cunt to you, she uses her other hand to tease her rapidly-hardening dog-cock, before flashing you a sly smirk and dominantly ordering, [penelope.speech(Get over here. My pussy's getting hot and wet at the thought of getting you to fuck it, and my cock's desperate to get hilted deep inside of you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you [pc.step] forwards and prepare to follow Penelope's further instructions as she starts to dominantly have sex with you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ten minutes later, and with your body feeling well and truly relaxed, Penelope steps back and announces in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(Your massage is complete, [pc.sir]. I trust that you're satisfied?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Getting up off the massage table and getting dressed, you thank Penelope for her service and tell her what an excellent job she's done. Giving you a warm smile as she hears your praise, the beautiful border collie-girl replies, [penelope.speech(I'm happy to hear that you're pleased with your massage. Perhaps next time you'll also choose to purchase one of my special services...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FINISHED_REVERSAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ten minutes later, and you've given Penelope's body a thorough massage. Letting out a satisfied sigh, the border collie-girl stands up and announces in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(That'll be enough for one day, [pc.sir]. I trust that you're satisfied?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] back and starting to get dressed, you thank Penelope for allowing you to massage her, and express your pleasure at the massage she gave to you before that. Giving you a warm smile as she hears your praise, the beautiful border collie-girl replies, [penelope.speech(I'm happy to hear that you're pleased with your massage. Perhaps next time you'll also choose to purchase one of my special services...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FINISHED_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With that, Penelope asks you to accompany her back to reception, and so after exiting the room, you follow her down the corridor and find yourself once again standing before the reception's counter. After dismissing Daphne, the border collie-girl leans forwards over her counter and playfully pushes her large, [penelope.cupSize]-cup breasts towards you, before asking, [penelope.speech(Is there anything else which I can do for you today, [pc.sir]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_DOUBLE_FACIAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of orally servicing Penelope's cunt and cock, you tell her that you want to receive a double facial form her and hand over the one thousand five hundred flames which she's asked for. After smirking down at you and letting out a horny moan, the beautiful border collie-girl steps over to a nearby cabinet and safely stores your money in it, before returning to the massage table. After pulling off her virgin-killer sweater, she hooks her thumbs into her lacy panties and slides them all the way down her legs, before kicking them off and leaving her dog-like pussy and cock fully exposed.
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(Let's start by putting that tongue of yours to work,)] she states in her posh accent, before stepping over your face and dropping her wet cunt down onto your mouth. Eager to get started, you immediately part your [pc.lips] and push your [pc.tongue+] into Penelope's wet, canine cunt. Dominantly grinding her pussy down, the beautiful border collie-girl moans, [penelope.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it! ~Aah!~ Eat me out... You'll be getting a taste of my cock soon enough...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you eagerly obey the dominant dog-girl and keep thrusting your tongue deep into her hot cunt, she starts stroking her rapidly-hardening dog-cock in order to get it fully erect for the blowjob you're soon to be giving her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FASHION_SHOW"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have sex with Penelope while she's wearing one of her special outfits, you tell her that you want her to do a mock fashion show for you and hand over the one thousand five hundred flames which she's asked for. Happily taking your flames, the beautiful border collie-girl steps over to a nearby cabinet and safely stores your money in it, before beginning to run through a description of each of her five outfits.
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(First of all, I have a little number which I like to call 'At the ball'. As the name suggests, this involves me donning a ballgown, a pair of elbow-length gloves, and some pieces of expensive jewellery,)] Penelope says in her posh accent. Moving swiftly on, she continues, [penelope.speech(If you'd prefer something a little more casual, then my 'About town' outfit might be for you. It's stylish in its simplicity, and includes a blouse, cardigan, and tight-fitting jeans.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After giving you these two options, the border collie-girl flashes you a dirty look, and with a smirk settling on her beautiful face, she teases, [penelope.speech(If those two sound too boring, then I've got some more risqué choices for you. First up is what I like to call 'Drunken alley', which takes the form of a daring, bright-pink outfit consisting of a clubbing dress, strappy sandals, and plenty of accessories. It's the sort of thing you'd see some drunken slut wearing while she's getting fucked in a dirty backalley.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		It's clear from Penelope's sultry tone of voice that she's getting turned on at the thought of wearing such a slutty getup, but before you have the chance to make a comment on this, she quickly continues, [penelope.speech(I've also got an outfit which I like to call 'Less is more', which basically just consists of me wearing some revealing lingerie. It's not the most imaginative of my outfits, but it's nevertheless a very popular choice. Anyway, that leads me on to my final offering, which I call 'Latex indulgence'. As you might guess, this consists of me squeezing into several pieces of bright-red latex gear. It also includes a little surprise which I have fun with during my strip-tease... So, which outfit would you like to fuck me in?)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Penelope finishes explaining her outfit choices to you, and she seductively bites her lip and gives you a playful wink as she waits to hear what your choice will be...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FASHION_SHOW_BALL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to see and have sex with Penelope while she's wearing a ballgown, you tell her that you'd like to see her 'At the ball' outfit. Flashing you a sly smile, she steps over to the door and says, [penelope.speech(I'll get changed as quickly as I can, but it will still take me several minutes. Please wait here until I return.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the border collie-girl exits the room, leaving you waiting on the massage table for her return. Thankfully, her time estimate was accurate, and after just a few minutes the door opens once again, and in steps Penelope. Just as you requested, she's wearing a flowing ballgown, which along with a pair of elbow-length gloves and high heels, is a pretty shade of light blue. A silver tiara sits atop her head, and you see that she's also wearing a diamond necklace and pair of pearl earrings. Performing a little curtsy as she enters, this gorgeous dog-girl slowly walks up to you, before doing a little roleplay by teasing in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(Good [style.afternoon], [pc.sir]. Would you care for a dance? Or perhaps you'd rather I hike my gown up so that we can have a good fuck?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a playful laugh after asking this lewd question, Penelope does a little spin on the spot, before pulling up her gown and flashing you the lacy burgundy thong which she's wearing. Allowing her gown to fall back into position, she asks, [penelope.speech(So, would you like me to be a good, submissive little doggy for you, or should I take charge?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FASHION_SHOW_TOWN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to see and have sex with Penelope while she's wearing a casual outfit, you tell her that you'd like to see her 'About town' outfit. Flashing you a quick smile, she steps over to the door and says, [penelope.speech(I'll get changed as quickly as I can, but it will still take me several minutes. Please wait here until I return.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the border collie-girl exits the room, leaving you waiting on the massage table for her return. Thankfully, her time estimate was accurate, and after just a few minutes the door opens once again, and in steps Penelope. Just as you requested, she's wearing a stylish, casual outfit, consisting of a white blouse, tight, blue jeans, and a tan cardigan. A pair of aviators, gold jewellery, and a white watch make up her accessories. Blowing you a little kiss as she enters, this gorgeous dog-girl slowly walks up to you, before doing a little roleplay by teasing in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(Hey there, #IF(pc.isFeminine())beautiful#ELSEhandsome#ENDIF. I haven't seen you in this part of town before. How about we go and get a drink, or perhaps you'd rather we go straight over to my place and have a good fuck?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a playful laugh after asking this lewd question, Penelope steps forwards and takes hold of you hand, before planting it on her chest and getting you to fondle her [penelope.cupSize]-cup breasts. Letting out an erotic sigh, she asks, [penelope.speech(So, would you like me to be a good, submissive little doggy for you, or should I take charge?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FASHION_SHOW_ALLEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to see and have sex with Penelope while she's wearing a slutty clubbing outfit, you tell her that you'd like to see her 'Drunken alley' outfit. Flashing you a dirty smirk, she steps over to the door and says, [penelope.speech(I'll get changed as quickly as I can, but it will still take me several minutes. Please wait here until I return.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the border collie-girl exits the room, leaving you waiting on the massage table for her return. Thankfully, her time estimate was accurate, and after just a few minutes the door opens once again, and in steps Penelope. Just as you requested, she's wearing a slutty clubbing dress, choker and strappy heels, each of which are an offensively-bright shade of pink. Her accessories take the form of a significant amount of rose gold jewellery, which includes hoop earrings, a nose ring, and a pair of nipple barbells which can be seen pushing out beneath the fabric of her dress. Licking her lips as she enters, this gorgeous dog-girl puts on a drunken swagger as she steps up to you, before doing a little roleplay by teasing, [penelope.speech(Hey babe, I'm feeling, like, totally wasted... How about you take me down that alley, pull down my thong, and give me a good, hard fuck?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Breaking her roleplay to let out a playful laugh after asking this lewd question, Penelope shamelessly lifts the bottom of her dress and flashes you the trashy, tiger-striped v-string panties which are just barely managing to cover her cunt and sheathed cock. Letting out an erotic moan, she asks, [penelope.speech(So, would you like me to be a good, submissive little doggy for you, or should I take charge?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FASHION_SHOW_LINGERIE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to see and have sex with Penelope while she's wearing nothing but lingerie, you tell her that you'd like to see her 'Less is more' outfit. Biting her lip and flashing you a playful smirk, she steps over to the door and says, [penelope.speech(I'll get changed as quickly as I can, but it will still take me several minutes. Please wait here until I return.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the border collie-girl exits the room, leaving you waiting on the massage table for her return. Thankfully, her time estimate was accurate, and after just a few minutes the door opens once again, and in steps Penelope. Just as you requested, she's wearing nothing but a set of dark purple lingerie, which consists of a chemise, a crotchless thong, and a pair of toeless stockings which are held up by a suspender belt. Dropping her hand down to tease over her exposed cock and cunt as she enters, this gorgeous dog-girl slowly walks up to you, before doing a little roleplay by teasing in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(I thought that we could have some fun before going to bed... You know that you can't resist me when I wear this... You want to fuck me, don't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Breaking her roleplay to let out a playful laugh after asking this lewd question, Penelope shamelessly reaches down to spread her [penelope.labia+] and flash you her [penelope.pussy+]. Letting out an erotic moan, she asks, [penelope.speech(So, would you like me to be a good, submissive little doggy for you, or should I take charge?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FASHION_SHOW_LATEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to see and have sex with Penelope while she's wearing latex gear, you tell her that you'd like to see her 'Latex indulgence' outfit. Biting her lip and flashing you a dirty smirk, she steps over to the door and says, [penelope.speech(I'll get changed as quickly as I can, but it will still take me several minutes. Please wait here until I return.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the border collie-girl exits the room, leaving you waiting on the massage table for her return. Thankfully, her time estimate was accurate, and after just a few minutes the door opens once again, and in steps Penelope. Just as you requested, she's wearing a set of bright-red latex gear, consisting of a long-sleeved crop top, a corset, stocking, bra, panties, and stiletto heels. Letting out a sensual moan as she enters, this gorgeous dog-girl slowly struts up to you, before doing a little roleplay by teasing in her posh accent, [penelope.speech(You be a good [pc.girl] now and sit still while I make myself more comfortable...)]
	</p>
	
	<p>
		With that, Penelope slowly unzips her latex bra, before shrugging out of it to fully expose her big, [penelope.cupSize]-cup breasts. Teasing her paw-like hands over her tits, she gives her erect nipples a playful pinch, before letting out a sensual moan and sliding her fingers down over her corset towards her groin. Unzipping her latex panties, she tosses them over to join her bra on the floor, leaving her dog-cock, pussy, and asshole completely exposed. It's at this moment that you find out what the 'little surprise' which she alluded to earlier is, for as she teases her fingers down over her pussy, she starts to pull on something, and you watch in amazement as she slides a full-sized, realistic purple dildo out of her dripping cunt. Lifting it to her lips, she pushes it into her mouth, before letting out a wet gagging noise as she hilts it fully down her throat. After lewdly sucking and choking on it for a few moments, Penelope slides the dildo out of her mouth, before pushing the slimy, saliva-coated toy back into her hot twat.
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(I do so love playing with toys while wearing this outfit,)] she sighs, before letting out a deeply erotic moan and asking, [penelope.speech(So, would you like me to be a good, submissive little doggy for you, or should I take charge?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FASHION_SHOW_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Responding to Penelope's query with action, you [pc.step] forwards and dominantly pull the beautiful border collie-girl into your [pc.arms]. Letting out a submissive moan, she looks lovingly into your eyes as you prepare to fuck her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_FASHION_SHOW_SEX_START_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting Penelope to take the lead, you tell her that you'd prefer to be the submissive partner. Letting out a hungry moan, the beautiful border collie-girl responds to your declaration by stepping forwards and dominantly pulling you into her arms before preparing to fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MASSAGE_PENELOPE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having finished giving you her special service, Penelope lets out one last passionate moan, before informing you that the fun's over. Disentangling yourself from the beautiful border collie-girl, you set about getting your things back in order while Penelope proceeds to clean herself up.
	</p>
	<p>
		[penelope.speech(That was a lot of fun... Thank you for purchasing one of my special services, [pc.sir],)] Penelope says as she steps over to unlock the door. Telling her that you had a lot of fun too, you make sure that you've retrieved all of your possessions before preparing to head back to reception...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
</dialogue>