<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- Exterior: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unlike most of the Foloi Fields, the area which you find yourself travelling through seems to have been completely spared by Lunette's roaming bands of marauders. The surrounding fields are all in good condition, and the occasional stone barns and field shelters which you pass have managed to escape the destructive forces of the demonic centaur herds.
	</p>
	<p>
		Upon a small hill sitting right in the middle of this area of untouched farmland, you see what might be the reason for this area being shielded from Lunette's daughters; four huge, modern-looking industrial barns are linked to one another by a long, single-story concrete office building. A thin strip around this modern farm has been concreted over, and tall arcane floodlights have been evenly positioned on the hard surface,
		#IF(game.isDayTime())
			 ready to bathe the premises in artificial, fluorescent light as soon as the sun sets.
		#ELSE
			 which are bathing the premises in artificial, fluorescent light, allowing it to be seen from many miles away.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As you approach this industrial blot on an otherwise-rural landscape, you see a series of large, free-standing letters sitting atop the concrete office building, which spell out the words 'Evelyx's Dairy'. Although the barns are windowless, preventing any passersby from seeing inside to confirm for themselves, this name is enough to let anyone know that this farm specialises in milk production.
	</p>
	<p>
		The path you're on leads you right up close to Evelyx's Dairy, but although there are many large, glass windows set into the sides of the concrete office building, they've been treated with a reflective finish, preventing you from taking a look inside. A sign positioned beside the entrance informs you that the farm is [style.italicsGood(open 24/7)], and any member of the public is welcome to head inside and enquire about either breeding their cows or working as one.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking up the gravel path which leads to the farm's entrance, you wonder if you should head inside, or instead continue on your way... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR_ENTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to head inside Evelyx's Dairy, you [pc.walk] up the gravel path and approach the concrete office building. The main entrance consists of a pair of huge, mirrored-glass doors, and as you approach them, some kind of hidden arcane sensor detects your presence and sets them into motion. Sliding along rails recessed into the floor, the glass doors swiftly part, allowing you to [pc.step] forwards into the building.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Exterior: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing in the cavernous, modern-looking entrance hall to Evelyx's Dairy. Beneath your [pc.feet], clean, white tiles cover the floor, while up above your head, fluorescent lamps embedded in the high ceiling cast a bright, unnatural light over your surroundings. Several uninspiring pieces of abstract art hang on the plain white walls, and beneath them, numerous low-backed, black sofas have been arranged around stylish coffee tables. 
	</p>
	<p>
		There are a couple of people making use of these sofas, and as you enter the area, they give you a quick glance before looking back down to their magazines as they see that you're not the person who they were waiting for.
		#IF(dale.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_innoxia_fields_dairyFarm_reception)
			 Other than these members of the public, the only other person you can see
			#IF(dale.isPlayerKnowsName())
				 is the donkey-boy receptionist, Dale, who's busily filling out some paperwork behind his desk.
			#ELSE
				 is a donkey-boy receptionist, who's busily filling out some paperwork behind the desk over on the far side of the room.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 Other than these members of the public, there's nobody else in sight, as the reception desk over on the far side of the room is currently unstaffed.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		From here, you could either exit the farm and head back out into the Foloi Fields, or [pc.walk] on over to the reception desk...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXIT_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you've had enough of Evelyx's Dairy for now, you [pc.walk] over to the large glass doors, and after they've slid aside, you head out into the Foloi Fields once again...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Corridor: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Just like the entrance hall, the corridor which runs down the centre of the farm's office building is floored in clean, white tiles, and illuminated by the bright, unnatural light of fluorescent lamps embedded in the high ceiling above your head. Instead of abstract artworks, however, the walls are home to numerous inspirational pictures and posters, which bear all manner of trite slogans encouraging the farm's cows to work hard.  
	</p>
	<p>
		At one end of the corridor, there's a large sign bearing the word 'Dormitories', while at the other end, a securely locked door prevents you from going any further. Three doors are set into one side of the corridor, with each one signposted as leading into a different barn, while on the other side you can find the farm's offices and milk storage area.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Locked door in corridor: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LOCKED_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The door at this end of the corridor is securely locked and there are no windows or other means of seeing what's on the other side. A menacing sign fixed to one side of this door warns you that if you're caught trying to gain entry to the area beyond, you'll not only be instantly terminated from working here, but you'll also be subjected to prosecution.
	</p>
	<p>
		Even if you did want to see find out what's on the other side, there's really no way to bypass the door's locking mechanism, and so all that you can do is turn around and head back the way you came...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="LOCKED_DOOR_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to get past the locked door, you [pc.step] back into the corridor and wonder where to go to next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Reception: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(dale))
		<p>
			Positioned on the opposite side of the entrance hall to the pair of large, glass doors, there sits a long reception desk. It's of a very modern, stylish design, and has tall, smooth white sides and a frosted glass top. Another pair of mirrored glass doors, which no doubt lead into the rest of the farm, are positioned behind this desk, while to their side a large analogue clock hangs from the wall. Sitting behind the desk
			#IF(dale.isPlayerKnowsName())
				 is the donkey-boy receptionist, Dale, and as you approach he looks up from his paperwork and flashes you a kind smile.
			#ELSE
				 is a greater donkey-boy receptionist, and as you approach he looks up from his paperwork and flashes you a kind smile. Looking down at the small name plate sitting on the desk in front of him, you see that this donkey-boy is called 'Mr. [dale.surname]'.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_started))
			#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(dale))
				#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(dale))
					<p>
						[pc.Stepping] forwards, you present your swollen belly to the donkey-boy, and upon seeing that you're pregnant, he very quickly realises that he must be the father. Tentatively reaching out to gently rub his strong hands over your distended stomach, he marvels, [dale.speech(I really got you pregnant? Wow... Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help! I'll try to make time for you if you need it.)]
					</p>
				#ELSE
					<p>
						[pc.Stepping] forwards, you present your swollen belly to the donkey-boy, letting him know that you're still pregnant with his children. Tentatively reaching out to gently rub his strong hands over your distended stomach, he smiles and repeats his previous offer, [dale.speech(Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help. I'll try to make time for you if you need it.)]
					</p>
				#ENDIF
				<p>
					Thanking Dale for his kind offer, you tell him that you're able to handle things yourself, to which he replies, [dale.speech(Well, if you change your mind then just let me know. Is there anything else I can help you with today?)]
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					[dale.speech(Hi, [pc.name]!)] he happily calls out, before sitting to attention and quickly straightening his black tie. Brushing down his navy blue shirt, 
					#IF(dale.getTotalTimesHadSex(pc)>0)
						 he winks at you and teases, [dale.speech(How's work going? You haven't been getting lonely in there without me, have you?)]
					#ELSE
						 he asks, [dale.speech(How's work going? If you've got any complaints or suggestions, please let me know!)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					As you tell the donkey-boy that everything is going fine, and that you don't have anything to complain about, he quickly finishes the last drop of coffee in his mug, before looking at you with weary eyes and saying in his usual upbeat tone of voice,
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_reception_sex))
						 [dale.speech(Well, if there's anything you want, then let me know. Oh, and I've got my eye on you; don't try getting under my desk again...)]
					#ELSE
						 [dale.speech(Well, if there's anything you want, then just say the word.)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					With that, Dale starts to reorganise the stacks of paperwork in front of him, leaving you wondering whether to simply continue on your way past him or to stop and ask him about something... 
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(dale.isPlayerKnowsName())
			<p>
				[dale.speech(Hi, [pc.name]!)] he happily calls out, before sitting to attention and quickly straightening his black tie. Brushing down his navy blue shirt, he asks, [dale.speech(Would you like to inquire about our cow sex services? Or are you here to ask about becoming a cow yourself?)] 
			</p>
			<p>
				Stifling a yawn, the donkey-boy quickly finishes the last drop of coffee in his mug, before looking at you with weary eyes and waiting to hear what it is you want...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[dale.speech(Oh, you can call me Dale, don't worry about that,)] he happily says after noticing where you're looking. Sitting to attention and quickly straightening his black tie, he brushes down his navy blue shirt and continues, [dale.speech(I haven't seen you here before, so welcome to Evelyx's Dairy! If you're here to make inquiries about bulk milk orders, then I'm afraid to say that we don't have any contracts available right now. If, on the other hand, you're here for more personal business, then we offer a service whereby you can pay to have sex with one of our cows. No, those aren't <i>actual</i> cows, before you ask; that's just what we call our employees whose work involves being milked in the barns.)] 
			</p>
			<p>
				Despite his friendly mannerisms, you notice that there's a weary look in Dale's [dale.eyeColour] eyes, and after finishing his introduction, he stifles a yawn and sinks down in his chair a little. Suddenly remembering something, he quickly bends down to retrieve an item from under his desk. Seeing this as a good moment to introduce yourself to him, you tell Dale your name, and as he straightens back up and places a few sheets of paper on the desk before him, he flashes you another kind smile and says, [dale.speech(Pleased to meet you, [pc.name].)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Moving some empty coffee cups aside, Dale slides the papers he's just retrieved towards you and continues, [dale.speech(We're always looking for new cows, so if you were interested in that sort of work, then all you need to do is read over this contract, sign up, and we can get you started straight away. Sorry if that's not what you're here for, but I have to offer this to every new visitor, regardless of who they are...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Shrugging off his slight embarrassment at having to offer you the opportunity to become a 'cow', the donkey-boy smiles and says, [dale.speech(Just let me know if you're interested in either of these things, and I can give you more details.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				As Dale takes a moment to reorganise the stacks of paperwork in front of him, you wonder what to say next... 
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Positioned on the opposite side of the entrance hall to the pair of large, glass doors, there sits a long reception desk. It's of a very modern, stylish design, and has tall, smooth white sides and a frosted glass top. Another pair of mirrored glass doors, which no doubt lead into the rest of the farm, are positioned behind this desk, while to their side a large analogue clock hangs from the wall.
			#IF(dale.isPlayerKnowsName())
				 Despite the exterior sign promising that the farm is 'open 24/7', the donkey-boy receptionist, Dale, is currently absent from his post, and a sign left on the desk's top reveals:
			#ELSE
				 Despite the exterior sign promising that the farm is 'open 24/7', the farm's receptionist is currently absent from their post, and a sign left on the desk's top reveals:
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'>
			<b>Reception Desk Closed</b>
			<br/>Normal service will resume at [style.time(5)].
			<br/>Please feel free to take a seat in the waiting area.
		</p>
		<p>
			Looking over to the clock hanging on the wall behind this reception desk, you see that the current time is [style.currentTime]. If you wanted to, you could return to the waiting area and loiter about until
			#IF(dale.isPlayerKnowsName())
				#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_started))
					 Dale returns. Then again, as you're an employee, you could always head over to the dormitory and see if you can find Dale in there...
				#ELSE
					 Dale returns...
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				 the receptionist returns...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(dale))
			You thank Dale for his time and say that you've got to leave, before [pc.stepping] back into the waiting area. Flashing you one last smile, the donkey-boy gives you a wave, and after stifling a weary sigh, he says, [dale.speech(Thanks for stopping by. We're open at all hours every day of the week, so come back at any time!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF(dale.isPlayerKnowsName())
				As Dale isn't currently on duty, there's very little else for you to do except [pc.step] back into the waiting area. Taking a quick look around, you wonder whether to loiter about and wait for him to return, or exit Evelyx's Dairy and head elsewhere...
			#ELSE
				As the receptionist isn't currently on duty, there's very little else for you to do except [pc.step] back into the waiting area. Taking a quick look around, you wonder whether to loiter about and wait for them to return, or exit Evelyx's Dairy and head elsewhere...
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_BLOWJOB_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you stand before Dale's desk, you find yourself thinking about how much fun the two of you had in the barn. Wanting to spend some more time with his hot, thick donkey-cock, you flash him a mischievous grin and [pc.step] around to his side of the desk. Realising that you're planning on doing something lewd, Dale tries to move his chair to block your advance, but he's too slow for you, and before he makes another move to stop you, you've managed to drop down and shuffle forwards beneath his desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(What are you doing?!)] the donkey-boy urgently hisses down at you, [dale.speech(There are clients waiting right over there, and I might have to get up to go to the barns at any moment! You can't do this here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Responding by telling him not to worry so much, you let out an excited [pc.moan] as you reach forwards and start undoing Dale's trousers. The donkey-boy tries to stop you from gaining access to his cock, but as he's in full sight of several clients over in the waiting area, he can't make too much of a fuss, and so you're easily able to swat his hands aside and pull down his underwear. Despite his protestations, Dale's thick, dark donkey-cock is already half-erect, and as you plant a kiss on his wide, flared head, it quickly rises to full attention.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Look, I appreciate your enthusiasm, but this isn't the place for this,)] Dale hisses again. Before he can say anything else, however, the donkey-boy's attention is caught by one of the clients who are sitting in the waiting area. You hear them call out some kind of question, to which Dale responds by telling them that Evelyx will see them as soon as she's free. Taking this opportunity to win him over and agree to let you suck his cock, you deliver a long, wet lick to the underside of the donkey-boy's hot, throbbing shaft,
		#IF(pc.isFaceVirgin())
			 before pouting up at him and telling him that you've never given anyone a blowjob before, and that you were hoping that he could be your first.
		#ELSE
			 before pouting up at him and telling him that you wanted to do something nice for him, and so you wanted to deepthroat him while he works.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isFaceVirgin())
			Having a weakness for loving to take people's virginities, Dale is unable to ignore or refuse your request, and so after letting out a deep, horny grunt, he hisses, [dale.speech(Ok, let's do this then. Just take it as slow as you want, and please try not to make too much noise...)]
		#ELSE
			Turned on and clearly wanting this to happen almost as much as you do, Dale lets out a deep, horny grunt, before hissing, [dale.speech(Ok, let's do this then. Just take it as slow as you want, and please try not to make too much noise...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isFaceVirgin())
			This being your first time sucking someone's cock, you decide to take your time and really enjoy this experience. Moving your mouth down to Dale's [dale.ballSize] balls, you plant a series of kisses on them, letting out a satisfied, muffled moan in the process as you enjoy their musky, masculine taste. Moving up, you then dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start licking his thick, hot shaft, continuing to moan and pant as you do so. Finally working your way up to kiss the flat, flared head of Dale's equine cock, you lick up the salty precum that's oozing from his urethra, before experimentally wrapping your [pc.lips+] around his shaft and taking it into your mouth.
		#ELSE
			Wanting to make sure that he enjoys this just as much as you will, you decide to take your time and give the donkey-boy's genitals your full, loving attention. Moving your mouth down to his [dale.ballSize], dark balls, you plant a series of kisses on them, letting out a satisfied, muffled moan in the process as you enjoy their musky, masculine taste. Moving up, you then dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start licking his thick, hot shaft, continuing to moan and pant as you do so. Finally working your way up to kiss the flat, flared head of Dale's equine cock, you lick up the salty precum that's oozing from his urethra, before wrapping your [pc.lips+] around his shaft and taking it into your mouth.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(That's it... Don't stop...)] Dale groans under his breath, before placing one of his hands on the back of your head and encouraging you to keep going by applying a gentle downward pressure. Happy to see from his reaction that he's enjoying this, you give the donkey-boy what he wants and drop your head down, taking his thick, hot donkey-cock first into your mouth, and then down your throat. Delighting in his musky, masculine scent and taste, you start eagerly bobbing your head up and down in his lap, causing a mixture of precum and saliva to drool from the corners of your mouth as you give him a blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Planting one last kiss on Dale's delicious donkey-dick, you take a moment to savour the musky, masculine taste of his cock before putting an end to things by shuffling back out from under his desk. Letting out a satisfied groan, Dale looks down at you and sighs, [dale.speech(That was amazing... That is, I mean to say, you really shouldn't be doing that sort of thing here while I'm at work...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smirking up at him, you tease Dale by telling him that even if he pretends to not want it, the reaction from his hot, hard cock is all you need to know that he loves it. Stroking your [pc.hand] up his inner thigh, you let out an amused laugh as you see his softening cock twitch in excitement in reaction to your touch. Quickly pulling up his trousers and underwear, the donkey-boy admits, [dale.speech(Yes, well, I did say that it was amazing, didn't I? What do you want me to say, that I'd like for you to do this again?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Interrupting him before he can say anything else, you tell Dale that you'll definitely treat him to this again in the future. Letting out a defeated sigh as he realises that he's not going to be able to convince you to not bother him while at work, the donkey-boy waits for you to return to the other side of his desk before asking if there was anything else you needed from him.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Talking: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You ask Dale if he's got a moment in which to talk. He casts a weary eye over the stack of paperwork in front of him, and you think that he's going to decline, but after letting out a deep sigh he gives you a genuinely warm smile and says, [dale.speech(Of course, [pc.name]. What it is that you'd like to talk about?)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Happy to hear that the donkey-boy is willing to make time for you, you wonder what to talk to him about first...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_TALK_HIMSELF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know a little more about Dale, you ask him about what led to him working here at Evelyx's Dairy, and for how long has he been doing it.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(You know, you're the first person to ever ask me about that,)] he replies with a small laugh. Leaning back in his chair, he brushes down his tall, donkey-like ears with one hand as he thinks for a moment, before replying, [dale.speech(It must be going on three years since I started working here now. I used to work at an office over in Dominion, but after a relationship with one of my colleagues went bad, she made working there unbearable. I don't want to bore you with all of the petty details, but basically things ended with me deciding to leave the city just to get away from her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After interrupting to offer the donkey-boy your sympathy, you listen as he continues, [dale.speech(So I decided to travel to Elis and try and make a living there. On my way through the Fields, I saw a sign offering a receptionist job at a farm, and after following the directions, I arrived here. Evelyx was almost as desperate to have this vacancy filled as I was to be getting a job, and so before I'd even arrived at Elis, I found myself working here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to know more, you ask Dale if he ended up getting a new place to live in Elis, or found somewhere a little closer to work. Letting out a small laugh, he reveals, [dale.speech(Well, technically my permanent residence is a small apartment in Elis, but with how much work Evelyx keeps on piling on me, I haven't been home in weeks. I don't really mind, though; my apartment's in the rough part of town, and the beds in the dormitories here are comfortable enough.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Dale seems to be at the limit of how much he wants to reveal about himself, and so pointedly asks, [dale.speech(Is there anything else you'd like to talk about?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_TALK_WORK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious about what kind of duties Dale is expected to perform as the farm's receptionist, you ask him about what kind of paperwork he's currently dealing with.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Well, these are the cows' daily performance reports which need to be assessed and signed off,)] he replies, gesturing to the stack of papers in front of him. Rubbing his weary eyes, he lets out a small sigh and reveals, [dale.speech(This should be the responsibility of the office workers, but the number of cows we have working here has more than quadrupled over the past two years, and Evelyx hasn't hired any additional employees to keep up. So the short of it is that this extra paperwork keeps on getting offloaded onto me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Noting the significant amount of papers before him, you ask Dale if he's able to keep up with his receptionist duties on top of all this. Puffing up his cheat a little in pride, he smiles and boasts, [dale.speech(Of course! It's a lot of work, but someone needs to do it. I've also had to take on responsibility for attending to any new cows we employ, and even with that, I'm still able to get all of my work completed each day.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although he displays an admirable work ethic, you can't help but feel like this workload must be taking its toll on Dale's health. As you express this to him, the donkey-boy simply dismisses your concerns with a wave of his hand and states, [dale.speech(Us donkey-morphs are used to hard work, so this is nothing. I mostly get enough sleep, and always have three healthy meals a day. There's no need to be worried about me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Running his hand back over his tall, donkey-like ears, he smiles and brings the topic to a close by asking, [dale.speech(Is there something else which you wanted to discuss?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_TALK_EVELYX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to hear Dale's opinion of his boss, you ask him what Evelyx is like.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Well, she's a direct daughter of the elder lilin, Lisophia,)] the donkey-boy says, as though that should explain everything. Seeing that you'd like some more information than that, however, he quickly continues, [dale.speech(Lisophia's well known for her greed, and her daughter's inherited that trait by having a complete obsession with money. I don't mind the workload, but some of my colleagues over in the office are almost at their breaking point with how hard Evelyx is working them. She refuses to hire more people as that would, in her own words, 'eat up all of the profits'.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Asking what else Dale can tell you about this greedy succubus, you listen as Dale smiles and states, [dale.speech(Well, there's not really too much that I know about her. I met her for my initial interview, and I see her every few months for a quarterly performance report, but other than that I only very briefly interact with her when taking visitors to and from her office. She hates to be interrupted, and only meets with people who have important business to discuss with her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning back in his chair, Dale thinks for a moment, before stating, [dale.speech(She's not a bad person. Sure, she works her employees hard, but she also gives the cows pretty decent working conditions. You'd be hard pressed to find a modern dairy farm that gives their cows the same level of comfort or flexible hours that this one does.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having said all there is on the matter, the donkey-boy smiles at you and states, [dale.speech(Anyway, enough about Evelyx. Is there anything else you wanted to ask?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_TALK_FARM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Interested to hear about this farm's history, you ask Dale what he knows about how it got started.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(I can't really help you much there,)] he sighs, [dale.speech(I only started working here a few years ago, and by that time everything was already pretty much as it is now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment, the donkey-boy suddenly seems to remember something, and after asking you to wait for one moment, he bends down and starts rummaging around in the drawers behind his desk. After a couple of minutes of searching, the donkey-boy finds what he was looking for, and pulls out a framed, aerial photograph of a traditional-looking farmhouse. Placing it on the desk for you to look at, he explains, [dale.speech(Apparently, that's what this farm used to look like. Of course, that old house was demolished a long time ago, and I guess that the surrounding barns were similarly torn down after they fell into disrepair.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having discovered all that Dale knows about this farm's history, you move on to ask him about how it currently functions. As this is a topic which he's much more familiar with, the donkey-boy enthusiastically replies, [dale.speech(Well, we operate in the same way that most other modern dairy farms do. We employ a large number of 'cows', who lie in their stalls for up to sixteen hours a day, having their milk drained by machines. This milk is treated and stored in large vats, and then a carriage arrives twice a day to transport the milk to the processing and bottling plant on the outskirts of Dominion.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With all of your questions about the farm now answered, you wonder what to ask about next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_TALK_LUNETTE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know why this farm has been spared from the destruction wrought by Lunette's marauders, you ask Dale what he knows about the elder lilin or her daughters.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Well, I don't really know anything special about Lunette herself, other than what anyone else could tell you about her,)] he replies, before glancing around and lowering his voice to reveal, [dale.speech(As for why this farm isn't attacked like most of the others in the Fields... Well, I probably shouldn't be telling you this, but I heard from one of the other workers that Evelyx has some kind of deal with Lunette...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wanting to know more, you ask the donkey-boy what kind of deal that would be. Nervously glancing back over his shoulder to make sure that nobody's eavesdropping, he speculates, [dale.speech(I don't know what goes on in there, but it's definitely got something to do with the fourth barn we have here. I regularly attend to some of the cows in all three of the other barns, but as far as I know, nobody who works here has ever been inside the fourth one. We've know that some of Lunette's daughters are given regular access to it, but what goes on inside, nobody knows...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After taking a moment to think about whether or not to say any more, the donkey-boy runs his hand over his tall ears, before leaning in close to you and practically whispering, [dale.speech(Of course, there's the matter of what happened to the receptionist whose job I took... One of the other workers told me that in the days before she disappeared, this receptionist was asking a lot of questions about that fourth barn. Although everyone calls him crazy, this worker swears that he saw Evelyx leading the receptionist towards the fourth barn on the night that she vanished...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Clearly thinking that he's already said too much, Dale sits back up and clears his throat, before saying, [dale.speech(Anyway, it's best not to ask too many questions about Lunette. She's bad news, and the less I or anyone else has to do with her, the better.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking Dale for the information, you wonder what to ask about next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_TALK_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having asked Dale everything which you wanted to know, you thank him for his time and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Sex: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know more about having sex with one of the Dairy's cows, you ask Dale for the full details. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Of course, hold on one moment, please,)] he replies with a smile. Quickly bending down and opening one of the drawers beneath his desk, the donkey-boy retrieves a sheet of laminated paper and places it in front of you. Looking down at the paper, you see that the page is split into three parts, and as you scan over the text, Dale begins to deliver a confident, well-practised sales pitch.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_started))
			[dale.speech(As you should already know, you cows are split into three barns based on your promotion level; 'Trainee', 'Heifer', and 'Cow', and you can choose any one of these to have sex with,)]
		#ELSE
			[dale.speech(Our cows are split into three barns based on their promotion level; 'Trainee', 'Heifer', and 'Cow', and you can choose any one of these to have sex with,)]
		#ENDIF
		 he begins, before pointing to the top of the page and explaining, [dale.speech(The requirement for trainees to get promoted is for them to be publicly fucked, so if you decide to choose a trainee to have sex with, then you'll be their first. I can tell you from experience that quite a few of them are still virgins, and if not, then their pussies will still be nice and tight. The trainee will have been the one to request a member of the public to come and fuck her, so you don't get to choose your partner if you choose a trainee. Oh, and you should also know that the trainees can be of any race, not just cow-girls.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving down the page, you see that the next option is to fuck a 'Heifer', and Dale continues, [dale.speech(Heifers have been publicly fucked at least once; that's how they earned their promotion from trainee. As such, they're not going to be virgins, and some of them have been used quite a lot, meaning that they might not have the tightest pussies. Heifers get promoted once they've been impregnated, so none of them will be pregnant. Just like trainees, heifers request to have sex, and so you're not going to be able to choose your partner. Heifers get access to cow-girl transformatives, so you're more likely than not to end up being partnered with a cow-girl, but there's still a chance that they'll be of a different race.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving down the end of the paper, you see the final option is to fuck a 'Cow'. Flashing you a smile, Dale finishes his narration by explaining, [dale.speech(Cows have been fucked a lot and bred at least once, often multiple times. Their pussies are well-used and pretty loose, and as such they aren't as popular as trainees or heifers. They don't get to choose when they get fucked, though, so you can look around and choose whichever cow you like the look of the most. Every cow in this barn is a cow-girl, so if that's not your thing you'd be better off going with a trainee. Take a moment to look at the prices, and let me know if you want one. Oh, and we offer partial refunds if your cow isn't to your liking. You'll get back what you paid minus five hundred flames to cover admin fees.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking the donkey-boy for the information, you look down at the bottom of the page where the prices and key points for each promotion level are displayed, and read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
			<b>Trainee [style.moneyFormat(10000, b)]</b>
			<br/>Will you get a virgin to break in? If not, at least their pussies will be nice and tight!
			<br/>Our most popular offering, trainees are guaranteed to be a good fuck!
			<br/>
			<br/><b>Heifer [style.moneyFormat(5000, b)]</b>
			<br/>Graduated from trainee, these heifers are desperate to get knocked up!
			<br/>Give them a creampie and help them to get promoted!
			<br/>
			<br/><b>Cow [style.moneyFormat(2500, b)]</b>
			<br/>Experienced and always happy to be getting your attention!
			<br/>Choose whichever cow takes your fancy and make her feel wanted!
		</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_SEX_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After hearing Dale's sales pitch and reading over the prices, you find yourself feeling less than impressed by what's on offer. Telling the donkey-boy that you're not interested in having sex with a cow after all, you hand the laminated sheet of paper back to him.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(No worries,)] he replies with a warm smile on his face, [dale.speech(Just let me know if there's anything else I can do for you.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_SEX_TRAINEE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the idea of giving a trainee her first public fuck, you place [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames on the desk and tell Dale that you've made your choice. Quickly counting out the money and securely storing it in a safe anchored to the floor beside his hoofs, Dale presses a button beneath his desk, before smiling and saying, [dale.speech(Thank you for your business. I've signalled to the trainees that someone's here to fuck them. It typically doesn't take more than a few minutes before one of them requests it, so if you'd like to take a seat while you wait, I'll call for you when she's ready.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're asked, you [pc.step] over to the nearest sofa and sink down onto it. True to Dale's prediction, you only have to wait for two minutes before he calls over to you to let you know that a trainee has requested a fuck. Leaving a 'Be back soon' sign for anyone who shows up while he's away, the donkey-boy leads you past his desk and into the corridor beyond. Swiftly moving across the white tiled floor, the two of you approach a nearby door signposted as 'Trainee Barn'. Producing a set of keys, Dale unlocks the door and heads inside, before beckoning you to follow him.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] forwards, you find yourself entering a huge barn, with corrugated metal walls and ceiling. Although its walls lack windows, skylights and arcane lamps fill the cavernous interior with a bright, artificial light. What must be at least a hundred milking stalls are lined up along both sides of this barn, and as you follow Dale down the middle of them, you find yourself being presented with the naked rear ends of the cows who are making use of them. The steady hum of countless milking machines fills the barn, and now and again, one of the trainees releases a particularly loud moan.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Here we are,)] Dale suddenly says. Stopping beside a milking stall which has a pink, arcane light flashing on the top of it, you watch as the donkey-boy steps up behind the trainee, who turns out to be [cow.a_fullRace(true)], and asks, [dale.speech(Are you ready for this?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(cow.isVaginaVirgin())
			[cow.speech(Yes,)] [cow.name] replies, before nervously blurting out, [cow.speech(I'm still a virgin though!)]
		#ELSE
			[cow.speech(Yes,)] [cow.name] replies, before letting out a sultry moan and revealing, [cow.speech(This isn't my first time, but I've never done it in a place like this before...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping around to one side of the trainee, Dale reaches down and takes hold of her exposed ass, before pulling her cheeks apart and using his thumbs to spread her [cow.labiaSize] [cow.labia]. As he presents [cow.namePos] [cow.pussyCapacity] cunt to you, the donkey-boy
		#IF(cow.isVaginaVirgin())
			 flashes you a grin and sighs, [dale.speech(I wish I were you right now... There's nothing better than getting to take a trainee's virginity like this. So, you're up for it, right?)]
		#ELSE
			 smiles and asks, [dale.speech(So, is she to your liking?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_SEX_HEIFER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have sex with one of the heifers, you place [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames on the desk and tell Dale that you've made your choice. Quickly counting out the money and securely storing it in a safe anchored to the floor beside his hoofs, Dale presses a button beneath his desk, before smiling and saying, [dale.speech(Thank you for your business. I've signalled to the heifers that someone's here to fuck them. It typically doesn't take more than a few minutes before one of them requests it, so if you'd like to take a seat while you wait, I'll call for you when she's ready.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're asked, you [pc.step] over to the nearest sofa and sink down onto it. True to Dale's prediction, you only have to wait for two minutes before he calls over to you to let you know that a heifer has requested a fuck. Leaving a 'Be back soon' sign for anyone who shows up while he's away, the donkey-boy leads you past his desk and into the corridor beyond. Swiftly moving across the white tiled floor, the two of you head half-way down the corridor and arrive at a door signposted as 'Heifer Barn'. Producing a set of keys, Dale unlocks the door and heads inside, before beckoning you to follow him.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] forwards, you find yourself entering a huge barn, with corrugated metal walls and ceiling. Although its walls lack windows, skylights and arcane lamps fill the cavernous interior with a bright, artificial light. What must be at least a hundred milking stalls are lined up along both sides of this barn, and as you follow Dale down the middle of them, you find yourself being presented with the naked rear ends of the cows who are making use of them. The steady hum of countless milking machines fills the barn, and now and again, one of the heifers releases a particularly loud moan.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Here we are,)] Dale suddenly says. Stopping beside a milking stall which has a pink, arcane light flashing on the top of it, you watch as the donkey-boy steps up behind the heifer, who turns out to be [cow.a_fullRace(true)], and asks, [dale.speech(Are you ready for this?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[cow.speech(Oh yeah,)] [cow.name] eagerly replies, before letting out an excited squeal and revealing, [cow.speech(I love getting fucking like this... Come on, give it to me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping around to one side of the eager heifer, Dale reaches down and takes hold of her exposed ass, before pulling her cheeks apart and using his thumbs to spread her [cow.labiaSize] [cow.labia]. As he presents [cow.namePos] [cow.pussyCapacity] cunt to you, the donkey-boy grins and asks, [dale.speech(So, is she to your liking?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKER_SEX_COW_SEARCH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to have sex with one of the cows, you place [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames on the desk and tell Dale that you've made your choice. Quickly counting out the money and securely storing it in a safe anchored to the floor beside his hoofs, Dale leaves a 'Be back soon' sign for anyone who shows up while he's away, before leading you past his desk and into the corridor beyond. Swiftly moving across the white tiled floor, the two of you head down to the far end of the corridor and arrive at a door signposted as 'Cow Barn'. Producing a set of keys, Dale unlocks the door and heads inside, before beckoning you to follow him.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] forwards, you find yourself entering a huge barn, with corrugated metal walls and ceiling. Although its walls lack windows, skylights and arcane lamps fill the cavernous interior with a bright, artificial light. What must be at least a hundred milking stalls are lined up along both sides of this barn, and as you follow Dale down the middle of them, you find yourself being presented with the naked rear ends of the cows who are making use of them. The steady hum of countless milking machines fills the barn, and now and again, one of the cows releases a particularly loud moan.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(So, unlike the other two barns, you can take your pick,)] Dale says, before playfully slapping the ass of the cow next to him and causing her to let out an extremely lewd moan. Smiling at her reaction, he says, [dale.speech(They're all pretty desperate for it. Just let me know which one you like the look of the most.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MILKER_SEX_COW_SEARCH_FOUND"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Walking] down the aisle between the rows of moaning cows, you soon find one which takes your fancy, who takes the form of
		#IF(cow.isVisiblyPregnant())
			 a heavily pregnant
		#ENDIF
		 [cow.fullRace(true)].
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_cow_search_high_mileage))
			 Her holes are loose and wet, and as you stop to gaze at her exposed cunt, she playfully sways her [cow.hips+] at you and begs,
			#IF(pc.hasPenis())
				 [cow.speech(Come on, you know you want to choose me! Stick your cock in my pussy, babe, and I'll milk your balls dry!)]
			#ELSE
				 [cow.speech(Come on, you know you want to choose me!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 Her holes are in relatively good condition, especially considering how many times she must have been fucked. As you stop to gaze at her exposed cunt, she playfully sways her [cow.hips+] at you and begs,
			#IF(pc.hasPenis())
				 [cow.speech(Come on, you know you want to choose me! I'm tighter than most of the other cows; my pussy's gonna feel really good squeezing down around your cock!)]
			#ELSE
				 [cow.speech(Come on, you know you want to choose me! I'm tighter than most of the other cows!)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing that you've made your choice, Dale steps forwards and takes hold of [cow.namePos] exposed ass, before pulling her cheeks apart and using his thumbs to spread her [cow.labiaSize] [cow.labia]. As he presents [cow.namePos] [cow.pussyCapacity] cunt to you, the donkey-boy grins and asks, [dale.speech(So, is she to your liking?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a long, deep moan as she feels Dale's fingers touching her [cow.pussy+], the cow turns her head back and moans, [cow.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes, come on... Don't back out now, babe... Fuck my pussy and make me yours!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the look of this cow, you tell Dale that you're happy with what's on offer. Letting go of her ass, the donkey-boy steps away from [cow.name] and explains, [dale.speech(Most people like to use a cow's pussy, but you're free to use any of her holes. The only rules are that you're not to remove her breast pumps or fiddle with the milking machine. Have fun, and I'll be back when you've finished.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the donkey-boy rushes off to quickly get back to his desk. Left alone with [npc.name], you move up close behind her, and as you run your [pc.fingers+] over her exposed pussy, she 
		#IF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_innoxia_fields_dairyFarm_barn1)
			#IF(cow.isVaginaVirgin())
				 lets out a little moan, before shyly panting, [cow.speech(I'm a virgin... But I want to be promoted... Just, please be gentle, ok?)]
			#ELSE
				 lets out a little moan and pants, [cow.speech(It's not like I'm a virgin, but it's still my first time being fucked like this... Just, go easy on me, ok?)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_innoxia_fields_dairyFarm_barn2)
			 moans and pants, [cow.speech(Please, I want to be promoted, so could you try and get me knocked up? I'll be a good little cow for you, I promise... Just give me a nice big creampie...)]
		#ELSE
			 moans and eagerly pants, [cow.speech(That's it, I'm your good little cow! Use me for as long as you'd like, and in whatever way you desire...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking your [pc.fingers+] away from [npc.namePos] [cow.pussy+], you wonder how best to use her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_SEX_START_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not too thrilled at the prospect of having sex with [cow.name], you shake your head and tell Dale that you've changed your mind.
		#IF(cow.isVaginaVirgin())
			 The donkey-boy shakes his head in disbelief, before letting out a good-natured laugh and exclaiming, [dale.speech(You really don't want to take her virginity?! Well, I guess not everybody is into that sort of thing... Come on then, let's head back to my desk and I'll get you your refund.)]
		#ELSE
			 The donkey-boy nods his head in understanding, before saying, [dale.speech(Come on then, let's head back to my desk and I'll get you your refund.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaving the disappointed cow behind, you and Dale head back to the reception area. Retrieving your money from the safe, minus the five hundred flames to cover admin fees, the donkey-boy gives you your refund and asks, [dale.speech(So, is there anything else I can do for you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun with [cow.name], and feeling well and truly satisfied, you take a [pc.step] back and tell her that you've finished.
		#IF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_innoxia_fields_dairyFarm_barn1)
			#IF(cow.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
				 Panting and moaning, [cow.name] sighs, [cow.speech(That was so good... Fuck... I've qualified for a promotion now as well...)]
			#ELSE
				 Panting and moaning, [cow.name] sighs, [cow.speech(You didn't exactly satisfy me, you know... Whatever, at least I've qualified for a promotion now...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_innoxia_fields_dairyFarm_barn2)
			#IF(cow.isHasAnyPregnancyEffects())
				 Letting out a happy moan, [cow.name] sighs, [cow.speech(Oh yeah, that's what I wanted... I hope I'll get pregnant from this so I can get promoted!)]
			#ELSE
				#IF(cow.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
					 Panting and moaning, [cow.name] sighs, [cow.speech(That was great... But you didn't even try and knock me up... I'll never get promoted at this rate...)]
				#ELSE
					 Panting and moaning, [cow.name] lets out an annoyed tut and sighs, [cow.speech(You didn't exactly satisfy me, you know... And you didn't even try and knock me up... I'll never get promoted at this rate...)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(cow.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
				 Panting and moaning, [cow.name] sighs, [cow.speech(That was great... I love getting fucked like this...)]
			#ELSE
				 Panting and moaning, [cow.name] sighs, [cow.speech(That was fun and all... But you didn't exactly satisfy me, you know...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As you get your things back in order, the [cow.race] presses a button on a small arcane device in front of her, signalling to reception that she's finished. A minute later, and Dale is happily stepping up to your side.
		#IF(cow.getTotalFluidInArea(ORIFICE_VAGINA)>0)
			 Looking down at the cum leaking from [cow.namePos] well-fuck cunt, the donkey-boy smiles and comments,
		#ELSEIF(cow.getTotalFluidInArea(ORIFICE_ANUS)>0)
			 Looking down at the cum leaking from [cow.namePos] well-fuck asshole, the donkey-boy smiles and comments,
		#ELSE
			 Looking down at the panting [cow.name], the donkey-boy smiles and comments,
		#ENDIF
		 [dale.speech(You sure gave her a good time, huh? Come on, let's get out of here and give her some space.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_AFTER_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Leaving [cow.name] behind, you [pc.walk] along beside Dale as he leads you back to the reception area. Sitting down at his desk with a weary sigh, he rubs his eyes and puts on another smile as he asks, [dale.speech(So, can I do anything else for you today, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Work: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_WORK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Curious to find out more about working here as a cow, you tell Dale that you're interested in the job offer and would like to know what it would entail.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(You're interested in becoming a cow? That's great! I'm sure you'd love working here!)] the donkey-boy exclaims, before starting to explain what your duties would be, [dale.speech(All you have to do is simply lie down in one of our milking stalls and have a machine suck on your breasts. Happy cows produce more milk, so the milking stalls and machines are some of the best and most comfortable on the market.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wondering how much money you could make by doing this, you ask Dale what the salary is. Leaning forwards in his chair, he says, [dale.speech(That depends on what promotion level you're at. We start all new cows as 'trainees', and then after producing enough milk and meeting some other requirements, you get promoted to 'heifer', and then 'cow'. Trainees make one hundred flames per hour, heifers make one hundred and fifty, and cows made two hundred. We don't have any strict requirements for your body, but you'll need a vagina and to be lactating, and we do encourage heifers and cows to transform into cow-morphs, but that isn't mandatory.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you think about what Dale's just said, he add, [dale.speech(Oh, and you earn a bonus of five hundred flames every time you're fucked in the stalls. Trainees and heifers have full control over when they have sex, but if you make it to being a cow, you can be fucked at any time while you're working. You also get access to our dormitory and wash facilities, and you get a selection of rewards after each four-hour milking session.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wondering what sort of behaviour is prohibited for cows, you ask Dale what rules you're expected to follow. Giving you a friendly smile, he reveals, [dale.speech(The only rules are that you can't access the barns which aren't of your promotional level, and physically interacting with the other cows is grounds for immediate termination. We had a few incidents in the past where an orgy got really out of control, and so we now have to insist on cows not being allowed to fuck one another. That is, unless you do it via the normal way of paying to gain access to them.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reaching down beneath his desk, Dale produces a small, black ear tag, of the sort you'd typically see on feral cattle. Holding it up so that you can see it, the donkey-boy says, [dale.speech(You'll get one of these to serve as your identification, and it will grant you access to your allocated barn. You don't have to wear it, but 
		#IF(!pc.isPiercedEar())
			 it is encouraged, and I can pierce your ears for you if you think you'd like to wear it.
		#ELSE
			 it is encouraged.
		#ENDIF
		 So, just let me know if you like the sound of all that, and I can get you signed up straight away.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_WORK_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that this sounds like too good an opportunity to pass up on, you tell Dale that you'll accept the work conditions and sign the contract. Happily smiling at you, the donkey-boy slides the papers over his desk and hands you a pen, saying, [dale.speech(That's great, [pc.name]! I'm responsible for attending to any new cows, so I guess I'll be seeing you over in the barn later.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Quickly reading over the contract to make sure that there aren't any hidden clauses, you sign on the dotted line and give Dale his pen back. You receive the black ear tag in return, and after taking a closer look at it, you note that it's got a single bronze pip on it. Seeing what it is you're looking at, Dale explains, [dale.speech(We upgrade that to two silver pips when you get promoted to heifer, and then to three golden ones when you become a cow. Once you've earned a promotion, come and see me and I'll upgrade it for you.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_WORK_ACCEPT_PIERCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling the donkey-boy that you'd like to take him up on his offer of piercing your ears, you lean forwards as he produces an arcane piercing gun and tells you to come closer. Reaching forwards, he very carefully and accurately slides the piercing gun into place your ear, and with a painless click, it's pierced. Repeating the process for your other ear, the donkey-boy puts the device away and says, [dale.speech(There you go, [pc.name]. You can wear that tag at any time now.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_WORK_ACCEPT_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turning his chair to one side, the donkey-boy gestures towards the doors behind him and continues, [dale.speech(You've got full access to the building now, although remember that you can only enter the barn which corresponds to your promotional level. So for you, that'll be the trainee barn. Oh, and a word of advice; don't disturb the boss. Evelyx hates being interrupted, and you really don't want to get on her bad side. You can try talking to the other members of staff, but I doubt that they'll have much time for you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking Dale for all of the information, you ask him how to get started. Once again gesturing to the pair of mirrored glass doors, he explains, [dale.speech(Just head through there and find the nearby door signposted as 'Trainee Barn'. Your ear tag will unlock the door, and once you're inside, find an empty stall and lie down in it. Each stall has a state-of-the-art arcane device attached to it, so just follow the instructions it gives you and you'll be good to go. Good luck on your first day, and I guess I'll be seeing you soon!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_WORK_DECLINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You really don't like the sound of this job, and so tell the donkey-boy that you're going to have to pass on it. Nodding his head in an understanding manner, Dale replies, [dale.speech(Yeah, it's not a job for everyone. If you change your mind, just let me know. Now, is there anything else you wanted today?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Work promotions: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion1))
		<p>
			Handing your ear tag to Dale, you tell him that you've earned a promotion, and would like to be upgraded to a 'heifer'. Flashing you a happy smile, the donkey-boy takes your tag and exclaims, [dale.speech(Congratulations, [pc.name]! I knew you'd make it to heifer. Now hold on a moment while I get your tag upgraded...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, Dale places your tag down beneath his desk, and after operating some kind of whirring arcane machine that's out of your sight, he straightens up and hands you your tag back. Instead of the single bronze pip, it now has two silver ones, and as you take a closer look at it, the donkey-boy explains, [dale.speech(You won't be able to access the trainee barn any more, but that tag will grant you access to the heifer barn. Congratulations again, [pc.name], and good luck on your journey towards earning that cow promotion!)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion2))
		<p>
			Handing your ear tag to Dale, you tell him that you've earned a promotion, and would like to be upgraded to a 'cow'. Flashing you a happy smile, the donkey-boy takes your tag and exclaims, [dale.speech(Congratulations, [pc.name]! I knew you'd make it all the way to being a cow. Now hold on a moment while I get your tag upgraded...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, Dale places your tag down beneath his desk, and after operating some kind of whirring arcane machine that's out of your sight, he straightens up and hands you your tag back. Instead of the two silver pips, it now has three gold ones, and as you take a closer look at it, the donkey-boy explains, [dale.speech(You won't be able to access the heifer barn any more, but that tag will grant you access to the cow barn. Congratulations again, [pc.name], and good luck on your journey towards earning your final promotion!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Handing your ear tag to Dale, you tell him that you've earned your final promotion, and would like to be upgraded to whatever comes after being a cow. Pushing your tag back towards you, the donkey-boy explains, [dale.speech(There's no rank after cow, so I can't upgrade your ear tag. This final promotion is something a little different... Well, to tell you the truth, even I don't know what exactly it involves. All I know is that cows who ask for their final promotion need to be given a meeting with Evelyx herself, so once you're ready for that, just let me know and I can arrange for you to see her.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Sensing a tone of unease in Dale's normally-confident voice, you ask him if something's the matter with this final promotion. Shaking his head, he says, [dale.speech(No, no, there's nothing wrong with it... It's just that the few cows who decide to ask about this final promotion usually never come back from their meeting with Evelyx... Yeah, I know, that sounds bad, but I guess that they must be promoted to another farm somewhere else in the Fields that I'm not aware of. Only a couple out of the two dozen or so that went for Evelyx's meeting actually refused her final promotion, and although I tried to ask them about it, they said that they were bound to secrecy...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Feeling more and more at unease about this final promotion the more Dale tells you about it, you ask him if there's anything else you should know about it. Glancing around to make sure that nobody's nearby to listen in on your conversation, the donkey-boy lowers his voice and says, [dale.speech(Well, I feel like it might have something to do with the disappearance of the receptionist who came before me. Some of the cows have mentioned that in the days before she vanished, she was asking questions about the secretive fourth barn and saying that it had something to do with cows who took the final promotion... I mean, I'm not suggesting anything... Sure, Evelyx can be harsh at times, but I'm sure that she wouldn't have done anything bad to that receptionist or the cows who take this last promotion... Right?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Really not sure about taking this final promotion by now, you thank Dale for the information. After taking a moment to think about it, you tell the donkey-boy that you'll ask for a meeting with Evelyx if you later decide that you want to find out what this final promotion involves.
			#IF(dale.getTotalTimesHadSex(pc)>0)
				 Visibly relaxing as he hears you say this, Dale flashes you a warm smile and says, [dale.speech(I really like having you around, [pc.name], and I'd hate to see you leave forever like all those other cows...)]
			#ELSE
				 Nodding his head as he hears you say this, Dale flashes you a warm smile and says, [dale.speech(Sure, give it some thought and just let me know if you want to see Evelyx.)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_MILKER_WORK_PROMOTION_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion1))
			Thanking Dale for his kind words, you wonder whether to head on over to the heifer barn straight away, or to instead ask the donkey-boy for something else first...
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion2))
			Thanking Dale for his kind words, you wonder whether to head on over to the cow barn straight away, or to instead ask the donkey-boy for something else first...
		#ELSE
			Thanking Dale again for his words of warning, you wonder whether to arrange a meeting with Evelyx straight away, or to instead leave your special promotion for another time...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion_meeting_happened))
		<p>
			Having changed your mind about your final promotion, you tell Dale that you'd like to have another meeting with Evelyx about it. Although he flashes you a worried look, Dale nevertheless reaches forwards and presses a button on the arcane intercom that's sitting on his desk. After emitting a short, loud buzzing noise, a posh, feminine voice speaks through it and impatiently snaps, [evelyx.speech(What is it, Dale?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(I have your employee, [pc.name], here in reception again, Ma'am,)] Dale replies,[dale.speech([pc.She] says that [pc.sheHad] changed [pc.her] mind about receiving [pc.her] final promotion, and would like to speak with you about it again.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(That dumb cow has changed [pc.her] mind, has [pc.she]?)] Evelyx's voice icily crackles out from the intercom, and after letting out a frustrated sigh, she says, [evelyx.speech(Fine, I'll see [pc.herHim] again, but make [pc.herHim] wait another thirty minutes first to put [pc.herHim] in [pc.her] place.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As the intercom clicks off, Dale motions towards the sofas on the other side of the reception and says, [dale.speech(If you'll first wait for thirty minutes, I'll show you to Evelyx's office.)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			Deciding that it would be best to do as the donkey-boy suggests, you head on over to the sofas and sit down. Thankfully, your half an hour wait seems to fly by as you wonder how your meeting with the succubus will turn out this time, and before you know it Dale is calling out, [dale.speech([pc.Name]! I can show you through to Evelyx's office now.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Curious to find out what's being offered for your final promotion, you tell Dale that you'd like to have a meeting with Evelyx about it. Although he flashes you a worried look, Dale nevertheless reaches forwards and presses a button on the arcane intercom that's sitting on his desk. After emitting a short, loud buzzing noise, a posh, feminine voice speaks through it and impatiently snaps, [evelyx.speech(What is it, Dale?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(I have your employee, [pc.name], here in reception, Ma'am,)] Dale replies, [dale.speech([pc.SheIs] asking about receiving [pc.her] final promotion, and would like to speak with you about it)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(Oh, another cow has managed to meet the promotional requirements?)] Evelyx's voice crackles out from the intercom, and after letting out a short hum, she says, [evelyx.speech(Very well, I'll see [pc.herHim], but make [pc.herHim] wait for thirty minutes first to put [pc.herHim] in [pc.her] place.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As the intercom clicks off, Dale motions towards the sofas on the other side of the reception and says, [dale.speech(If you'll first wait for thirty minutes, I'll show you to Evelyx's office.)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			Deciding that it would be best to do as the donkey-boy suggests, you head on over to the sofas and sit down. Thankfully, your half an hour wait seems to fly by as you wonder what your meeting with the succubus will involve, and before you know it Dale is calling out, [dale.speech([pc.Name]! I can show you through to Evelyx's office now.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Standing up, you trot over to Dale's desk, before accompanying the donkey-boy down the corridor to the wooden door bearing the words 'Evelyx's Office'. After raising his fist to deliver a quick knock, Dale opens the door for you and announces your arrival by saying into the room beyond, [dale.speech([pc.Name] is here to see you, Ma'am.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX_ENTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] forwards into the spacious office, you look around to see that Evelyx's lair is extravagantly furnished. Mahogany shelves are filled with expensive-looking tomes and golden decorations, while large portraits of demons and landscape paintings hang from the walls. A rich, burgundy rug has been placed in the centre of the floor, and over on the far side, you see Evelyx herself sitting in a huge leather chair behind a masterfully-carved wooden desk. Dale closes the door behind you as you enter, and despite the fact
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion_meeting_happened))
			 that you've previously been through this meeting with her before, Evelyx acts as though she doesn't know who you are as she casts her piercing gaze over your body.
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_monica_meeting))
			 that you've met her before, Evelyx acts as though she doesn't know who you are as she casts her piercing gaze over your body.
		#ELSE
			 that there's no clear sign of any danger, you can't help but feel like you've walked right into a trap. 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(Come here, cow,)] Evelyx commands, curling one of her slender fingers in a come-hither motion. As you approach her desk, you take a good look at the owner of this farm. The flawless skin covering her body is a light shade of blue, and while her face has a youthful appearance, the cynical, penetrating gaze from her orange eyes suggests that she's far older than she looks. Her orange nail polish and lipstick matches not only the same shade as her eyes, but also the orange hue that tips the ends of her four small, swept-back horns. Her long, black hair is tied up into a ponytail by means of an orange scrunchie, and a pair of large, [evelyx.cupSize]-cup breasts swell out beneath the succubus's smart, black feminine suit. A gap at the base of her desk allows you to see that instead of humanoid feet, Evelyx has a pair of hard hoofs.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(So then, '[pc.name]', you thought that it was appropriate for you, nothing more than one of my cows, to bother me, a direct daughter of the elder lilin Lisophia?)]
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion_meeting_happened))
			 she asks in her posh, naturally-condescending accent, showing absolutely no sign of acknowledging the fact that the two of you have had this meeting before.
		#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_monica_meeting))
			 she asks in her posh, naturally-condescending accent, showing absolutely no sign of acknowledging the fact that the two of you have met before.
		#ELSE
			 she asks in a posh, naturally-condescending accent.
		#ENDIF
		 Before you can give her an answer, the succubus holds up a hand for silence, before asking another question, [evelyx.speech(Have you been working hard for me, cow?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Giving the blue-skinned succubus a nod, you tell her that you've worked extra hard for her, and have produced enough milk to have earned your final promotion. Flashing you a smirk as she hears you say this, Evelyx taps several sheets of paper which are laid out over her desk, before revealing, [evelyx.speech(Everything you've been up has been tracked and written down here in your performance report. I'll read through this and be the judge of whether you've been a good cow or not, after which we can discuss your promotion. Now present me with your pussy; I want to get a good look at the cunt I'll be fucking if your performance report is acceptable.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX_ENTER_OBEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you manoeuvre your lower [pc.legRace]'s body around so that your hindquarters are facing Evelyx. Spreading your rear legs a little, you dutifully obey the blue-skinned succubus and present her with your [pc.pussy+]. After spending a moment silently judging the appearance of your cunt, Evelyx lets out an approving hum and commands in her posh accent, [evelyx.speech(Hold that position until I'm finished.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Again doing as you're told, you remain standing in that position, and can't help but start to feel incredibly turned on by having your pussy occasionally glanced at by this dominant, blue-skinned succubus. Taking her time to read over your performance report, she keeps you in this humiliating pose for a good ten minutes, before finally finishing the last page and stating, [evelyx.speech(According to these documents, your performance has been acceptable, and so I grant you permission to receive your final promotion. I'm pleased to see that you're an obedient cow. That will make the rest of this so much easier. Now kneel before me while I explain what this will involve.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Obediently hurrying to do as you're told, you quickly kneel down before Evelyx. Allowing the briefest hint of a happy smirk to flash across her face, the blue-skinned succubus makes one final mark on your performance report, before stating, [evelyx.speech(You will have the option to refuse my offer, but before I explain it to you, you must agree to never tell anyone about what it is that I'm offering you. Do you agree to these terms?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX_ENTER_REFUSE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to humiliate yourself in such a fashion, you tell Evelyx that you'd rather remain standing as you are. Giving you an intense, icy glare, the blue-skinned succubus pointedly produces a pen from out of her desk's drawer, before making a black mark on your performance report. Not letting her annoyance at your disobedience affect the tone of her voice, she calmly states in her posh accent, [evelyx.speech(You are to remain silent until I'm finished.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing no harm in following that command, you stay quiet as the dominant, blue-skinned succubus takes her time to read over your performance report. After a good ten minutes, she finally finishes the last page and states, [evelyx.speech(According to these documents, your performance has been acceptable, and so despite your silly little rebellious act just now, I grant you permission to receive your final promotion. Now kneel before me while I explain what it involves.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that you'll have to do what she says this time if you want to get any further with your promotion, you do as Evelyx says and kneel down before her. Allowing the briefest hint of a triumphant smirk to flash across her face, the blue-skinned succubus makes one final mark on your performance report, before stating, [evelyx.speech(You will have the option to refuse my offer, but before I explain it to you, you must agree to never tell anyone about what it is that I'm offering you. Do you agree to these terms?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX_CONTRACT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.isBadEndsEnabled())
		<p>
			Agreeing not to mention the specifics of this final promotion to anyone, should you decide to refuse, you ask Evelyx what exactly it is that you're to be offered. As though it's the most mundane thing in the world, she flatly states, [evelyx.speech(Your final promotion will involve signing a contract to willingly become my lifelong slave. I'll have you assigned to the fourth barn, which is where I keep the other promoted cows, and you'll spend the rest of your days being fucked, bred, and milked. The contract is non-transferable, so you don't need to worry about me selling you off to anyone else.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Before you can react to this extreme offer, Evelyx stands up and pulls up her skirt, revealing that she's transformed to give herself a huge, flared, knotted demonic cock, which instead of being light blue like the rest of her skin, is the same orange hue as her eyes and horns. As she strokes her four massive, heavy balls, she states in her usual calm, posh tone, [evelyx.speech(Cows like you are the only ones who get to see what my cock looks like. I know a submissive little slut when I see one, and so I know that you won't be able to resist this. Now hurry up and sign the contract to become my slave so that I can move on to getting balls-deep in your pussy.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After sliding a piece of paper across the desk towards you, which you see is the contract to become Evelyx's lifelong slave, the succubus slaps her semi-flaccid cock down onto the desk beside it with a heavy thud. Holding out a pen towards you, she simply demands, [evelyx.speech(Sign it, slave.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Agreeing not to mention the specifics of this final promotion to anyone, should you decide to refuse, you ask Evelyx what exactly it is that you're to be offered. As though it's the most mundane thing in the world, she flatly states, [evelyx.speech(I know about your relation to Lilaya, so I can't offer you the usual slave contract which I give to the other cows as their final promotion. Instead, I had this contract drawn up that will officially acknowledge your agreement to be whored out to Lunette's centaurs once per day. Pleasing those daughters of Lunette is the only thing which keeps my farm from being destroyed, and while they appreciate the slaves which I allow them to use, I'm sure they'll be very happy to rut such a close relative of Lyssieth's. In exchange for your services, I shall generously reward you with a thousand flames each times you're fucked.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Before you can react to this extreme offer, Evelyx stands up and pulls up her skirt, revealing that she's transformed to give herself a huge, flared, knotted demonic cock, which instead of being light blue like the rest of her skin, is the same orange hue as her eyes and horns. As she strokes her four massive, heavy balls, she states in her usual calm, posh tone, [evelyx.speech(Cows like you are the only ones who get to see what my cock looks like. I know a submissive little slut when I see one, and so I know that you won't be able to resist this. Now hurry up and sign the contract to become my whore so that I can move on to getting balls-deep in your pussy.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After sliding a piece of paper across the desk towards you, which you see is the contract to allow Evelyx to pimp you out to Lunette's centaurs, the succubus slaps her semi-flaccid cock down onto the desk beside it with a heavy thud. Holding out a pen towards you, she simply demands, [evelyx.speech(Sign it, whore.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX_CONTRACT_DONT_SIGN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not liking the sound of Evelyx's offer, you push the contract back over the desk towards her, trying your best while doing so to not stare hungrily at her fat, twitching cock. Seeing that you're refusing to accept her final promotion, the succubus gives you an icy, piercing stare, before calmly transforming her cock away and pulling down her skirt. Picking up the contract, she calmly states in her posh accent, [evelyx.speech(You are fortunate that you've been such a good cow while working for me. I shall forgive your insolence, and allow you to accept my offer at another time. For the rest of today, however, I want you gone from my sight. Now leave.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thinking that it's best to do as you're told, you turn around and quickly step over to the door. With Evelyx continuing to give you a cold look, you hurriedly exit her office, before closing the door behind you and stepping back out into the corridor beyond. Letting out a sigh, you wonder what you're going to do now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX_CONTRACT_SIGNED"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.isBadEndsEnabled())
		<p>
			Feeling madly turned on at the prospect of fully submitting to Evelyx and becoming her lifelong slave, you take the pen from her and quickly read over the contract. Just as she said, there's a clause which prevents her from selling you to anyone else, but other than that, it looks like she'll be free to do whatever she likes with you. Hungrily glancing over at her fat, demonic cock as it twitches on the desk, you make up your mind and sign the contract.
		</p>
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(That's my good slave,)] Evelyx praises you as you sign yourself into being nothing more than her property. Picking up the piece of paper, the succubus carefully files it away in one of her drawers, before smirking at you and commanding, [evelyx.speech(Now hand over all of your belongings. You may retain any cattle or bondage clothing which you're wearing; it's only right for a cow slave to be wearing those things. Everything else, including all of your flames, you are to surrender to me this instant.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Feeling madly turned on at the prospect of agreeing to become Evelyx's whore, you take the pen from her and quickly read over the contract. Just as she said, it states that you agree to let her whore you out once a day in exchange for a thousand flames. Thankfully, there's no binding agreement to force you to perform this action every day, and it seems to be entirely voluntary on your part. Hungrily glancing over at her fat, demonic cock as it twitches on the desk, you make up your mind and sign the contract.
		</p>
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(That's my good whore,)] Evelyx praises you as you sign yourself to effectively recognise Evelyx as your pimp. Picking up the piece of paper, the succubus carefully files it away in one of her drawers, before smirking at you and commanding, [evelyx.speech(It's time for me to find out how good your cunt feels to fuck. Present yourself to me, whore. I'm starting to feel quite aroused, and could do with emptying my balls deep into your horny pussy.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX_CONTRACT_SIGNED_END"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.isBadEndsEnabled())
		<p>
			Having finished taking all of your possessions from you, Evelyx finally declares, [evelyx.speech(It's time for you to find out what your Mistress's cock feels like. Present me with your cunt, slave. I'm starting to feel quite aroused, and could do with emptying my balls deep into your worthless slave pussy.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As she talks, Evelyx's calm, posh manner of speaking starts to transform into a more lewd, lustful tone, and as her semi-flaccid cock starts to rise into a massive erection, she hungrily moans, [evelyx.speech(I'm going to fuck you senseless, slave! ~Mmm!~ My fat cock's so desperate to pound your hot, filthy cunt! Hurry up and present it to me!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As she talks, Evelyx's calm, posh manner of speaking starts to transform into a more lewd, lustful tone, and as her semi-flaccid cock starts to rise into a massive erection, she hungrily moans, [evelyx.speech(I'm going to fuck you senseless, my sexy little whore! ~Mmm!~ My fat cock's so desperate to pound your hot, filthy cunt! Hurry up and present it to me!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX_CONTRACT_SIGNED_FUCK_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.isBadEndsEnabled())
		<p>
			Madly turned on and desperate to please your Mistress, you hurry to turn around and present your hindquarters to her. As she similarly starts to be overcome by her lust, Evelyx gets more excited, dominant, and even a little sadistic, and as she delivers a sharp slap to your ass, she moans, [evelyx.speech(That's it, do as your Mistress commands! ~Mmm!~ You're so desperate for my cock, aren't you, my worthless little slave cow slut?! Go on, beg for me to pound your filthy cunt!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a lewd squeal as your owner delivers another stinging slap to your ass, you desperately pant, [pc.speech(Yes, Mistress! ~Ooh!~ Please, pound my filthy slave cunt!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(Get down so that I can mount you then, you dumb cow!)] she excitedly demands, and as you drop down to lie on the floor of her office, your owner steps forwards and quickly presses the [evelyx.cockHead+] of her huge, demonic cock against your [pc.labia+]. Consumed by her lust, she wastes no time in thrusting forwards, and you let out a desperate, high-pitched squeal as you feel her [evelyx.cock+] slamming deep into your [pc.pussy+]. Grabbing hold of your [pc.hips+], the blue-skinned succubus rams her fat, throbbing shaft as deep as possible into your pussy, before starting to roughly fuck you in a wild, lust-fuelled frenzy...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Madly turned on and desperate to please Evelyx, you hurry to turn around and present your hindquarters to her. As she similarly starts to be overcome by her lust, the blue-skinned succubus gets more excited, dominant, and even a little sadistic, and as she delivers a sharp slap to your ass, she moans, [evelyx.speech(That's it, do as I command! ~Mmm!~ You're so desperate for my cock, aren't you, my worthless little cow whore?! Go on, beg for me to pound your filthy cunt!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a lewd squeal as Evelyx delivers another stinging slap to your ass, you desperately pant, [pc.speech(Yes! ~Ooh!~ Please, pound my filthy cunt!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(Get down so that I can mount you then, you dumb cow!)] she excitedly demands, and as you drop down to lie on the floor of her office, Evelyx steps forwards and quickly presses the [evelyx.cockHead+] of her huge, demonic cock against your [pc.labia+]. Consumed by her lust, she wastes no time in thrusting forwards, and you let out a desperate, high-pitched squeal as you feel her [evelyx.cock+] slamming deep into your [pc.pussy+]. Grabbing hold of your [pc.hips+], the blue-skinned succubus rams her fat, throbbing shaft as deep as possible into your pussy, before starting to roughly fuck you in a wild, lust-fuelled frenzy...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.isBadEndsEnabled())
		<p>
			Having emptied her balls into you like she said she would, Evelyx steps back and regains her posh-sounding accent as she declares, [evelyx.speech(Your cunt was most acceptable, slave. Whoever adopts you is sure to be pleased.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Panting and moaning as you try to recover from your owner's brutal pounding, you wonder what she means by your adoption. Before you can ask any questions about it, however, Evelyx sits down on her office chair and commands, [evelyx.speech(Come and clean my cock off with your mouth. Once you've finished, I'll show you to your new home, then I'll contact the nearby herds so that we can get you auctioned off as soon as possible.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Although Evelyx's words raise yet more questions in your mind, you reason that you'll find out what she means soon enough, and so you stay quiet as you obediently shuffle forwards and start to lick the sexual fluids from her softening cock. Getting to pleasure your owner in such a submissive manner keeps you in a state of high arousal, and you continue to let out soft, horny moans as you set about licking her hot, demonic shaft clean.
		</p>
		<p>
			Thanks to your enthusiasm, it only takes you a few minutes to swallow down every last drop of both your and Evelyx's sexual fluids from her massive, orange cock. Seeing that you've finished, your owner stands up and pulls her skirt down to cover herself up, before ordering, [evelyx.speech(Follow me, slave. It's time to see your new home.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having emptied her balls into you like she said she would, Evelyx steps back and regains her posh-sounding accent as she declares, [evelyx.speech(Your cunt was most acceptable, whore. Whichever of Lunette's centaurs gets to fuck you is sure to be pleased.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As you pant and moan as you try to recover from the succubus's brutal pounding, Evelyx sits down on her office chair and commands, [evelyx.speech(Come and clean my cock off with your mouth. Once you've finished, you can get out of my sight. I won't be able to start whoring you out until I've informed the local herds of your availability, so your services will not be required until tomorrow at the earliest.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Obediently shuffling forwards as she says this, you start to lick the sexual fluids from the succubus's softening cock. Getting to pleasure Evelyx in such a submissive manner keeps you in a state of high arousal, and you continue to let out soft, horny moans as you set about licking her hot, demonic shaft clean.
		</p>
		<p>
			Thanks to your enthusiasm, it only takes you a few minutes to swallow down every last drop of both your and Evelyx's sexual fluids from her massive, orange cock. Seeing that you've finished, the succubus pulls her skirt down to cover herself up, before ordering, [evelyx.speech(Now get out of here, whore. Come back and visit me directly tomorrow to begin your extra duties. There's no need to go through Dale for this; just knock on the door to my office.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="WORK_PROMOTION_EVELYX_AFTER_SEX_NO_BAD_END_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With nothing to be gained from disobeying Evelyx at this stage, you suppress your urges to beg for more sex and do as you're told. Trotting over to the door to her office, you quickly return to the corridor beyond, before wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Monica quest content: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_monica_meeting))
		<p>
			Wanting to discuss the matter of obtaining Monica's breast pump with Evelyx again,
			#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_CHUUNI))
				 you loudly declare to Dale that you require another fateful meeting with the succubus.
			#ELSE
				 you ask Dale if it would be possible to have another meeting with the succubus.
			#ENDIF
			 Although he flashes you a worried look, Dale nevertheless reaches forwards and presses a button on the arcane intercom that's sitting on his desk. After emitting a short, loud buzzing noise, a posh, feminine voice speaks through it and impatiently snaps, [evelyx.speech(What is it this time, Dale?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion_meeting_happened) || flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_started))
				[dale.speech(I have your employee, [pc.name], here in reception again, Ma'am,)]
			#ELSE
				[dale.speech(I have that [pc.race], [pc.name], here in reception again, Ma'am,)]
			#ENDIF
			 Dale replies,[dale.speech([pc.SheIs] asking about that custom breast pump, and would like to see you again regarding it.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(That insolent little thing has come crawling back, has [pc.she]?)] Evelyx's voice icily crackles out from the intercom, and after letting out a frustrated sigh, she says, [evelyx.speech(Fine, I'll see [pc.herHim] again, but make [pc.herHim] wait another fifteen minutes first.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As the intercom clicks off, Dale motions towards the sofas on the other side of the reception and says, [dale.speech(If you'll first wait for fifteen minutes, I'll show you to Evelyx's office.)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_CHUUNI))
				Letting out a laugh as you hear this absurd request, you spin around on the spot and strike a suitably intimidating pose, before declaring to the donkey-boy that you've got no time to waste with such silly games. Making an idle threat about obliterating the universe if you're kept waiting any longer, you [pc.step] past the reception desk and force Dale to accompany you to Evelyx's office...
			#ELSE
				Deciding that it would be best to do as the donkey-boy suggests, you head on over to the sofas and sit down. Wondering what you're going to say to the succubus this time, you prepare to wait for fifteen minutes...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to find out if Evelyx's Dairy is still in possession of Monica's custom breast pump, you ask Dale if any of the old equipment from the previous farm is still being kept here. Raising his eyebrows, he replies, [dale.speech(We've still got a lot of that old stuff in storage, yeah. Why do you want to know?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Telling Dale what it is that you're after, you wait as the donkey-boy thinks for a moment, before revealing, [dale.speech(A custom breast pump like that wouldn't have been thrown away, so it's probably still in storage somewhere. If you're after it, then I'll have to run your request by Evelyx, as she's the one who signs off on all equipment which we buy or sell here. Hold on a moment...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, Dale reaches forwards and presses a button on the arcane intercom that's sitting on his desk. After emitting a short, loud buzzing noise, a posh, feminine voice speaks through it and impatiently snaps, [evelyx.speech(What is it, Dale?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion_meeting_happened))
				[dale.speech(I have your employee, [pc.name], here in reception again, Ma'am,)]
			#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_started))
				[dale.speech(I have one of your employees, [pc.name], here in reception, Ma'am,)]
			#ELSE
				[dale.speech(I have [pc.a_race], [pc.name], here in reception, Ma'am,)]
			#ENDIF
			 Dale replies,[dale.speech([pc.SheIs] asking about acquiring an item which we might have in storage; a custom breast pump from the old farm.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(What?! You really thought that it was a good idea to waste my time with this?!)] Evelyx's voice angrily crackles out from the intercom, but in just a moment she completely reverses her attitude and asks in a curious tone, [evelyx.speech(Hold on, is [pc.she] willing to pay for this? If so, then maybe we can strike a deal...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Not wanting to miss what might be your only opportunity to obtain Monica's breast pump, you nod your head to Dale, who conveys to his boss that you are indeed willing to pay to get your [pc.hands] on that item. A smug-sounding laugh comes through over the intercom, followed by the short order, [evelyx.speech(Send [pc.her] in after fifteen minutes. I'll have that breast pump ready and waiting for [pc.herHim].)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As the intercom clicks off, Dale motions towards the sofas on the other side of the reception and says, [dale.speech(If you'll first wait for fifteen minutes, I'll show you to Evelyx's office.)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			Deciding that it would be best to do as the donkey-boy suggests, you head on over to the sofas and sit down. Wondering what Evelyx is going to demand in return for Monica's breast pump, you prepare to wait for fifteen minutes...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After making you wait for almost twenty minutes, you hear the voice of Evelyx suddenly call out over Dale's intercom, [evelyx.speech(Show them through now, Dale. I don't have all day, so be quick about it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Yes, Ma'am!)] Dale replies, before urgently beckoning you forwards. Rising from the sofa, you follow the donkey-boy as he leads you through the doors behind his desk, down a corridor, and to a wooden door bearing the words 'Evelyx's Office'. After raising his fist to deliver a quick knock, Dale opens the door for you and announces your arrival by saying into the room beyond, [dale.speech([pc.Name] is here to see you, Ma'am.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_CHUUNI) && !flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion_meeting_happened))
			Not letting Dale steal your opportunity to make a suitable first impression, you confidently [pc.step] into the spacious office and strike an impressive pose, before loudly declaring yourself to be the most powerful being in existence. After stating that you have unimaginable cosmic powers under your control, you finally take a moment to look around at Evelyx's extravagantly furnished lair.
		#ELSE
			[pc.Stepping] forwards into the spacious office, you look around to see that Evelyx's lair is extravagantly furnished.
		#ENDIF
		 Mahogany shelves are filled with expensive-looking tomes and golden decorations, while large portraits of demons and landscape paintings hang from the walls. A rich, burgundy rug has been placed in the centre of the floor, and over on the far side, you see Evelyx herself sitting in a huge leather chair behind a masterfully-carved wooden desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_CHUUNI) && !flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion_meeting_happened))
			[evelyx.speech(What an amusing thing you are. Come,)] 
		#ELSE
			[evelyx.speech(Come,)] 
		#ENDIF
		 Evelyx commands, curling one of her slender fingers in a come-hither motion. As you approach her desk, you take a good look at the owner of this farm. The flawless skin covering her body is a light shade of blue, and while her face has a youthful appearance, the cynical, penetrating gaze from her orange eyes suggests that she's far older than she looks. Her orange nail polish and lipstick matches not only the same shade as her eyes, but also the orange hue that tips the ends of her four small, swept-back horns. Her long, black hair is tied up into a ponytail by means of an orange scrunchie, and a pair of large, [evelyx.cupSize]-cup breasts swell out beneath the succubus's smart, black feminine suit. A gap at the base of her desk allows you to see that instead of humanoid feet, Evelyx has a pair of hard hoofs.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion_meeting_happened))
			[evelyx.speech(So then, [pc.name], you thought that it was appropriate for you, nothing more than one of my cows, to bother me, a direct daughter of the elder lilin Lisophia?)] she asks in a posh, naturally-condescending accent. Before you can give her an answer, the succubus pointedly places Monica's breast pump down on her desk, before asking the direct question, [evelyx.speech(Why do you desire this, cow?)]
		#ELSE
			[evelyx.speech(So then, '[pc.name]', you thought that it was wise to bother me, a direct daughter of the elder lilin Lisophia?)] she asks in a posh, naturally-condescending accent. Before you can give her an answer, the succubus pointedly places Monica's breast pump down on her desk, before asking the direct question, [evelyx.speech(Why do you desire this?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_CHUUNI))
		<p>
			Confidently leading the way, you tell Dale to keep up as you stride through the doors behind his desk, down a corridor, and to the familiar wooden door bearing the words 'Evelyx's Office'. Rushing forwards to get in front of you, the donkey-boy hastily raises his fist to deliver a quick knock, before opening the door and apologising into the room beyond, [dale.speech(I'm so sorry, Ma'am! I couldn't stop [pc.herHim]; [pc.name] was insistent upon seeing you immediately.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			After making you wait for almost twenty minutes, you hear the voice of Evelyx suddenly call out over Dale's intercom, [evelyx.speech(Show them through now, Dale. I don't have all day, so be quick about it!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(Yes, Ma'am!)] Dale replies, before urgently beckoning you forwards. Rising from the sofa, you follow the donkey-boy as he leads you through the doors behind his desk, down a corridor, and to the familiar wooden door bearing the words 'Evelyx's Office'. After raising his fist to deliver a quick knock, Dale opens the door for you and announces your arrival by saying into the room beyond, [dale.speech([pc.Name] is here to see you, Ma'am.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] forwards into the spacious office, you look around to once again see that Evelyx's lair is extravagantly furnished. Mahogany shelves are filled with expensive-looking tomes and golden decorations, while large portraits of demons and landscape paintings hang from the walls. A rich, burgundy rug has been placed in the centre of the floor, and over on the far side, you see Evelyx herself sitting in a huge leather chair behind a masterfully-carved wooden desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_CHUUNI))
			[evelyx.speech(What insolence! Count yourself lucky that I'm keen to see this deal struck; ordinarily I'd have you thrown out of here for pulling a stunt like this! Now that you're here, however, I suppose we can get right down to business. Come,)]
		#ELSE
			[evelyx.speech(Come,)]
		#ENDIF
		 Evelyx commands, curling one of her slender fingers in a come-hither motion. As you approach her desk, you take a good look at the owner of this farm. The flawless skin covering her body is a light shade of blue, and while her face has a youthful appearance, the cynical, penetrating gaze from her orange eyes suggests that she's far older than she looks. Her orange nail polish and lipstick matches not only the same shade as her eyes, but also the orange hue that tips the ends of her four small, swept-back horns. Her long, black hair is tied up into a ponytail by means of an orange scrunchie, and a pair of large, [evelyx.cupSize]-cup breasts swell out beneath the succubus's smart, black feminine suit. A gap at the base of her desk allows you to see that instead of humanoid feet, Evelyx has a pair of hard hoofs.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasTraitActivated(PERK_CHUUNI))
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(Fifty thousand flames, and this worthless thing is all yours!)] the succubus states as she produces and pointedly places Monica's breast pump down on her desk. Smirking at the outrageous figure she's just given to you, Evelyx hold up a finger for you to wait and listen before responding, and after a moment, she pulls open one of her desk's drawers to retrieve the enchanted ring which she showed to you before. [evelyx.speech(Of course, I suppose that I could offer you an alternative... All you'd have to do is put on this ring and answer a few questions for me...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(So then, [pc.name], you've come crawling back, just as I knew you would,)] she mocks. Before you can respond, the succubus pointedly places Monica's breast pump down on her desk, before stating, [evelyx.speech(Fifty thousand flames, and this worthless thing is all yours!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smirking at the outrageous figure she's just given to you, Evelyx hold up a finger for you to wait and listen before responding, and after a moment, she pulls open one of her desk's drawers and produces the enchanted ring which she showed to you before. [evelyx.speech(Of course, I suppose that I could offer you an alternative... All you'd have to do is put on this ring and answer a few questions for me...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		With that, Evelyx holds up the ring to give you a better look, and you see that it consists of a thin band of black metal with a stylised pair of orange lips attached to one side of it. From the way Evelyx takes great care to let it slip down onto any of her slender, feminine fingers, you can tell that there must be some kind of serious enchantment on it. Sensing your cautious appraisal of this item, Evelyx laughs and reveals, [evelyx.speech(Oh, don't worry, I'm not trying to trick you. Put this ring on, and you're going to want nothing more than to eat out every girl you meet. Your mind's going to be filled with all sorts of dirty thoughts about sticking your tongue into every kind of cunt imaginable, including mine. Oh, and the best part is that you won't be able to take it off! So, it's either pay up or wear this ring. The choice is yours.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you consider your options, you notice that once again a horny gleam has entered Evelyx's eyes after talking about you performing cunnilingus, clearly revealing that she has a kink for that sort of thing, and so you wonder if you could use this knowledge to seduce her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Seeing no reason not to give Evelyx the truth, you tell her that the breast pump she's holding is special to Monica, and that you'd like to get it back for her. Letting out an amused, mocking laugh as she hears you say this, the blue-skinned succubus smirks at you and explains, [evelyx.speech(I assumed that your motivation was something utterly pathetic like that. Ordinarily, I'd never agree to even letting you into my office under these circumstances, but it so happens that I've got a deal to offer you. This breast pump must have cost, what, no more than a thousand flames to have made? My time is extremely precious, however, and you've already taken up so much of it... I couldn't see myself handing this over to you for anything less than fifty thousand flames.)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Smirking at the outrageous figure she's just given to you, Evelyx hold up a finger for you to wait and listen before responding, and after a moment, she pulls open one of her desk's drawers and produces what looks to be some kind of ring, before drawling, [evelyx.speech(Of course, I suppose that I could offer you an alternative... All you'd have to do is put on this ring and answer a few questions for me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Evelyx holds up the ring to give you a better look, and you see that it consists of a thin band of black metal with a stylised pair of orange lips attached to one side of it. From the way Evelyx takes great care to let it slip down onto any of her slender, feminine fingers, you can tell that there must be some kind of serious enchantment on it. Sensing your cautious appraisal of this item, Evelyx laughs and reveals in her posh, condescending tone, [evelyx.speech(Oh, don't worry, I'm not trying to trick you. Put this ring on, and you're going to want nothing more than to eat out every girl you meet. Your mind's going to be filled with all sorts of dirty thoughts about sticking your tongue into every kind of cunt imaginable, including mine. Oh, and the best part is that you won't be able to take it off! So, it's either pay up or wear this ring. The choice is yours.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you consider your options, you notice that a horny gleam has entered Evelyx's eyes after talking about you performing cunnilingus, clearly revealing that she has a kink for that sort of thing, and so you wonder if you could use this knowledge to seduce her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_INTRO_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You really don't like the sound of these options, and so tell Evelyx that you'll have to think about her deal and come back at another time. Although she wasn't exactly giving you a friendly look before, a positively disgusted look flashes over the succubus's face as she hears your response, and after tutting under her breath, she sneers, [evelyx.speech(Then get out of my sight. Don't come back again unless you're ready to accept my generous offer. Oh, and don't even think about having the nerve to come back and bother me with this foolishness again today. You'll wait until tomorrow at the earliest before being allowed to speak with me regarding this matter.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you turn to leave, Evelyx presses the button on the intercom that's sitting on her desk, before snapping, [evelyx.speech(Get in here, Dale.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The donkey-boy receptionist arrives running just as you get to the door, and after correctly assessing the situation, he asks you to accompany him back to the reception area. Doing so, you soon find yourself once again standing before Dale's desk, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_PAID"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid wearing that ring at all costs, you tell Evelyx that you're willing to pay her for the breast pump, before placing the fifty thousand flames she's demanded on the desk in front of her. The succubus's eyes light up as she sees the money, and after carelessly tossing Monica's breast pump to you, she greedily seizes the cash and starts counting it. With a big grin on her face, she waves you away and declares, [evelyx.speech(It's a shame that I didn't get to experiment on you with my ring, but this more than makes up for it. You've got what you wanted, now get out of my sight.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not willing to pay the outrageous sum of fifty thousand flames in exchange for Monica's breast pump, you tell Evelyx that you're willing to put on her ring. A wicked grin flashes across the succubus's face as she hears this, and as she slides the ring across the desk towards you, she states, [evelyx.speech(You have to answer my questions as part of the deal, understand?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Agreeing to her terms, and pick up Evelyx's ring and slide the metal band down around one of your [pc.fingers+]. Instantly, images of dripping-wet pussies flash across your mind, and you can't help but picture yourself down on the floor of Evelyx's office with your head  between her legs. You find yourself starting to drool as you imagine your tongue buried deep in her delicious, hot cunt, but before your daydreaming gets out of hand, you're suddenly snapped back to reality by the succubus's amused laughter. A triumphant, mocking smirk is plastered across her face, and her posh accent starts to give way to a lewd, hungry tone of voice as she teases, [evelyx.speech(I can tell what naughty thoughts you're having from that lewd expression on your face. It looks like my little creation is a success. You want to eat pussy, don't you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the ring's effects still fresh and strong in your mind, you find yourself quickly answering in the positive, which causes Evelyx to let out another amused chuckle. Interlacing her fingers, she places her elbows down on her desk and leans forwards, before stating, [evelyx.speech(Let's get down to business with my first question... You couldn't imagine anything better than being allowed to eat me out right now, could you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_AGREE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With the fantasy of eating her out still running wild in the back of your mind, you answer Evelyx truthfully and tell her that all you want right now is to be servicing her pussy with your mouth and tongue.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(Good, good,)] she replies in a delighted tone. Pushing her chair back so that you can look down over the top of her desk to see her groin, Evelyx pulls up her pencil skirt and slides her lacy orange thong all the way down her legs, before kicking it off to one side. Leaning back in her chair, she spreads her legs and presents herself to you, allowing you to see that both her cunt and asshole are the same orange hue as her eyes and horns. Teasing her light blue fingers down over her tiny, exotic-looking labia, she uses them to part her folds and show you how vice-tight her already-wet twat is.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(All of this talk is getting me turned on,)] she teases, and you find yourself unable to look away as you hungrily stare at the succubus's delicious-looking pussy. Seeing the look on your face, Evelyx smirks and asks her second question, [evelyx.speech(So what do you think of what you're being allowed to see? Is this not the prettiest little cunt you've ever seen?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_DISAGREE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although the fantasy of eating her out is still running wild in the back of your mind, you somehow manage to resist the ring's effects and tell Evelyx that all you aren't particularly bothered about being allowed to eat her out right now.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(Oh, is that so? Well, let's see if you change your tune after this,)] she replies in an annoyed tone. Pushing her chair back so that you can look down over the top of her desk to see her groin, Evelyx pulls up her pencil skirt and slides her lacy orange thong all the way down her legs, before kicking it off to one side. Leaning back in her chair, she spreads her legs and presents herself to you, allowing you to see that both her cunt and asshole are the same orange hue as her eyes and horns. Teasing her light blue fingers down over her tiny, exotic-looking labia, she uses them to part her folds and show you how vice-tight her already-wet twat is.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(Despite your insolence, I'm getting quite turned on,)] she teases, and you find yourself unable to look away as you hungrily stare at the succubus's delicious-looking pussy. Seeing the look on your face, Evelyx smirks and asks her second question, [evelyx.speech(So what do you think of what you're being allowed to see? Is this not the prettiest little cunt you've ever seen?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_NEXT_FLATTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Even without the influence of the ring, you'd definitely consider Evelyx's tight, brightly-coloured cunt to be alluring, but with the enchanted item's influence strong in your mind, you find yourself utterly enraptured by the sight of this succubus's pussy. Letting out a hungry whine, you find yourself flattering Evelyx by telling her in multiple different ways how her cunt is by far the prettiest you've ever seen.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes, that's it, keep going,)] she softly moans in an approving voice. As you continue to tell the succubus what she wants to hear, she starts to slide her fingers into her pussy, and after spending a moment listening to you, she withdraws her slender digits and holds them up to show you that they're coated in a slick layer of slimy girlcum. Presenting her fingers to you, she smirks and states, [evelyx.speech(Question time's over. Now it's time for you to obey. Lick my fingers clean, then get your head down between my legs. Satisfy me, and I'll remove the seal on your ring.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_NEXT_UNIMPRESSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Even without the influence of the ring, you'd definitely consider Evelyx's tight, brightly-coloured cunt to be alluring, but with the enchanted item's influence strong in your mind, you find yourself utterly enraptured by the sight of this succubus's pussy. Despite this, however, you're able to summon some resistance to its effects, and although you don't really mean it, you tell Evelyx that her cunt isn't all that impressive, and that you've seen plenty of prettier pussies than hers before.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(I knew I should have put a submission enchantment on that ring as well,)] she tuts under her breath as she hears your response. Seeing that you're still staring hungrily at her twat, despite your words, Evelyx starts to slide her fingers into her pussy, and after spending a moment fingering herself, she withdraws her slender digits and holds them up to show you that they're coated in a slick layer of slimy girlcum. Presenting her fingers to you, she smirks and states, [evelyx.speech(Resist this if you can. Come here and lick my fingers clean, then get your head down between my legs. Satisfy me, and I'll remove the seal on your ring.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_FINAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to tear your eyes away from her inviting pussy, you find yourself [pc.stepping] forwards to obey, before suddenly getting one last moment of clarity, allowing you to stop and say no if you really wanted to miss out on this...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_REFUSE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Despite every fibre of your being screaming for you to obey and get a taste of Evelyx's sweet pussy, you somehow manage to summon the strength to refuse Evelyx's offer, and so tell the succubus that you're not interested in performing cunnilingus on her. Rolling her eyes and letting out an annoyed tut, she huffs, [evelyx.speech(I really should have added that submission enchantment... Well, whatever, I'll just get one of the cows to get in here and finish me off. As for that ring, you can forget it if you think I'll take the sealing enchantment off after letting me down like this. If ever you do manage to remove it, then don't come back here trying to pawn it off to me; I'm not interested in that defective junk. Now take your damn breast pump and get out of my sight.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_FINAL_PUSSY_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Both unable and unwilling to disobey Evelyx's order, you [pc.step] around to her side of the desk, before dropping down onto the floor before her. Holding out her fingers, she smirks as you lean forwards and eagerly lick the slimy girlcum from them. Letting out a triumphant laugh, she spreads her legs and presents you with her wet cunt, and as she slides her now-saliva-coated fingers over her folds, she teases, [evelyx.speech(You want a taste of this, do you? Then beg for it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hungrily gazing at Evelyx's orange-lipped pussy, you do as you're told and desperately beg to be allowed to eat her out.
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_monica_ring_questions_failed))
			 Satisfied with your display of submission, the succubus reveals, [evelyx.speech(If you'd been more truthful with your answers to my questions, I would have considered loosening myself up a little for you, but as you decided to lie about how much you wanted to service my tight little pussy, you're going to have to work hard at getting your tongue into it. Now get started.)]
		#ELSE
			 Satisfied with your display of submission, the succubus makes an offer, [evelyx.speech(As you were truthful with your answers to my questions, I suppose I could loosen myself up a little for you if you'd like. Otherwise, you're going to have to work hard at getting your tongue into my tight little cunt. So, what'll it be? Want me to stay nice and tight for you, or should I loosen up a little?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_OBEY_ORAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_monica_ring_questions_failed))
			As you lean forwards to do as you're told and get started on eating Evelyx out, the impatient succubus grabs your head and roughly pulls you forwards between her legs. Before you know what's happening, her tight, wet cunt is grinding up against your [pc.lips+], and after planting a passionate kiss on her orange labia, you eagerly dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start to greedily lick Evelyx's soft folds.
		#ELSE
			Not wanting her to change anything, you tell Evelyx that her tight, wet pussy is perfect as it is, before leaning forwards to get started on eating her out. As you make your move, the impatient succubus grabs your head and roughly pulls you forwards between her legs, and before you know what's happening, her tight, wet cunt is grinding up against your [pc.lips+]. Delighted with the situation you find yourself in, you plant a series of passionate kisses on Evelyx's orange labia, before eagerly darting out your [pc.tongue+] and starting to greedily lick her soft folds.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it,)] the succubus moans as she grinds your face into her cunt. Letting out a high-pitched squeal in response to your enthusiastic licking, her posh accent is almost completely replaced by a lewd, passionate tone of voice as she moans, [evelyx.speech(~Ooh!~ Like that! Yes! ~Mmm!~ Don't you dare stop! I'll be squirting all over your face soon enough!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Desperately hungry to give her an orgasm and experience that, you bury your face between Evelyx's thighs and continue to greedily eat her out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_OBEY_ORAL_START_LOOSEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although her pussy is perfect as it is, you tell Evelyx that it might be easier for you to pleasure her if she were to loosen it up a little before getting started. Smirking down at you, the succubus lets out a little moan, and you gaze longingly at her wet pussy as you watch her use her demonic self-transformative powers to spread her labia and visibly loosen her cunt. As you start to compliment her on the appearance of her freshly-transformed pussy, the impatient succubus grabs your head and roughly pulls you forwards between her legs. Before you know what's happening, her slightly-loose, wet cunt is grinding up against your [pc.lips+], and after planting a passionate kiss on her orange labia, you eagerly dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start to greedily lick Evelyx's soft folds.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it,)] the succubus moans as she grinds your face into her cunt. Letting out a high-pitched squeal in response to your enthusiastic licking, her posh accent is almost completely replaced by a lewd, passionate tone of voice as she moans, [evelyx.speech(~Ooh!~ Like that! Yes! ~Mmm!~ Don't you dare stop! I'll be squirting all over your face soon enough!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Desperately hungry to give her an orgasm and experience that, you bury your face between Evelyx's thighs and continue to greedily eat her out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_OBEY_ORAL_START_GAPING_MESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to push your luck a little, you tell Evelyx that you'd like it if she were to go all the way and transform her tight, cute pussy into a gaping, sloppy mess for you to service. A look of amused surprise flashes across the succubus's face as she hears your audacious request, but instead of doing the expected and refusing you, she teases in her posh, condescending tone, [evelyx.speech(My, my, what a dirty, kinky little thing you are. Do you know what most people would give to be granted the opportunity to service a pussy as perfect as mine? And you'd rather I transform to give you the sort of cunt you'd find on some worn-out, worthless whore?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeling as though it's too late to back out now, and still wanting her to do as you ask, you respond to Evelyx's question in the affirmative. Letting out an amused laugh, she declares, [evelyx.speech(You're a bold one, to be asking this of me. Luckily for you, I do enjoy sometimes transforming myself in new and exciting ways... Fine, I'll do as you ask, but you'd better show me how grateful you are once you've got your head between my legs.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus starts to focus her demonic self-transformative powers into her pussy, and you watch in delighted awe as her tight, cute cunt starts to take on a new form. To begin with, the succubus's tiny labia start to spread apart, before rapidly increasing in size and turning into huge, meaty flaps. Her entire cunt then quickly darkens into a more desaturated, brownish shade of orange, and after reaching down to part her now-dangling labia, Evelyx presents you with her cunt's passage as it continues to loosen up into a gaping hole. With an excited squeal, she finishes things off by increasing the rate of her girlcum production, turning her now-gaping twat into a slimy, drooling pit. Going all the way in turning her cute pussy into the sort of ruined mess that you requested, the succubus makes one final change, and as she shuffles into a more comfortable, slouched down position in her chair, you're suddenly hit by a waft of strong, feminine musk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(Is this what you had in mind, you filthy little thing?)] Evelyx teases as she lets go of her meaty labia to let them hang loosely down to either side of her musky, sloppy hole. Nodding your head in approval, you can't help but lean forwards towards her inviting, ruined cunt. As you start to compliment her on the appearance of her freshly-transformed twat, the impatient succubus grabs your head and roughly pulls you forwards between her legs. Before you know what's happening, her drooling, musky pussy is grinding up against your [pc.lips+], and after planting a passionate kiss on her darkened, sagging labia, you eagerly dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start to greedily lick the inner sides of Evelyx's gaping hole.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(~Mmm!~ I've never tried it like this before,)] the succubus moans as she grinds your face into her ruined pussy. Letting out a high-pitched squeal in response to your enthusiastic licking, her posh accent is almost completely replaced by a lewd, passionate tone of voice as she moans, [evelyx.speech(~Ooh!~ That feels better than I expected! Yes! ~Mmm!~ Don't you dare stop! My sloppy, messy cunt's going to be squirting all over your face soon enough!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Desperately hungry to give her an orgasm and experience that, you bury your face between Evelyx's thighs as you continue to greedily lick and kiss her gaping, musky mess of a cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_RING_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After letting out one last deep, horny moan, Evelyx pushes you away from her, before returning to speak in her posh accent once more as she declares, [evelyx.speech(That was a good performance, but I've had enough for now. Show me your ring.)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you show Evelyx the ring she got you to wear, and after a wave of her hand, you feel the enchanted seal disappearing from it. Standing up and retrieving her lacy thong from where she kicked it to earlier, the succubus slides her underwear up her legs as she says, [evelyx.speech(You can do whatever you like with that ring. Thanks to your performance as a test subject, I've decided to make some modifications to the ones I was planning to have made for my slaves. Now take that breast pump and get out of my sight. We're done here.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_SEDUCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Recognising that Evelyx has a fetish for oral sex, you tell her that if she wants you to give her pussy some oral attention, all she has to do is ask. The succubus's eyes widen as she hears what it is you're saying, and after letting out a surprised laugh, she says, [evelyx.speech(You're a bold one, aren't you? Ordinarily, I'd punish such rudeness by having you thrown out of here, but today's your lucky day; my sex slave is away being trained and transformed this week, and so I've been missing out on my daily oral sessions. Seeing as you're so eager, you can stand in for them.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pushing her chair back so that you can look down over the top of her desk to see her groin, Evelyx pulls up her pencil skirt and slides her lacy orange thong all the way down her legs, before kicking it off to one side. Leaning back in her chair, she spreads her legs and presents herself to you, allowing you to see that both her cunt and asshole are the same orange hue as her eyes and horns. Teasing her light blue fingers down over her tiny, exotic-looking labia, she uses them to part her folds and show you how vice-tight her already-wet twat is.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(That worthless breast pump will be all yours,)] she states. Continuing to play with her pussy, she bites her lip and states, [evelyx.speech(All you need to do is eat me out. So what are you waiting for? Get over here and get started.)] 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_SEDUCE_ORAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		More than happy to do as you're told, you [pc.step] around to Evelyx's side of the desk, before dropping down before her and shuffling up between her legs. As you lean forwards to get started on eating Evelyx out, the impatient succubus grabs your head and roughly pulls you forwards into her groin. Before you know what's happening, her tight, wet cunt is grinding up against your [pc.lips+], and after planting a passionate kiss on her orange labia, you eagerly dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start to greedily lick Evelyx's soft folds.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it,)] the succubus moans as she grinds your face into her cunt. Letting out a high-pitched squeal in response to your enthusiastic licking, her posh accent is almost completely replaced by a lewd, passionate tone of voice as she moans, [evelyx.speech(~Ooh!~ Like that! Yes! ~Mmm!~ Don't you dare stop! I'll be squirting all over your face soon enough!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Desperately hungry to give her an orgasm and experience that, you bury your face between Evelyx's thighs and continue to greedily eat her out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_SEDUCE_VAGINAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not particularly keen on the idea of eating Evelyx out, you [pc.step] around to her side of the desk, but rather than kneeling down before her as she's demanded, you instead expose your cock to the horny succubus. Letting out a flustered tut as she sees that you're not obeying her, Evelyx snaps, [evelyx.speech(What do you think you're doing? Get down and eat me out already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Refusing to do as she says, you move your [pc.cock+] closer to Evelyx's face, before telling her that her pussy is too hot to simply be content with oral, and that what it really wants is to be fucked. Turned on and desperately horny from her lack of recent sex, the succubus rolls her eyes and lets out a long sigh of annoyance. After then glaring at you for a moment, she relents and sighs, [evelyx.speech(Fine... You can fuck me, but I want you to know that this is only because I haven't had any sex this week! You'd better make this damn good, and don't for a second think that this means you're the one in charge here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Standing up, the blue-skinned succubus takes a long stride forwards, before hiking her skirt up around her waist and bending face-first over her desk. Spreading her legs, she lifts her ass and presents you with her tight, wet cunt, before looking back over her shoulder and snapping, [evelyx.speech(Stick it in already! And remember, you're here for my pleasure, not yours!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to do as she asks, you
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 [pc.step] forwards and rear up on your hind legs, before dropping your front [pc.feet] down onto the desk and effectively mounting the horny succubus. Lining your cock up to her orange labia, you start bucking your hips and rubbing your [pc.cockHead+] up and down over her wet cunt.
		#ELSE
			 [pc.step] forwards between the succubus's legs, before lining your cock up to her orange labia and starting to rub your [pc.cockHead+] up and down over her wet cunt.
		#ENDIF
		 Letting out a deeply erotic, yet frustrated moan, Evelyx pushes back and allows her posh accent to be almost completely replaced by a lewd, passionate tone of voice as impatiently demands, [evelyx.speech(~Aah!~ Stop it! Just put it in already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Smirking at her impatience, you give the blue-skinned succubus what she wants, and after pushing the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+] into her tight, wet twat, you thrust forwards and sink your hard shaft into her hot pussy. After then pulling back, you thrust forwards once again, and with Evelyx beginning to let out a stream of erotic moans and squeals, you start to fuck her over her desk...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_SEDUCE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With her pussy reduced to a quivering, sloppy mess, Evelyx lets out a deep, satisfied sigh and pushes you back, before returning to speak in her posh accent once more as she declares, [evelyx.speech(That's just what I needed today... I've finished with you now, [pc.name], so take your worthless breast pump and get out of my sight. We're done here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you hurry to get your things back in order, the blue-skinned succubus stands up and retrieves her lacy thong from where she kicked it to earlier. After sliding her underwear up her legs, Evelyx glares at you in a decidedly unfriendly fashion, before snapping, [evelyx.speech(Hurry up and get out of here! I have important matters to attend to!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MONICA_QUEST_MEETING_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you turn to leave, Evelyx presses the button on the intercom that's sitting on her desk, before snapping, [evelyx.speech(Get in here, Dale.)]
	</p>
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_daily_fuck_unlocked))
		<p>
			The donkey-boy receptionist arrives running just as you get to the door, and after correctly assessing the situation, he asks you to accompany him back to the reception area. As the two of you begin to set off down the corridor, Evelyx calls out from her office behind you, [evelyx.speech(Oh, Dale?! If [pc.name] would like to come back and offer me the same experience again tomorrow, then show [pc.herHim] to my office!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(Yes, Ma'am!)] Dale calls out, before leading you back to the reception area. Moments later, you find yourself once again standing before the donkey-boy's desk, wondering what to do next...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			The donkey-boy receptionist arrives running just as you get to the door, and after correctly assessing the situation, he asks you to accompany him back to the reception area. Doing so, you soon find yourself once again standing before Dale's desk, wondering what to do next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Evelyx repeat sex meeting content: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_SEX_MEETING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Remembering Evelyx's offer to go and see her again in her office, you tell Dale that you'd like a special meeting with his succubus boss. Nodding in acknowledgement of your request, Dale reaches forwards and presses a button on the arcane intercom that's sitting on his desk. After emitting a short, loud buzzing noise, a posh, feminine voice speaks through it and impatiently snaps, [evelyx.speech(What is it this time, Dale?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion_meeting_happened) || flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_started))
			[dale.speech(I have your employee, [pc.name], here in reception again, Ma'am,)]
		#ELSE
			[dale.speech(I have that [pc.race], [pc.name], here in reception again, Ma'am,)]
		#ENDIF
		 Dale replies,[dale.speech([pc.SheIs] asking about having another meeting with you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(Oh, [pc.sheIs] back for more, is [pc.she]?)] Evelyx's voice asks over the intercom, and after letting out an amused hum, she says, [evelyx.speech(I'll allow [pc.herHim] to see me again, but make [pc.herHim] wait for fifteen minutes first.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the intercom clicks off, Dale motions towards the sofas on the other side of the reception and says, [dale.speech(If you'll first wait for fifteen minutes, I'll show you to Evelyx's office.)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding that it would be best to do as the donkey-boy suggests, you head on over to the sofas and sit down. Wondering what you're going to do with the succubus this time, you prepare to wait for fifteen minutes...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_SEX_MEETING_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After making you wait for almost twenty minutes, you hear the voice of Evelyx suddenly call out over Dale's intercom, [evelyx.speech(Show them through now, Dale. I don't have all day, so be quick about it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Yes, Ma'am!)] Dale replies, before urgently beckoning you forwards. Rising from the sofa, you follow the donkey-boy as he leads you through the doors behind his desk, down a corridor, and to a wooden door bearing the words 'Evelyx's Office'. After raising his fist to deliver a quick knock, Dale opens the door for you and announces your arrival by saying into the room beyond, [dale.speech([pc.Name] is here to see you, Ma'am.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] forwards into the spacious office, you look around to once again see that Evelyx's lair is extravagantly furnished. Mahogany shelves are filled with expensive-looking tomes and golden decorations, while large portraits of demons and landscape paintings hang from the walls. A rich, burgundy rug has been placed in the centre of the floor, and over on the far side, you see Evelyx herself sitting in a huge leather chair behind a masterfully-carved wooden desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(Hurry up and get over here. My cunt's not going to lick itself,)] Evelyx impatiently snaps. As you approach her desk, you take a good look at the owner of this farm. The flawless skin covering her body is a light shade of blue, and while her face has a youthful appearance, the cynical, penetrating gaze from her orange eyes suggests that she's far older than she looks. Her orange nail polish and lipstick matches not only the same shade as her eyes, but also the orange hue that tips the ends of her four small, swept-back horns. Her long, black hair is tied up into a ponytail by means of an orange scrunchie, and a pair of large, [evelyx.cupSize]-cup breasts swell out beneath the succubus's smart, black feminine suit. A gap at the base of her desk allows you to see that instead of humanoid feet, Evelyx has a pair of hard hoofs.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(evelyx))
		#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(evelyx))
			<p>
				Glancing down at your swollen belly, Evelyx realises that she's the one who got you pregnant, but with a wave of her hand she dismissively states, [evelyx.speech(Don't even think of sending any of those bastards you're carrying to me; I don't owe them anything.)] 
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Glancing down at your swollen belly, Evelyx sees that you're still pregnant with her children, but with a wave of her hand she dismissively repeats her previous statement, [evelyx.speech(Don't even think of sending any of those bastards you're carrying to me; I don't owe them anything.)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Pushing her chair back so that you can look down over the top of her desk to see her groin, Evelyx pulls up her pencil skirt and slides her lacy orange thong all the way down her legs, before kicking it off to one side. Leaning back in her chair, she spreads her legs and presents herself to you, allowing you to see that both her cunt and asshole are the same orange hue as her eyes and horns. Teasing her light blue fingers down over her tiny, exotic-looking labia, she uses them to part her folds and show you how vice-tight her already-wet twat is.
	</p>
	#IF(evelyx.isVisiblyPregnant() && evelyx.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(pc))
		#IF(!evelyx.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
			<p>
				From this angle, you're also able to see that Evelyx has a visibly pregnant belly. Seeing what it is you're looking at, she tuts in annoyance, [evelyx.speech(Yes, you got me pregnant. It's incredibly inconvenient, so don't ever do it again...)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				From this angle, you're also able to see that Evelyx still has a visibly pregnant belly. Seeing what it is you're looking at, she tuts in annoyance, [evelyx.speech(Yes, I'm still pregnant, thanks to you. It's incredibly inconvenient, so don't ever do it again...)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		As the blue-skinned succubus continues to play with her pussy, she flashes you a smirk and says, [evelyx.speech(You're a good [pc.girl], obediently coming back to service my cunt like this. Even though I had my sex slave transformed and trained to be a perfect little cunt-licker, that useless whore doesn't satisfy me like you did.
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_daily_fuck_gaped))
			 As a special reward for being so good, I'll transform my pussy into the sort of gaping mess that you like if you want me to. I know what a dirty, kinky little thing you are...
		#ELSE
			 As a special reward for being so good, I'll loosen up my pussy for you if you'd like. It can be a little too tight for some people...
		#ENDIF
		)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_SEX_MEETING_TF_NONE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting Evelyx to loosen her pussy, you tell her that she's perfect just the way she is. Smugly smirking as she hears this, the succubus spreads her legs a little wider and demands, [evelyx.speech(So what are you waiting for? Get down here and eat me out already!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_SEX_MEETING_TF_LOOSEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although her pussy is perfect as it is, you tell Evelyx that it might be easier for you to pleasure her if she were to loosen it up a little before getting started. Flashing you a smirk, the succubus lets out a little moan, and you gaze longingly at her wet pussy as you watch her use her demonic self-transformative powers to spread her labia and visibly loosen her cunt. As you start to compliment her on the appearance of her freshly-transformed pussy, the impatient succubus interrupts you by snapping, [evelyx.speech(Yes, yes, I know that my pussy is perfect. Just get down here and eat me out already!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_SEX_MEETING_TF_GAPING"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_daily_fuck_gaped))
		<p>
			Deciding to take Evelyx up on her offer, you tell her that you'd like it if she were to again go all the way and transform her tight, cute pussy into a gaping, sloppy mess for you to service. A look of amusement flashes across the succubus's face as she hears your audacious request, and she teases in her posh, condescending tone, [evelyx.speech(You really are such a dirty, kinky little thing, aren't you? Do you know what most people would give to be granted the opportunity to service a pussy as perfect as mine? And you'd rather I transform to give you the sort of cunt you'd find on some worn-out, worthless whore?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Knowing that she'll give you what you want, you eagerly respond to Evelyx's question in the affirmative. Letting out another amused laugh, she declares, [evelyx.speech(Luckily for you, I did very much enjoy it the last time we did this... I'll once again do as you ask, but you'd better show me how grateful you are once you've got your head between my legs.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Deciding to push your luck a little, you tell Evelyx that you'd like it if she were to go all the way and transform her tight, cute pussy into a gaping, sloppy mess for you to service. A look of amused surprise flashes across the succubus's face as she hears your audacious request, but instead of doing the expected and refusing you, she teases in her posh, condescending tone, [evelyx.speech(My, my, what a dirty, kinky little thing you are. Do you know what most people would give to be granted the opportunity to service a pussy as perfect as mine? And you'd rather I transform to give you the sort of cunt you'd find on some worn-out, worthless whore?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Feeling as though it's too late to back out now, and still wanting her to do as you ask, you respond to Evelyx's question in the affirmative. Letting out an amused laugh, she declares, [evelyx.speech(You're a bold one, to be asking this of me. Luckily for you, I do enjoy sometimes transforming myself in new and exciting ways... Fine, I'll do as you ask, but you'd better show me how grateful you are once you've got your head between my legs.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		With that, the succubus starts to focus her demonic self-transformative powers into her pussy, and you watch in delighted awe as her tight, cute cunt starts to take on a new form. To begin with, the succubus's tiny labia start to spread apart, before rapidly increasing in size and turning into huge, meaty flaps. Her entire cunt then quickly darkens into a more desaturated, brownish shade of orange, and after reaching down to part her now-dangling labia, Evelyx presents you with her cunt's passage as it continues to loosen up into a gaping hole. With an excited squeal, she finishes things off by increasing the rate of her girlcum production, turning her now-gaping twat into a slimy, drooling pit. Going all the way in turning her cute pussy into the sort of ruined mess that you requested, the succubus makes one final change, and as she shuffles into a more comfortable, slouched down position in her chair, you're suddenly hit by a waft of strong, feminine musk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(You really like me like this, you filthy little thing?)] Evelyx asks in amusement. As you respond in the positive, she laughs and spreads her legs, and with her slender fingers still pulling her dangling labia back to show off her ruined cunt, she demands, [evelyx.speech(Get down here and show me how much you love it then. I want your tongue deep in my sloppy, gaping pussy.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_SEX_MEETING_ORAL_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF(evelyx.getVaginaCapacity()==CAPACITY_SEVEN_GAPING)
		<p>
			More than happy to do as she asks, you quickly move forwards and drop down in front of Evelyx, who lets go of her meaty labia to let them hang loosely down to either side of her musky, sloppy hole. Licking your lips in anticipation of what's to come, you eagerly lean forwards towards her inviting, ruined cunt. As you start to compliment her on the appearance of her freshly-transformed twat, the impatient succubus grabs your head and roughly pulls you forwards between her legs. Before you know what's happening, her drooling, musky pussy is grinding up against your [pc.lips+], and after planting a passionate kiss on her darkened, sagging labia, you eagerly dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start to greedily lick the inner sides of Evelyx's gaping hole.
		</p>
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(~Mmm!~ It feels so different, being eaten out like this,)] the succubus moans as she grinds your face into her ruined pussy. Letting out a high-pitched squeal in response to your enthusiastic licking, she pants, [evelyx.speech(~Ooh!~ It's so good! Yes! ~Mmm!~ Don't you dare stop! My sloppy, messy cunt's going to be squirting all over your face soon enough!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Desperately hungry to give her an orgasm and experience that, you bury your face between Evelyx's thighs as you continue to greedily lick and kiss her gaping, musky mess of a cunt...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			More than happy to do as she asks, you quickly move forwards and drop down in front of Evelyx. Although you quickly lean forwards to get started, you're not fast enough for the impatient succubus, who grabs your head and roughly pulls you forwards between her legs. Before you know what's happening, her [evelyx.pussyCapacity], wet cunt is grinding up against your [pc.lips+], and after planting a passionate kiss on her orange labia, you eagerly dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start to greedily lick Evelyx's soft folds.
		</p>
		<p>
			[evelyx.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it,)] the succubus moans as she grinds your face into her cunt. Letting out a high-pitched squeal in response to your enthusiastic licking, she pants, [evelyx.speech(~Ooh!~ Like that! Yes! ~Mmm!~ Don't you dare stop! I'll be squirting all over your face soon enough!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Desperately hungry to give her an orgasm and experience that, you bury your face between Evelyx's thighs and continue to greedily eat her out...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_SEX_MEETING_VAGINAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not particularly keen on the idea of eating Evelyx out, you [pc.step] around to her side of the desk, but rather than kneeling down before her as she's demanded, you instead expose your cock to the horny succubus. Letting out a flustered tut as she sees that you're not obeying her, Evelyx snaps, [evelyx.speech(What do you think you're doing? Get down and eat me out already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Refusing to do as she says, you move your [pc.cock+] closer to Evelyx's face, before telling her that her pussy is too hot to simply be content with oral, and that what it really wants is to be fucked. Although the succubus rolls her eyes and lets out a long sigh of annoyance, she's too turned on to continue trying to get her own way, and so after glaring at you for a moment, she relents and sighs, [evelyx.speech(Fine... You can fuck me, but I want you to know that this is only because my sex slave is such a useless whore, and she hasn't given me any real satisfaction lately! You'd better make this damn good, and don't for a second think that this means you're the one in charge here!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Standing up, the blue-skinned succubus takes a long stride forwards, before hiking her skirt up around her waist and bending face-first over her desk. Spreading her legs, she lifts her ass and presents you with her
		#IF(evelyx.getVaginaCapacity()==CAPACITY_SEVEN_GAPING)
			 sloppy, gaping mess of a cunt,
		#ELSE
			 [evelyx.pussyCapacity], wet cunt,
		#ENDIF
		 before looking back over her shoulder and snapping, [evelyx.speech(Stick it in already! And remember, you're here for my pleasure, not yours!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		More than happy to do as she asks, you
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 [pc.step] forwards and rear up on your hind legs, before dropping your front [pc.feet] down onto the desk and effectively mounting the horny succubus.
			#IF(evelyx.getVaginaCapacity()==CAPACITY_SEVEN_GAPING)
				 Lining your cock up to her darkened, dangling labia, you start bucking your hips and rubbing your [pc.cockHead+] up and down over her ruined, musky hole.
			#ELSE
				 Lining your cock up to her orange labia, you start bucking your hips and rubbing your [pc.cockHead+] up and down over her wet cunt.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 [pc.step] forwards between the succubus's legs, before lining your cock up to her
			#IF(evelyx.getVaginaCapacity()==CAPACITY_SEVEN_GAPING)
				 darkened, dangling labia and starting to rub your [pc.cockHead+] up and down over her ruined, musky hole.
			#ELSE
				 orange labia and starting to rub your [pc.cockHead+] up and down over her wet cunt.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		 Letting out a deeply erotic, yet frustrated moan, Evelyx pushes back and angrily demands, [evelyx.speech(~Aah!~ Stop it! Just fucking put it in already!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(evelyx.getVaginaCapacity()==CAPACITY_SEVEN_GAPING)
			Smirking at her impatience, you give the blue-skinned succubus what she wants, and after easily sliding the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+] past her dangling labia into her slimy, musky hole, you thrust forwards and push your hard shaft deep into her ruined pussy. After then pulling back, you thrust forwards once again, and with Evelyx beginning to let out a stream of erotic moans and squeals, you start to fuck her over her desk...
		#ELSE
			Smirking at her impatience, you give the blue-skinned succubus what she wants, and after pushing the [pc.cockHead+] of your [pc.cock+] into her tight, wet twat, you thrust forwards and sink your hard shaft into her hot pussy. After then pulling back, you thrust forwards once again, and with Evelyx beginning to let out a stream of erotic moans and squeals, you start to fuck her over her desk...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_SEX_MEETING_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With her pussy reduced to a quivering, sloppy mess, Evelyx lets out a deep, satisfied sigh and pushes you back, declaring, [evelyx.speech(Fuck, that's just what I needed today... I've finished with you now, [pc.name], so get out of my sight. We're done here.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you hurry to get your things back in order, the blue-skinned succubus stands up and retrieves her lacy thong from where she kicked it to earlier. After sliding her underwear up her legs, Evelyx glares at you in a decidedly unfriendly fashion, before snapping, [evelyx.speech(Hurry up and get out of here! I have important matters to attend to!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_SEX_MEETING_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you turn to leave, Evelyx presses the button on the intercom that's sitting on her desk, before snapping, [evelyx.speech(Get in here, Dale.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The donkey-boy receptionist arrives running just as you get to the door, and after correctly assessing the situation, he asks you to accompany him back to the reception area. As the two of you begin to set off down the corridor, Evelyx calls out from her office behind you, [evelyx.speech(Oh, Dale?! If [pc.name] would like to come back and offer me the same experience again tomorrow, then show [pc.herHim] to my office!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Yes, Ma'am!)] Dale calls out, before leading you back to the reception area. Moments later, you find yourself once again standing before the donkey-boy's desk, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Dormitory: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		At one end of the farm's long corridor, a sign reading 'Dormitories' is fixed to the wall above two large doors, each of which has a round glass window fixed into it at head height. The door on the left bears a sign reading 'Non-cow Employees Only', and after taking a brief glance through its window, you see that the room beyond is very small and cramped, and there are only a handful of shabby-looking bunk beds in there.
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(dale))
			 As you scan over the room's interior, you see the unmistakable form of Dale sleeping on the bottom bunk of one of these beds.
			#IF(dale.getTotalTimesHadSex(pc)>0)
				#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_dorm_sex))
					 Although you feel yourself getting aroused at the thought of fucking him in his bed again, you've already worn him out enough for one night, and so decide to leave him to get some much needed sleep.
				#ELSE
					 You feel yourself getting aroused at the thought of sneaking into his dorm and fucking the donkey-boy in his bed, and if you were feeling daring, you could always make this fantasy a reality.
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 As you scan over the room's interior, you see that at this time of day there's nobody in there.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		The other door at the end of the corridor is signed as being for 'Cows Only', and as you're one of them, you decide to push open the door and head inside. Unlike the other dorm, this one is large and spacious, and while the dozens of beds in here aren't of the best quality, they're leagues better than the ones in the other dorm. Looking around, you see that about a quarter of the beds are occupied by resting milkers, and then another quarter are stripped and in the process of having their sheets washed, leaving around half of the beds available for you to use.
	</p>
	<p>
		Over on the far side of the dorm, there's an adjoining wetroom which houses arcane washing machines, as well as shower and toilet facilities. The only other interesting features of this place are a row of sturdy metal lockers which are lined up along one wall, and an arcane-powered vending machine which sits at the end of them. This vending machine appears to offer a limited selection of transformative potions, and as you take a closer look, you see a sign has been fixed to the wall beside it, reading:
	</p>
	<div class='container-full-width' style='text-align:center; width:75%; margin:8px 12.5%;'>
		<b>Dormitory Rules</b>
		<br/>- Cows must strip and wash their bedding after using a bed.
		<br/>- [style.colourMinorGood(Good cows)] should be naked at all times, so please strip and leave your clothing in your locker.
		<br/>- [style.colourGood(Very good cows)] will spend their money at the vending machine.
		<br/>- Cows are [style.colourBad(strictly forbidden)] from engaging in sexual activities with one another.
	</div>
	<p>
		If you were planning on working today, then it might be a good idea to make use of the secure lockers and safely leave your clothing in this area. You could also choose to buy one of the potions from the vending machine, or use the shower and toilet facilities if you so wanted to...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_REST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling tired and in need of a rest, you find a free bed and sink down onto it, before setting your phone's alarm and pulling the covers over yourself. Although there's a steady background noise of milkers' hoofs and shoes clopping across the floor, as well as some snoring off on one side of the dorm, you find yourself easily drifting off to sleep...
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>Beep-beep... beep-beep... bee-</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Rolling over, you fumble for your phone and quickly turn off the alarm before sinking back onto the bed with a sigh. A nearby milker looks quizzically at the electronic device in your hand for a moment, before shrugging her shoulders and continuing on her way to the showers. With one last yawn, you get out of bed and quickly strip the sheets, before dumping the covers into one of the wetroom's arcane washing machines. Wondering who's responsible for making the beds after the sheets have been cleaned, you [pc.step] back into the dormitory and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		[style.italicsGood(You feel completely refreshed!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_SHOWER_QUICK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling dirty and in need of a quick clean, you head into the dorm's adjoining wetroom and [pc.step] past the arcane washing machines to enter the large, communal showers. A dozen shower-heads are fixed high up on both sides of the tiled walls, and several of them are already in use by cows who've had the same idea as you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that there's a rule forbidding cows from engaging in sexual activities with one another, you try to avoid getting any lewd thoughts as you choose a free space and turn on the tap. As the hot water starts to flow over your body, you realise that these other cows are also thinking about the rules, for even over the sound of flowing water you hear them let out the occasional frustrated moan as they stop themselves from making a move on one another.
	</p>
	<p>
		Thinking that it would be best for everyone if you were to hurry things along, you get down to business and quickly wash your body. As you lather the soap over your [pc.breasts+] and down to your [pc.hips+], you see that the cow using the shower opposite to yours is staring at you with a desperate, hungry look in her eyes. Looking down, you see that her hand is frantically working away between her legs, and you can't help but gulp as you realise that she's fingering herself to the sight of your body.
	</p>
	<p>
		With things starting to heat up in the showers, and not wanting anything to lead to the loss of your job, you finish washing your body as quickly as you can. Ignoring the deep, erotic moan of the other cow's orgasm, you finish up and turn off the taps, before hurrying out of the showers, drying yourself off, and returning to the main area of the dormitory...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_SHOWER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling extremely dirty and in need of a thorough clean, you head into the dorm's adjoining wetroom and [pc.step] past the arcane washing machines to enter the large, communal showers. A dozen shower-heads are fixed high up on both sides of the tiled walls, and several of them are already in use by cows who've had the same idea as you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing that there's a rule forbidding cows from engaging in sexual activities with one another, you try to avoid getting any lewd thoughts as you choose a free space and turn on the tap. As the hot water starts to flow over your body, you realise that these other cows are also thinking about the rules, for even over the sound of flowing water you hear them let out the occasional frustrated moan as they stop themselves from making a move on one another.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not letting the erotic atmosphere ruin your plans, you proceed to get down to business and set about thoroughly washing your body. As you lather the soap over your [pc.breasts+] and down to your [pc.hips+], you see that the cow using the shower opposite to yours is staring at you with a desperate, hungry look in her eyes. Looking down, you see that her hand is frantically working away between her legs, and you can't help but gulp as you realise that she's fingering herself to the sight of your body.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although things are starting to heat up in the showers, you refuse to rush and continue to methodically wash every last part of your body. Ignoring the deep, erotic moan of the other cow's orgasm, you rinse yourself off and then, much to the cow's delight, you repeat the entire washing process. By the time you finally turn off the taps, the other cow has orgasmed to the sight of you no less than three times. After flashing a pointed glance her way, you [pc.step] out of the showers, dry yourself off, and return to the main area of the dormitory...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Vending machine: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_VENDING_MACHINE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to take a closer look at the dorm's vending machine, you wait a moment for another cow to finish using it, before [pc.stepping] up to it and seeing what's on offer. Beneath a large picture of a beautiful cow-girl exposing her gigantic breasts and telling you via speech-bubble to buy everything to look more like her, the products which are on sale are listed beside their price:
	</p>
	
	<div class='container-full-width'>
		<div class='container-full-width inner' style='margin-bottom:4px;'>
			[style.boldTfGeneric(Water)] [style.moneyFormat(20, b)] | [style.boldTfGeneric(Bubble Milk)] [style.moneyFormat(30, b)] | [style.boldTfGeneric(Bread Roll)] [style.moneyFormat(30, b)] | [style.boldTfGeneric(Bubble Cream)] [style.moneyFormat(40, b)] | [style.boldTfGeneric(Berry Trifle)] [style.moneyFormat(60, b)]
			<br/>If you're a hungry or thirsty cow, then you can buy your food or drink right here!
		</div>
		<div class='container-full-width inner' style='margin-bottom:4px;'>
			[style.boldCow(Pretty Cow Potion)] [style.moneyFormat(1200, b)]
			<br/>You don't want to be called ugly behind your back, do you? Buy this and be prettier than 'her'!
		</div>
		<div class='container-full-width inner' style='margin-bottom:4px;'>
			[style.boldCow(Busty Cow Potion)] [style.moneyFormat(1400, b)]
			<br/>Cows with larger breasts are more attractive! It's scientifically&#8482; proven!
		</div>
		<div class='container-full-width inner' style='margin-bottom:4px;'>
			[style.boldCow(Milky Cow Potion)] [style.moneyFormat(1600, b)]
			<br/>The more milk you produce, the quicker you'll earn a promotion!
		</div>
		<div class='container-full-width inner' style='margin-bottom:4px;'>
			[style.boldCow(Wet Cow Potion)] [style.moneyFormat(1800, b)]
			<br/>A drooling cunt is just what you need to give our clients a good time!
		</div>
		<div class='container-full-width inner' style='margin-bottom:4px;'>
			[style.boldCow(Happy Cow Potion)] [style.moneyFormat(2000, b)]
			<br/>It's, like, so annoying to be thinking so much, right?
		</div>
	</div>
	<p>
		Reading over the options again, you can't help but think to yourself that everything is extremely expensive, and likely not worth the cost. Then again, as the slogan painted beneath these options says, 'Good cows support Evelyx's Dairy by making as many purchases as they can every day!'. Despite how blunt and uninspired this marketing gimmick is, you do find yourself thinking you'd like to be a good, pretty cow...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_VENDING_MACHINE_PURCHASE_DRINK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling thirsty, you insert [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames into the vending machine and press the option corresponding to [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]. A whirring sound comes from within the arcane-powered contraption, and then moments later a plastic bottle falls down into the tray at the base.
	</p>
	<p>
		You retrieve this drink and wonder whether to buy anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_VENDING_MACHINE_PURCHASE_FOOD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling hungry, you insert [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames into the vending machine and press the option corresponding to [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]. A whirring sound comes from within the arcane-powered contraption, and then moments later your selected item of food falls down into the tray at the base.
	</p>
	<p>
		You retrieve your purchase and wonder whether to buy anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_VENDING_MACHINE_PURCHASE_POTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You insert [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames into the vending machine and press the option marked as '[#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]'. A whirring sound comes from within the arcane-powered contraption, and then moments later a glass bottle chinks down into the tray at the base.
	</p>
	<p>
		You retrieve this potion and wonder whether to buy anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_VENDING_MACHINE_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough of the vending machine, you [pc.step] away, allowing another cow who was waiting behind you to move forwards and start inserting coins into it. Giving her some space, you slowly [pc.walk] across the large, spacious dormitory and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Dale: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_DALE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling horny and wanting Dale to help you get some relief, you head back out into the corridor, and after carefully checking to make sure that nobody's watching, you ignore the 'Non-cow Employees Only' sign on the door and quickly slip into the other dormitory. Once inside, you look around to make sure that Dale is the only person in here, and after making sure that the two of you are alone, you stealthily approach the bunk bed in which the donkey-boy is sleeping.
	</p>
	<p>
		Whether thanks to your stealth or the fact that he's a heavy sleeper, Dale doesn't wake from his slumber as you [pc.step] over to his bed. Looking down on his sleeping face, you can't help but excitedly bite your lip in anticipation of what you're about to do. Allowing your gaze to wander down, you see that the donkey-boy's sheets are half-pulled back, allowing you to watch his muscular pecs rise and fall in time with his deep, slow breaths.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down between his legs, you see Dale's huge, sheathed cock bulging out from beneath the thin sheets. The sight of this, combined with the heady, masculine scent that's emanating from the sleeping donkey-boy, drives you wild with lust, and you can't help but let out a quiet, horny [pc.moan] as you wonder how you're going to fuck him...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_DALE_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In a sudden moment of clarity which cuts through your lustful desires, you realise that Dale doesn't get much sleep, and that waking him in this manner might not be the healthiest thing for him. Taking one last look at his sleeping figure, you sneak back out of the sleeping quarters, before heading back to the cows' dormitory and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_DALE_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to give him a nice surprise, you stealthily slip in under the sheets and nuzzle up against Dale. Although he rolls over to press his hot, furry body against yours, the donkey-boy remains deeply asleep, and while you enjoy the feeling of having him snuggle up against you, you're here for something a little more than that. Knowing how to wake him up, you tease your [pc.hand] down over his muscular, furry stomach, before stroking your [pc.fingers+] over his cock's thick, hot sheath. Just as you'd hoped, his dark, animalistic donkey-cock starts to push out and rise to attention, and as you wrap your [pc.hand] around his thick shaft, Dale lets out a deep grunt and slowly begins to wake up.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(dale))
		<p>
			#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(dale))
				[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he suddenly realises what's going on, but after this initial shock of finding you in his bed, Dale immediately notices your swollen belly pressing against him and realises that he's the father. Tentatively reaching out to gently rub his strong hands over your distended stomach, he marvels, [dale.speech(I got you pregnant? Wow... Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help! I'll try to make time for you if you need it. That's why you're here at this hour, right?)]
			#ELSE
				[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he suddenly realises what's going on, but after this initial shock of finding you in his bed, Dale immediately notices that you're still pregnant with his children. Tentatively reaching out to gently rub his strong hands over your distended stomach, he repeats his previous offer, [dale.speech(Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help. I'll try to make time for you if you need it. That's why you're here at this hour, right?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Thanking Dale for his kind offer, you tell him that you're not here to ask for his support. Giving his cock a playful stroke, you put on your most seductive voice and tell the donkey-boy that you're here for a fuck. This quickly snaps Dale out of his sleepy state, and after thrusting his hot, throbbing cock up against your [pc.hand], he playfully grunts, [dale.speech(You're here for more of my cock? Lucky you; my cock's wanting more of you too.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at Dale's words, you plant a quick kiss on his lips and wonder how he's going to want to take you...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he suddenly realises what's going on. Placing one of your [pc.fingers+] over his lips, you use your other [pc.hand] to give his cock a playful stroke as you put on your most seductive voice and tell the donkey-boy that you're here for a fuck. This quickly finishes snapping Dale out of his sleepy state, and after thrusting his hot, throbbing cock up against your [pc.hand], he playfully grunts, [dale.speech(You're here for more of my cock? Lucky you; my cock's wanting more of you too.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at Dale's words, you plant a quick kiss on his lips and wonder how he's going to want to take you...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_DALE_SEX_START_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isFaceVirgin())
			Although you've never given anyone head before, you find yourself craving the taste of Dale's thick donkey-cock.
		#ELSE
			With Dale's masculine scent heavy in the air around him, you find yourself craving the taste of his thick donkey-cock.
		#ENDIF
		 Dropping down at the end of his bed, you lift the sheets and slip in under the covers, letting out an excited [pc.moan] as you work your way up between the donkey-boy's legs. Despite the fact that you have to pull his boxers down to gain access to his groin, Dale remains deeply asleep, allowing you to tease your [pc.fingers+] over his cock's thick, hot sheath. Just as you'd hoped, his dark, animalistic donkey-dick starts to push out and rise to attention, and as you deliver a slow, wet lick to his thick shaft, Dale lets out a deep grunt and slowly begins to wake up.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(dale))
		<p>
			#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(dale))
				[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he lifts the covers to see you planting a loving kiss on his [dale.ballSize] balls. After this initial shock of finding you in his bed, Dale immediately notices your swollen belly and realises that he's the father. Gazing down at your distended stomach, he marvels, [dale.speech(I got you pregnant? Wow... Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help! I'll try to make time for you if you need it. That's why you're here at this hour, right?)]
			#ELSE
				[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he lifts the covers to see you planting a loving kiss on his [dale.ballSize] balls. After this initial shock of finding you in his bed, Dale immediately notices that you're still pregnant with his children. Gazing down at your distended stomach, he repeats his previous offer, [dale.speech(Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help. I'll try to make time for you if you need it. That's why you're here at this hour, right?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			After thanking Dale for his kind offer, you tell him that you're not here to ask for his support, and after lewdly sucking on the tip of his cock for a moment, you tease him by asking what it looks like you're here for. After the donkey-boy has let out a good-natured laugh in response to your teasing, you
			#IF(pc.isFaceVirgin())
				 playfully bite your lip and tell him that you've never sucked cock before, and that you were hoping he could be your first.
			#ELSE
				 playfully bite your lip and tell him that you wanted to do something nice for him, and so you're going to give him a blowjob.
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out a deep, aroused grunt as he hears this, Dale uses one of his hands to take hold of his throbbing shaft and point it towards your mouth, saying, [dale.speech(Go on then, you can take things at your own pace. I'll be here all night, after all...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he lifts the covers to see you planting a loving kiss on his [dale.ballSize] balls. Using your [pc.hand] to give his cock a playful stroke, you deliver another loving kiss to the musky underside of his hot donkey-cock, before putting on your most seductive voice and telling the donkey-boy
			#IF(pc.isFaceVirgin())
				 that you've never sucked cock before, and that you were hoping he could be your first.
			#ELSE
				 that you wanted to do something nice for him, and so you're going to give him a blowjob.
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out a deep, aroused grunt as he hears this, Dale uses one of his hands to take hold of his throbbing shaft and point it towards your mouth, saying, [dale.speech(Go on then, you can take things at your own pace. I'll be here all night, after all...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isFaceVirgin())
			This being your first time sucking someone's cock, you decide to take your time and really enjoy this experience. Moving your mouth down to Dale's [dale.ballSize] balls, you plant a series of kisses on them, letting out a satisfied, muffled moan in the process as you enjoy their musky, masculine taste. Moving up, you then dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start licking his thick, hot shaft, continuing to moan and pant as you do so. Finally working your way up to kiss the flat, flared head of Dale's equine cock, you lick up the salty precum that's oozing from his urethra, before experimentally wrapping your [pc.lips+] around his shaft and taking it into your mouth.
		#ELSE
			Wanting to make sure that he enjoys this just as much as you will, you decide to take your time and give the donkey-boy's genitals your full, loving attention. Moving your mouth down to his [dale.ballSize], dark balls, you plant a series of kisses on them, letting out a satisfied, muffled moan in the process as you enjoy their musky, masculine taste. Moving up, you then dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start licking his thick, hot shaft, continuing to moan and pant as you do so. Finally working your way up to kiss the flat, flared head of Dale's equine cock, you lick up the salty precum that's oozing from his urethra, before wrapping your [pc.lips+] around his shaft and taking it into your mouth.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(That's it... Don't stop...)] Dale groans under his breath, before placing one of his hands on the back of your head and encouraging you to keep going by applying a gentle downward pressure. Happy to see from his reaction that he's enjoying this, you give the donkey-boy what he wants and drop your head down, taking his thick, hot donkey-cock first into your mouth, and then down your throat. Delighting in his musky, masculine scent and taste, you start eagerly bobbing your head up and down, causing a mixture of precum and saliva to drool from the corners of your mouth as you give him a blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_DALE_SEX_START_PUSSY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isVaginaVirgin())
			Although you're still a virgin, you find yourself desperate to feel Dale's thick donkey-cock thrusting deep into your unspoiled cunt.
		#ELSE
			Gazing lustfully down at the bulge between Dale's legs, you find yourself desperate to feel his thick donkey-cock thrusting deep into your horny cunt.
		#ENDIF
		 Taking hold of the edge of his sheets, you slowly pull them down, letting out an excited [pc.moan] as you fully reveal the donkey-boy's furry, muscular body. Despite the fact that you have to pull his boxers down to gain access to his groin, Dale remains deeply asleep, allowing you to tease your [pc.fingers+] over his cock's thick, hot sheath. Just as you'd hoped, his dark, animalistic donkey-dick starts to push out and rise to attention, and as you climb up onto his bed to straddle him, Dale lets out a deep grunt and slowly begins to wake up.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(dale))
		<p>
			#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(dale))
				[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he suddenly realises what's going on, but after this initial shock of waking to you climbing on top of him, Dale immediately notices your swollen belly and realises that he's the father. Tentatively reaching out to gently rub his strong hands over your distended stomach, he marvels, [dale.speech(I got you pregnant? Wow... Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help! I'll try to make time for you if you need it. That's why you're here at this hour, right?)]
			#ELSE
				[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he suddenly realises what's going on, but after this initial shock of waking to you climbing on top of him, Dale immediately notices that you're still pregnant with his children. Tentatively reaching out to gently rub his strong hands over your distended stomach, he repeats his previous offer, [dale.speech(Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help. I'll try to make time for you if you need it. That's why you're here at this hour, right?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			After thanking Dale for his kind offer, you tell him that you're not here to ask for his support, and after dropping your [pc.hips+] down to lewdly slide your [pc.pussy+] up and down over his cock, you tease him by asking what it looks like you're here for. After the donkey-boy has let out a good-natured laugh in response to your teasing, you
			#IF(pc.isVaginaVirgin())
				 playfully bite your lip and tell him that you're still a virgin, and that you were hoping he could be your first.
			#ELSE
				 playfully bite your lip and tell him that you wanted to do something nice for him, and so you're going to ride his cock.
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out a deep, aroused grunt as he hears this, Dale uses one of his hands to take hold of his throbbing shaft and rub it up against your [pc.pussy+], saying, [dale.speech(Go on then, you can ride me and take things at your own pace. I'll be here all night, after all...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he wakes to the sight of you climbing on top of him. Placing one of your [pc.fingers+] over his lips, you drop your [pc.hips+] down to lewdly slide your [pc.pussy+] up and down over his cock as you put on your most seductive voice and tell the donkey-boy that
			#IF(pc.isVaginaVirgin())
				  you're still a virgin, and that you were hoping he could be your first.
			#ELSE
				 you wanted to do something nice for him, and so you're going to ride his cock.
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out a deep, aroused grunt as he hears this, Dale uses one of his hands to take hold of his throbbing shaft and rub it up against your [pc.pussy+], saying, [dale.speech(Go on then, you can ride me and take things at your own pace. I'll be here all night, after all...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(pc.isVaginaVirgin())
		<p>
			Not wanting to rush this, you continue to slide your [pc.pussy+] up and down the length of Dale's thick, hot donkey-cock, imagining what it's going to feel like once it's inside of you. Your soft moans of anticipation are soon changing into excited squeals as you lift your [pc.hips+] and experimentally press your virgin cunt down against the flat, flared head of Dale's animalistic dick. His musky, slippery precum soon coats your [pc.labia+], and as you continue to somewhat-awkwardly press your pussy down against the throbbing head of his dark shaft, the donkey-boy reassures you by softly grunting, [dale.speech(That's it... You're doing fine... ~Mmm!~ Just take it slow and lower yourself down...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Following Dale's instructions, you let out a deeply erotic [pc.moan] as you slowly lower yourself down and force his hot, throbbing donkey-cock into your virgin pussy...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Smirking at Dale's words, you continue to slide your [pc.pussy+] up and down the length of his thick, hot donkey-cock for a moment, before lifting your [pc.hips+] and pressing your horny cunt down against the flat, flared head of his animalistic dick. His musky, slippery precum soon coats your [pc.labia+], and as you continue to tease your pussy down against the throbbing head of his dark shaft, Dale softly grunts, [dale.speech(That's it... ~Mmm!~ Now lower yourself down and take it...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eager to follow Dale's instructions, you let out a deeply erotic [pc.moan] as you lower yourself down and force his hot, throbbing donkey-cock into your pussy. Your [pc.labia+] lewdly spread around his thick, dark shaft as you drop down, and after letting out yet another [pc.moan+], you start to eagerly ride his cock...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_DALE_SEX_START_ANAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isAssVirgin())
			Although you're still an anal virgin, you find yourself desperate to feel Dale's thick donkey-cock thrusting deep into your unspoiled asshole.
		#ELSE
			Gazing lustfully down at the bulge between Dale's legs, you find yourself desperate to feel his thick donkey-cock thrusting deep into your horny asshole.
		#ENDIF
		 Taking hold of the edge of his sheets, you slowly pull them down, letting out an excited [pc.moan] as you fully reveal the donkey-boy's furry, muscular body. Despite the fact that you have to pull his boxers down to gain access to his groin, Dale remains deeply asleep, allowing you to tease your [pc.fingers+] over his cock's thick, hot sheath. Just as you'd hoped, his dark, animalistic donkey-dick starts to push out and rise to attention, and as you climb up onto his bed to straddle him, Dale lets out a deep grunt and slowly begins to wake up.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(dale))
		<p>
			#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(dale))
				[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he suddenly realises what's going on, but after this initial shock of waking to you climbing on top of him, Dale immediately notices your swollen belly and realises that he's the father. Tentatively reaching out to gently rub his strong hands over your distended stomach, he marvels, [dale.speech(I got you pregnant? Wow... Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help! I'll try to make time for you if you need it. That's why you're here at this hour, right?)]
			#ELSE
				[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he suddenly realises what's going on, but after this initial shock of waking to you climbing on top of him, Dale immediately notices that you're still pregnant with his children. Tentatively reaching out to gently rub his strong hands over your distended stomach, he repeats his previous offer, [dale.speech(Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help. I'll try to make time for you if you need it. That's why you're here at this hour, right?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			After thanking Dale for his kind offer, you tell him that you're not here to ask for his support, and after dropping your [pc.hips+] down to lewdly slide your [pc.asshole+] up and down over his cock, you tease him by asking what it looks like you're here for. After the donkey-boy has let out a good-natured laugh in response to your teasing, you
			#IF(pc.isAssVirgin())
				 playfully bite your lip and tell him that you're still an anal virgin, and that you were hoping he could be your first.
			#ELSE
				 playfully bite your lip and tell him that you wanted to do something nice for him, and so you're going to anally ride his cock.
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out a deep, aroused grunt as he hears this, Dale uses one of his hands to take hold of his throbbing shaft and rub it up against your [pc.asshole+], saying, [dale.speech(I'm not really into anal stuff, but seeing as it's with you, I can go along with it. Just take things at your own pace. I'll be here all night, after all...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[dale.speech(~Mmm!~ That's it, [pc.name]... Wait, [pc.name]?!)] he exclaims as he wakes to the sight of you climbing on top of him. Placing one of your [pc.fingers+] over his lips, you drop your [pc.hips+] down to lewdly slide your [pc.asshole+] up and down over his cock as you put on your most seductive voice and tell the donkey-boy that
			#IF(pc.isAssVirgin())
				  you're still an anal virgin, and that you were hoping he could be your first.
			#ELSE
				 you wanted to do something nice for him, and so you're going to anally ride his cock.
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out a deep, aroused grunt as he hears this, Dale uses one of his hands to take hold of his throbbing shaft and rub it up against your [pc.asshole+], saying, [dale.speech(I'm not really into anal stuff, but seeing as it's with you, I can go along with it. Just take things at your own pace. I'll be here all night, after all...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(pc.isAssVirgin())
		<p>
			Not wanting to rush this, you continue to slide your [pc.asshole+] up and down the length of Dale's thick, hot donkey-cock, imagining what it's going to feel like once it's inside of you. Your soft moans of anticipation are soon changing into excited squeals as you lift your [pc.hips+] and experimentally press your virgin asshole down against the flat, flared head of Dale's animalistic dick. His musky, slippery precum soon coats your [pc.ass+], and as you continue to somewhat-awkwardly press your asshole down against the throbbing head of his dark shaft, the donkey-boy reassures you by softly grunting, [dale.speech(That's it... You're doing fine... ~Mmm!~ Just take it slow and lower yourself down...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Following Dale's instructions, you let out a deeply erotic [pc.moan] as you slowly lower yourself down and force his hot, throbbing donkey-cock into your virgin asshole...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Smirking at Dale's words, you continue to slide your [pc.asshole+] up and down the length of his thick, hot donkey-cock for a moment, before lifting your [pc.hips+] and pressing your horny asshole down against the flat, flared head of his animalistic dick. His musky, slippery precum soon coats your [pc.ass+], and as you continue to tease your asshole down against the throbbing head of his dark shaft, Dale softly grunts, [dale.speech(That's it... ~Mmm!~ Now lower yourself down and take it...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eager to follow Dale's instructions, you let out a deeply erotic [pc.moan] as you lower yourself down and force his hot, throbbing donkey-cock into your ass. Your [pc.asshole+] lewdly spreads around his thick, dark shaft as you drop down, and after letting out yet another [pc.moan+], you start to eagerly ride his cock...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_DALE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a pair of synchronised sighs, you and Dale bring an end to the sex. Lying back on his bed and heavily panting for breath, the donkey-boy grunts, [dale.speech(Wow... That was great...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a satisfied moan as you
		#IF(sex.getSexTypeCount(dale, pc, sex.newSexType(PENETRATION_PENIS, ORIFICE_ANUS))>0)
			#IF(pc.getTotalFluidInArea(ORIFICE_ANUS)>0)
				 feel cum drooling out of your well-fucked asshole,
			#ELSE
				 feel your well-fucked asshole continuing to quiver and contract,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(sex.getSexTypeCount(dale, pc, sex.newSexType(PENETRATION_PENIS, ORIFICE_VAGINA))>0)
			#IF(pc.getTotalFluidInArea(ORIFICE_VAGINA)>0)
				 feel cum drooling out of your well-fucked pussy,
			#ELSE
				 feel your well-fucked pussy continuing to quiver and contract,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(sex.getSexTypeCount(dale, pc, sex.newSexType(PENETRATION_PENIS, ORIFICE_MOUTH))>0)
			 swallow down the mixture of cum and saliva that's still in your mouth,
		#ELSE
			 nuzzle into his muscular chest,
		#ENDIF
		 you tell Dale that you had a lot of fun as well, before thanking him for giving you what you wanted. Flashing you a grin as he pulls on his underwear, the donkey-boy sleepily sighs, [dale.speech(Yeah, that sure was a fun way to wake up... Now I need to... Get some sleep...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the donkey-boy's head rolls to one side, and within a matter of seconds, he's deeply snoring away as he sinks back into a heavy sleep. All thoughts of spending the night sleeping by his side are quickly dispelled from your mind, as you suddenly hear someone out in the corridor bumping into the door to this dormitory. Remembering that you're not supposed to be in here, you slowly get up off the bed so as to not wake Dale, before preparing to sneak back out to the other dormitory...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DORMITORY_DALE_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After pulling the covers over Dale, you stealthily exit his communal sleeping quarters. Thankfully you manage to avoid being seen by any of the other cows, and after [pc.stepping] back out into the corridor, you quickly slip back into the cows' dormitory and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Storage: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STORAGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A pair of large, metal doors have been left propped wide open, allowing you to see that they link the corridor to what is quite obviously the farm's milk storage area. A series of fluorescent lamps set into the high ceiling keep this spacious room permanently bathed in a bright, unnatural light. The floor's sterile, white tiles and the series of huge, steel fluid storage vats which are lined up along the walls give this large room a very industrial atmosphere.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking around, you see that this space doubles as an office, as there are several desks positioned over on one side of the room. There are several office workers stationed at these desks, each one of whom is busily filling out paperwork. Curiously enough, each one of them is a blue-skinned succubus, and they're all wearing the exact same uniform of a light-pink shirt, black micro skirt, and black high heels. Suddenly noticing your presence, they each lift their heads to give you a cursory glance, before quickly returning to their work.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although these succubi seem to be quite busy, you suppose that you could always approach them and see if they'll talk with you. Then again, it might be best to leave them to their work and [pc.step] back out into the corridor...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STORAGE_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to try and engage these blue-skinned succubi in conversation, you start to [pc.walk] over towards the far side of the room where their desks are located. As you draw near, the closest succubus looks up from her work, and upon seeing that you're heading towards her, she lets out an annoyed tut and a sigh, before bluntly stating in a posh accent, [style.feminineStrongSpeech(We don't have time to talk with you cows. If you require something, then go and bother Dale at reception. If what you have to say is urgent, then he'll permit you to speak with Evelyx.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Upon hearing this, one of the other succubi looks up and flashes you an arrogant, scornful sneer, before addressing the first succubus by asking, [style.feminineSpeech(What would sister have to speak about with one of... <i>them</i>? All those cows know about is how to spread their legs and lie still.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubi, who apparently seem to not only be Evelyx's subordinates but also her sisters, each let out an arrogant, mocking laugh. Agreeing with her sister's assessment, the first succubus dismisses you with a wave of her hand and the quick words, [style.feminineStrongSpeech(Get out of here. Go on, shoo!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that you're not going to be able to get anything more from these succubi, other than perhaps an angry word, you decide to turn around and head back out into the corridor...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Evelyx's office: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_OFFICE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing before a polished wooden door, upon which a brass plaque is fixed, reading 'Evelyx's Office'. Although there are a pair of large, glass windows set into the walls on either side of this door, they're one-way mirrored, preventing you from seeing inside.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_finished_no_bad_end))
			#IF(!pc.isTaur())
				Apart from spending a moment to wonder whether Evelyx is watching you from behind the other side of this glass, there's really nothing for you to do here. After all, you need a tauric lower body in order to receive your daily centaur fuck, so if you wanted to earn some money by submitting to one of Lunette's daughters, you'll have to get transformed and return at another time...
			#ELSEIF(!pc.hasVagina() || !pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				Apart from spending a moment to wonder whether Evelyx is watching you from behind the other side of this glass, there's really nothing for you to do here. After all, you need a vagina and to be able to access it in order to receive your daily centaur fuck, so if you wanted to earn some money by submitting to one of Lunette's daughters, you'll have to get that sorted out and return at another time...
			#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_no_bad_end_daily_fuck))
				Apart from spending a moment to wonder whether Evelyx is watching you from behind the other side of this glass, there's really nothing for you to do here. After all, you've already had your daily centaur fuck, so if you wanted to earn some money by submitting to one of Lunette's daughters, you'll have to return again tomorrow...
			#ELSE
				Having accepted Evelyx's final promotion and signed the contract, you're eligible to receive your daily centaur fuck. So, if you wanted to earn some money by submitting to one of Lunette's daughters, all you'd have to do is knock on the door before you...
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Apart from spending a moment to wonder whether Evelyx is watching you from behind the other side of this glass, there's really nothing for you to do here. After all, you can't imagine that the succubus would take kindly to one of her employees deciding to randomly knock on her door. If you had any business with Evelyx, Dale would be the person to see about it...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_OFFICE_ENTER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to receive your daily centaur fuck, you knock on the door to Evelyx's office, and immediately hear her call out from the other side, [evelyx.speech(Enter!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Pushing open the door, you [pc.step] forwards into the succubus's spacious office, and once again take a look around to see that Evelyx's lair is extravagantly furnished. Mahogany shelves are filled with expensive-looking tomes and golden decorations, while large portraits of demons and landscape paintings hang from the walls. A rich, burgundy rug has been placed in the centre of the floor, and over on the far side, you see Evelyx herself sitting in a huge leather chair behind a masterfully-carved wooden desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(Ready for a good, hard rutting, my dirty little whore?)] Evelyx asks. Taking a quick look at the succubus, you once again note how flawless the light blue skin is which covers her body, and while her face has a youthful appearance, the cynical, penetrating gaze from her orange eyes suggests that she's far older than she looks. Her orange nail polish and lipstick matches not only the same shade as her eyes, but also the orange hue that tips the ends of her four small, swept-back horns. Her long, black hair is tied up into a ponytail by means of an orange scrunchie, and a pair of large, [evelyx.cupSize]-cup breasts swell out beneath the succubus's smart, black feminine suit. A gap at the base of her desk allows you to see that instead of humanoid feet, Evelyx has a pair of hard hoofs.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(evelyx))
		#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(evelyx))
			<p>
				Glancing down at your swollen belly, Evelyx realises that she's the one who got you pregnant, but with a wave of her hand she dismissively states, [evelyx.speech(Don't even think of sending any of those bastards you're carrying to me; I don't owe them anything.)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Glancing down at your swollen belly, Evelyx sees that you're still pregnant with her children, but with a wave of her hand she dismissively repeats her previous statement, [evelyx.speech(Don't even think of sending any of those bastards you're carrying to me; I don't owe them anything.)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	#IF(evelyx.isVisiblyPregnant() && evelyx.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(pc))
		#IF(!evelyx.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
			<p>
				As she stands up from behind her desk, you see that Evelyx has a visibly pregnant belly. Seeing what it is you're looking at, she tuts in annoyance, [evelyx.speech(Yes, you got me pregnant. It's incredibly inconvenient, so don't ever do it again...)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				As she stands up from behind her desk, you see that Evelyx still has a visibly pregnant belly. Seeing what it is you're looking at, she tuts in annoyance, [evelyx.speech(Yes, I'm still pregnant, thanks to you. It's incredibly inconvenient, so don't ever do it again...)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			With that, she steps past you and commands in her posh accent, [evelyx.speech(Now follow me. There are already several centaurs waiting for you, and the sooner we get you auctioned off, the sooner one of them can rut your pussy and then leave. Oh, and don't ask me to pay you upfront. You'll be getting your thousand flames after you've performed.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Standing up from behind her desk, she steps past you and commands in her posh accent, [evelyx.speech(Now follow me. There are already several centaurs waiting for you, and the sooner we get you auctioned off, the sooner one of them can rut your pussy and then leave. Oh, and don't ask me to pay you upfront. You'll be getting your thousand flames after you've performed.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_OFFICE_ENTER_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling turned on and desperate to feel Evelyx's fat, demonic cock pounding your pussy once again, you let out a horny moan and beg for her to get you warmed up by rutting you right here on the floor of her office. Quickly turning around to point your hindquarters at her, you present the succubus with your horny pussy and tell her that you want her to empty her heavy balls deep in your hot cunt.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(My, my, what a slutty whore you are,)] Evelyx states, and as she talks, you hear her posh accent once again starting to give way to a lustful, dominant tone. Stepping forwards to give your [pc.ass+] a sharp slap, she pulls up her skirt to reveal her huge, flared, knotted cock, before letting out a hungry moan and asking, [evelyx.speech(Your filthy little cunt thinks that it's good enough for my cock, does it? Go on then, you dirty cow whore, get down so I can give you a good, hard pounding!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hurrying to do as you're told, you drop down to lie on the floor of Evelyx's office. Letting out a hungry moan, the succubus quickly steps forwards and impatiently presses the [evelyx.cockHead+] of her huge, demonic cock against your [pc.labia+]. Consumed by her lust, she wastes no time in thrusting forwards, and you let out a desperate, high-pitched squeal as you feel her [evelyx.cock+] slamming deep into your [pc.pussy+]. Grabbing hold of your [pc.hips+], the blue-skinned succubus rams her fat, throbbing shaft as deep as possible into your pussy, before starting to roughly fuck you in a wild, lust-fuelled frenzy...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_OFFICE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having given you a good, hard fuck and emptied her heavy balls into your still-quivering pussy, Evelyx steps back and regains her posh-sounding accent as she declares, [evelyx.speech(Your cunt was most acceptable, whore. Whoever purchases you today is sure to be pleased.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Panting and moaning as you try to recover from Evelyx's brutal pounding, you're vaguely aware of the succubus using her arcane intercom to contact one of the farm's office workers. A few moments later, and a blue-skinned succubus whose facial features vaguely resemble Evelyx's enters the office. Smirking at this new arrival, the farm's owner sits down on her office chair and addresses both of you by issuing two commands, [evelyx.speech(Come and clean my cock off with your mouth, whore. As for you, sister, you're to clean my cum from out of this whore's cunt. I can't auction her off in this state.)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.isIncestEnabled())
		<p>
			Obediently shuffling forwards as she says this, you start to lick the sexual fluids from the succubus's softening cock. Getting to pleasure Evelyx in such a submissive manner keeps you in a state of high arousal, and you continue to let out soft, horny moans as you set about licking her hot, demonic shaft clean.
		</p>
		<p>
			While you use your tongue to clean Evelyx's cock, her sister, who's brought several cloths with her in expectation of having to perform this duty, kneels down behind you and starts to wipe the cum from out of your cunt. Seeing what it is that her sister is doing, Evelyx allows a slight smirk to settle on her face as she asks, [evelyx.speech(What do you think you're doing? Is your big sister's cum not good enough for you? With this sort of behaviour, I start to question your loyalty... If you don't want mother to find out about your bad behaviour, then I suggest that you show a little more enthusiasm.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly wanting to avoid getting on her mother's bad side, Evelyx's younger sister drops the cloth that she was using, before leaning forwards and starting to lick the cum from your hot pussy. Forcing herself to swallow, she uses her mouth to clean out your cunt while you use your own to do the same to Evelyx's cock.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Obediently shuffling forwards as she says this, you start to lick the sexual fluids from the succubus's softening cock. Getting to pleasure Evelyx in such a submissive manner keeps you in a state of high arousal, and you continue to let out soft, horny moans as you set about licking her hot, demonic shaft clean. While you use your tongue to clean Evelyx's cock, her sister, who's brought several cloths with her in expectation of having to perform this duty, kneels down behind you and starts to wipe the cum from out of your cunt.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Thanks to your enthusiasm, it only takes a few minutes for both you and Evelyx's sister to be finished with your cleaning duties. Seeing that her cock is now completely clean, the succubus stands up and pulls her skirt down to cover herself up, before addressing her sister, [evelyx.speech(You may leave now, sister, but return to me an hour from now; I need to have you disciplined. Oh, and come wearing that lingerie I gave you; I'll be having my sex slave use you, and he likes it when his toys dress up for him.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminine(Yes, Evelyx,)] the succubus replies in a slightly nervous voice. Hurrying out of the room, she leaves you and Evelyx alone together.
	</p>
	<p>
		[evelyx.speech(Now follow me, whore. Let's get you auctioned off and rutted before those centaurs grow bored and decide to vandalise my farm,)] Evelyx commands, before swiftly striding over to follow her sister out of her office, leaving you to follow on behind her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_OFFICE_AUCTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Obediently following Evelyx, you trot along behind her as she strides out of her office and towards the locked door that sits at one end of the farm's long corridor. Unlocking this door, she leads you through it and down the short continuation of the corridor that's to be found on the other side. Coming to a halt in front of yet another wooden door, she turns to face you and explains, [evelyx.speech(Beyond here is the auction room. Once inside, you are to ignore the centaurs and step up onto the central platform. Stay silent and do only what I say. Do <i>not</i> show any kind of favouritism towards any of the centaurs. The last thing I want is for them to lose their temper and start fighting in here. Do you understand?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After you've quickly responded in the affirmative, Evelyx unlocks the door to this 'auction room' and leads you inside. Within the dimly-lit interior, you look around to see that the floor is covered in a rich, burgundy carpet, while dozens of large, taur-compatible sofas have been positioned so as to surround a raised, central platform, which unlike the rest of the dark room is brightly illuminated by means of several arcane spotlights. As you do as you were just told and trot up towards the central platform, you can't help but glance around at the numerous huge, demonic centauresses who are lounging about on the sofas.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminine(She looks like a good one! Get over here and let me get a feel of those tits!)] one of them excitedly declares.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminineStrong(Show me your cunt so I can give you a quick fuck!)] another of them demands.
	</p>
	<p>
		Remembering what Evelyx said, you ignore these comments and step up onto the central platform. Remaining stationary, you listen as Evelyx addresses this herd of Lunette's daughters, [evelyx.speech(Thank you, ladies, for coming here today. As I previously stated, this cow isn't a slave, and so you'll be bidding to fuck her, not adopt her. Please remember that she's a relative of Lilaya's, and as such is of Lyssieth's lineage. Please take this into account when considering your bids.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminineStrong(I'd like to give that elder bitch a good, hard fuck! That imp-breeder daughter of hers would get it too!)] one of the centauresses exclaims in response.
	</p>
	<p>
		Hearing her sister say this, one of the other centauresses lets out a deep laugh and declares, [style.speechFeminine(Once mother's had us finish with the Fields, hopefully she'll have us go after Lyssieth next! I'd love to ruin that human-loving bitch's cunt with my fat cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After that, the centauresses make several more comments about how they'd like to dominate Lyssieth and Lilaya, before agreeing among themselves that you'll make a fine substitute. Showing just the briefest of smirks as she hears how eager they are to fuck you, Evelyx cautiously waits for a gap in the conversation before declaring, [evelyx.speech(Let us start the bidding! Getting to fuck a cunt related to Lyssieth is worth at least ten thousand flames, so let's start with that.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Remembering that you're only getting paid a thousand flames for this, you can't help but feel a little cheated as the centauresses eagerly agree to start the bidding at ten times that amount...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_OFFICE_AUCTION_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Remembering to do as you were told, you stay still and try not to look at any one centauress in particular as they bid against one another to claim your pussy. Clearly eager to get the opportunity to fuck a close relative of Lyssieth's, Lunette's daughters soon increase the bidding to an astronomical figure. Their willingness to blow such a huge sum of money on a one-time fuck is soon explained, however, as one of them loudly comments, [style.speechFeminineStrong(I got all this money from selling some runaway slaves I captured the other day!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminine(It's easier to just take money from people travelling through the Fields!)] another boasts.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to be outdone by her sisters, the centauress who's currently winning the bidding brags, [owner.speech(You get the most from looting people's houses! I've got more money that I could ever possibly spend from doing that!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having said that, this centauress really puts her money where her mouth is, and easily outbids her sisters. After all of the others have backed out of the bidding, this centauress is left with a big, evil grin on her face as Evelyx declares her to be the winner. After paying the blue-skinned succubus far more than the one thousand flames which is to be your share, she lets out a deep, hungry grunt, before bounding up onto your platform and giving your pussy a good grope.
	</p>
	<p>
		[owner.speech(This cunt's related to Lyssieth, huh?)] she growls as she continues to roughly molest your twat. Unable to prevent a horny moan from escaping your mouth, you bite your lip and whine as [owner.name] forcefully pushes her fingers into your [pc.pussy+] and asks, [owner.speech(Hungry for my cock, whore? I'm going to be doing this to Lyssieth and her imp-fucking slut of a daughter one day, so consider yourself practice for that!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_OFFICE_AUCTION_END_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Before you can reply to [owner.namePos] insulting words about Lyssieth and Lilaya, she rears up and roughly mounts you right there on the stage before all of her sisters and Evelyx. Wasting no time with any kind of foreplay, she immediately thrusts her powerful hips forwards and slams her fat, demonic horse-cock deep into your horny cunt.
	</p>
	<p>
		[owner.speech(That's it, you dirty whore! ~Mmm!~ Take my cock you slut!)] she exclaims, and you can't help but let out a stream of erotic moans as she starts to ruthlessly slam her [owner.cock+] in and out of your [pc.pussy+] right there on the auction room's stage...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_OFFICE_AUCTION_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had her fun with you, [owner.name] steps back and gives your ass a sharp slap, before looking at your pussy and grunting in amusement, [owner.speech(My fat cock's turned your cunt into a real filthy mess, you dirty whore.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, she joins the few of her sisters who'd remained to watch her entire performance, before exiting the room by means of a large door that heads straight out into the Fields. Hurrying over to the door, Evelyx calls out after them, [evelyx.speech(Thank you for coming, ladies! I hope to see you again!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus locks the door, before turning to you and stating in her posh accent, [evelyx.speech(You did well, whore. Now let's get you back to reception so dale can pay you out of the company's expense funds.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EVELYX_OFFICE_AUCTION_SEX_END_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With your pussy still quivering, and your legs struggling to recover from holding up the weight of that centauress, you do your best to keep up as Evelyx leads you back to the farm's reception. Upon arrival, she briefly orders Dale to give you your one thousand flames, before turning to you and saying, [evelyx.speech(Come back tomorrow if you want to do that again.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the blue-skinned succubus swiftly strides off back to her office. Seeming to think it's best to not ask what you've just done to earn a thousand flames, Dale produces the money from a safe below his desk, before innocently asking, [dale.speech(Is there anything else I can do for you, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you safely put your earnings away, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Training barn: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_TRAINING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Being of a modern, industrial design, the barn which you find yourself standing in is constructed out of a mix of concrete and sheet metal, and is illuminated by the same kind of fluorescent lamps which are found throughout the rest of Evelyx's Dairy. Thankfully, the comfort of the cows was clearly taken into consideration when this barn was built, for while the structure itself is cold and inhospitable in appearance, there are numerous air conditioning and heating units fitted into the walls, which softly hum away as they work to make sure that the ambient temperature remains pleasantly warm. Underfoot, laminate wooden flooring helps to soften the overall appearance of the barn, as do the motivational posters of cow-girls which have been plastered all over the walls.
	</p>
	<p>
		This background appearance of the barn is only barely registered in your mind, however, as what grabs and holds your attention are the two long rows of milking stalls which run all the way down its considerable length. [pc.Walking] down the natural corridor which is formed between these stalls, you look to your left and right to see that these milking stalls are positioned so as to be facing the walls of the barn. As a result of this, the many dozens of trainees who are being milked in here all have their exposed rear ends pointing towards you, and as they're of all sorts of different races, you find yourself presented with almost every type of pussy imaginable.
	</p>
	<p>
		Continuing to [pc.walk] down the length of the barn, you see that there's an identical sign positioned between every few stalls. Stopping to see what they say, you read:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REQUIREMENTS"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		<b>Before Entering A Milking Stall:</b>
		<br/><b>1.</b>
		#IF(pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_NIPPLES))
			 [style.colourMinorGood(You must have your breasts and nipples exposed.)]
		#ELSE
			 [style.colourMinorBad(You must have your breasts and nipples exposed.)]
		#ENDIF
		<br/><b>2.</b>
		#IF(!pc.hasVagina() || pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_VAGINA))
			 [style.colourMinorGood(If you have a vagina, it too must be exposed.)]
		#ELSE
			 [style.colourMinorBad(If you have a vagina, it too must be exposed.)]
		#ENDIF
		<br/><b>3.</b>
		#IF(!pc.hasBreastsCrotch() || pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_NIPPLES_CROTCH))
			 [style.colourMinorGood(If you have crotch-breasts or udders, they too must be exposed.)]
		#ELSE
			 [style.colourMinorBad(If you have crotch-breasts or udders, they too must be exposed.)]
		#ENDIF
		<br/>Reminder: Cows may use the lockers in the dormitory to store their clothing.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_NIPPLES) || (pc.hasVagina() && !pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_VAGINA)) || (pc.hasBreastsCrotch() && !pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_NIPPLES_CROTCH)))
			As [style.colourMinorBad(you do not currently meet all of the requirements)], you cannot start work at the moment. You'll have to expose yourself in the manner described on the sign before making use of one of the empty milking stalls...
		#ELSEIF(pc.hasStatusEffect(SE_FATIGUED))
			Although you currently meet all of the requirements, [style.colourMinorBad(you're far too tired to work right now)]. You'll have to go and take a rest in the dormitories before being able to come back and make use of one of the empty milking stalls...
		#ELSE
			As [style.colourMinorGood(you currently meet all of the requirements)], you could start work right now if you wanted to. As you've exposed yourself in the manner described on the sign, you could make use of one of the empty milking stalls and get started...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_TRAINING_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing before a solid metal door, above which a sign identifies the area beyond as the 'Trainee Barn'. An arcane card-reader has been secured to the wall beside this door, and a small sign next to this explains that the door can be unlocked by swiping a trainee ear tag over the arcane device. Experimentally pushing on the door, you discover that it's securely locked, and it seems like the only way to open it is by following the sign's instructions.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
			#IF(pc.hasClothingType(CT_innoxia_quest_dairy_ear_tag, true))
				As you're a trainee, and are still in possession of your ear tag, you quickly swipe it over the card-reading device. After letting out a short beep, the door [style.colourGood(automatically unlocks)], allowing you to continue on inside...
			#ELSE
				Although you're a trainee, you're no longer in possession of your ear tag, and so until you recover it the door will [style.colourBad(remain locked)]...
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			As you've been promoted past the rank of trainee, your ear tag has been upgraded and will no longer work on this door. Letting out a sigh as you remember the time which you spent earning your promotion in there, you take one last look at the [style.colourBad(locked)] door and prepare to continue on your way...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_TRAINING_DOOR_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to get past the locked door, you're left with no other choice but to [pc.step] back into the corridor and decide to head elsewhere...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_DOOR_EXIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having finished in the trainee barn for now, you find yourself once again approaching the metal door which links this place to the rest of Evelyx's Dairy. There's no card-reader attached to this side of the door, and according to a nearby sign, all you need to do to unlock it from here is to simply push on it.
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as the sign says, you push on the metal door, and sure enough it freely swings open, allowing you to exit the barn and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Heifer barn: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_HEIFER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Being of a modern, industrial design, the barn which you find yourself standing in is constructed out of a mix of concrete and sheet metal, and is illuminated by the same kind of fluorescent lamps which are found throughout the rest of Evelyx's Dairy. Thankfully, the comfort of the cows was clearly taken into consideration when this barn was built, for while the structure itself is cold and inhospitable in appearance, there are numerous air conditioning and heating units fitted into the walls, which softly hum away as they work to make sure that the ambient temperature remains pleasantly warm. Underfoot, laminate wooden flooring helps to soften the overall appearance of the barn, as do the motivational posters of cow-girls which have been plastered all over the walls.
	</p>
	<p>
		This background appearance of the barn is only barely registered in your mind, however, as what grabs and holds your attention are the two long rows of milking stalls which run all the way down its considerable length. [pc.Walking] down the natural corridor which is formed between these stalls, you look to your left and right to see that these milking stalls are positioned so as to be facing the walls of the barn. As a result of this, the many dozens of heifers who are being milked in here all have their exposed rear ends pointing towards you, and as they're mostly cow-girls, you find yourself presented with the most cow-pussy you're ever likely to see in one place.
	</p>
	<p>
		Continuing to [pc.walk] down the length of the barn, you see that there's an identical sign positioned between every few stalls. Stopping to see what they say, you read:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_HEIFER_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing before a solid metal door, above which a sign identifies the area beyond as the 'Heifer Barn'. An arcane card-reader has been secured to the wall beside this door, and a small sign next to this explains that the door can be unlocked by swiping a trainee ear tag over the arcane device. Experimentally pushing on the door, you discover that it's securely locked, and it seems like the only way to open it is by following the sign's instructions.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==1)
			#IF(pc.hasClothingType(CT_innoxia_quest_dairy_ear_tag, true))
				As you're a heifer, and are still in possession of your ear tag, you quickly swipe it over the card-reading device. After letting out a short beep, the door [style.colourGood(automatically unlocks)], allowing you to continue on inside...
			#ELSE
				Although you're a heifer, you're no longer in possession of your ear tag, and so until you recover it the door will [style.colourBad(remain locked)]...
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')>1)
			As you've been promoted past the rank of heifer, your ear tag has been upgraded and will no longer work on this door. Letting out a sigh as you remember the time which you spent earning your promotion in there, you take one last look at the [style.colourBad(locked)] door and prepare to continue on your way...
		#ELSE
			As you haven't yet been promoted past the rank of trainee, your ear tag won't work on this door, and so until you're promoted to heifer this door will [style.colourBad(remain locked)]...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_HEIFER_DOOR_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to get past the locked door, you're left with no other choice but to [pc.step] back into the corridor and decide to head elsewhere...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Cow barn: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_COW"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Being of a modern, industrial design, the barn which you find yourself standing in is constructed out of a mix of concrete and sheet metal, and is illuminated by the same kind of fluorescent lamps which are found throughout the rest of Evelyx's Dairy. Thankfully, the comfort of the cows was clearly taken into consideration when this barn was built, for while the structure itself is cold and inhospitable in appearance, there are numerous air conditioning and heating units fitted into the walls, which softly hum away as they work to make sure that the ambient temperature remains pleasantly warm. Underfoot, laminate wooden flooring helps to soften the overall appearance of the barn, as do the motivational posters of cow-girls which have been plastered all over the walls.
	</p>
	<p>
		This background appearance of the barn is only barely registered in your mind, however, as what grabs and holds your attention are the two long rows of milking stalls which run all the way down its considerable length. [pc.Walking] down the natural corridor which is formed between these stalls, you look to your left and right to see that these milking stalls are positioned so as to be facing the walls of the barn. As a result of this, the many dozens of cows who are being milked in here all have their exposed rear ends pointing towards you, and as they're all cow-girls, you find yourself presented with the most cow-pussy you're ever likely to see in one place.
	</p>
	<p>
		Continuing to [pc.walk] down the length of the barn, you see that there's an identical sign positioned between every few stalls. Stopping to see what they say, you read:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_COW_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing before a solid metal door, above which a sign identifies the area beyond as the 'Cow Barn'. An arcane card-reader has been secured to the wall beside this door, and a small sign next to this explains that the door can be unlocked by swiping a trainee ear tag over the arcane device. Experimentally pushing on the door, you discover that it's securely locked, and it seems like the only way to open it is by following the sign's instructions.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==2)
			#IF(pc.hasClothingType(CT_innoxia_quest_dairy_ear_tag, true))
				As you're a cow, and are still in possession of your ear tag, you quickly swipe it over the card-reading device. After letting out a short beep, the door [style.colourGood(automatically unlocks)], allowing you to continue on inside...
			#ELSE
				Although you're a cow, you're no longer in possession of your ear tag, and so until you recover it the door will [style.colourBad(remain locked)]...
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			As you haven't yet been promoted to a cow, your ear tag won't work on this door, and so until you've earned your promotion this door will [style.colourBad(remain locked)]...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_COW_DOOR_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to get past the locked door, you're left with no other choice but to [pc.step] back into the corridor and decide to head elsewhere...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Barn work: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_NO_MILK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling yourself that it's time to get down to work, you look around at the nearby milking stalls and quickly choose one of them. Deciding to do a four-hour shift, you approach your selected stall and sink down into the half-standing, half-prone position which its padded surfaces support. Once in this position, you find yourself looking down at a small arcane device that's positioned just in front of you. Consisting of a flat screen and a primitive keyboard with a dozen well-worn buttons, this arcane device resembles a form of very simple computer, and as it detects that you're in the stall, its screen lights up and starts impatiently flashing a red warning, reading:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldBad(No Lactation Detected)]
		<br/><b>Instructions for cow:</b>
		<br/><b>1.</b> Insert lactation-booster feeding tube into mouth.
		<br/><b>2.</b> Drink every drop of the lactation-booster.
		<br/><b>3.</b> Enjoy your milking.
		<br/>Failure to follow these instructions will result in automatic shut-down of this machine.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		As you finish reading this warning, a long, plastic tube drops down from a machine fitted high up on the ceiling, and thanks to its transparent material you're able to see that it's full of a creamy-yellow liquid. With the machine continuing to flash its warning, you wonder whether to drink this fluid in order to start lactating, or refuse and decide against working here after all...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_NO_MILK_NO_DRINK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You really don't like the idea of drinking a mysterious fluid under these circumstances, and so quickly stand back up and [pc.step] away from the milking stall. As you do so, the arcane machine stops flashing its warning, and as it powers down, the plastic tube retracts back up towards the ceiling.
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a sigh, you wonder whether you should go and transform yourself to produce milk on your own terms, or instead give up on this job altogether...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_NO_MILK_DRINK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Really wanting to commit to working as a cow, you decide to do as the machine instructs, and after taking the tube into your mouth, you start to suck out and swallow down the thick, creamy liquid. Thankfully, the mysterious fluid isn't at all unpleasant to drink, and as you gulp it down, you think to yourself that it sort of tastes like milk. Within a few moments, you've done as the arcane machine demands, and as the last drop slides down your throat, you feel your [pc.nipples+] start to tingle...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_NO_MILK_DRINK_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Detecting that you're now able to lactate, the arcane machine stops flashing its warning, and as the feeding tube retracts back up towards the ceiling, the screen of the computer-like device changes to read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldGood(Cow Ready For Milking)]
		<br/>Milking pumps require attachment.
		<br/>Press any button to call for assistance.
		</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SESSION_END_EFFECTS_INITIAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Before you know it, four hours have passed, and while the powerful milking machine completely drained your [pc.breasts] of all of your milk several hours ago, it's still been happy to suck out as much of your milk as you've been able to regenerate since then. To let you know that your session has come to an end, the arcane machine's screen displays a message to you, reading:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SESSION_END_EFFECTS_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling like you're not done yet, you decide to spend another four hours working, and thanks to the ergonomic design of the milking stall's padded supports, the time quickly passes by in comfort. To let you know that your repeat session has come to an end, the arcane machine's screen one again displays a message to you, reading:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SESSION_END_EFFECTS_AFTER_INTERRUPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You aren't interrupted again during your session, and thanks to the ergonomic design of the milking stall's padded supports, the time quickly passes by in comfort. Before you know it, the full four hours have passed, and while the powerful milking machine completely drained your [pc.breasts] of all of your milk several hours ago, it's still been happy to suck out as much of your milk as you've been able to regenerate since then. To let you know that your session has come to an end, the arcane machine's screen displays a message to you, reading:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SESSION_END_EFFECTS_CORE"><![CDATA[
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldMinorGood(Milking Session Complete)]
		<br/>
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
			You have earned [style.moneyFormat(400, span)]!
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==1)
			You have earned [style.moneyFormat(600, span)]!
		#ELSE
			You have earned [style.moneyFormat(800, span)]!
		#ENDIF
		<br/>In this session, you were milked of [style.colourMinorGood([style.fluid([#SPECIAL_PARSE_0])])]!
		<br/>Throughout your career with us, you have been milked of [style.colourGood([style.fluid([#SPECIAL_PARSE_1])])]!
		<br/>You have worked for
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_hours')<=4)
			 [style.colourGood([#flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_hours')]/16)]
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_hours')<=8)
			 [style.colourMinorGood([#flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_hours')]/16)]
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_hours')<=12)
			 [style.colourMinorBad([#flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_hours')]/16)]
		#ELSE
			 [style.colourBad([#flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_hours')]/16)]
		#ENDIF
		 hours in this session.
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_hours')<16)
			<br/>[style.colourMinorGood(A good cow would choose to continue working and earn more money!)]
		#ELSE
			<br/>[style.colourMinorBad(You cannot legally work any more until you've taken a break!)]
		#ENDIF
		<br/>
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion1))
				<br/>[style.boldExcellent(Promotion Available!)]
				<br/>Congratulations, Trainee! Please report to reception at the earliest possible convenience to receive your promotion to 'Heifer'!
			#ELSE
				<br/>[style.boldBlueLight(Promotion Requirements:)]
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(flags.getSavedLong("evelyx_total_milked")>100000)
				[style.colourGood(Total Milked:)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Total Milked:)]
			#ENDIF
			 [style.fluid([#SPECIAL_PARSE_1])]/[style.fluid(100000)]
			<br/>
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_fucked))
				[style.colourGood(Been mated at least once)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Been mated at least once)]
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				[style.colourGood(Has a vagina)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Has a vagina)]
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.isFeminine())
				[style.colourGood(Is feminine)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Is feminine)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==1)
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion2))
				<br/>[style.boldExcellent(Promotion Available!)]
				<br/>Congratulations, Heifer! Please report to reception at the earliest possible convenience to receive your promotion to 'Cow'!
			#ELSE
				<br/>[style.boldBlueLight(Promotion Requirements:)]
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(flags.getSavedLong("evelyx_total_milked")>1000000)
				[style.colourGood(Total Milked:)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Total Milked:)]
			#ENDIF
			 [style.fluid([#SPECIAL_PARSE_1])]/[style.fluid(1000000)]
			<br/>
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_impregnated))
				[style.colourGood(Impregnated while being milked)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Impregnated while being milked)]
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				[style.colourGood(Has a vagina)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Has a vagina)]
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.isFeminine())
				[style.colourGood(Is feminine)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Is feminine)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==2 && !flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion_meeting))
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_promotion3))
				<br/>[style.boldExcellent(Promotion Available!)]
				<br/>Congratulations, Cow! Please report to reception at the earliest possible convenience to receive your special promotion offer!
			#ELSE
				<br/>[style.boldBlueLight(Promotion Requirements:)]
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(flags.getSavedLong("evelyx_total_milked")>10000000)
				[style.colourGood(Total Milked:)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Total Milked:)]
			#ENDIF
			 [style.fluid([#SPECIAL_PARSE_1])]/[style.fluid(10000000)]
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				[style.colourGood(Has a vagina)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Has a vagina)]
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.isFeminine())
				[style.colourGood(Is feminine)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Is feminine)]
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_COW_MORPH || !pc.isAbleToHaveRaceTransformed())
				[style.colourGood(Is a cow-girl, or cannot have race transformed)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Is a cow-girl, or cannot have race transformed)]
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.getLegConfiguration()==LEG_CONFIGURATION_QUADRUPEDAL)
				[style.colourGood(Has a quadrupedal lower body)]
			#ELSE
				[style.colourBad(Has a quadrupedal lower body)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_hours')<16)
			As you're wondering whether to work another four-hour shift, the text in front of you flickers and changes, and you read:
		#ELSE
			As you're about to unhook yourself from the milking machine, the text in front of you flickers and changes, and you read:
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldExcellent(Reward Menu)]
		<br/>
		#IF(evelyx.isAnyCowTransformationAvailable(pc))
			[style.colourGood(Better Body:)] Be a good cow and trust us to make your body better with this potion.
		#ELSE
			[style.colourDisabled(Better Body:)] Your body does not currently require any improvements.
		#ENDIF
		<br/>
		#IF(evelyx.isAnyCowFetishAvailable(pc))
			[style.colourGood(Improved Mind:)] You'll enjoy being a cow much more after this.
		#ELSE
			[style.colourDisabled(Improved Mind:)] Your mind does not currently require any improvements.
		#ENDIF
		<br/>
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_accessories_trainee))
				[style.colourDisabled(Trainee Accessories:)] You have previously received this one-time reward!
			#ELSEIF(evelyx.isCowAbleToEquipGear(pc))
				[style.colourGood(Trainee Accessories:)] A bronze cow-bell collar and matching nose ring will suit you nicely!
			#ELSE
				[style.colourMinorBad(Trainee Accessories:)] You are unable to equip a nose ring and collar, so cannot receive this reward!
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==1)
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_accessories_heifer))
				[style.colourDisabled(Heifer Accessories:)] You have previously received this one-time reward!
			#ELSEIF(evelyx.isCowAbleToEquipGear(pc))
				[style.colourGood(Heifer Accessories:)] A silver cow-bell collar and matching nose ring will suit you nicely!
			#ELSE
				[style.colourMinorBad(Heifer Accessories:)] You are unable to equip a nose ring and collar, so cannot receive this reward!
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_innoxia_evelyx_work_accessories_cow))
				[style.colourDisabled(Cow Accessories:)] You have previously received this one-time reward!
			#ELSEIF(evelyx.isCowAbleToEquipGear(pc))
				[style.colourGood(Cow Accessories:)] A gold cow-bell collar and matching nose ring will suit you nicely!
			#ELSE
				[style.colourMinorBad(Cow Accessories:)] You are unable to equip a nose ring and collar, so cannot receive this reward!
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')!=2)
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
				[style.colourSex(Mated:)] Get mated by a member of the public and receive a bonus of [style.moneyFormat(500, span)]!
			#ELSE
				[style.colourMinorBad(Mated:)] You require a vagina and to be able to access it before you can be mated.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')>0)
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_COW_MORPH && pc.getRaceStage()!=RACE_STAGE_GREATER)
				[style.colourDisabled(Lesser cow-girl transformation:)] You are already a lesser cow-girl.
			#ELSEIF(!pc.isAbleToHaveRaceTransformed())
				[style.colourMinorBad(Lesser cow-girl transformation:)] You cannot have your race transformed, so cannot become a lesser cow-girl.
			#ELSE
				[style.colourTfPartial(Lesser cow-girl transformation:)] Be a good cow and assume your true form!
			#ENDIF
			<br/>
			#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_COW_MORPH && pc.getRaceStage()==RACE_STAGE_GREATER)
				[style.colourDisabled(Greater cow-girl transformation:)] You are already a greater cow-girl.
			#ELSEIF(!pc.isAbleToHaveRaceTransformed())
				[style.colourMinorBad(Greater cow-girl transformation:)] You cannot have your race transformed, so cannot become a greater cow-girl.
			#ELSE
				[style.colourTfGreater(Greater cow-girl transformation:)] Be a good cow and assume your true form!
			#ENDIF
			#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')>1)
				<br/>
				#IF(pc.getLegRace()==RACE_COW_MORPH && pc.getLegConfiguration()==LEG_CONFIGURATION_QUADRUPEDAL)
					[style.colourDisabled(Cowtaur:)] You are already a cowtaur.
				#ELSEIF(!pc.isAbleToHaveRaceTransformed())
					[style.colourMinorBad(Cowtaur:)] You cannot have your race transformed, so cannot become a cowtaur.
				#ELSE
					[style.colourTfGreater(Cowtaur:)] Be a good cow and have your lower body transformed into that of a feral cow!
				#ENDIF
				<br/>
				#IF(pc.getTattooInSlot(IS_ANUS)!=null)
					[style.colourDisabled(Tattoo:)] You already have a tattoo on your ass.
				#ELSE
					[style.colourGood(Tattoo:)] Good cows have an identification tattoo on their ass, and it's time to receive yours!
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Sex interrupt for when player is working as a cow: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SEX_INTERRUPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Just as you're settling into the flow of being milked, you suddenly hear the door to the barn swing open. While this happens all the time as cows come and go from being milked, this time it's different, as immediately after the door's opening, you hear the unmistakable voice of Dale talking to someone. Looking back over your shoulder, you see the donkey-boy receptionist entering the barn, and [partner.walking] alongside him you see [partner.a_fullRace(true)]. Stepping over to a small control panel fixed to the wall beside the barn's entrance, Dale presses a button, and then a moment later the arcane machine in front of you displays the text: 
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
			[style.colourSex(Mating opportunity)]
			<br/>If you are chosen, you will receive a bonus of [style.moneyFormat(500, span)].
			<br/>Be a good cow and show yourself off.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		All of the arcane machines throughout the barn seem to have displayed the same message to their stall's occupant, for as Dale and [partner.name] start to walk down the aisle between the milking stalls, you hear the cows desperately moaning and begging to be mated. Before you know it, the two of them are right behind you, and as he's been doing with all of the cows that they've passed, Dale slides his fingers over your pussy, before spreading your labia and showing off your cunt to the stranger. [pc.A_moan+] escapes from your mouth as you feel [partner.namePos] gaze upon your exposed pussy, which leads into Dale saying, [dale.speech(This one's eager for it. I'm sure you'll enjoy [pc.her] pussy.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!partner.isMute())
			#IF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_GENTLE)
				[partner.speech([pc.She] does look good, yes. I just wonder if there's another cow that I'd prefer,)] [partner.name] muses. As [partner.she]
			#ELSEIF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_ROUGH)
				[partner.speech(Yeah, [pc.her] cunt looks like it could take a good, hard fucking. There might be another cow that I'd prefer to break though,)] [partner.name] growls. As [partner.she]
			#ELSE
				[partner.speech(Yeah, [pc.her] cunt looks like it'd be good to fuck. There might be another cow that I'd prefer to choose though,)] [partner.name] says. As [partner.she]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 As [partner.name]
		#ENDIF
		 takes a moment to think about whether or not to choose you, you're given an opportunity to influence [partner.her] decision. If you weren't too keen on getting fucked right now, you could stay quiet and hope that you aren't chosen, or if you were wanting to earn those extra five hundred flames, you could always show off and beg for the [partner.race] to fuck your horny cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SEX_INTERRUPT_QUIET"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You really don't feel like getting fucked by this [partner.race], and so as Dale continues to spread your [pc.labia+] and show you off to this stranger, you remain as quiet and still as possible, hoping that [partner.she]'ll lose interest and choose a different cow.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SEX_INTERRUPT_SHOW_OFF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling turned on at the prospect of being fucked by this stranger, but not wanting to come off as being too desperate, you sway your [pc.hips+] from side to side and lift your [pc.ass+] up towards [partner.herHim]. Continuing to spread your [pc.labia+] and show you off to [partner.name], Dale helps you to get what you want by saying, [dale.speech(See? [pc.SheIs] wanting you to choose [pc.herHim]. You're not going to say no to this pussy, are you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SEX_INTERRUPT_BEG"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling incredibly turned on at the prospect of being fucked by this stranger, and not at all bothered about coming off as being desperate, you sway your [pc.hips+] from side to side and lift your [pc.ass+] up towards [partner.herHim], before letting out an erotic [pc.moan] and desperately begging for [partner.herHim] to fuck you. Continuing to spread your [pc.labia+] and show you off to [partner.name], Dale helps you to get what you want by saying, [dale.speech(See? [pc.SheIs] getting turned on already. You're not going to say no to this hot, horny pussy, are you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SEX_INTERRUPT_FUCKED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Obviously liking the look of you, [partner.name] lets out an approving
		#IF(partner.isFeminine())
			 moan
		#ELSE
			 grunt
		#ENDIF
		 and [partner.steps] forwards,
		#IF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_GENTLE)
			 before gently pushing Dale's hands away and softly teasing [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] over your [pc.pussy+].
		#ELSEIF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_ROUGH)
			 before swatting Dale's hands away and roughly stuffing [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] into your [pc.pussy+].
		#ELSE
			 before pushing Dale's hands away and greedily sliding [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] over your [pc.pussy+].
		#ENDIF
		 You can't help but let out [pc.a_moan+] in response to [partner.namePos] move, and as you turn your head back to flash [partner.herHim] a seductive look,
		#IF(partner.isMute())
			 this stranger, who is obviously unable to talk, gives Dale a swift nod to convey the fact that [partner.sheIs] happy with [partner.her] choice.
		#ELSE
			 this stranger excitedly states,
			#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
				 [partner.speech(I like my cows pregnant, so [pc.she]'ll do nicely.)]
			#ELSEIF(!partner.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
				 [partner.speech(Yes, [pc.she]'ll do! I'm going to enjoy this...)]
			#ELSE
				 [partner.speech(Yes, [pc.she]'ll do! I'll try and get [pc.her] knocked up for you.)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(I'll leave the two of you to it then. I'll be back once you've finished,)] Dale says, before swiftly departing and leaving you alone with [partner.name]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SEX_INTERRUPT_FUCKED_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!partner.isMute())
		#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_ANUS, true) && partner.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
			<p>
				#IF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_GENTLE)
					[partner.speech(Your cunt's cute and all, but that's not what I'm interested in,)] [partner.name] teases, before gently sliding [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] up and down over your [pc.asshole+]. Letting out a soft [partner.moan], [partner.she] excitedly states, [partner.speech(I'm going to fuck your ass!)]
				#ELSEIF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_ROUGH)
					[partner.speech(You think I'm here to fuck your cunt, you dumb cow?)] [partner.name] cruelly teases, before roughly slapping your [pc.ass+]. Letting out a mocking laugh as a surprised cry bursts out of your mouth, [partner.she] suddenly starts forcefully rubbing her thumb up and down over your [pc.asshole+] while [partner.moaning], [partner.speech(I'm going to enjoy pounding your ass! I'm going to stuff my cock <i>deep</i> into here and turn you into my dirty little buttslut!)]
				#ELSE
					[partner.speech(Your cunt's tempting, but that's really not what I'm interested in,)] [partner.name] teases, before eagerly sliding [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] up and down over your [pc.asshole+]. Letting out an erotic [partner.moan], [partner.she] excitedly states, [partner.speech(I'm going to fuck your ass!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				#IF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_GENTLE)
					[partner.speech(Your cunt's so cute,)] [partner.name] sighs, before playfully teasing [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] up and down over your [pc.clit+]. Letting out a soft [partner.moan], [partner.she] excitedly states, [partner.speech(Let's get to it! I can't wait to find out how good your pussy's going to feel around my cock!)]
				#ELSEIF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_ROUGH)
					[partner.speech(You've got such a lewd, filthy cunt, haven't you, you dumb cow?)] [partner.name] cruelly teases, before delivering a few sharp slaps to your exposed pussy. Letting out a mocking laugh as a surprised cry bursts out of your mouth, [partner.she] suddenly starts forcefully rubbing her thumb up and down over your [pc.clit+] while [partner.moaning], [partner.speech(I'm going to enjoy pounding your pussy! I'm going to stuff my cock <i>deep</i> into your cunt and turn you into my dirty little whore!)]
				#ELSE
					[partner.speech(Your cunt's so hot,)] [partner.name] [partner.moans], before playfully rubbing [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] up and down over your [pc.clit+]. Letting out an erotic [partner.moan], [partner.she] excitedly states, [partner.speech(Let's get to it! I can't wait to find out how good your pussy's going to feel around my cock!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_ANUS, true) && partner.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
		<p>
			Quickly taking out [partner.her] [partner.cock+], [partner.name] immediately starts rubbing the [partner.cockHead+] up and down over your [pc.asshole+], causing you to let out a lewd [pc.moan]. Taking hold of your [pc.hips+], [partner.she] wastes no further time and thrusts forwards, sinking [partner.her] [partner.cock+] into your [pc.asshole+]. With the milking machine continuing to pump away at your [pc.breasts+], [partner.name] starts energetically fucking your ass in front of the
			#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
				 trainees to either side of you...
			#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==1)
				 heifers to either side of you...
			#ELSE
				 cows to either side of you...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Quickly taking out [partner.her] [partner.cock+], [partner.name] immediately starts rubbing the [partner.cockHead+] up and down over your [pc.pussy+], causing you to let out a lewd [pc.moan]. Taking hold of your [pc.hips+], [partner.she] wastes no further time and thrusts forwards, sinking [partner.her] [partner.cock+] into your [pc.pussy+]. With the milking machine continuing to pump away at your [pc.breasts+], [partner.name] starts energetically fucking you in front of the
			#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
				 trainees to either side of you...
			#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==1)
				 heifers to either side of you...
			#ELSE
				 cows to either side of you...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SEX_INTERRUPT_IGNORED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The [partner.race] looks at you for a moment, before letting out a disapproving tut and [partner.stepping] over to the next cow in line. Taking his fingers away from your exposed pussy, Dale hurries after the stranger, leaving you alone once again. Having not been chosen, you're left to listen to the sounds of the [partner.race] fucking one of the other cows further down the line while you continue to be milked...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Standard work dialogues: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_INITIAL_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling yourself that it's time to get down to work, you look around at the nearby milking stalls and quickly choose one of them. Deciding to do a four-hour shift, you approach your selected stall and sink down into the half-standing, half-prone position which its padded surfaces support. Once in this position, you find yourself looking down at a small arcane device that's positioned just in front of you. Consisting of a flat screen and a primitive keyboard with a dozen well-worn buttons, this arcane device resembles a form of very simple computer, and as it detects that you're in the stall, its screen lights up and displays some text for you to read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldGood(Cow Ready For Milking)]
		<br/>Milking pumps require attachment.
		<br/>Press any button to call for assistance.
		</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_INITIAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Realising that you're unable to attach the milking machine's breast pumps to yourself while in this position, you do as the arcane device says and press one of the buttons. A ringing bell can be heard off in the distance, and an orange arcane light attached to the top of your stall starts flashing. A few moments later and you hear the door to the barn open, and you turn your head to see Dale hurrying over to your stall. Within a few moments he's by your side, and flashes you a warm smile as he sees that you require assistance in getting your pumps attached.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(dale))
		#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(dale))
			<p>
				The donkey-boy's eyes then suddenly widen as he notices your swollen belly, and as you give him a knowing glance, he realises that he's the father. Tentatively reaching out to gently rub his strong hands over your distended stomach, he marvels, [dale.speech(I really got you pregnant? Wow... Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help! I'll try to make time for you if you need it.)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				The donkey-boy's eyes then widen a little as he sees your swollen belly, letting him know that you're still pregnant with his children. Tentatively reaching out to gently rub his strong hands over your distended stomach, he repeats his previous offer, [dale.speech(Just let me know if there's anything I can do to help. I'll try to make time for you if you need it.)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			Thanking Dale for his kind offer, you tell him that you're able to handle things yourself, to which he replies, [dale.speech(Well, if you change your mind then just let me know. Now let's get you hooked up to the machine...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Bending down to the large arcane machine that's positioned beside your stall, the donkey-boy flicks its 'on' button, and as it starts humming away, he gently takes hold of your [pc.breasts] and attaches the milking machine's suction pumps over your nipples.
		#IF(pc.hasBreastsCrotch())
			 Kneeling down, he quickly attaches more pumps to your [pc.udders+], before standing up and taking a step back.
		#ENDIF
		 Taking a moment to make sure that everything's working correctly, he looks over the pressure readings on the machine and checks to make sure that the pumps are remaining securely attached to your [pc.breasts]. With an approving nod and a hum, he then asks, [dale.speech(Is that comfortable for you? Is there anything else you'd like me to do for you before I leave?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_INITIAL_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling very comfortable, you thank Dale for his attention and tell him that you don't require anything else. Telling you to relax and enjoy your time, the donkey-boy hurries off back to his desk, leaving you to be milked by the machine...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Dale sex: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_DALE_TEASE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to tease the donkey-boy a little, you tell him that you're not comfortable in your current position, and ask him if he could help you to adjust the stall's padded supports. More than happy to help you, Dale quickly replies, [dale.speech(Of course, [pc.name]! Which ones do you need adjusting?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With everything going according to your plan, you direct the donkey-boy towards the supports near your groin, and as he bends down to adjust them, you playfully comment on how you're getting turned on by having him so close to your private parts. Continuing to direct him towards the supports around your rear end, you provocatively flirt with Dale, before asking him to give his honest opinion on whether or not you look decently fuckable. Although he's been happy to play along with your flirting up until this point, Dale pauses for a moment as you ask this, before clearing his throat and awkwardly replying, [dale.speech(Well, of course you look good. I mean, you're... That is to say... Yes.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning your head back to give Dale a cheeky smirk, you see the unmistakable shape of his [dale.cockSize] cock pushing out against the fabric of his trousers. As you compliment him on the size of his bulge, the donkey-boy finally catches on with what you're doing, and asks with a sigh, [dale.speech(You didn't really need my help with the supports, did you? You were just trying to get me to fuck your hot... I mean, to pound your... I mean, I appreciate your attention, but I really do have a lot of work to do, so I couldn't possibly stop to... Well, you know...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite his claim that he's got work to get back to, Dale shows no sign of leaving your side, and you suppose that now that you've got him turned on, it wouldn't be too hard to get him to go all the way and fuck you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_DALE_TEASE_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to get Dale in trouble by causing him to skip work, you tell him that you enjoyed the little flirting session the two of you just had, before stating that you're comfortable in your stall now. Letting out a deep sigh, the donkey-boy flashes you a grin and reveals, [dale.speech(You had me right on the edge there. Just a little more teasing and I would have... Well, anyway, I'd better get back to my desk!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the donkey-boy hurries off back to reception, leaving you alone to enjoy your milking session...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_DALE_TEASE_SEX_PUSSY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a playful, disappointed whine, you tell Dale that it's a real shame that he has to get back to his work. Lifting your [pc.hips+], you flash the donkey-boy your most seductive look and ask him to at least give your pussy a kiss before he has to leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Well, if that's what it'll take to keep you happy,)] Dale replies with a good-natured laugh. Stepping around behind you, he drops down and plants a big, wet kiss on your exposed cunt. Just as you'd hoped he would, the aroused donkey-boy doesn't stop there, as he can't help himself from then sliding his tongue over your [pc.labia+] and giving your [pc.clit+] a quick kiss.
	</p>
	#IF(!pc.isVaginaVirgin() && pc.hasHymen())
		<p>
			Having got him right where you want him, you let out an excited [pc.moan] and quickly inform Dale that even though you're not a virgin, your hymen has been regrown. Playfully pushing your [pc.pussy+] back against his face, you tease the donkey-boy by saying that your pussy is sure to feel every bit as good as if you were a real virgin, before telling him to get out his cock and fuck you already. Striking directly at Dale's weakness for liking to take virginities, you can't help but grin as the donkey-boy stands up and starts undoing his trousers.
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(I really shouldn't, but I suppose if I'm quick then I won't get in trouble,)] he says to justify his decision to himself. Within a matter of seconds, Dale's trousers and underwear have been pulled down, and you let out an excited [pc.moan] as he takes hold of your [pc.hips] and starts sliding the underside of his huge, erect donkey-cock up and down over your [pc.ass+]. Letting out a deep, desperate grunt, he pulls back and takes hold of his animalistic shaft in one hand, before prodding the wide, flared head against your exposed cunt. As his slippery precum oozes out to coat your [pc.labia+], he softly groans, [dale.speech(I'll try to be gentle for you... Are you ready for this?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly replying in the positive, you tell Dale to get started, and then a second later you're letting out another erotic [pc.moan] as you feel him slowly pushing forwards and sliding his hot, throbbing donkey-cock into your pussy. Although he tries to be gentle, Dale's thick shaft gives you a brief sensation of pain as it tears your hymen, but after letting out a brief cry, you quickly recover and start panting and moaning as you feel your [pc.labia+] spreading lewdly around his dark donkey-cock...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.isVaginaVirgin())
		<p>
			Having got him right where you want him, you let out an excited [pc.moan] and quickly inform Dale that you're still a virgin. Playfully pushing your [pc.pussy+] back against his face, you tease the donkey-boy by saying that your pussy hasn't ever felt this way before, and that you need him to get out his cock and fuck you already. Striking directly at Dale's weakness for liking to take virginities, you can't help but let out a breathless moan as the donkey-boy stands up and starts undoing his trousers.
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(I really shouldn't, but how could I say no to that?)] he says to justify his decision to himself. Within a matter of seconds, Dale's trousers and underwear have been pulled down, and you let out an excited [pc.moan] as he takes hold of your [pc.hips] and starts sliding the underside of his huge, erect donkey-cock up and down over your [pc.ass+]. Letting out a deep, desperate grunt, he pulls back and takes hold of his animalistic shaft in one hand, before prodding the wide, flared head against your exposed, virgin cunt. As his slippery precum oozes out to coat your [pc.labia+], he softly groans, [dale.speech(I'll try to be gentle for you... Are you ready for this?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly replying in the positive, you tell Dale to get started, and then a second later you're letting out another erotic [pc.moan] as you feel him slowly pushing forwards and starting to slide his hot, throbbing donkey-cock into your virgin pussy...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having got him right where you want him, you let out an excited [pc.moan] and push your [pc.pussy+] back against Dale's face, before impatiently telling him to get out his cock and fuck you already. Unable to resist your command, the donkey-boy lets out a horny groan, and after planting one last kiss on your [pc.labia+], he stands up and hastily starts undoing his trousers.
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(I really shouldn't, but I suppose if I'm quick then I won't get in trouble,)] he says to justify his decision to himself. Within a matter of seconds, Dale's trousers and underwear have been pulled down, and you let out an excited [pc.moan] as he takes hold of your [pc.hips] and starts sliding the underside of his huge, erect donkey-cock up and down over your [pc.ass+]. Letting out a deep, desperate grunt, he pulls back and takes hold of his animalistic shaft in one hand, before prodding the wide, flared head against your exposed cunt. As his slippery precum oozes out to coat your [pc.labia+], he softly groans, [dale.speech(I'll try to be gentle for you... Are you ready for this?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly replying in the positive, you tell Dale to get started, and then a second later you're letting out another erotic [pc.moan] as you feel him slowly pushing forwards and sliding his hot, throbbing dick into your pussy. Excitedly pushing back against him, you start panting and moaning as you feel your [pc.labia+] spreading lewdly around his dark donkey-cock...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_DALE_TEASE_SEX_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a playful, disappointed whine, you tell Dale that it's a real shame that he has to get back to his work. Looking up at him, you flash the donkey-boy your most seductive look and ask him to at least give you a kiss before he has to leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Well, if that's what it'll take to keep you happy,)] Dale replies with a good-natured laugh. Stepping around in front of you, he drops down and plants a big, wet kiss on your [pc.lips+]. Having got him right where you want him, you eagerly dart out your [pc.tongue+], and in a matter of moments the aroused donkey-boy is passionately making out with you. After a short while of desperately kissing one another in this manner, Dale finally pulls back and laughs, [dale.speech(Well, that was more than I was expecting!)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isFaceVirgin())
		<p>
			With the donkey-boy's face still right in front of your own, you take this opportunity to lower your voice and lewdly whisper to him that you've never sucked cock before. Licking your [pc.lips], you tell him that you want him to be your first, and after pointedly glancing down at the huge bulge in his trousers, you tell him to take out his dick and let you have a taste of it. Striking directly at Dale's weakness for liking to take virginities, you can't help but let out a breathless moan as the donkey-boy stands up and starts undoing his trousers.
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(I really shouldn't, but how could I say no to that?)] he says to justify his decision to himself. Within a matter of seconds, Dale's trousers and underwear have been pulled down, and you let out an excited [pc.moan] as you find yourself staring directly at his huge, erect donkey-cock. Letting out a deep, desperate grunt, Dale takes hold of his animalistic shaft in one hand, before pressing the wide, flared head against your mouth. After excitedly planting a big, wet kiss on his cock, you start greedily licking up his salty, musky precum, and as you dart out your [pc.tongue+] to give his throbbing shaft a long, wet lick, Dale softly groans, [dale.speech(I'll try to be gentle for you... Are you ready to take it in your mouth?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly replying in the positive, you part your [pc.lips] and open wide, allowing Dale to slowly push forwards and slide his thick, throbbing donkey-cock down your virgin throat. Within a matter of moments a stream of precum and saliva is drooling from the corners of your mouth, and you're letting out a series of gargling moans as the donkey-boy's dark shaft slides back and forth past your [pc.lips+]...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With the donkey-boy's face still right in front of your own, you take this opportunity to lower your voice and lewdly whisper to him that you're craving the taste of his cock right now. Licking your [pc.lips] and pointedly glancing down at the huge bulge in his trousers, you tell him to take out his dick and give it to you. Unable to resist your command, the donkey-boy lets out a horny groan, and after planting one last kiss on your [pc.lips+], he stands up and hastily starts undoing his trousers.
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(I really shouldn't, but I suppose if I'm quick then I won't get in trouble,)] he says to justify his decision to himself. Within a matter of seconds, Dale's trousers and underwear have been pulled down, and you let out an excited [pc.moan] as you find yourself staring directly at his huge, erect donkey-cock. Letting out a deep, desperate grunt, Dale takes hold of his animalistic shaft in one hand, before pressing the wide, flared head against your mouth. After excitedly planting a big, wet kiss on his cock, you start greedily licking up his salty, musky precum, and as you dart out your [pc.tongue+] to give his throbbing shaft a long, wet lick, Dale softly groans, [dale.speech(I'll try to be gentle for you... Are you ready to take it in your mouth?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly replying in the positive, you part your [pc.lips] and open wide, allowing Dale to slowly push forwards and slide his thick, throbbing donkey-cock down your throat. Within a matter of moments a stream of precum and saliva is drooling from the corners of your mouth, and you're letting out a series of gargling moans as the donkey-boy's dark shaft slides back and forth past your [pc.lips+]...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_DALE_TEASE_SEX_ANAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a playful, disappointed whine, you tell Dale that it's a real shame that he has to get back to his work. Lifting your [pc.hips+], you flash the donkey-boy your most seductive look and ask him to at least give your ass a kiss before he has to leave.
	</p>
	<p>
		[dale.speech(Well, if that's what it'll take to keep you happy,)] Dale replies with a good-natured laugh. Stepping around behind you, he drops down and plants a big, wet kiss on each of your ass cheeks. Just as you'd hoped he would, the aroused donkey-boy doesn't stop there, as he can't help himself from then giving your [pc.ass+] a good grope.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isAssVirgin())
		<p>
			Having got him right where you want him, you let out an excited [pc.moan] and quickly inform Dale that you're still an anal virgin. Playfully pushing your [pc.ass+] back towards him, you tease the donkey-boy by saying that you haven't ever felt this way before, and that you need him to get out his cock and fuck your ass already. Striking directly at Dale's weakness for liking to take virginities, you can't help but let out a breathless moan as the donkey-boy stands up and starts undoing his trousers.
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(I really shouldn't, and I'm not really into anal stuff, but how could I say no to that?)] he says to justify his decision to himself. Within a matter of seconds, Dale's trousers and underwear have been pulled down, and you let out an excited [pc.moan] as he takes hold of your [pc.hips] and starts sliding the underside of his huge, erect donkey-cock up and down over your [pc.ass+]. Letting out a deep, desperate grunt, he pulls back and takes hold of his animalistic shaft in one hand, before prodding the wide, flared head against your exposed, virgin asshole. As his slippery precum oozes out to coat your rear entrance, he softly groans, [dale.speech(I'll try to be gentle for you... Are you ready for this?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly replying in the positive, you tell Dale to get started, and then a second later you're letting out another erotic [pc.moan] as you feel him slowly pushing forwards and starting to slide his hot, throbbing donkey-cock into your virgin asshole...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having got him right where you want him, you let out an excited [pc.moan] and push your [pc.ass+] back towards Dale, before impatiently telling him to get out his cock and fuck your ass already. Unable to resist your command, the donkey-boy lets out a horny groan, and after giving your [pc.ass+] one last grope, he stands up and hastily starts undoing his trousers.
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(I really shouldn't, and I'm usually not really into anal stuff, but I suppose if I'm quick then I won't get in trouble,)] he says to justify his decision to himself. Within a matter of seconds, Dale's trousers and underwear have been pulled down, and you let out an excited [pc.moan] as he takes hold of your [pc.hips] and starts sliding the underside of his huge, erect donkey-cock up and down over your [pc.ass+]. Letting out a deep, desperate grunt, he pulls back and takes hold of his animalistic shaft in one hand, before prodding the wide, flared head against your exposed asshole. As his slippery precum oozes out to coat your rear entrance, he softly groans, [dale.speech(I'll try to be gentle for you... Are you ready for this?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly replying in the positive, you tell Dale to get started, and then a second later you're letting out another erotic [pc.moan] as you feel him slowly pushing forwards and sliding his hot, throbbing dick into your ass. Excitedly pushing back against him, you start panting and moaning as you feel your [pc.asshole+] spreading lewdly around his dark donkey-cock...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_DALE_TEASE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough, Dale takes a step back, and in between his heavy panting for breath, he says, [dale.speech(I really... Need to get back to work now... That was great...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a satisfied moan as you
		#IF(sex.getSexTypeCount(dale, pc, sex.newSexType(PENETRATION_PENIS, ORIFICE_ANUS))>0)
			#IF(pc.getTotalFluidInArea(ORIFICE_ANUS)>0)
				 feel cum drooling out of your well-fucked asshole,
			#ELSE
				 feel your well-fucked asshole continuing to quiver and contract,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(sex.getSexTypeCount(dale, pc, sex.newSexType(PENETRATION_PENIS, ORIFICE_VAGINA))>0)
			#IF(pc.getTotalFluidInArea(ORIFICE_VAGINA)>0)
				 feel cum drooling out of your well-fucked pussy,
			#ELSE
				 feel your well-fucked pussy continuing to quiver and contract,
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			 swallow down the mixture of cum and saliva that's still in your mouth,
		#ENDIF
		 you tell Dale that you had a lot of fun as well, before thanking him for giving you what you wanted. Flashing you a grin as he pulls his underwear and trousers back up, the donkey-boy says, [dale.speech(I'm glad that I didn't talk myself out of doing this. We'll have to do it again some time...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Returning Dale's grin with a smile of your own, you say goodbye to him, and as he rushes off back to his desk, you're left to settle into the comfort of your milking stall and be milked for the next four hours...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- End work: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough of working in the barn for one day, you press the key labelled as 'End' on the arcane device's keyboard. Immediately, the milking machine stops humming away, and as the pumps lose pressure, they fall from your [pc.breasts] to the floor. Standing up and stretching, you feel a wave of fatigue wash over you, and can't help but think that it would be nice to head over to the dormitories and get some rest...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_BODY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of the offered 'Better Body' reward, you press the button on the arcane device's keyboard which corresponds to it. Immediately, a long, plastic tube drops down from the ceiling, and the text on the device's screen changes to read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldCow(Better Body)]
		<br/><b>Instructions for cow:</b>
		<br/><b>1.</b> Insert transformative potion tube into mouth.
		<br/><b>2.</b> Drink every drop of the transformative potion.
		<br/><b>3.</b> Enjoy your new body.
		<br/>Failure to follow these instructions will result in automatic shut-down of this machine.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the machine's instructions, you quickly place the tube in your mouth and start to suck out the sickly-sweet potion. After greedily swallowing down every last drop, you can't help but let out a deeply erotic [pc.moan] as you feel your body start to transform. As the transformative effects begin to manifest themselves, the arcane machine somehow detects what's happening to you and displays information on each of your transformations...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_BODY_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After letting out a few final moans as the transformation comes to an end, you take a moment to get used to the feel of your new body, before wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_MIND"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Liking the sound of the offered 'Improved Mind' reward, you press the button on the arcane device's keyboard which corresponds to it. Immediately, a long, plastic tube drops down from the ceiling, and the text on the device's screen changes to read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldCow(Improved Mind)]
		<br/><b>Instructions for cow:</b>
		<br/><b>1.</b> Insert mind-altering potion tube into mouth.
		<br/><b>2.</b> Drink every drop of the mind-altering potion.
		<br/><b>3.</b> Enjoy your new perspective.
		<br/>Failure to follow these instructions will result in automatic shut-down of this machine.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the machine's instructions, you quickly place the tube in your mouth and start to suck out the sickly-sweet potion. After greedily swallowing down every last drop, you can't help but let out a deeply erotic [pc.moan] as you feel your head start to spin. As the mind-altering effects begin to manifest themselves, the arcane machine somehow detects what's happening to you and displays information on each one of your changes...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_MIND_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After letting out a few final, horny moans as the mind-altering transformation comes to an end, you find yourself feeling very happy with your decision to work here at Evelyx's Dairy. Letting out a satisfied sigh, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_CLOTHING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to pass on the opportunity to receive the 
		#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
			 'Trainee Accessories'
		#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==1)
			 'Heifer Accessories'
		#ELSE
			 'Cow Accessories'
		#ENDIF
		 reward, you excitedly press the corresponding button. Immediately, a little bell rings somewhere in the distance, before a pink arcane light attached to the top of your stall starts flashing. Moments later, you hear the barn door being opened, and you turn your head to see one of the blue-skinned succubi who work in the farm's office striding towards you. As she comes to a halt beside your stall, this succubus lets out an annoyed sigh and complains, [style.speechFeminine(I don't know why Dale isn't responsible for doing this! I hate having to deal with you cows! Now stay still so I can get this over and done with!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you hold yourself still for the succubus, who
		#IF(pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_NECK)!=null)
			#IF(pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_PIERCING_NOSE)!=null)
				 hastily unequips your [pc.slotClothing(NECK, false)] and [pc.slotClothing(PIERCING_NOSE, false)], and then
			#ELSE
				 hastily unequips your [pc.slotClothing(NECK, false)], and then
			#ENDIF
		#ELSEIF(pc.getClothingInSlot(IS_PIERCING_NOSE)!=null)
			 hastily unequips your [pc.slotClothing(PIERCING_NOSE, false)], and then
		#ENDIF
		 despite complaining about having to perform this duty, can't resist taking the time to give your ass a few sharp slaps. After chuckling in amusement as you let out a startled cry, she sighs, [style.speechFeminine(It must be so easy working as a cow. If only I could bring myself to do something so degrading, my life would be so much easier...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not at all interested in anything you have to say in response to this, the succubus gets down to business,
		#IF(!pc.isPiercedNose())
			 and after producing an arcane piercing tool and quickly clipping it against your nose to painlessly pierce it, she produces your accessories and begins to equip them on you...
		#ELSE
			 and after producing your accessories she begins to equip them on you...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_CLOTHING_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[style.speechFeminine(There we go, all done,)] the succubus says as she looks over your new [pc.slotClothing(NECK, true)] and [pc.slotClothing(PIERCING_NOSE, true)]. Letting out another weary sigh, she mutters, [style.speechFeminine(I wish Evelyx would give me some more time off. I could do with growing myself a nice, fat cock and fucking you for a while... Oh well...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus turns around on the spot and swiftly departs, leaving you lying in your milking stall wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to take this opportunity to get some relief from the sexual tension built up by the machine sucking away at your nipples, you press the button corresponding to the 'Request mate' reward. Immediately, you hear a little bell ringing somewhere in the distance, but your initial excitement at the prospect of being fucked is quickly dampened as the text on the arcane machine's screen changes to read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldSex(Cow Requiring Mating)]
		<br/><b>Instructions for cow:</b>
		<br/><b>1.</b> Wait for a client to arrive.
		<br/><b>2.</b> Do not leave your stall.
		<br/><b>3.</b> Enjoy your mating.
		<br/>Failure to follow these instructions could result in termination of cow's job contract.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		With this text continuing to be displayed on the screen, you're left waiting in frustration for a good twenty minutes before you're finally given your reward. Just as you think that you can't take waiting any longer, the door to the barn finally opens, and you turn your head to see Dale leading [partner.a_fullRace(true)] towards you. Within a matter of moments, the donkey-boy is standing right behind you, and you can't help but let out an erotic [pc.moan] as he uses his fingers to spread your [pc.labia+] and show off your pussy to [partner.name]. Continuing to spread your cunt in this lewd manner, Dale asks the stranger, [dale.speech(Is [pc.she] to your liking?)]
	</p>
	#IF(partner.isMute())
		<p>
			Clearly not able to talk, [partner.name] simply gives Dale an approving nod, after which the donkey-boy lets go of your pussy and says, [dale.speech(I'll leave the two of you to it then. I'll be back once you've finished.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, Dale departs, leaving you alone with [partner.name]...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_GENTLE)
				#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
					#IF(pc.hasHymen())
						Seeing that your hymen is still intact, [partner.name] lets out a soft [partner.moan] and sighs, [partner.speech(Oh yes, [pc.sheIs] perfect. It looks like I'll be the lucky one to take [pc.her] virginity...)]
					#ELSE
						Smiling down at your [pc.pussy+], [partner.name] lets out a soft [partner.moan] and sighs, [partner.speech(Oh yes, [pc.sheIs] perfect...)]
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					Smiling down at your [pc.pussy+], [partner.name] lets out a soft [partner.moan] and sighs, 
					#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
						 [partner.speech(I like my cows pregnant, so [pc.sheIs] perfect...)]
					#ELSEIF(!partner.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
						 [partner.speech(Oh yes, [pc.sheIs] perfect. I'll try and get [pc.her] knocked up for you...)]
					#ELSE
						 [partner.speech(Oh yes, [pc.sheIs] perfect...)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ELSEIF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_ROUGH)
				#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
					#IF(pc.hasHymen())
						Seeing that your hymen is still intact, [partner.name] lets out a deep, hungry [partner.moan] and states, [partner.speech(Yeah, [pc.her] virgin cunt's going to do nicely. I'll give [pc.herHim] a good, hard pounding to make sure that [pc.she] always remembers how [pc.she] lost it...)]
					#ELSE
						Hungrily gazing down at your [pc.pussy+], [partner.name] lets out [partner.a_moan+] and states, [partner.speech(Yeah, [pc.her] cunt's going to do nicely. I'll give [pc.herHim] a good, hard pounding!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					Hungrily gazing down at your [pc.pussy+], [partner.name] lets out [partner.a_moan+] and states, 
					#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
						 [partner.speech(I like my cows pregnant, so [pc.she]'ll do nicely. I can't wait to give [pc.herHim] a good, hard pounding!)]
					#ELSEIF(!partner.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
						 [partner.speech(Yeah, [pc.her] cunt's going to do nicely. I'll give [pc.herHim] a good, hard pounding and try and get [pc.her] knocked up for you!)]
					#ELSE
						 [partner.speech(Yeah, [pc.she]'ll do nicely. I can't wait to give [pc.herHim] a good, hard pounding!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
					#IF(pc.hasHymen())
						Seeing that your hymen is still intact, [partner.name] lets out [partner.a_moan+] and exclaims, [partner.speech(Oh yeah, that virgin cunt of [pc.hers] is perfect! I can't wait to take [pc.her] virginity...)]
					#ELSE
						Smiling down at your [pc.pussy+], [partner.name] lets out [partner.a_moan+] and exclaims, [partner.speech(Oh yeah, that cunt of [pc.hers] is perfect!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					Smiling down at your [pc.pussy+], [partner.name] lets out [partner.a_moan+] and exclaims, 
					#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
						 [partner.speech(I like my cows pregnant, so [pc.sheIs] perfect!)]
					#ELSEIF(!partner.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
						 [partner.speech(Oh yes, [pc.sheIs] perfect! I'll try and get [pc.her] knocked up for you...)]
					#ELSE
						 [partner.speech(Oh yeah, [pc.sheIs] perfect!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[dale.speech(I'll leave the two of you to it then. I'll be back once you've finished,)] Dale says, before swiftly departing and leaving you alone with [partner.name]...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_SEX_START"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!partner.isMute())
		#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_ANUS, true) && partner.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
			<p>
				#IF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_GENTLE)
					[partner.speech(Your cunt's cute and all, but that's not what I'm interested in,)] [partner.name] teases, before gently sliding [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] up and down over your [pc.asshole+]. Letting out a soft [partner.moan], [partner.she] excitedly states, [partner.speech(I'm going to fuck your ass!)]
				#ELSEIF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_ROUGH)
					[partner.speech(You think I'm here to fuck your cunt, you dumb cow?)] [partner.name] cruelly teases, before roughly slapping your [pc.ass+]. Letting out a mocking laugh as a surprised cry bursts out of your mouth, [partner.she] suddenly starts forcefully rubbing her thumb up and down over your [pc.asshole+] while [partner.moaning], [partner.speech(I'm going to enjoy pounding your ass! I'm going to stuff my cock <i>deep</i> into here and turn you into my dirty little buttslut!)]
				#ELSE
					[partner.speech(Your cunt's tempting, but that's really not what I'm interested in,)] [partner.name] teases, before eagerly sliding [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] up and down over your [pc.asshole+]. Letting out an erotic [partner.moan], [partner.she] excitedly states, [partner.speech(I'm going to fuck your ass!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				#IF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_GENTLE)
					[partner.speech(Your cunt's so cute,)] [partner.name] sighs, before playfully teasing [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] up and down over your [pc.clit+]. Letting out a soft [partner.moan], [partner.she] excitedly states, [partner.speech(Let's get to it! I can't wait to find out how good your pussy's going to feel around my cock!)]
				#ELSEIF(partner.getTheoreticalSexPaceDomPreference()==SEX_PACE_DOM_ROUGH)
					[partner.speech(You've got such a lewd, filthy cunt, haven't you, you dumb cow?)] [partner.name] cruelly teases, before delivering a few sharp slaps to your exposed pussy. Letting out a mocking laugh as a surprised cry bursts out of your mouth, [partner.she] suddenly starts forcefully rubbing her thumb up and down over your [pc.clit+] while [partner.moaning], [partner.speech(I'm going to enjoy pounding your pussy! I'm going to stuff my cock <i>deep</i> into your cunt and turn you into my dirty little whore!)]
				#ELSE
					[partner.speech(Your cunt's so hot,)] [partner.name] [partner.moans], before playfully rubbing [partner.her] [partner.fingers+] up and down over your [pc.clit+]. Letting out an erotic [partner.moan], [partner.she] excitedly states, [partner.speech(Let's get to it! I can't wait to find out how good your pussy's going to feel around my cock!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_ANUS, true) && partner.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
		<p>
			Quickly taking out [partner.her] [partner.cock+], [partner.name] immediately starts rubbing the [partner.cockHead+] up and down over your [pc.asshole+], causing you to let out a lewd [pc.moan]. Taking hold of your [pc.hips+], [partner.she] wastes no further time and thrusts forwards, sinking [partner.her] [partner.cock+] into your [pc.asshole+]. With the milking machine continuing to pump away at your [pc.breasts+], [partner.name] starts energetically fucking your ass in front of the
			#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
				 trainees to either side of you...
			#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==1)
				 heifers to either side of you...
			#ELSE
				 cows to either side of you...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Quickly taking out [partner.her] [partner.cock+], [partner.name] immediately starts rubbing the [partner.cockHead+] up and down over your [pc.pussy+], causing you to let out a lewd [pc.moan]. Taking hold of your [pc.hips+], [partner.she] wastes no further time and thrusts forwards, sinking [partner.her] [partner.cock+] into your [pc.pussy+]. With the milking machine continuing to pump away at your [pc.breasts+], [partner.name] starts energetically fucking you in front of the
			#IF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==0)
				 trainees to either side of you...
			#ELSEIF(flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_work_level')==1)
				 heifers to either side of you...
			#ELSE
				 cows to either side of you...
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_COW_GIRL_PARTIAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it's time to take your job as a cow more seriously, you press the button which corresponds to the 'Lesser cow-girl transformation' reward. Immediately, a long, plastic tube drops down from the ceiling, and the text on the device's screen changes to read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldTfPartial(Lesser cow-girl transformation)]
		<br/><b>Instructions for cow:</b>
		<br/><b>1.</b> Insert transformative potion tube into mouth.
		<br/><b>2.</b> Drink every drop of the transformative potion.
		<br/><b>3.</b> Enjoy your new body.
		<br/>Failure to follow these instructions will result in automatic shut-down of this machine.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the machine's instructions, you quickly place the tube in your mouth and start to suck out the sickly-sweet potion. After greedily swallowing down every last drop, you can't help but let out a deeply erotic [pc.moan] as you feel your body start to transform. As the transformative effects begin to manifest themselves, your mind starts to spin, and you dip in and out of conciousness as your body undergoes some radical transformations to turn you into a lesser cow-girl...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_COW_GIRL_PARTIAL_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A few minutes later, and your whizzing head starts to settle down. Regaining full control of your body, you both see and feel that most of your body has transformed to be human, but that you now have cow-like ears, eyes, and hair, along with a cow-like tail and a pair of horns. Letting out a deep sigh that comes out sounding a little like a 'moo', you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_COW_GIRL_GREATER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it's time to take your job as a cow very seriously, you press the button which corresponds to the 'Greater cow-girl transformation' reward. Immediately, a long, plastic tube drops down from the ceiling, and the text on the device's screen changes to read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldTfGreater(Greater cow-girl transformation)]
		<br/><b>Instructions for cow:</b>
		<br/><b>1.</b> Insert transformative potion tube into mouth.
		<br/><b>2.</b> Drink every drop of the transformative potion.
		<br/><b>3.</b> Enjoy your new body.
		<br/>Failure to follow these instructions will result in automatic shut-down of this machine.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the machine's instructions, you quickly place the tube in your mouth and start to suck out the sickly-sweet potion. After greedily swallowing down every last drop, you can't help but let out a deeply erotic [pc.moan] as you feel your body start to transform. As the transformative effects begin to manifest themselves, your mind starts to spin, and you dip in and out of conciousness as your body undergoes some radical transformations to turn you into a greater cow-girl...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_COW_GIRL_GREATER_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A few minutes later, and your whizzing head starts to settle down. Regaining full control of your body, you both see and feel that all of your body has transformed to be cow-like in nature, and you now also have a cow-like tail and a pair of horns. Letting out a deep sigh that comes out sounding a little like a 'moo', you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_COWTAURESS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it's time to fully commit to your job as a cow, you press the button which corresponds to the 'Cowtaur' reward. Immediately, a long, plastic tube drops down from the ceiling, and the text on the device's screen changes to read:
	</p>
	<p style='text-align:center;'>
		<i>
		[style.boldTfGreater(Cowtaur)]
		<br/><b>Instructions for cow:</b>
		<br/><b>1.</b> Insert transformative potion tube into mouth.
		<br/><b>2.</b> Drink every drop of the transformative potion.
		<br/><b>3.</b> Enjoy your new body.
		<br/>Failure to follow these instructions will result in automatic shut-down of this machine.
		</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the machine's instructions, you quickly place the tube in your mouth and start to suck out the sickly-sweet potion. After greedily swallowing down every last drop, you can't help but let out a deeply erotic [pc.moan] as you feel your body start to transform. As the transformative effects begin to manifest themselves, your mind starts to spin, and you dip in and out of conciousness as your body undergoes some radical transformations to turn your lower body into that of a feral cow...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_COWTAURESS_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With the transformation coming to an end, you take a few minutes to test out the movement capabilities of your new body. Your lower half from the waist down is identical in form to that of a feral cow's body, and as you reposition yourself to get comfortable in your miking stall, you can't help but let out a deep sigh, which ends up coming out sounding a little like a 'moo'. Biting your lip, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_REWARD_TATTOO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Really wanting to show your commitment to this job, you press the button which corresponds to the 'Tattoo' reward. Immediately, you hear a little bell ring somewhere in the distance, before a blue arcane light attached to the top of your stall starts flashing. Moments later, you hear the barn door being opened, and you turn your head to see one of the blue-skinned succubi who work in the farm's office striding towards you. As she comes to a halt beside your stall, this succubus lets out an annoyed sigh and complains, [style.speechFeminine(Evelyx should really train Dale to handle this! I really hate having to spend time around you cows! Now stay still so I can get this over and done with!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you hold still as the succubus gains access to your ass, before using the arcane tattoo gun she brought with her to start applying the tattoo to your rear end. The sensation of being tattooed isn't painful, but it still stings a little, and you find yourself letting out a few whines as the succubus carries out her work. Thankfully, the whole process only takes a few minutes, and as she turns the arcane tattoo gun off, the succubus smirks down at her handiwork and teases, [style.speechFeminine(I can't believe that you cows voluntarily ask for this treatment. With your ID number permanently tattooed onto your ass, you look like you're nothing more than our property! Here, take a look, you dumb cow. This is what it looks like.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus holds up a little mirror, allowing you to look down at the tattoo that's just been applied to your [pc.ass+]. Written in black ink, you see that it reads 'Evelyx's Dairy Milker #[#~~flags.getSavedLong('evelyx_player_number')]', and you find yourself letting out a happy little [pc.moan] as you realise that what the succubus said is true, and that you do look like nothing more than property of Evelyx's Dairy. Upon hearing your reaction, the succubus lets out a short laugh in disbelief, before suddenly groping your
		#IF(pc.hasVagina())
			 exposed pussy
		#ELSE
			 ass
		#ENDIF
		 and sighing, [style.speechFeminine(If only Evelyx gave us time off work, I'd give you a real good, hard fuck right now, you dirty little cow... Oh well...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the succubus turns around on the spot and swiftly departs, leaving you lying in your milking stall wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had enough, [partner.name] pulls back, before slapping [partner.her] softening [partner.cock] against your [pc.pussy+] and teasing, [partner.speech(You were a good fuck, cow...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Whether from being informed by some kind of arcane device, or simply from his intuition, Dale chooses this moment to make his return. As [partner.name] cleans [partner.her] cock off by wiping it over your ass, the door to the barn opens, and the donkey-boy receptionist swiftly makes his way over to your stall, before addressing your partner, [dale.speech(I hope all was to your satisfaction. If you've finished with this cow, I can escort you back to reception now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After taking a moment to give your cunt one last grope, [partner.name] falls in beside Dale and exits the barn, leaving you panting and moaning
		#IF(sex.getSexTypeCount(partner, pc, sex.newSexType(PENETRATION_PENIS, ORIFICE_ANUS))>0)
			#IF(pc.getTotalFluidInArea(ORIFICE_ANUS)>0)
				 as you feel cum drooling out of your well-fucked asshole...
			#ELSE
				 as you feel your well-fucked asshole continuing to quiver and contract...
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(pc.getTotalFluidInArea(ORIFICE_VAGINA)>0)
				 as you feel cum drooling out of your well-fucked pussy...
			#ELSE
				 as you feel your well-fucked pussy continuing to quiver and contract...
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_WORK_AFTER_SEX_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With [partner.name] and Dale having left the barn, you take a few minutes to calm down, before wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Slave barn: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_SLAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stalls lining the sides of this huge barn. Dozens of cow-tauress slaves happily having their breast and udder milk pumped out.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BARN_SLAVE_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Locked door prevents you from escaping the Slave Barn...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- Auction: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUCTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Luxurious seating surrounds a central stage, upon which willing slaves are auctioned off to the highest bidder...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
</dialogue>