<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- ROXY_FACE_SITTING_ORGASM  -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ROXY_FACE_SITTING_ORGASM_ALREADY_ADDICTED"><![CDATA[
		Roxy's moans start to increase in volume, and without warning, she suddenly reaches down to grab hold of your head, before letting her legs collapse out from under her. Your mouth is completely smothered by her [roxy.pussy+], and as you let out a muffled cry of surprise, the rat-girl screams, [roxy.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes! Get yer fuckin' tongue in deep! ~Mmm!~ Yes!)]
	<br/><br/>
		Doing as she commands, you drive your tongue deep into the rat-girl's [roxy.pussy+], before eagerly starting to eat her out, desperate for another dose of her addictive girlcum. Your enthusiastic response causes Roxy to suddenly clamp her thighs down around your head, and you feel her [roxy.pussy] quivering and squeezing down around your tongue as she reaches her orgasm. [roxy.speechNoEffects(Fuck! ~Aah!~ Fuck! Yes! ~Aaah!~)]
	<br/><br/>
		As Roxy screams, a huge spurt of female ejaculate squirts out from [roxy.her] [roxy.pussy+], directly into your open mouth. [roxy.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~)] the rat-girl screams, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Fuckin' drink it down! ~Mmm!~ Yes!)]
	<br/><br/>
		Not needing to be told twice, you hungrily gulp down Roxy's addictive juices, thrusting your tongue up into her [roxy.pussy+] to try and get as much of it into your mouth as possible. As her slimy girlcum slides down your throat, the desperate craving starts to creep into your mind once more, and, reaching up to grab Roxy's thighs, you pull her down onto your face. As you start to hungrily lick up as much of the rat-girl's juices as you possibly can, she starts to come down from her climax, and, continuing to sit on your face, she starts to laugh, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh! That's right, lick it all up! Tastes good, don't it?)]
	<br/><br/>
		[pc.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ ~Mmmm!~)] you reply, your words muffled into the rat-girl's [roxy.pussy+].
	<br/><br/>
		[roxy.speechNoEffects(Fuck, it's fuckin' good to have me own personal pussy licker. Yer just can't get enough o' my sweet fuckin' cunt, can yer?)]
	<br/><br/>
		You can't help but let out a desperate, muffled moan into Roxy's [roxy.pussy] as you continue hungrily licking up as much of her girlcum as you possibly can.
	<br/><br/>
		[roxy.speechNoEffects(I think that'll do fer now,)] Roxy laughs, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Yer can always come back an' pay me a thousand flames if yer want some more.)]
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ROXY_FACE_SITTING_ORGASM_NEW_ADDICTION"><![CDATA[
		Roxy's moans start to increase in volume, and without warning, she suddenly reaches down to grab hold of your head, before letting her legs collapse out from under her. Your mouth is completely smothered by her [roxy.pussy+], and as you let out a muffled cry of surprise, the rat-girl screams, [roxy.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Yes! Get yer fuckin' tongue in deep! ~Mmm!~ Yes!)]
	<br/><br/>
		Doing as she commands, you drive your tongue deep into the rat-girl's [roxy.pussy+], before desperately starting to eat her out. Your enthusiastic response causes Roxy to suddenly clamp her thighs down around your head, and you feel her [roxy.pussy] quivering and squeezing down around your tongue as she reaches her orgasm. [roxy.speechNoEffects(Fuck! ~Aah!~ Fuck! Yes! ~Aaah!~)]
	<br/><br/>
		As Roxy screams, a huge spurt of female ejaculate squirts out from [roxy.her] [roxy.pussy+], directly into your open mouth. [roxy.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~)] the rat-girl screams, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Fuckin' drink it down! ~Mmm!~ Yes!)]
	<br/><br/>
		With little option but to do as she says, you gulp down Roxy's juices, before continuing to thrust your tongue up into her [roxy.pussy+]. As her slimy girlcum slides down your throat, you suddenly find yourself with a desperate craving for more, and, reaching up to grab Roxy's thighs, you pull her down onto your face. As you start to hungrily lick up as much of the rat-girl's juices as you possibly can, she starts to come down from her climax, and, continuing to sit on your face, she starts to laugh, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh! That's right, lick it all up! Tastes good, don't it?)]
	<br/><br/>
		[pc.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ ~Mmmm!~)] you reply, your words muffled into the rat-girl's [roxy.pussy+].
	<br/><br/>
		[roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh! Probably a bit late now, but I should let yer know sumthin. I went and bought one o' those special potions from some bitch up in Dominion. 'Makes yer girlcum real fuckin' addictive,' she said. 'Just get some cunt to eat yer out, and they'll be beggin' to be yer permanent pussy licker,' she said. From the way yer actin', it's lookin' like she was tellin' the truth!)]
	<br/><br/>
		You can't help but let out a desperate, muffled moan into Roxy's [roxy.pussy] as she reveals this. The addictive nature of her girlcum is already having a profound effect on your mind, and even as she reveals the fact that you've been tricked into drinking her addictive juices, you can't help but continue hungrily licking and kissing her pussy.
	<br/><br/>
		[roxy.speechNoEffects(Fuckin' looks like you're well an' truly addicted to my cunt now, ain't yer?)] Roxy laughs, [roxy.speechNoEffects(That's enough fer me.)]
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BLOW_SMOKE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BLOW_SMOKE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!npc.hasStatusEffect(SE_SMOKING))
		Leaning over to one side, and allowing the full weight of her body to drop down onto your face, Roxy grabs a cigarette from under the counter, before putting the end in her mouth and taking a deep drag on it. Looking down at you, the rat-girl unintentionally ends up blowing smoke all over your face as she laughs, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh-heh-heh! Yer doin' a decent job, just make sure ta get yer tongue in nice an' deep!)]
	#ELSE
		Taking a deep drag on her cigarette, Roxy looks down at you and unintentionally ends up blowing smoke all over your face as she laughs, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh-heh-heh! Yer doin' a decent job, just make sure ta get yer tongue in nice an' deep!)]
	#ENDIF
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="BLOW_SMOKE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!npc.hasStatusEffect(SE_SMOKING))
		Letting out an annoyed tut, Roxy turns to one side, before reaching over beneath the counter, grabbing a cigarette, and desperately putting the end in her mouth. After deeply inhaling on the cigarette, the rat-girl looks down at you and lets out a cackling laugh, unintentionally blowing the smoke all over your face in the process, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh-heh-heh! That's it! Keep on gettin' yer tongue deep in my sweet little cunt!)]
	#ELSE
		Inhaling deeply on her cigarette, Roxy looks down at you and lets out a cackling laugh, unintentionally blowing the smoke all over your face in the process, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh-heh-heh! That's it! Keep on gettin' yer tongue deep in my sweet little cunt!)]
	#ENDIF
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="BLOW_SMOKE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(!npc.hasStatusEffect(SE_SMOKING))
		Not being able to cope for too long without a cigarette in her mouth, Roxy reaches over and grabs one from beneath the counter, before putting it in her mouth and taking a deep drag on it. Looking down at you, she ends up blowing the smoke all over your face as she lets out yet another of her abrasive, cackling laughs, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh-heh-heh! Bet yer never tasted a pussy as sweet as mine, eh?!)]
	#ELSE
		Taking a deep drag on the cigarette still in her mouth, Roxy looks down at you and lets out yet another of her abrasive, cackling laughs, blowing the smoke all over your face in the process, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh-heh-heh! Bet yer never tasted a pussy as sweet as mine, eh?!)]
	#ENDIF
	]]></htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- FACE_SITTING_TEASE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_TEASE_START"><![CDATA[
	Letting out a short burst of her annoying, cackling laughter, Roxy grinds her [roxy.pussy+] down against your mouth, before teasing, 
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_TEASE_START"><![CDATA[
	Happily grinding her [roxy.pussy+] up and down over your mouth, the one-eyed rat-girl lets out another of her abrasive laughs and teases, 
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_TEASE_START"><![CDATA[
	Shifting her hips, Roxy rubs her [roxy.pussy+] all over your [pc.face], before moving it back down and planting it firmly over your mouth. Letting out a high-pitched, abrasive laugh, she teases, 
	]]></htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_TEASE_END"><![CDATA[
	[roxy.speechNoEffects(Go on, yer tongue can get deeper than that!)]
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_TEASE_END"><![CDATA[
	[roxy.speechNoEffects(Yer love the taste o' my hot little puss, don't yer?)]
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_TEASE_END"><![CDATA[
	[roxy.speechNoEffects(Keep on drinkin' all them sweet juices o' mine!)]
	]]></htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_ADDICTION_TEASE_START"><![CDATA[
	Grinding her [roxy.pussy+] down against your mouth, Roxy then suddenly lifts her hips, depriving you of the source of her delicious girlcum. Being addicted to the taste of her pussy, you can't stop yourself from desperately lifting your head and licking at her [roxy.pussy+]. This turns out to be exactly what the rat-girl wanted, as she slams her wet cunt back down onto your face and laughs, 
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_ADDICTION_TEASE_START"><![CDATA[
	Rubbing her wet pussy back and forth over your [pc.lips], Roxy suddenly lifts her hips a little, forcing you to crane your neck in order to keep on licking and lapping at her delicious girlcum. Seeing that you're hopelessly addicted to her juices, the rat-girl lets out another of her abrasive laughs, and teases, 
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_ADDICTION_TEASE_START"><![CDATA[
	Letting her legs splay out to either side, Roxy drops the full weight of her body onto your face, causing her pussy to squelch down against your mouth. As she feels you desperately licking up every last drop of her girlcum, she lets out an abrasive laugh and teases, 
	]]></htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_ADDICTION_TEASE_END"><![CDATA[
	[roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh-heh-heh! That's it! Yer can't get enough o' me yummy cunt, can yer? Keep on lickin' it then like an 'ungry dog!)]
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_ADDICTION_TEASE_END"><![CDATA[
	[roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh-heh-heh! That's it! Keep on lickin'; we wouldn't want yer goin' away from this without bein' 'opelessly addicted to me sweet little puss, would we?!)]
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="FACE_SITTING_ADDICTION_TEASE_END"><![CDATA[
	[roxy.speechNoEffects(Heh-heh-heh! Go on, keep on lickin' me yummy little puss just like that! Show me 'ow desperate fer me cunt ya are!)]
	]]></htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- CUSTOMER_INTERRUPTION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CUSTOMER_INTERRUPTION"><![CDATA[
	Roxy suddenly looks across over the counter, before planting her [roxy.pussy+] firmly down over your face and angrily shouting at what must be a customer who's just entered the store, [roxy.speechNoEffects(What yer doin', yer fuckin' cunt? Don't be pickin' shit up that yer ain't gonna buy! Oh, runnin' off, are yer?! Good! Don't fuckin' come back!)]
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="CUSTOMER_INTERRUPTION"><![CDATA[
	Obviously having seen someone enter the store out of the corner of her eye, Roxy plants her [roxy.pussy+] down over your face and shouts out, [roxy.speechNoEffects(This ain't a meetin' place fer gormless twats! If yer ain't buyin' anythin', then you three can fuck off right now! Yeah, that's what I thought!)]
	]]></htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="CUSTOMER_INTERRUPTION"><![CDATA[
	Having caught sight of someone entering her store, Roxy plants her [roxy.pussy+] down over your mouth and turns to shout, [roxy.speechNoEffects(Yer gonna just stand there like some fuckin' stupid twat, or yer gonna buy somethin'? Oh, just gonna run off instead, are yer? Don't bother comin' back, yer daft cunt!)]
	]]></htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
