<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

    <!-- Shady dealer encounter: -->

    <htmlContent tag="INTRO"><![CDATA[
   	<p>
		You find yourself walking through labyrinthine alleyways, with not a soul in sight. Back-doors and steaming vents line the dark brick walls, and you often have to navigate around overflowing bins and stacks of empty crates in order to make progress.<br/><br/>
	#IF(flags.hasSavedLong('AceXpShadyDealer'))
		Once again you hear a voice coming from behind one of those stacks of crates.<br/>
		[style.speechAndrogynous(Hey, we meet again. Do you want to make a deal?)]<br/><br/>
		Knowing that you have once again come across that shady dealer, you take a moment to decide what to do.
	#ELSE
	    Suddenly you hear a voice coming from behind one of those stacks of crates.<br/>
	    [style.speechAndrogynous(Psst! You, yes you! Are you up for the bargain of your life?)]<br/><br/>
	    Unsure of who is talking to you, and not knowing what to make of this, you take a moment to decide what to do.
	#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
    </htmlContent>

    <htmlContent tag="TRADE"><![CDATA[
   	<p>
	#IF(flags.hasSavedLong('AceXpShadyDealer'))
	    Approaching the stack of crates, you see the shady dealer once again.<br/><br/>
	    Quickly looking you up and down they say: [style.speechAndrogynous(You know the drill, don't ya. Only the best wares, for bargain prices! But make it quick, I don't want any more trouble with the Enforcers than I already have!)]<br/><br/>
	#ELSE
		Carefully approaching the stack of crates, you see the person addressing you. They have a quite androgynous look, and are mostly clad in dark clothes. Casting a quick glance left and right to check if anyone else is around they start what is probably a well rehearsed sales pitch:<br/>
		[style.speechAndrogynous(I have only the best wares, you won't find anything like this anywhere else, I guarantee you! All for a price of course! Oh, and if you happen to have come across some interesting items, just show 'em! I might take them off your hands. Can't offer much though, you know, money being tight.)]<br/><br/>
	#ENDIF
	    You take a moment to consider if you should make a deal with this shady trader.
	</p>
	]]>
    </htmlContent>

</dialogue>
