<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_MENU"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QuestLine.SIDE_EISEK_MOB) && flags.hasFlag(FLAG_dsg_elis_eisek_mob_quest_persuade) && !flags.hasFlag(FLAG_dsg_elis_eisek_talk_post_mob_quest))
		<p>
			As you approach the stall, you notice a sheep-girl speaking with Eisek. A pang of adrenaline rushes through you as you recognise her from the same mob that had been trying to drive him out. Fearing the worst, you quicken your pace, but she leaves before you can do or say anything.
		</p>
		<p>
			Catching sight of you, a smile grows across Eisek's face. [eisek.speech(Greetings, [pc.name],)] he says, [eisek.speech(The strangest thing happened just before you got here. Some members of that mob stopped by and...actually apologised to me. I assume you had something to do with that.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eisek chuckles when you mention that you didn't expect any of them to actually return. [eisek.speech(So, what can I do for my favourite doer of good deeds?)]
		</p>
		[##flags.setFlag(FLAG_dsg_elis_eisek_talk_post_mob_quest, true)]
	#ELSEIF(eisek.getAffection(pc) >= 15)
		<p>
			Catching sight of you as you approach, a smile grows across Eisek's face as he greets you. [eisek.speech(Ah, and what can I do for my favourite customer?)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(eisek.getAffection(pc) >= 30)
		<p>
			Catching sight of you as you approach, a broad smile grows across Eisek's face as he greets you and you catch a glimpse of his tail twitching involuntarily as he greets you. [eisek.speech(My favourite customer? The day is brighter already.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Catching sight of you as you approach, a faint smile creeps across Eisek's face. [eisek.speech(Greetings, [pc.name],)] he says, [eisek.speech(What can I do for you?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- TALK_DRAGONFALL_SPECIFIC -->
	<!-- TODO: Break up this wall of text -->
	<!-- lol, jk, it got longer -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_DRAGONFALL_SPECIFIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A puff of steam leaves Eisek's nostrils as you broach the subject again. He closes his eyes for a moment, thinking, before finally giving his response.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Alright,)] he says, somewhat dejectedly, [eisek.speech(I suppose you have already heard something of it from that mob. There's no harm in telling you the truth of the matter.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(We dragons were not always as we are now, a scattered and isolated people wringing our survival from the land. Once, the dragons of old were proud servants of Lisophia. For her Glistering Hoard they performed all sorts of brute tasks, extorted the peasants on her land, plundered countless villages, and in return she not only made them strongest creatures in the land but also let them keep their own hoards. They were proud of their lot in life, so proud that they could not see the winds of change blowing.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Lisophia's greed knew no bounds, and after a time she decided she no longer wished to share. She demanded that the dragons of old surrender all of the treasure they had kept. Of course, this angered them, they fought back, and for that Lisophia's retribution was swift and terrible. My ancestors said very little about what happened and wrote down even less, so great was their shame, but I know that at the end of a great battle almost all the dragons of old were left with only a fraction of their former strength. What Lisopha gave she could just as easily take away, you see.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(No longer afraid, mortal society rejected them for the crimes they committed in Lisophia's service, and the Lilin hated them for their arrogance. They and their children down the generations were forced to become outcasts. That is the Dragonfall. A millennia-long punishment for the hubris of my forefathers and why those who know about it wish for us to remain outcasts.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After a long silence, Eisek regains lets long sigh accompanied with another cloud of steam. [eisek.speech(I...do not wish to talk about this any further. Let us change the subject.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- TALK_HIMSELF -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_HIMSELF"><![CDATA[
	#IF(eisek.getAffection(pc) >= 15)
		<p>
			Having earned his trust, the [eisek.race] opens up a little. [eisek.speech(I come from Cimryth's Crag, a rocky little valley high in the mountains far to the west of here. My family has farmed there for a hundred years.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Expressing surprise that his farm is in the mountains, you ask Eisek how he can grow anything up there and how he can carry enough to sell all the way down. Trying not to sound too proud, he explains [eisek.speech(Cimryth chose well when she decided where to settle my ancestors. Heat rises from the earth there, and ice never touches the ground. She brought soil from the foothills with her, and the greenhouses she designed took care of the rest. It is for this reason the Crag is named after her, and it is my honour to carry on in her tradition.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eisek flexes his wings slightly before continuing, [eisek.speech(It is easy enough to carry my weight in goods on a downward glide from the Crag, and the thermals on the way back are strong.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			From the sounds of things, the [eisek.race] is doing much or even all of this on his own. When you ask him if he's got anyone helping him, his face darkens. [eisek.speech(I do not,) he answers tersely. You decide not to pry further.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Eisek opens his mouth to respond, but shuts it again just as quickly. A brief look of hesitation flashes across his face before he answers your question. [eisek.speech(My product comes from the mountains,)] he says carefully, [eisek.speech(On the first day of each month I bring it here and on the third day I leave.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			When you ask how he can grow anything in the mountains, his answer is only a cryptic [eisek.speech(There are ways.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			From the way he dodged your questions he evidently doesn't trust you enough yet.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- TALK_BUSINESS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_BUSINESS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_EISEK_SIDE_MOB))
		#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_EISEK_SIDE_STALL))
			<p>
				His eyes light up at the question. [eisek.speech(I cannot thank you enough, [pc.name]. With this new stall I am on equal footing with the other merchants, and since you drove away that crowd of hooligans I can actually focus on running it. Sales have really started to pick up and I have seen many new customers.)] He studies you intently for a brief instant before continuing with a warm smile. [eisek.speech(Do not worry, you will always be my favourite.)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				eisek.speech(You have done me a great service in convincing that mob of the truth,)] he says, trying not to sound too excited, [eisek.speech(without them to frighten away customers, I have been selling through my stock on some days.)] He scratches his chin in thought before flashing you a cheeky grin. [eisek.speech(Though, you still talk the most.)]
			</p>		
	#ELSE
		<p>
			He ponders your question for a moment, looking off into the distance, before answering [eisek.speech(Well enough, I suppose. I never planned to succeed through volume. Although...) the [eisek.race] pauses as he surveys the other stalls up and down the avenue. [eisek.speech(My stall could use some work. There is nothing I can do about the size, I need to fly with it...although I would not mind an awning for some shade. It is definitely not as eye-catching compared with the others. If only I could get some better fabric and a better sign...hmm, but I cannot leave my stall undefended with that mob out there. I would come back to it in ruins for sure.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As if suddenly aware that he's been thinking aloud, he snaps out of his trance and looks back at you, doing his best to hide his embarrassment. [eisek.speech(Ah, but I am sure you that did not come to hear me ramble. I am fortunate that not all of the locals are thick-skulled. They are not talkative like you, but they buy what I have to sell, and that is good enough for me.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- TALK_FAMILY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_FAMILY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You ask Eisek about the family he mentioned. The question seems to hit him off-balance and he initially pretends that he didn't hear it as his expression darkens. When he finally does respond, he stares at the counter and says only [eisek.speech(I do not wish to talk about that,)] in a barely audible whisper.
	</p>
	<p>
		Probably not a good idea to push further.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- TALK_WHY_ELIS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_WHY_ELIS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		
		#IF(pc.isAdvancedRaceKnowledgeDiscovered(SUBSPECIES_dsg_dragon))
			 From what you read about dragons
		#ELSE
			 From what you know about dragon stereotypes
		#ENDIF
		, they dislike strangers. How did Eisek come to run a stall in a town full of them, especially when some of them are so hostile?
	</p>
	<p>
		The [eisek.race] lets out a rumbling chuckle. [eisek.speech(Ah yes, ironic, isn't it? Well as much as we dragons value our solitude, there are some things we must rely on traders for. About three years ago, they stopped coming to the Crag and after a bad storm smashed up a few greenhouses last winter I had little other choice.)] He pauses for a moment, looking you over with a small smile before continuing, [eisek.speech(Thanks to you, my little gamble on civilisation has worked out better than I could have hoped for.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- TALK_OTHER_DRAGONS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_OTHER_DRAGONS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Met? Only one. A family friend of sorts hailing from the desert. She was a skilled glassfromer who once helped me repair a greenhouse. We have not spoken in...a long time,)], he replies, looking slightly misty-eyed at the recall of some private memory, [eisek.speech(As for others, I only know about the existence of others from the sight of their fields in bloom during the day or the glow of the their kilns during the night. They were not so desperate as I was to make contact with strangers, however, and you would be wise to leave them alone should you encounter them in the wilds.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- VENDOR -->
	<!-- TODO: Check if this is even necessary -->
	<htmlContent tag="VENDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(The cream of the crop. You will not find better in the whole of this market.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- TALK_ASK_ABOUT_MOB -->
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_ASK_ABOUT_MOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Something about the crowd you dispersed when you first met Eisek bothers you. They seemed rather organized for a random bunch of thugs, and to their credit, they did at least leave without a fight. What did they hope to gain by driving him out?
	</p>
	<p>
		Eisek meets your question with a steaming snort. 
		#IF (flags.hasFlag(FLAG_dsg_elis_eisek_asked_about_mob))
			 [eisek.speech(As I said before, the first one showed up maybe three months ago. I ignored him and he came back with friends. The Enforcers came two or three times, but harassment is hardly a serious crime. The ones that got arrested would be absent for the next day or so, but they'd always come back, none the worse for wear. They were a nuisance more than anything and I was mostly concerned that they were scaring away customers. Well, that was before their friends came back with more friends...)]
		#ELSE
			 [eisek.speech(Oh them. The first one showed up maybe three months ago. I ignored him and he came back with friends. The Enforcers came two or three times, but harassment is hardly a serious crime. The ones that got arrested would be absent for the next day or so, but they'd always come back, none the worse for wear. They were a nuisance more than anything and I was mostly concerned that they were scaring away customers. Well, that was before their friends came back with more friends...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		As he trails off, you get the impression that the [eisek.race] is avoiding your question
		#IF (flags.hasFlag(FLAG_dsg_elis_eisek_asked_about_mob))
		 again
		#ENDIF
		 . Eisek leans against the counter when you try to steer the conversation back to the crowd's motivation. [eisek.speech(You heard them as well as I did. They think that I am like the dragons of old, from before the Dragonfall,)] he says quietly.
	</p>
	<p>
		You're not really sure what the "dragons of old" really means or what a "Dragonfall" is. Do you press him for more information, focus on the matter at hand, or drop the subject entirely?
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- TALK_DRAGONFALL_VAGUE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_DRAGONFALL_VAGUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		When you ask Eisek what he means by "dragons of old", he dodges your gaze. [eisek.speech(My ancestors did things to their ancestors. Things I am not proud of,)] he answers, as quietly as before.
	</p>
	<p>
		He's obviously hiding something but it's unlikely you'll get any more out of him without earning his trust.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- MOB_QUEST_START -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MOB_QUEST_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From the sound of things, it is the mob will return sooner or later and you're not sure a verbal telling off will be enough next time. They did appear to be common townsfolk, however, and a search around town could reveal more about them. You tell Eisek as much.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(So, if you find them, what will you do?)] he asks, trying to hide his concern, [eisek.speech(If you harm them for my sake, you will have proven their point.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You reassure the [eisek.race] that <i>when</i> you find them, it need not come to that. There may yet be other options. Although your words do not seem to have much effect, Eisek grudgingly agrees.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Very well...)] he pauses and looks down at the counter as if thinking of what to say next, [eisek.speech(But please be careful. I will await news of your...success.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- MOB_QUEST_COMPLETE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_MOB_QUEST_COMPLETE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(flags.hasFlag(elis_eisek_mob_quest_persuade))
		<p>
			You tell Eisek that the mob won't be returning but he doesn't look convinced.
		</p>
		<p>
			[eisek.speech(Is that so? And how did you manage such a feat?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You explain that since you'd learned so much about him, you were able to persuade the townsfolk into listening to the truth: that Eisek wasn't anything like his ancestors.
		</p>
		<p>
			The [eisek.race]'s eyes widen slightly in surprise. He speaks haltingly, each word carefully chosen, [eisek.speech(I admit, I did not think you actually cared. Forgive me for doubting you.)] He then reaches under the counter and retrieves something. [eisek.speech(I have little in the way of rewarding you but perhaps these will do,)] he says as he places three bright yellow fruit covered in green, scale-like leaves on the counter, [eisek.speech(My orchards can produce very few of these now, but if you would like to...empathize with my kind further, they will help you. If you require more, I can keep some on hand, just for you.)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(elis_eisek_mob_quest_intimidate))
		<p>
			You tell Eisek that the mob won't be returning but he doesn't look convinced.
		</p>
		<p>
			[eisek.speech(Is that so? And how did you manage such a feat?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You explain that you beat up the mob's strongest member in front of them and threatened the rest with a good thrashing.
		</p>
		<p>
			The [eisek.race]'s eyes narrow slightly. [eisek.speech(So...you convinced them that I was not in fact a violent beast with feats of violence?)] he asks rhetorically. After pondering this for a moment, he continues flatly [eisek.speech(It seems I have misjudged the ways of civilized folk. Forgive me. I do not mean to sound ungrateful. For your trouble.)] And with that, he places a small sack of flames on the counter.
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(elis_eisek_mob_quest_intimidate_arcane))
		<p>
			You tell Eisek that the mob won't be returning but he doesn't look convinced.
		</p>
		<p>
			[eisek.speech(Is that so? And how did you manage such a feat?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You explain that you demonstrated your arcane prowess and defeated the mob's strongest member. That was enough to cow the townsfolk.
		</p>
		<p>
			The [eisek.race]'s eyes narrow slightly. [eisek.speech(So...you convinced them that I was not in fact a violent beast with feats of arcane violence?)] he asks rhetorically. After pondering this for a moment, he continues flatly [eisek.speech(It seems I have misjudged the ways of civilized folk. Forgive me. I do not mean to sound ungrateful. For your trouble.)] And with that, he places a small sack of flames on the counter.
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(flags.hasFlag(elis_eisek_mob_quest_failed))
		<p>
			You tell Eisek apologetically that you weren't able to convince the mob to leave him alone. A look of concern crosses his face. [eisek.race(Were you...harmed?)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			The [eisek.race] relaxes slightly when you tell him your pride was more wounded than anything else. A small wisp of steam escapes from one side of his mouth on his otherwise stony face. [eisek.speech(I see,)] he says simply, [eisek.speech(Regardless, you have my thanks for trying.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- LEAVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	#IF(eisek.getAffection(pc) >= 30)
		<p>
			The [eisek.race] tilts his head slightly as you bid him farewell. [eisek.speech(Leaving so soon? As you wish. I hope it will not be long before you visit again, I enjoy your company.)]
		</p
	#ELSEIF(eisek.getAffection(pc) >= 15)
		<p>
			The [eisek.race] closes his eyes and nods his head slightly as you bid him farewell. [eisek.speech(Thank you for stopping by,)] he says, before quickly adding [eisek.speech(Please come visit again.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			The [eisek.race] closes his eyes and nods his head slightly as you bid him farewell. [eisek.speech(Thank you for stopping by.)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- STALL_QUEST_START -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STALL_QUEST_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking back to what Eisek accidentally let slip about improvements to his stall, you ask him what he'd like on a sign representing his business. The [eisek.race] tilts his head slightly at you. [eisek.speech(...Why do you ask? The details of an object out of my grasp matter little.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You evade his suspicion and reframe the question as wanting to know what qualities his goods posses that are so important that he'd put them on a sign if he had one, hypothetically. [eisek.speech(Hmm...)] he rumbles, leaning forward slightly on the counter, [eisek.speech(They are brought down from the mountains, yes, from the clear air. And I keep them cold while I am here, they stay fresh that way.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		While his guard is still down, you slip in another question about his favourite colour to which he responds [eisek.speech(Orange. Is there...an aim behind this?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You don't bother trying to worm your way out with a grand explanation and admit to only being curious. With this new information, it seems you have some shopping to do. Perhaps there's a store in town that deals in fabric?
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- STALL_QUEST_COMPLETE -->
	<!-- Add variants for different PC personalities and body types-->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STALL_QUEST_COMPLETE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Eisek's eyes widen as his gaze catches the materials you have triumphantly brought back.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(So that strange line of questions earlier was for this?)] he asks as you set down the bolts of cloth and wooden poles down on the counter. His tone is reserved, but the way his tail twitches when he examines the new sign gives away his excitement.
	</p>
	<p>
		With your objective within sight, you come clean. Yes, those strange questions about signs and favourite colours were about getting him the improvements to his stall that he wanted, and there is nothing he can do to stop them now.
	</p>
	<p>
		The next half hour is spent helping Eisek put up the awning and replace the fabric and signage covering the counter. When the two of you are done, the transformation is total and the stall stands on equal footing with all of its neighbours.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(Why did you do all this for me?)] Eisek asks, in a much quieter voice than usual.
	</p>
	<p>
		You tell him simply that after everything that's happened, he deserves to win for once. Not to just avoid losing, to win. The [eisek.race] is silent, speechless for a few long minutes before he presses a hefty pouch-full of flames into one of your hands and grips the other in a firm handshake.
	</p>
	<p>
		[eisek.speech(I am glad that I chose to come to this town. I met you in it. You have my sincerest thanks, [pc.name].)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
