<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_CANAL_REPEAT_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that [npc.name(a)] is prowling around this area, you make sure to stay on high alert as you wander down the track that runs alongside Dominion's canal. Just as you suspected, as you cautiously pass a collection of leafy bushes growing on one side of the path, a shadowy figure leaps out, blocking your path.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_REPEAT_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that [npc.name(a)] is prowling around this area, you make sure to stay on high alert, carefully checking each and every dark corner and recess as you walk through the twisting passages. Just as you suspected, as you cautiously pass an inset doorway, a shadowy figure leaps out, blocking your path.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_REPEAT_PREGNANCY_REVEAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You instantly recognise the [npc.fullRace(true)], and you instinctively jump back into a fighting stance as you expect this encounter to be much the same as the last one. As [npc.she] steps out from the shadows, however, you notice that there's definitely something different about [npc.herHim] this time. The consequence of ejaculating inside of [npc.herHim] is staring you right in the face, and you gulp as you see [npc.herHim] pointing down at her pregnant belly.
	</p>
	#IF npc.hasFetish(FETISH_PREGNANCY)
	#THEN
		<p>
			[npc.speech(That's right, you got me knocked up!)] she shouts, the excitement in [npc.her] voice clearly giving away the fact that [npc.sheIs] got a thing for being pregnant. After confirming that you're the father of [npc.her] children, [npc.she] continues,
				#IF npc.isAttractedTo(pc)
				#THEN [npc.speech(Don't think I'm letting you off the hook though! Pregnant [npc.girl]s get horny too, and you're gonna help me with that, understood?!)]
				#ELSE [npc.speech(Don't think I'm letting you off the hook though! I could do with some cash, so just give up and let me rob you already!)])
				#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'> 
			[style.colourSex(You ended up getting [npc.name] pregnant, and, although [npc.she] seems pleased, [npc.she] still wants to fight you!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Look what you did, you asshole!)] [npc.she] shouts, confirming that you're the father of [npc.her] children. [npc.speech(Do you know how annoying it is being pregnant?! You're gonna pay for this!)]
		</p>
		<p style='text-align:center;'> 
			[style.colourSex(You ended up getting [npc.name] pregnant, and now [npc.she] wants revenge!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_REPEAT_STILL_PREGNANT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You instantly recognise the [npc.fullRace(true)], and you jump back into a fighting stance as you expect this encounter to be much the same as the last one. [npc.sheIs] still sporting a round belly, and [npc.she] absent-mindedly strokes [npc.her] swollen bump as [npc.she] reacts to your sudden appearance in [npc.her] territory.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You again?!)] [npc.she] shouts. [npc.speech(This'll be a lot easier if you give up right now!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isAttractedTo(pc)
		#THEN
			Your powerful arcane aura is clearly turning [npc.herHim] on, and from [npc.her] hungry gaze that lingers on your body, you're able to get a good idea of what [npc.she] wants to do with you.
			#IF game.isNonConEnabled()
			#THEN Knowing that defeat will result in being raped by this horny [npc.race], you ready yourself for a fight.
			#ELSE Knowing that defeat will result in this horny [npc.race] wanting to have sex with you, you ready yourself for a fight.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Although your powerful arcane aura is turning [npc.herHim] on a little, it doesn't look as though [npc.sheIs] really all that interested in your body, and will most likely only rob you if you were to lose this fight.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You instantly recognise the [npc.fullRace(true)], and you jump back into a fighting stance as you expect this encounter to be much the same as the last one.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You again?!)] [npc.she] shouts. [npc.speech(This'll be a lot easier if you give up right now!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isAttractedTo(pc)
		#THEN
			Your powerful arcane aura is clearly turning [npc.herHim] on, and from [npc.her] hungry gaze that lingers on your body, you're able to get a good idea of what [npc.she] wants to do with you.
			#IF game.isNonConEnabled()
			#THEN Knowing that defeat will result in being raped by this horny [npc.race], you ready yourself for a fight.
			#ELSE Knowing that defeat will result in this horny [npc.race] wanting to have sex with you, you ready yourself for a fight.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Although your powerful arcane aura is turning [npc.herHim] on a little, it doesn't look as though [npc.sheIs] really all that interested in your body, and will most likely only rob you if you were to lose this fight.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_CANAL_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself wandering down the track that runs alongside Dominion's canal. As you walk past a collection of leafy bushes growing on one side of the path, a shadowy figure suddenly leaps out, blocking your path.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking down yet another narrow passage, lined by a series of inset doorways. As you're passing one such recess, a figure suddenly jumps out from the shadows, blocking your path.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You leap back, narrowly avoiding a blow aimed at your stomach, and prepare yourself for a fight. Looking up, you see [npc.a_fullRace(true)] grinning devilishly at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(What do we have here?)] [npc.she] asks, letting out a short laugh as [npc.she] sees that you're ready to fight [npc.herHim]. [npc.speech(It'll be a lot easier if you just give up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF npc.isAttractedTo(pc)
		#THEN
			Your powerful arcane aura is clearly turning [npc.herHim] on, and from [npc.her] hungry gaze that lingers on your body, you're able to get a good idea of what [npc.she] wants to do with you.
			#IF game.isNonConEnabled()
			#THEN Knowing that defeat will result in being raped by this horny [npc.race], you ready yourself for a fight.
			#ELSE Knowing that defeat will result in this horny [npc.race] wanting to have sex with you, you ready yourself for a fight.
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Although your powerful arcane aura is turning [npc.herHim] on a little, it doesn't look as though [npc.sheIs] really all that interested in your body, and will most likely only rob you if you were to lose this fight.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_PAY_OFF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF pc.isNeurotic()
		#THEN
			Wanting to avoid a fight if at all possible, you take a step backwards, fumbling about to grab a handful of flames to offer to [npc.name]. [pc.speech(I don't want to fight! Please, just take my money and leave me alone!)]
		#ELSE
			#IF pc.isConfident()
			#THEN
				Not wanting to waste your time dealing with this pathetic [npc.race], you produce a handful of flames, before confidently stepping forwards and holding them out to the mugger. [pc.speech(Count yourself lucky that I've got far more important things to do than waste my time on a miserable wretch like yourself!)]
			#ELSE
				Not wanting to get caught up in a fight with this [npc.race], you decide to take the safer route, and offer [npc.herHim] a handful of your flames. [pc.speech(Here's your money. Now step aside and let me pass.)]
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Give that to me!)] [npc.name] snaps, [npc.her] desire to rob you of your money obviously the motivating factor behind [npc.her] assault. Before you can reply, [npc.she] quickly steps forwards, before snatching the flames out of your [pc.hand]. With a mocking laugh, [npc.she] stands aside and sneers, [npc.speech(Now get out of my sight!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF pc.isVigilant()
		#THEN
			With the conflict now resolved, you continue on your way, making sure to keep an eye on [npc.name] in case [npc.she] tries following you. Thankfully, it looks like [npc.sheIs] more concerned with counting out [npc.her] ill-gotten gains than attempting to make any sort of threatening move, and after just a moment, you turn a corner and leave the [npc.race] behind.
		#ELSE
			#IF pc.isCareless()
			#THEN
				With the conflict now resolved, you continue on your way, not even bothering to give [npc.name] a backwards glance. After just a moment, you turn a corner and leave the [npc.race] behind, thankful that you were able to avoid a violent confrontation.
			#ELSE
				With the conflict now resolved, you continue on your way, giving [npc.name] one last backwards glance to make sure [npc.she] isn't going to follow you. Thankfully, it looks like [npc.sheIs] more concerned with counting out [npc.her] ill-gotten gains than attempting to make any sort of threatening move, and after just a moment, you turn a corner and leave the [npc.race] behind.
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_OFFER_BODY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight, and unwilling to hand over any of your money, you decide to do the only other thing you can think of, and flash a seductive smile at [npc.name]. [pc.speech(There's no need to fight. If you're looking for a bit of fun, all you have to do is ask...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Oh really?)] [npc.name] replies, stepping forwards in an intimidating manner. You remain in place, biting your [pc.lip] and trying to make yourself as small as possible as you attempt to entice [npc.name] into using you for some sexual relief.
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your delight, your would-be attacker reaches up and grabs you by the [pc.arms], before pulling you forwards into a tight embrace. Pressing [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours, [npc.she] thrusts [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth, aggressively kissing you for a moment before pulling back, growling, [npc.speech(You're going to be a good [pc.girl] now, aren't you bitch?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Whimpering in the affirmative, you surrender yourself to [npc.namePos] dominant touch, allowing yourself to be used as payment for trespassing on [npc.her] territory...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_OFFER_BODY_SOLO_WITH_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight, and unwilling to hand over any of your money, you decide to do the only other thing you can think of, and flash a seductive smile at [npc.name]. [pc.speech(There's no need to fight. If you're looking for a bit of fun, all you have to do is ask...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Oh really?)] [npc.name] replies, stepping forwards in an intimidating manner. You remain in place, biting your [pc.lip] and trying to make yourself as small as possible as you attempt to entice [npc.name] into using you for some sexual relief.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Are you sure about this?)] [npc2.name] asks, stepping forwards in preparation to defend you from [npc.namePos] advances.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Don't worry, [npc2.name],)] you reply, reaching out to take hold of [npc2.her] [npc2.arm], before firmly pushing [npc2.her] to one side. [pc.speech(I've got this. You just keep a lookout for anyone else.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Much to your delight, your would-be attacker isn't put off by [npc2.namePos] interruption, and reaches up to grab you by the [pc.arms], before pulling you forwards into a tight embrace. Pressing [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours, [npc.she] thrusts [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth, aggressively kissing you for a moment before pulling back, growling, [npc.speech(You're going to be a good [pc.girl] now, aren't you bitch? Your little friend over there can watch me fuck you senseless!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Whimpering in delight, you surrender yourself to [npc.namePos] dominant touch, allowing yourself to be used as payment for trespassing on [npc.her] territory...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_OFFER_BODY_WITH_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight, and unwilling to hand over any of your money, you decide to do the only other thing you can think of, and flash a seductive smile at [npc.name]. [pc.speech(There's no need to fight. If you're looking for a bit of fun, [npc2.name] and I are more than happy to play along...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IFnpc2.isAttractedTo(npc) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
		#THEN[npc2.speech(That's right,)] [npc2.name] teases. [npc2.speech(We can satisfy your desires...)]
		#ELSE[npc2.speech([pc.Name]!)] [npc2.name] interjects. [npc2.speech(I-I really don't want to do this!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Mmm, fucking the two of you at once? How could anyone say no to that?!)] [npc.name] laughs, stepping forwards and placing [npc.a_hand] on each of your waists. With a hungry growl, [npc.she] dominantly pulls the two of you up against [npc.herHim], before leaning in to give you a passionate kiss. 
	</p>
	<p>
		As you press yourself up against [npc.name], [npc.she] suddenly breaks off the kiss, before turning to [npc2.name] and giving [npc2.herHim] a taste of [npc.her] [npc.lips].
		#IFnpc2.isAttractedTo(npc) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
		#THEN [npc2.Name] lets out a delighted [npc2.moan], before eagerly returning the kiss and [npc2.moaning], [npc2.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes!)]
		#ELSE [npc2.Name] lets out a flustered yelp, before pushing [npc.name] away from [npc2.herHim] and shouting, [npc2.speech(G-Get away from me!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Before either of you can make another move, [npc.name] suddenly reaches up to grab you both by the shoulders, and with a determined push, forces the two of you down onto all fours. Dropping down behind you, [npc.name] growls, [npc.speech(You dirty sluts! I'll put the two of you in your place!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEY_ATTACK_OFFER_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight, and unwilling to hand over any of your money, you decide to do the only other thing you can think of. Turning towards [npc2.name], you step towards [npc2.herHim], and in a low tone, you ask, [pc.speech(You'll take one for the team, won't you, [npc2.name]? I don't really want to get into a fight, and I'm not handing over any of my money. All you need to do is spread your legs...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IFnpc2.isAttractedTo(npc) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
		#THEN[npc2.speech(Sure thing, [pc.name],)] [npc2.name] replies. [npc2.speech(If that's really what you want me to do...)]
		#ELSE[npc2.speech([pc.Name]! W-What the hell?!)] [npc2.name] replies in alarm. [npc2.speech(I-I really don't want to do that!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(What are you two muttering about?!)] [npc.name] calls out, stepping forwards and preparing to fight the two of you. 
	</p>
	<p>
		#IFnpc2.isAttractedTo(npc) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
		#THEN[npc2.speech(We were just deciding who's going to be the lucky one you get to fuck!)] [npc2.name] replies, turning around and stepping up to [npc.name]. [npc2.speech(And it turns out it's me!)]
		#ELSE[pc.speech(We were just deciding who's going to be the lucky one you get to fuck!)] you reply, spinning [npc2.name] around and pushing [npc2.herHim] towards [npc.name]. [npc2.speech(And it turns out it's [npc2.name]!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Before either of you can make another move, [npc.name] lets out a hungry [npc.moan], before reaching up to grab [npc2.namePos] [npc2.arm]. With a dominant pull, [npc.she] forces [npc2.name] into [npc.her] embrace, before planting a passionate kiss on [npc2.her] [npc2.lips]. After a moment, [npc.she] breaks away, before growling, [npc.speech(You're going to be a good [npc2.girl] now, aren't you bitch? Your little friend over there can watch me fuck you senseless!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You let out a sigh of relief, happy that you had [npc2.name] to use as a bargaining chip. Leaning back against a nearby wall, you decide to keep watch for any other aggressors while [npc.name] has [npc.her] fun with your companion...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STORM_ATTACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking down the deserted streets of Dominion, the eerie silence broken only by the occasional crash of arcane thunder high above you. There are many hiding places for a would-be attacker to conceal themselves in, and as you pass one such place, taking the form of a building's shadowy doorway, a figure suddenly leaps out at you. Thankfully, as you were taking care to be alert, you quickly step backwards and manage to avoid a punch aimed at your stomach.
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning to face the assailant, you see [npc.a_fullRace(true)] grinning devilishly at you. There's no mistaking that hungry look in [npc.her] [npc.eyes], and you know that the arcane thunder has driven [npc.herHim] into a state of uncontrollable lust. [npc.She] looks determined to claim you as [npc.her] prize, and is ready to fight you in order to claim your body.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Aww, there's no need for that!)] [npc.she] teases, the desperation clearly audible in [npc.her] voice as [npc.she] sees that you're ready to fight [npc.herHim]. [npc.speech(Just give up! Come on! I <i>need</i> a good fuck right now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The arcane storm, combined with your powerful aura, has filled [npc.herHim] with a wild lust, and you have a good idea of what [npc.she] wants to do with you.
		#IF game.isNonConEnabled()
		#THEN Knowing that defeat will result in being raped by this horny [npc.race], you ready yourself for a fight.
		#ELSE Knowing that defeat will result in this horny [npc.race] wanting to have sex with you, you ready yourself for a fight.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STORM_ATTACK_OFFER_BODY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight, you decide to give [npc.name] what [npc.she] wants. Flashing a seductive smile [npc.her] way, you [pc.moan], [pc.speech(Come on then, I'm all yours!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		A delighted, lust-filled smile breaks out across [npc.namePos] face, and [npc.she] instantly rushes forwards, reaching up to grab you by the [pc.arms] before pulling you forwards into a tight embrace. Pressing [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours, [npc.she] thrusts [npc.her] [npc.tongue] into your mouth, aggressively kissing you for a moment before pulling back, growling, [npc.speech(Oh yes... Fuck, I'm just so horny!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeling very much the same way, you surrender yourself to [npc.namePos] dominant touch, allowing [npc.herHim] to use you for some sexual relief...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_ATTRACTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] collapses to the floor, completely defeated. As [npc.she] gazes up at you, desperately whimpering and biting [npc.her] [npc.lip], you see that [npc.she] still has a hungry, lustful look in [npc.her] [npc.eyes]. In defeat, [npc.namePos] arcane aura is completely overwhelmed by the power of your own, and, unable to control [npc.her] burning desire, [npc.she] reaches down to [npc.her] crotch and starts stroking [npc.herself], making pitiful little whining noises as [npc.she] squirms on the floor.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(~Aah!~ What are you waiting for?! Please! Come fuck me!)] [npc.she] pleads, bucking [npc.her] [npc.hips+] against [npc.her] [npc.hand] as [npc.she] continues touching [npc.herself].
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder if you should indulge [npc.her] request. After all, [npc.she] <i>was</i> planning on doing the same to you, and [npc.she] quite clearly wants it. Then again, maybe it's best to just turn around and take your leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_NO_ATTRACTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] collapses to the floor, completely defeated. [npc.She] glances up at you for a moment, before casting [npc.her] gaze to the floor, and in that brief moment, you see that there's a desperate look of regret in [npc.her] [npc.eyes]. Making pitiful little whining noises, [npc.she] tries to shuffle away from you, clearly worried about what your intentions are.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(J-Just take my money and leave me alone!)] [npc.she] pleads, throwing [npc.her] #IFnpc.isFeminine()#THENpurse#ELSEwallet#ENDIF at your feet.
	</p>
	<p>
		You wonder if you should do as [npc.she] says, and leave [npc.herHim] alone. Then again, you <i>could</i> take advantage of [npc.her] weakened, vulnerable body...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to give [npc.name] what it is [npc.she] so desperately craves, you step up to [npc.herHim], before reaching down to take hold of [npc.her] [npc.arm] and pulling [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] [npc.feet]. The moment [npc.she] finds [npc.herself] standing, [npc.name] leans in against you, [npc.moaning], [npc.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Take me! Take me now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Without any further warning, [npc.she] suddenly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours, and, eager to return [npc.her] display of affection, you pull [npc.herHim] into your embrace, passionately returning [npc.her] kiss.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, you push [npc.name] away a little, grinning as you see [npc.her] lust-filled gaze roam up and down your body. Preparing to make your next move, you take a firm grip on [npc.her] [npc.hips+], before [pc.moaning], [pc.speech(This is going to be good...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to give [npc.name] what it is [npc.she] so desperately craves, you step up to [npc.herHim], before reaching down to take hold of [npc.her] [npc.hand]. WIth a disarming smile, you help to pull [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] [npc.feet], and the moment [npc.she] finds [npc.herself] standing, [npc.name] leans in against you, [npc.moaning], [npc.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Take me! Take me now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Without any further warning, [npc.she] suddenly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours, and, happy to return [npc.her] display of affection, you gently pull [npc.herHim] into your embrace, before starting to return [npc.her] passionate kiss.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, you pull back from [npc.name], grinning as you see [npc.her] lust-filled gaze roam up and down your body. Preparing to make your next move, you place your [pc.hands] [npc.her] [npc.hips+], before softly [pc.moaning], [pc.speech(I'll take good care of you...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_ROUGH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to give [npc.name] what it is [npc.she] so desperately craves, you step up to [npc.herHim], before reaching down to grab hold of [npc.her] [npc.arm] and yank [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] [npc.feet]. The moment [npc.she] finds [npc.herself] standing, [npc.name] leans in against you, [npc.moaning], [npc.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Take me! Take me now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Without any further warning, [npc.she] tries to press [npc.her] [npc.lips] against yours, but, seeing it coming, and wanting to leave no doubt in [npc.namePos] mind as to who's in charge, you quickly reach up and grab hold of [npc.her] neck, smirking in response to the sound of [npc.her] startled cry.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Don't you <i>dare</i> try to do anything without my permission, bitch!)] you snarl, using your commanding grip to tilt [npc.namePos] head to one side, before leaning in to give [npc.herHim] a forceful kiss. Roughly thrusting your [pc.tongue+] into [npc.her] mouth, you use your free [pc.hand] to reach around and give [npc.her] [npc.ass+] a dominant squeeze.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, you push [npc.name] away, grinning as you see [npc.her] lust-filled gaze roam up and down your body. Preparing to make your next move, you take a dominant grip on [npc.her] [npc.hips+], before growling, [pc.speech(Good bitch. Now submit to your conqueror!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_SEX_SUBMIT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You really aren't sure what to do next, and start to feel pretty uncomfortable with the fact that you just beat up this poor [npc.race]. Leaning down, you do the first thing that comes into your mind, and start apologising, [pc.speech(Sorry... I was just trying to defend myself, you know... Erm... Is there anything I can do to make it up to you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		For a moment, a look of confusion crosses over [npc.namePos] face, but, as [npc.she] sees that you're genuinely troubled by what you've just done, an evil grin crosses [npc.her] face. [npc.She] stands up, and, grabbing you by the [pc.arm], roughly pulls you into [npc.her] as [npc.she] growls, [npc.speech(How about you start by apologising properly?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.NamePos] strong, dominant grip on your [pc.arm] causes you to let out a lewd little moan, and your submissive nature takes over as you do as [npc.she] asks. [pc.speech(I'm really sorry! Please forgive me! I'll do anything! Anything you ask! Just please, don't be mad!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.Name] roughly yanks you forwards, and with a menacing growl, [npc.she] forces [npc.her] tongue into your mouth. You let out a muffled yelp as your opponent takes charge, but as you feel [npc.her] [npc.hands] reaching down to start roughly groping your ass, you realise that you couldn't be happier with how things have turned out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With [npc.name] collapsed to the floor in defeat, you can't help but let out a triumphant laugh as you turn towards [npc2.name], [pc.speech(I think we should have some fun before we carry on! You take [npc.her] face, I'll get [npc.her] rear!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, you and [npc2.name] move into position around [npc.name]. As [npc.she] pushes [npc.herself] up onto all fours, you drop down onto your knees behind [npc.herHim], before shuffling forwards and bumping your groin against [npc.her] [npc.ass+].
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(You'd better be good at using your mouth,)] [npc2.name] says, dropping down to [npc2.her] knees in front of the defeated [npc.race].
	</p>
	<p>
		Completely exhausted from losing the fight against the two of you, [npc.name] is powerless to do anything other than prepare to get fucked...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_GIVE_TO_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With [npc.name] collapsed to the floor in defeat, you can't help but let out a triumphant laugh as you turn towards [npc2.name], [pc.speech(I think you should have some fun with this one!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc2.speech(Sure, that sounds good to me,)] [npc2.name] replies, smirking as [npc2.she] steps up to [npc.name], before reaching down to take hold of [npc.her] [npc.arm] and pulling [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] [npc.feet]. The moment [npc.she] finds [npc.herself] standing, [npc.name] leans in against [npc2.name], [npc.moaning], [npc.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Take me! Take me now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Without any further warning, [npc.she] suddenly presses [npc.her] [npc.lips] against [npc2.namePos], and, eager to return [npc.her] display of affection, [npc.she] pulls [npc.name] into [npc2.her] embrace, passionately returning [npc.her] kiss.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, [npc2.name] pushes [npc.name] away a little, grinning as [npc2.she] sees [npc.her] lust-filled gaze roam up and down [npc2.her] body. Preparing to make [npc2.her] next move, [npc2.name] takes a firm grip on [npc.her] [npc.hips+], before [npc2.moaning], [npc2.speech(This is going to be good...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_OFFER_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling a little sorry for [npc.name] as you see [npc.her] collapsed down on the floor, you turn towards [npc2.name], and ask, [pc.speech(You'll make [npc.herHim] feel better, won't you, [npc2.name]? All you need to do is spread your legs...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IFnpc2.isAttractedTo(npc) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
		#THEN[npc2.speech(Sure thing, [pc.name],)] [npc2.name] replies. [npc2.speech(If that's really what you want me to do...)]
		#ELSE[npc2.speech([pc.Name]! W-What the hell?!)] [npc2.name] replies in alarm. [npc2.speech(I-I really don't want to do that!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(W-What's going on?)] [npc.name] stutters, pushing [npc.herself] up onto [npc.her] [npc.feet] as [npc.she] realises that you aren't planning on assaulting [npc.herHim]. 
	</p>
	<p>
		#IFnpc2.isAttractedTo(npc) || !game.isNonConEnabled()
		#THEN[npc2.speech(We were just deciding who's going to be the lucky one you get to fuck!)] [npc2.name] replies, turning around and stepping up to [npc.name]. [npc2.speech(And it turns out it's me!)]
		#ELSE[pc.speech(We were just deciding who's going to be the lucky one you get to fuck!)] you reply, spinning [npc2.name] around and pushing [npc2.herHim] towards [npc.name]. [npc2.speech(And it turns out it's [npc2.name]!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Before either of you can make another move, [npc.name] lets out a hungry [npc.moan], before reaching up to grab [npc2.namePos] [npc2.arm]. With a dominant pull, [npc.she] forces [npc2.name] into [npc.her] embrace, before planting a passionate kiss on [npc2.her] [npc2.lips]. After a moment, [npc.she] breaks away, before growling, [npc.speech(You're going to be a good [npc2.girl] now, aren't you bitch? Your little friend over there can watch me fuck you senseless!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You let out a sigh of relief, happy that [npc2.name] is going to give [npc.name] some relief. Leaning back against a nearby wall, you decide to keep watch for any other aggressors while [npc.name] has [npc.her] fun with your companion...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_BANISH_NPC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Disgusted by the fact that this [npc.race] is assaulting innocent travellers, you step forwards, and, frowning down at [npc.herHim], you state, [pc.speech(I don't want to ever catch you doing this again. The next time I see you, I'll be with the Enforcers, and you can find out for yourself how they'll deal with you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(W-Wait, I-I just needed the money! Y-You can't do th-)] [npc.name] starts to stammer, brought to [npc.her] senses by the threat of the Enforcers getting involved.
	</p>
	<p>
		Not interested in listening to anything this criminal has to say, you cut [npc.herHim] off, [pc.speech(Be quiet! If you need money, go and get a job! How dare you try to justify your criminal activities! Now get out of here, before I decide to get the Enforcers right now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You see tears welling up in [npc.namePos] [npc.eyes], but, realising that [npc.sheIs] in no position to argue, quietly stands up and runs off, not even casting a backwards glance your way.
	</p>
	<p>
		With the way [npc.she] reacted to the threat of the Enforcers, you can be sure that you won't see [npc.herHim] in this alleyway ever again. Feeling pleased with the way you dealt with that lowlife, you set off and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_RAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Reaching down, you grab [npc.namePos] [npc.arm], and, pulling [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] feet, you start grinding yourself up against [npc.herHim]. Seeing the lustful look in your [pc.eyes], [npc.she] lets out a little [npc.sob], desperately trying to struggle out of your grip as you hold [npc.herHim] firmly in your embrace...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_RAPE_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Reaching down, you take hold of [npc.namePos] [npc.arm], and, pulling [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] feet, you start pressing yourself up against [npc.herHim]. Seeing the lustful look in your [pc.eyes], [npc.she] lets out a little [npc.sob], desperately trying to struggle out of your grip as you hold [npc.herHim] in your embrace...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_VICTORY_RAPE_ROUGH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Reaching down, you grab [npc.namePos] [npc.arm], and, roughly yanking [npc.herHim] to [npc.her] feet, you start forcefully grinding yourself up against [npc.herHim]. Seeing the lustful look in your [pc.eyes], [npc.she] lets out a little [npc.sob], desperately trying to struggle out of your grip as you firmly hold [npc.herHim] in your embrace...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't carry on fighting any more, and you feel your [pc.legs] giving out beneath you as you collapse to the ground, defeated. A mocking laugh causes you to look up, and you see [npc.name] grinning down at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hah! That was too easy!)] [npc.she] says, before leaning down to grab one of your [pc.arms].
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling you to your feet, [npc.name] starts grinding [npc.herself] up against you, [npc.moaning] into your [pc.ear] as [npc.she] starts groping your body.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You're my perfect little [npc.preferredBody(b)] now! Don't forget bitch, <i>I'm</i> the one in charge!)] [npc.she] growls, before pulling you into a forceful kiss.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_TF"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't carry on fighting any more, and you feel your [pc.legs] giving out beneath you as you collapse to the ground, defeated. A mocking laugh causes you to look up, and you see [npc.name] grinning down at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hah! That was too easy!)] [npc.she] says, before leaning down and pushing you to the ground.
	</p>
	<p>
		As [npc.she] pins you to the floor, [npc.she] produces a curious little bottle from somewhere out of sight, and shakes it from side to side, grinning. [npc.speech(I think you could do with some <i>improvements</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect [npc.preferredBody(b)]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.She] pulls out the little stopper from the top of the bottle, and as you open your mouth to protest, [npc.she] suddenly shoves the neck past your [pc.lips+]. As the sickly-sweet fluid pours out into your mouth, you let out a muffled whine; the only act of resistance that you're able to summon in your current state.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Come on! Swallow it all down already!)] [npc.she] growls, throwing the now-empty vessel to one side as [npc.she] tries to force you to swallow the strange fluid...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_NO_TF_ATTRACTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't carry on fighting any more, and you feel your [pc.legs] giving out beneath you as you collapse to the ground, defeated. A mocking laugh causes you to look up, and you see [npc.name] grinning down at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hah! That was too easy!)] [npc.she] says, before leaning down to grab one of your [pc.arms].
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling you to your feet, [npc.name] starts grinding [npc.herself] up against you, [npc.moaning] into your [pc.ear] as [npc.she] starts groping your body.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Don't try anything, bitch! <i>I'm</i> the one in charge here!)] [npc.she] growls, before pulling you into a forceful kiss.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_WANTS_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Neither you nor [npc2.name] can carry on fighting any more, and you both collapse to the ground, defeated. A mocking laugh causes the two of you to look up, and you see [npc.name] grinning down at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hah! That was too easy!)] [npc.she] says, before leaning down to grab one of [npc2.namePos] [npc2.arms].
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling [npc2.name] to [npc2.her] feet, [npc.name] starts grinding [npc.herself] up against [npc2.herHim], [npc.moaning] into [npc2.her] [npc2.ear] as [npc.she] starts groping [npc2.her] body.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Don't try anything, bitch! <i>I'm</i> the one in charge here!)] [npc.she] growls, before pulling [npc2.name] into a forceful kiss.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_NO_TF_NOT_ATTRACTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't carry on fighting any more, and you feel your [pc.legs] giving out beneath you as you collapse to the ground, defeated. A mocking laugh causes you to look up, and you see [npc.name] grinning down at you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hah! That was too easy!)] [npc.she] says, before leaning down to grab one of your [pc.arms].
	</p>
	<p>
		Pulling you to your feet, [npc.name] pushes you against a nearby wall, before demanding that you hand over your money. Reluctantly, you do as [npc.she] says, and, after giving [npc.herHim] some of your cash, [npc.she] roughly pushes you to the floor once more.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Don't even <i>think</i> about reporting this to the enforcers!)] [npc.she] growls down at you, before turning around and running off.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.speech(I think I'll fuck the two of you at once!)] [npc.name] laughs, pushing you down onto all fours before [npc.herHim]. With a hungry growl, [npc.she] dominantly pulls [npc2.name] up onto [npc2.her] [npc2.hands] and [npc2.feet], before giving each of you a swat on your asses. 
	</p>
	<p>
		As you find yourself down on the floor, side-by-side with [npc2.name], [npc.name] drops down behind you, growling, [npc.speech(You dirty sluts! I'll put the two of you in your place!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_USES_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.NamePos] [npc.arms] wrap around [npc2.namePos] back, and [npc.she] continues passionately making out with [npc2.herHim] for a few moments, before finally pulling away. Giving [npc2.herHim] an evil grin, [npc.name] hungrily licks [npc.her] [npc.lips], before growling, [npc.speech(You're going to be a good [npc2.girl] now, aren't you bitch? Your little friend over there can watch me fuck you senseless!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.NamePos] [npc.arms] wrap around your back, and [npc.she] continues passionately making out with you for a few moments, before finally pulling away. Giving you an evil grin, [npc.she] hungrily licks [npc.her] [npc.lips], and you realise that [npc.sheIs] probably not going to be content with just a kiss...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_EAGER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.NamePos] [npc.arms] wrap around your back, and you eagerly lean into [npc.herHim], passionately returning [npc.her] kiss for a few moments, before [npc.she] breaks away from you. Giving you an evil grin, [npc.she] hungrily licks [npc.her] [npc.lips], and you feel a rush of excitement as you realise that [npc.sheIs] going to want more than just a kiss...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_DEFEAT_SEX_RESIST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.NamePos] [npc.arms] wrap around your back, and you let out a distressed cry as [npc.she] pulls you into a forceful kiss. Summoning the last of your strength, you desperately try to push [npc.herHim] away, pleading for [npc.herHim] to stop. Giving you an evil grin, [npc.she] ignores your protests, and as you see [npc.herHim] hungrily licking [npc.her] [npc.lips], you realise that [npc.sheIs] not going to let you go...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_TRANSFORMATION_REFUSED_ATTRACTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Despite [npc.namePos] best efforts, you manage to twist your head to one side and spit the strange fluid out onto the floor. Your response is met by an anguished groan from your assailant, and, turning your head back up to look at them once more, you see them snarling down angrily at you, [npc.speech(You <i>[pc.bitch]</i>! Do you know how much that cost me?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After shouting down into your face, [npc.name] stands up, pulling you roughly to your [pc.feet] as [npc.she] does so, before pressing [npc.herself] against you and forcing you into a wet kiss. You're powerless to resist [npc.her] advances, and as [npc.her] [npc.hands] reach around to give your [pc.ass+] a squeeze, [npc.she] laughs, [npc.speech(I'll turn you into my perfect little [npc.preferredBody(b)] next time! For now, I'm going to get some fun out of you just as you are!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_TRANSFORMATION_REFUSED_NOT_ATTRACTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Despite [npc.namePos] best efforts, you manage to twist your head to one side and spit the strange fluid out onto the floor. Your response is met by an anguished groan from your assailant, and, turning your head back up to look at them once more, you see them snarling down angrily at you, [npc.speech(You <i>[pc.bitch]</i>! Do you know how much that cost me?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After shouting down into your face, [npc.name] stands up, pulling you roughly to your [pc.feet] as [npc.she] does so, before pushing you against a nearby wall and demanding that you hand over your money. Reluctantly, you do as [npc.she] says, and, after giving [npc.herHim] some of your cash, [npc.she] shoves you down to the floor once more.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(This money of yours is going to pay for your next potion!)] [npc.she] growls down at you. [npc.speech(Come back and pay me another visit, <i>or else</i>! And don't you dare refuse to swallow next time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.she] turns around and runs off, leaving you to recover from your ordeal and continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_TRANSFORMATION_ATTRACTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you struggle to recover from your transformation, [npc.name] pulls you to your [pc.feet], before pressing [npc.herself] against you and forcing you into a wet kiss. You're powerless to resist [npc.her] advances, and as [npc.her] [npc.hands] reach around to give your [pc.ass+] a squeeze, [npc.she] laughs, [npc.speech(I'll turn you into my perfect little [npc.preferredBody(b)]! Now for the real fun!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_COMBAT_TRANSFORMATION_NOT_ATTRACTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you struggle to recover from your transformation, [npc.name] pulls you to your [pc.feet], before pushing you against a nearby wall and demanding that you hand over your money. Reluctantly, you do as [npc.she] says, and, after giving [npc.herHim] some of your cash, [npc.she] roughly pushes you to the floor once more.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You're not good enough for me to be interested in you just yet!)] [npc.she] growls down at you. [npc.speech(Come back and pay me another visit, <i>or else</i>! I'm going to turn you into my perfect little [npc.preferredBody(b)]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.she] turns around and runs off, leaving you panting and sweating as you attempt to recover from the transformations that were just forced upon you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_VICTORY_RAPE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you step back from [npc.name], [npc.she] sinks to the floor, letting out a thankful sob as [npc.she] realises that you've finished. [npc.She] starts frantically gathering [npc.her] belongings, obviously quite keen to make [npc.her] exit before you decide to do anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_VICTORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you step back from [npc.name], [npc.she] sinks to the floor, totally worn out from [npc.her] orgasm. Looking up at you, a satisfied smile settles across [npc.her] face, and you realise that you gave [npc.herHim] exactly what [npc.she] wanted.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_VICTORY_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you step back from [npc.name], [npc.she] sinks to the floor, letting out a desperate whine as [npc.she] realises that you've finished. [npc.Her] [npc.hands] dart down between [npc.her] [npc.legs], and [npc.she] frantically starts masturbating as [npc.she] seeks to finish what you started.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_DEFEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As [npc.name] steps back and sorts [npc.her] clothes out, you sink to the floor, totally worn out from [npc.her] dominant treatment of you. [npc.She] looks down at you, and you glance up to see a very satisfied smile cross [npc.her] face. [npc.She] leans down and pats you on the head. [npc.speech(We should do this again some time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.she] walks off, leaving you panting on the floor. It takes a little while for you to recover from your ordeal, but eventually you feel strong enough to get your things in order and carry on your way.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
