<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- HALLWAY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HALLWAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		White walls and beige carpets. Despite the fact that Felicia has lived here for long enough to have gotten to know Arthur quite well, her apartment looks like she's only just moved in to it. Your immediate surroundings are void of decoration or furniture of any kind. The only things that stick out are the lights and the open-plan views of the apartment's dining and living rooms.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ENTRYWAY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRYWAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The entryway of [felicia.namePos] apartment is as empty as the rest of it, with the only item of note being the brown doormat beneath your [pc.feet]. With plain, white walls and a complete lack of decoration, there's almost nothing in this area that would be capable of holding your attention for more than a brief moment. The only things of interest are the heavy wooden door that leads out into the apartment building's corridor, and, to your right, an internal door which has been left open, granting you an unobstructed view into what very well might be the least interesting coat closet ever created. 
	</p>
	<p>
		Your only real options in this area are to turn around and head back into Felicia's apartment, or to call out goodbye and use the door to make your exit...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- FELICIA_BEDROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FELICIA_BEDROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The door to Felicia's bedroom is closed, and with the dog-girl watching you out of the corner of her eye, you realise that it would be a terrible idea to try and take a look inside. Turning away from the door, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BATHROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BATHROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The door to the apartment's bathroom is closed, and as you take a look at it, Felicia calls out, [felicia.speech(If you need to use the toilet, go ahead.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		From the sharp tone in her voice, you realise that she's just saying that to be polite, and would prefer you to not make use of her bathroom. Not wanting to annoy her, you tell her that you don't need the loo right now and turn away from the bathroom door...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- KITCHEN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="KITCHEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As is the case throughout most of Felicia's open-plan apartment, there's no wall separating this area from her dining area or living room, giving the kitchen a pleasant, open feel to it. Beneath your [pc.feet], the usual beige carpet has been replaced with light brown, laminated wooden flooring.
	</p>
	<p>
		The left wall is lined with marble-topped counters, and in the middle of them, a sink is positioned in front of a window that overlooks the streets of Demon Home below. At the border between the kitchen and living room there's a white, arcane-powered fridge, and sitting atop it, you see what must be the only colourful item in the entire apartment; a bright pink stuffed teddy bear. Beside it is the stove and a small, additional section of workspace, but apart from that, the kitchen is as barren as the rest of the apartment.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DINING_AREA -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DINING_AREA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In the middle of the room is a single, light brown table that looks to be just barely large enough to seat two people. You're unable to test this hypothesis out, however, as there's only one chair present, which is of the same drab brown shade as the table.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking around, you see that this dining room is just as devoid of decoration as the rest of the apartment, and there's nothing on the table, not even a salt shaker. Instead of the beige carpet found throughout the main section of the apartment, the dining room shares the same light brown wooden floor as the kitchen; its shade almost perfectly matches that of the 'dining set'.
	</p>
	<p>
		As is the case throughout most of Felicia's apartment, there's no separating wall around this dining room, granting you an unobstructed view of the kitchen and hallway.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- LIVING_AREA -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="LIVING_AREA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The living room is home to most of the apartment's furniture, which consists of a dark green sofa, a light brown coffee table, and a bookcase filled to the brim with an assortment of books. Next to the bookcase is a window, which opens to a view of the streets of Demon Home. There's no wall on two sides of this room, allowing you to look into the kitchen and hallway, while on the third side there's a firmly-closed door which leads into Felicia's bedroom.
	</p>
	<p>
		Felicia is sitting on the sofa, and although she occasionally glances up to see if you're still around, the vast majority of her attention is focused on the book that's in her paw-like hands.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- FELICIA_GREETINGS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FELICIA_GREETINGS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking Felicia up on her invitation, you [pc.step] forwards and enter what looks to be an almost completely empty apartment. Thanks to its open-plan design, you're able to look into the dining room off to your left, which only has a table and a single chair in it, the kitchen behind that, which looks to be equipped with just the basic fridge and stove, and the living room directly in front of you, which is where Felicia starts to lead you.
	</p>
	#IF(game.isHourBetween(6, 9))
		<p>
			[felicia.speech(Come on, [pc.name],)] she excitedly says as she leads you forwards, [felicia.speech(You can take a seat there; I'll just quickly finish drying off and then I'll be right with you!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.Stepping] forwards into the living room, you see that the only items of furniture which are present are a dark green sofa, a light brown coffee table, and bookcase that's stacked full of an assortment of books. Felicia darts off into her bedroom, closing the door behind her, leaving you to take a seat on the sofa and discover that it's comfier than it looks.
		</p>
		<p>
			After just a couple of minutes, the dog-girl emerges wearing an oversized brown sweater which obscures both her [felicia.cupSize]-cup breasts and bare, furry thighs. Sitting down beside you, Felicia tucks her legs up on the sofa, and with her tail starting to thud against the cushions behind her, she asks, [felicia.speech(So, what did you want to talk about?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[felicia.speech(Come on, [pc.name],)] she excitedly says as she leads you forwards, [felicia.speech(Let's sit down!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.Stepping] forwards into the living room, you see that the only items of furniture which are present are a dark green sofa, a light brown coffee table, and bookcase that's stacked full of an assortment of books. At Felicia's insistence, you take a seat on the sofa and discover that it's comfier than it looks. Sitting down beside you, the dog-girl tucks her legs up on the sofa, and with her tail starting to thud against the cushions behind her, she asks, [felicia.speech(So, what did you want to talk about?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- FELICIA_GREETINGS_APPROACH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FELICIA_GREETINGS_APPROACH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The white, fluffy form of Felicia is sitting on the dark green sofa in front of you. A book sits in her hand, stealing most of her focus, but as she glances up, she notices that you've approached her and asks, [felicia.speech(Oh, still here, [pc.name]? Well, if you want to talk some more then let me know what's on your mind!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="FELICIA_GOODBYE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling like you've spent enough time in Felicia's company, you stand up from the sofa and tell her that you need to get going.
	</p>
	<p>
		[felicia.speech(Ah, alright. I'm around in the mornings until about three in the afternoon, so if you ever need me, come back between those times,)] she states, before leaning over towards the bookshelf and picking out a book seemingly at random. Before she opens it, she flashes you a small smile, then begins to read.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.Stepping] away from the sofa, you wonder whether to head straight to the apartment's exit, or instead take some time to have a quick look around the place...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ARTHUR_WHEREABOUTS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARTHUR_WHEREABOUTS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking Felicia up on her invitation, you [pc.step] forwards and enter what looks to be an almost completely empty apartment. Thanks to its open-plan design, you're able to look into the dining room off to your left, which only has a table and a single chair in it, the kitchen behind that, which looks to be equipped with just the basic fridge and stove, and the living room directly in front of you, which is where Felicia starts to lead you.
	</p>
	#IF(game.isHourBetween(6, 9))
		<p>
			[felicia.speech(Come on, [pc.name],)] she excitedly says as she leads you forwards, [felicia.speech(You can take a seat there; I'll just quickly finish drying off and then I'll be right with you!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.Stepping] forwards into the living room, you see that the only items of furniture which are present are a dark green sofa, a light brown coffee table, and bookcase that's stacked full of an assortment of books. Felicia darts off into her bedroom, closing the door behind her, leaving you to take a seat on the sofa and discover that it's comfier than it looks.
		</p>
		<p>
			After just a couple of minutes, the dog-girl emerges wearing an oversized brown sweater which obscures both her [felicia.cupSize]-cup breasts and bare, furry thighs. Sitting down beside you, Felicia tucks her legs up on the sofa, and with her tail starting to thud against the cushions behind her, she asks, [felicia.speech(So, have you found Arthur yet?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[felicia.speech(Come on, [pc.name],)] she excitedly says as she leads you forwards, [felicia.speech(Let's sit down!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.Stepping] forwards into the living room, you see that the only items of furniture which are present are a dark green sofa, a light brown coffee table, and bookcase that's stacked full of an assortment of books. At Felicia's insistence, you take a seat on the sofa and discover that it's comfier than it looks. Sitting down beside you, the dog-girl tucks her legs up on the sofa, and with her tail starting to thud against the cushions behind her, she asks, [felicia.speech(So, have you found Arthur yet?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ARTHUR_WHEREABOUTS_NO -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARTHUR_WHEREABOUTS_NO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you tell Felicia that you haven't managed to find Arthur yet, you can visibly see her energy seep from her body, and both her tail and ears droop down and lie flat. She takes a few seconds to recollect herself before softly speaking, [felicia.speech(You'll find him eventually, don't worry...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Figuring that you should clear the sadness from the air, you decide to move straight on to asking her some questions...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ARTHUR_WHEREABOUTS_YES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ARTHUR_WHEREABOUTS_YES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you tell Felicia that you've managed to find Arthur, her body visibly lights up with excitement, and her tail starts wagging with an incredible strength and speed. Without warning, dog-girl suddenly pounces on you, and after wrapping her furry arms around your body, she hugs you to near death. With how soft her fur rubbing over your body, she exclaims, [felicia.speech(I can't thank you enough! You're the best person ever!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		There's a few more seconds of hugging before she finally releases you, allowing you to breathe again. Calming herself down, she returns to sitting beside you and asks, [felicia.speech(Is he okay? Where is he? Will he be moving back in soon?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reassuring Felicia by telling her that Arthur is doing well, you explain that he's going to be staying in Lilaya's mansion for the foreseeable future. Seeing the worried look in her eyes, you quickly tell the dog-girl that Rose will be sure to let her in to visit Arthur at any time, and you happily give her Lilaya's address.
	</p>
	<p>
		[felicia.speech(Aww... I really wanted him back here, but I guess this'll do,)] she replies with a little pout. Taking a second to collect herself, her happy demeanour returns and she states, [felicia.speech(Well, as long as I'm always welcome there then it'll be fine. So, did you want to talk about something, [pc.name]?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_MENU -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_MENU"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The comfy sofa, and almost sucks you in as you lean back and wonder what to ask Felicia about next. Sensing that you're wanting to change the topic of conversation, the dog-girl tilts her head to one side and asks, [felicia.speech(Is there something else you wanted to talk about?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_MENU_ARTHUR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_MENU_ARTHUR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to find out what Felicia knows about Arthur, you ask the white fluff ball if she's willing to talk about her ex-neighbour for a moment. Perking up slightly as she hears you mention Arthur by name, the white ball of fluff excitedly asks, [felicia.speech(Ah, what do you want to know?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_MENU_ABOUT_HER -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_MENU_ABOUT_HER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get to know her a little better, you ask Felicia if you can ask her some personal questions. The white fluff ball's ear pops up as she hears this, and her tail starts slowly swishing to thud into the cushions behind her. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[felicia.speech(Y-You want to talk about me?)] she asks, looking a bit flustered. Shuffling around a little in trepidation, she continues, [felicia.speech(There's not much to know, but if you want to ask, then go ahead.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_ARTHUR_PERSONALITY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_ARTHUR_PERSONALITY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You decide to ask Felicia about her perception of Arthur's personality, and so phrase your question to that effect.
	</p>
	<p>
		With her ears perking up, Felicia takes a few seconds to think, before answering, [felicia.speech(The first time you meet him you'd think he was a timid man, but ask him anything about what he's working on and you see just how full of life he is. Well, if you can stay awake during it, that is... Oh, and he gets so red when I ask what he wants for dinner. I wouldn't ask so much if he could actually cook.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_ARTHUR_HOBBIES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_ARTHUR_HOBBIES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You wonder what a man of science would do during his pastime: Read? Cool sparkly science stuff? People watching from out of his window? With these questions in mind, you ask Felicia if she's ever seen him do anything besides work on his experiments.
	</p>
	<p>
		[felicia.speech(Yeah, I've seen him read a few times,)] she answers, [felicia.speech(Often science papers... Actually, always science papers. I don't think I've seen him read anything else.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_ABOUT_HER_NAME -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_ABOUT_HER_NAME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to talk about her unusually-long surname, you ask Felicia to repeat to you what her full name is. Her cheeks slightly flush red from embarrassment as she hears you say this, and with her tail starting to swish, she states, [felicia.speech(It's Felicia Delilah-Hope Renmorre...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With her name now being the focus of the conversation, you ask Felicia how she came to have such a peculiar surname. Shuffling about a little on the sofa, she says, [felicia.speech(Well, like I told you before, it's a family tradition. We take both of our grandmothers' names as our middle name...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing that she's getting a little timid about sharing any further details, you decide to give Felicia a compliment to help relax the mood. Telling her that her name is very pretty, you can't help but smile as the dog-girl's tail powerfully wags against the cushions behind her, and she blushes even more and says, [felicia.speech(Thanks, [pc.name]...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_ABOUT_HER_PLACE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_ABOUT_HER_PLACE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to find out why Felicia's apartment is so empty, you ask her in the most tactful manner you can manage why she hasn't put up any decorations or got any furniture.
	</p>
	<p>
		The ball of white fluff looks oblivious for a moment, before narrowing her eyes in confusion and returning your question with one of her own, [felicia.speech(I've got all I need, why should I get anything more?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Responding by suggesting that decorations would give the place its own personality, you ask Felicia if she's ever considered redecorating.
	</p>
	<p>
		[felicia.speech(No, not really... I'm not interested in all that I guess,)] she bluntly responds.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_ABOUT_HER_FUR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_ABOUT_HER_FUR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Gazing in wonder at how silky and fluffy her luxuriant fur is, you ask Felicia how she manages to get it into such a perfect state.
	</p>
	<p>
		The dog-girl's tail swishes from side to side as you ask this question, and with a smile on her face revealing that she's taken your question as a compliment, she responds, [felicia.speech(Lots. Of. Conditioner.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Something tells you that's not the whole truth, but Felicia doesn't seem to want to reveal her secrets to you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_ABOUT_HER_FAVORITE_STORE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_ABOUT_HER_FAVORITE_STORE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to ask her about the sorts of things which she gets up to in the day, you ask Felicia if there are any interesting stores nearby which she frequents.
	</p>
	<p>
		The ball of white fluff takes a moment to think before stating, [felicia.speech(There aren't any here in Demon Home which I'm fond of, but over in the Shopping Arcade there's a place called Nyan's Clothing Emporium. I don't care much about the clothes, I just think cats are cute, and the owner is the sweetest person you'll ever meet.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_PET -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_PET"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The fluffiness of her hair, how it sways in the wind, you can't help but ask to touch it. Shuffling closer towards her, you move your [pc.hand] close to Felicia's head and ask if you can pet her.
	</p>
	<p>
		Felicia's ears perk up as she looks up at your [pc.hand]. Realising that you're serious about your request, she blushes slightly and responds, [felicia.speech(S-Sure...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With her permission, your [pc.hand] plops on to her head. Her soft fur feels even fluffier than it looks. As you rub her luxurious coat, the sound of her tail thudding into the sofa's cushions can be heard. The fluffiness is so powerful you almost lose yourself in the head pats, all the while Felicia blushing and becoming even more embarrassed about what's happening. It seems petting is her weakness.
	</p>
	<p>
		A wicked smile forming, you decide to give her a little scratch behind the ears. Felicia's ears perk up to what was thought impossible, her tail moving fast enough to become a blur. Within a minute, she's putty in your ear scratching [pc.hand], clearly trying to hold her composure. Finally, her strength breaks and she lets out the slightest, [felicia.speech(Awoo...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Immediately after letting out this small awoo, Felicia looks down and covers her mouth with her paw-like hands in embarrassment. With your [pc.hand] starting to cramp, and the dog-girl at the point of breaking, you decide that you've petted her enough for now. Felicia, still blushing, gives a small whimper as you take your [pc.hand] away, before taking a deep breath to regain herself. Meekly, she asks, [felicia.speech(W-What did you want to talk about now?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		<b>You've reached the end of Felicia's content (for now)...</b>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_LEWD -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_LEWD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The way she acts about Arthur, anyone would be curious as to what their real relationship is. With this thought in mind, you ask Felicia if she has a crush on him.
	</p>
	<p>
		[felicia.speech(No,)] she says flatly, the cute, innocent look in her puppy eyes immediately vanishing. With a steely tone in her voice, she flatly continues, [felicia.speech(He was a friend when I didn't have any. Nothing more.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_LEWD_CONTINUE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_LEWD_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to find out more about this dog-girl's sex life, you ask her if she has a crush on anyone else.
	</p>
	<p>
		Narrowing her eyes, Felicia shoots you a furious gaze for a moment, before taking a calming breath and simply replying, [felicia.speech(No.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_LEWD_PUSH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_LEWD_PUSH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can't believe how innocent she is, and to not even have a crush, she must be so pent up. You press on with your line of questioning and ask her what she'd think if someone had a crush on her, hoping to get some reaction. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[felicia.speech(I'm fine, please stop,)] she snaps.
	</p>
	<p>
		From her sharp tone and the furious glare in her eyes, you feel like it would probably be best to stop pushing her, or else [style.italicsBad(something bad will likely happen)]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- TALK_LEWD_DIG_DEEP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="TALK_LEWD_DIG_DEEP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unable to get your horniness under control, you move closer to Felicia and start to make a move on her. An angry scowl suddenly breaks out across her face, and she sternly demands, [felicia.speech(Leave. Now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that you must have struck a nerve, you start to backtrack, but it's too late. Cutting you off as you start to speak, Felicia barks, [felicia.speech(Leave, before I force you out!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Taken aback, and embarrassed for letting the horny get to you, you stand up and head over to the door. Stomping along after you, the dog-girl slams the door shut after you the moment you [pc.step] out into the corridor. Not wanting to anger her any more, you quickly leave the apartment building...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>