<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	<htmlContent tag="ROACH_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Roach morphs (or cockroach-morphs) are an ubiquitous insect morph, most common in urban or wooded environments. They can be distiguished from similar insect-morphs for their long, oval abdomens.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	<htmlContent tag="ROACH_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Roach-morphs are one of the more maligned insect-morph races, commonly associated with unpleasant but necessary lines of work. Hardy, adaptable, and tolerant of strong smells, urban roach-morphs often take jobs as janitors or waste collectors. Fastidious and with a sensitve sense of smell, a roach-morph can quickly clean away every speck of grime. Many resent the irony that they are seen as "dirty", while they are the ones following behind other morphs and cleaning their messes. To deal this, roach-morphs often present outwardly as jaded and taciturn, seeking to arouse as little attention as possible and only forming close connections with other similarly-shunned people.
	</p>
	<p>
		In more rural environments, roach-morphs (and many other insect-morphs in general) are seen much more positively. Having to do dirty, smelly work is seen more as a source of camaraderie than disgust, and the roach-morphs' stronger-than-normal stomach is looked on with admiration by others. For example, being able to diagnose livestock disease from smell (and resisting the urge to vomit long enough to tell someone) is a valuable asset to farming or ranching communities. Many roach-morphs there still are a bit skittish, and are more comfortable in relatively isolated woodlands. These hermits make a living foraging for wild herbs and mushrooms. There's even a well-established cockroach-run company that provides high-quality floral and herbal extracts for use in perfumes and as flavorings. While they maintain the utmost quality by personally tasting or smelling their product, the fact that roach-morphs are the ones doing the gathering, extraction and testing is kept quiet.
	</p>
	<p>
		Many roach-morphs have a sexual enjoyment of a particular strong smell. Musk and sweat are common fetishes, though some individuals narrow this attraction down to a single species and sex. Food-play, whether as feeder or feed-ee is another common kink, especially with distictive-smelling foods. Some are turned on by more esoteric smells, such as a particular perfume or flower, or the smell of earth after it rains.
	</p>
	<p>
		Like many races, roach-morphs are heavily affected by arcane storms. Roach-morphs go into a potent heat or rut, and will swarm together in massive groups to mate.
	</p>
	<p>
		Like most morphs, a roach's offspring will be a mix of the roach and the partner's race. Roach-morphs generally lay a clutch of eggs, and the rare individual possess an ovipositor to deposit them into another person instead.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
</bookText>
