<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- EXTERIOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		On the opposite side of the street to the Slavery Administration building, there's a timber-framed tavern which bears the name 'The Rusty Collar'. An old sign, every bit as weathered as the old wooden door onto which it's nailed, declares this establishment to be open twenty-four hours a day, seven days of the week. A peeling poster stuck to the wall beside it proudly declares this tavern to be the best place in all of Dominion in which to find and hire experienced bounty hunters. Near to the bottom of the poster, there's an image of a mean-looking wolf-boy, and a speech bubble coming from his mouth reads: 'We'll return your runaway slaves within two days, or your money back!'
	</p>
	<p>
		Although the crooked old windows are barely translucent, they are letting out a decent amount of light, which, combined with the loud sounds of merriment coming from within, informs you that there are a multitude of people currently inside the tavern. If you wanted to, you could push open the front door and take a look inside...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	

	<!-- ENTRANCE_INITITAL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE_INITITAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to take a look inside the tavern, you [pc.step] up to the front door and push it open, before heading inside and taking stock of your surroundings.
	</p>
	<p>
		The first thing which strikes you upon your entry is both the high level of background noise and the thick, smoky atmosphere. Despite the many arcane-enchanted candles which illuminate the interior, the high, timber-framed ceiling is practically hidden from view by the cloud of second-hand smoke.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking straight ahead, you see that the majority of the ground floor is filled with dozens of tables, around which bounty hunters and all sorts of unsavoury-looking individuals are seated. Opposite the door through which you've just entered, a large, wooden bar runs along part of the far wall, and is currently surrounded by patrons either demanding or consuming alcoholic drinks of all sorts. Looking over to your left, you see that there's a large wooden bounty board fixed to the wall, onto which dozens of pieces of paper have been tacked.
	</p>
	<p>
		None of the tavern's many occupants seem to pay any attention to your arrival, and you wonder whether you should take a closer look around, or turn around and head back out into Slaver Alley...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ENTRANCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself back at the entrance to the tavern, you wonder whether you should take your leave and head back out into Slaver Alley...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you've had enough of the tavern's noise and smoky atmosphere, you exit in the same way you entered, and soon find yourself standing back outside in Slaver Alley... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- FLOOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="FLOOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Crossing the tavern's main floor, you have to weave your way around dozens of tables, most of which have rough-looking bounty hunters and other such unsavoury individuals seated around them.
		#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_DEMON)
			 The ones who see that you're a demon obligingly scoot their chairs forwards to give you room to pass, while those who shout curses before then taking a look at you are soon uttering apologies and offering you their seat.
		#ELSE
			 Growls and grumbles fill the air as you squeeze past the chairs and tables, with a couple of particularly rowdy individuals shouting curses as you pass.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Ignoring these characters, you do your best to endure the thick, smoky atmosphere and the booming, inebriated shouts and laughter coming from the tavern's patrons.
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(wolfgang))
			 Continuing on your way to the other side of the room, you notice the familiar figures of the two dobermann-boys who were terrorising [kay.namePos] business. Sitting at one of the nearby tables, [wolfgang.name] and [karl.name] haven't noticed your presence, and you wonder whether you should leave them be or go and say hello...
		#ELSE
			 As you don't have any business with any of the people in this area, there's not much else to do but continue on your way to the other side of the room...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DOBERMANNS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_dobermannDefeatSeduced))
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to [wolfgang.name] and [karl.name] again, you [pc.walk] over to the table at which they're sitting and say hello. Looking up from their mugs of beer, the dobermann-boy bounty hunters flash you a pair of lustful grins as they see that you've returned to them.
		</p>
		<p>
			[wolfgang.speech(Hungry for our fat dog-cocks again, are you?)] [wolfgang.name] grunts.
		</p>
		<p>
			[karl.speech(I've been dreaming about stuffing you full of cum since our last fuck!)] [karl.name] adds, before downing his beer and asking, [karl.speech(So, you gonna come up to our room, or what?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Leaning back in their chairs and expectantly gazing up at you, the two horny dobermann-boys await your reply...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to talk to [wolfgang.name] and [karl.name] again, you [pc.walk] over to the table at which they're sitting and say hello. Looking up from their mugs of beer, the dobermann-boy bounty hunters recognise you from before, and flash you a pair of angry scowls.
		</p>
		<p>
			[wolfgang.speech(What the fuck do you want?)] [wolfgang.name] grunts.
		</p>
		<p>
			[karl.speech(If you're not here to offer us anything, then we're not interested,)] [karl.name] adds, before downing his beer and demanding, [karl.speech(Come on then, tell us what you want!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With the two angry dobermann-boys clearly not being interested in engaging in you in conversation, you wonder what to do now...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS_SEDUCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it'd be a lot of fun to seduce and fuck this hot pair of bounty hunters, you put on your most alluring look and lean down over their table.
		#IF(pc.hasAnyEnforcerStatusEffect())
			 Noticing their glances at your uniform, you reassure the two dobermann-boys that you're off-duty for the rest of today, before suggestively teasing them by saying that Enforcers like to let themselves go just as much as anybody else.
		#ELSEIF(pc.getRace()==RACE_DEMON)
			 Reassuring the two dobermann-boys that you're not going to make use of your demonic status to get them in trouble, you suggestively tease them by saying how your demonic body is always horny and hungry for a good fuck.
		#ELSE
			 Reassuring the two dobermann-boys that you've finished your business with Kay and have nothing to say about that subject, you start to suggestively tease and flirt with them.
		#ENDIF
		 After suspiciously looking you up and down for a moment, Wolfgang lets out a deep grunt and motions for you to come and sit down next to him. Pleased to discover that even these brutes quickly let their guard down at the slightest suggestion of getting laid, you happily sit down in Wolfgang's lap, causing him to let out another deep, amused grunt and declare, [wolfgang.speech(Fuck! You're eager, aren't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning into Wolfgang's large, muscular torso, you respond by saying how any [pc.girl] would be just as eager as you are, were they in your position. Playfully biting your [pc.lip], you continue to flirt with them by saying how everyone romanticises bounty hunters, and then suggesting that the two of them must never struggle to find a willing partner to fuck.
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(Yeah, that part's true enough,)] Karl grunts.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(So, you were wondering what it's like to get fucked by two fat dog-cocks, were you?)] Wolfgang asks, before slipping his paw-like hand down
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			 between your legs
		#ELSE
			 to your groin
		#ENDIF
		 and giving you a good grope. Smirking as you let out an erotic gasp, he suggests to his companion, [wolfgang.speech(How about we get this eager slut upstairs and give [pc.herHim] a good, hard fuck?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(Sounds good to me,)] Karl replies, before standing up and moving over to dominantly give your [pc.breasts+] a rough squeeze.
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeling just as turned-on as these two dobermann-boys clearly are, you tell them that you don't want to wait a moment longer. Encouraged by your enthusiasm, the two dobermann-boys stand up and lead you over to the staircase on the other side of the tavern. Reaching down to roughly grope your [pc.ass+], [wolfgang.name] reveals, [wolfgang.speech(We're renting a room up here. Come on, slut, it's the perfect place for you to get fucked.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an eager [pc.moan], you allow the dobermann-boys to accompany you up the stairs and down the corridor to their room. Being led inside, you see that the interior is just what anybody would expect. Apart from a couple of beds and chests of drawers, there's nothing else in here that draws your attention, and so as the door swings shut behind you, you turn back to face [wolfgang.name] and [karl.name] and wonder how to take things from here...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS_SEDUCE_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Happily sitting down in Wolfgang's lap, you lean into his large, muscular torso and tell both him and [karl.name] that you were hoping to have some fun with them again. Letting out a deep, amused grunt, [karl.name] declares from the other side of the table, [karl.speech(You're such a horny slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Hungry for another taste of our fat dog-cocks, are you?)] Wolfgang asks, before slipping his paw-like hand down
		#IF(pc.hasLegs())
			 between your legs
		#ELSE
			 to your groin
		#ENDIF
		 and giving you a good grope. Smirking as you let out an erotic gasp, he declares to his companion, [wolfgang.speech(Let's get this slut upstairs and give [pc.herHim] another good, hard fuck!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[karl.speech(Sounds good to me,)] [karl.name] replies, before standing up and moving over to dominantly give your [pc.breasts+] a rough squeeze.
	</p>
	<p>
		Feeling just as turned-on as these two dobermann-boys clearly are, you tell them that you don't want to wait a moment longer. Encouraged by your enthusiasm, the two dobermann-boys stand up and lead you over to the staircase on the other side of the tavern. Reaching down to roughly grope your [pc.ass+], [wolfgang.name] grunts, [wolfgang.speech(Come on, slut, lets get you up to the room we're renting. It's the perfect place for you to get fucked!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an eager [pc.moan], you allow the dobermann-boys to accompany you up the stairs and down the corridor to their room. Being led inside, you see that the interior is just what anybody would expect. Apart from a couple of beds and chests of drawers, there's nothing else in here that draws your attention, and so as the door swings shut behind you, you turn back to face [wolfgang.name] and [karl.name] and wonder how to take things from here...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling the bounty hunters that you've changed your mind and have other business to attend to, you [pc.step] back and move away from their table...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DOBERMANNS_UPSTAIRS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS_UPSTAIRS_FUCK_THEM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Despite the nature of your teasing, you don't want to submit to these two dobermann-boys, and so you switch to a more confident, dominant tone and tell them to get down on all fours and present themselves to you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Both Wolfgang and Karl let out a menacing growl as you say this, but despite their reaction, their horniness gets the better of them and they reluctantly do as you say. Dropping down onto all fours, the two dobermann-boys shuffle around to present their asses towards you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Dropping down onto your knees behind them, you reach forwards and give each of their behinds a dominant grope, grinning to yourself as they respond by letting out desperate grunts. Shuffling forwards, you can't help but let out an excited [pc.moan] as you prepare to fuck these bounty hunters...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS_SEX_OFFER_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd enjoy using your mouth, you inform the dobermann-boys that you were really hoping to get a good taste of their cocks. This desire of yours proves to be warmly received by the two bounty hunters, who, after getting you to drop down onto your knees, both pull out their huge, throbbing dog-cocks and sit down of the edge of the bed in front of you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Got a taste for dog-cum, have you, slut?)] Wolfgang asks, before suddenly grabbing the back of your head and pulling you down into his groin. Opening wide, you take his scarlet-skinned cock into your mouth, and with a muffled, spluttering [pc.moan], you start passionately kissing and sucking on his hot shaft. Grunting in pleasure, the dobermann-boy growls, [wolfgang.speech(Don't forget about Karl! Get started on giving him a handjob, bitch!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you reach over and start jerking off Karl's huge, knotted dog-cock. Having got exactly what you wanted, you focus on getting these two dobermann-boys to cum for you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS_SEX_OFFER_SPITROAST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd enjoy being penetrated at both ends, you inform the dobermann-boys that you were really hoping to get spit-roasted by them. This desire of yours proves to be warmly received by the two bounty hunters, who quickly push you down onto all fours and pull out their huge, throbbing dog-cocks. Wolfgang then immediately steps around to drop down onto his knees behind you, while Karl similarly sinks down onto the ground in front of your face.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Want a good double-stuffing of dog-cum, do you, slut?)] Wolfgang asks, before quickly gaining access to your
		#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
			 [pc.pussy+] and impatiently spreading your [pc.labia+] with both hands. Grunting in approval at what he sees, the dominant dobermann-boy wastes no further time and immediately thrusts forwards, slamming his hot dog-cock deep into your [pc.pussy+].
		#ELSE
			 [pc.asshole+] and impatiently spreading your [pc.assSize] ass cheeks with both hands. Grunting in approval at what he sees, the dominant dobermann-boy wastes no further time and immediately thrusts forwards, slamming his hot dog-cock deep into your [pc.asshole+].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		The sensation of suddenly being penetrated in such a forceful manner causes you to let out [pc.a_moan+], and as you do so, Karl takes full advantage of your open mouth by shuffling forwards and shoving his own huge dog-cock past your [pc.lips+]. Taking his scarlet-skinned cock into your mouth, you continue to let out a series of muffled, spluttering [pc.moans] as you start passionately kissing and sucking on his hot shaft. Grunting in pleasure, he growls, [karl.speech(That's right, take it deep!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having got exactly what you wanted, you focus on the pleasure of being spit-roasted by these two dobermann-boys, eagerly anticipating the part where they fill each of your ends with their hot dog-cum...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS_SEX_OFFER_RIDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd enjoy getting stuffed with their cocks, you inform the dobermann-boys that you were really hoping to ride them. This desire of yours proves to be warmly received by the two bounty hunters, who quickly pull out their huge, throbbing dog-cocks. Wolfgang then immediately lies down on his bed, pulling you down on top of him into the cowgirl position, while Karl sinks down behind you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Want a good double-stuffing of dog-cum, do you, slut?)] Wolfgang asks, before quickly gaining access to your
		#IF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
			 [pc.pussy+] and impatiently spreading your [pc.labia+] with both hands. Grunting in approval at what he sees, the dominant dobermann-boy wastes no further time, and after grabbing hold of your [pc.hips+], forcefully pulls you down and sinks his hot dog-cock deep into your [pc.pussy+].
		#ELSE
			 [pc.asshole+] and impatiently spreading your [pc.assSize] ass cheeks with both hands. Grunting in approval, the dominant dobermann-boy wastes no further time, and after grabbing hold of your [pc.hips+], forcefully pulls you down and sinks his hot dog-cock deep into your [pc.asshole+].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(!pc.hasVagina() || !pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_VAGINA, true))
			Not wanting to miss out on the fun, Karl shuffles up close behind you, and after giving your [pc.ass+] a good grope, he pushes his cock up against Wolfgang's, and on his companion's next thrust, forces his cock into your asshole. The sensation of having your back-door stuffed full of two huge dog-cocks causes you to let out [pc.a_moan+], which is met by a synchronised pair of deep, amused grunts from the two dobermann-boys. Leaning into your back, Karl dominantly growls, [karl.speech(That's right, bitch, keep moaning like a whore!)]
		#ELSEIF(!pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_ANUS, true))
			Not wanting to miss out on the fun, Karl shuffles up close behind you, and after giving your [pc.ass+] a good grope, he pushes his cock up against Wolfgang's, and on his companion's next thrust, forces his cock into your [pc.pussy+]. The sensation of having your cunt stuffed full of two huge dog-cocks causes you to let out [pc.a_moan+], which is met by a synchronised pair of deep, amused grunts from the two dobermann-boys. Leaning into your back, Karl dominantly growls, [karl.speech(That's right, bitch, keep moaning like a whore!)]
		#ELSE
			Not wanting to miss out on the fun, Karl shuffles up close behind you, and after giving your [pc.ass+] a good grope, he pushes the [karl.cockHead+] of his cock up against your [pc.asshole+]. On his companion's next thrust, he suddenly forces his cock into your asshole, causing you to let out [pc.a_moan+]. Leaning into your back, Karl dominantly growls, [karl.speech(That's right, bitch, keep moaning like a whore!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Having got exactly what you wanted, you focus on the pleasure of taking both of the two dobermann-boys' cocks at once, eagerly anticipating the part where they fill you with their hot dog-cum...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS_SEX_OFFER_NIPPLES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to give the dobermann-boys something a little different, you tell them that you were really hoping to have them fuck your nipples. Glancing at one another for a moment, Wolfgang muses, [wolfgang.speech(I've never fucked someone's nipples before... Sure, why not?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Excited to be given the chance to show off what you can do, you quickly slide off the sofa and drop down onto your knees. Pulling out their huge, throbbing dog-cocks, the two dobermann-boys stand up in front of you and hungrily stare at your chest as you expose your [pc.nipples+] and lift your [pc.breasts+] towards them.
	</p>
	<p>
		[wolfgang.speech(Want to get your tits stuffed full of dog-cum then, slut?)] Wolfgang asks, before suddenly grabbing your left breast with both hands and pulling it up towards his groin. Thrusting out your chest, you can't help but let out an excited [pc.moan] as the [wolfgang.cockHead+] of his scarlet-skinned cock teases over your [pc.nipple+]. Grunting in amusement at the noise you've just made, Wolfgang suddenly thrusts forwards, slamming his [wolfgang.cock+] deep into your [pc.breast+(true)].
	</p>
	<p>
		Following his companion's lead, Karl grabs your right breast, and after taking a moment to experimentally push his paw-like fingers into your fuckable nipple, he lines his cock up to it and thrusts forwards. [pc.Moaning] in delight as the two dobermann-boys fuck your tits, you once again push out your chest and try to focus on getting them to cum for you...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DOBERMANNS_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(sex.isDom(pc))
		<p>
			Having had your fun, you disentangle yourself from your two partners and [pc.step] back, allowing [wolfgang.name] and [karl.name] to crawl away and collapse onto their respective beds. Grinning at the dobermann-boys, you get your things in order and thank them for the good time.
		</p>
		<p>
			Each letting out a deep groan, the bounty hunters lie back and catch their breath. As you turn around and head towards the door, you hear [wolfgang.name] pant to [karl.name], [wolfgang.speech(I need a little while to rest after that...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having had his fun, [wolfgang.name] steps back and lights up a cigarette, before grunting, [wolfgang.speech(You're a good fuck, slut!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[karl.name] likewise steps away from you, and after grabbing a bottle of Canine Crush from under his bed, he takes a big swig of it and then exclaims, [karl.speech(Damn, that was great!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			After flashing the dobermann-boys a smile and expressing your own satisfaction in how things turned out, you tell them that you'd better be on your way. Satisfied from the good, hard fuck you've just given them, they sit down on their respective beds, and as you head towards the door, [wolfgang.name] pant to [karl.name], [wolfgang.speech(I need a little while to rest after that...)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Exiting their room, you let out one last satisfied sigh before heading down the corridor towards the stairs...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="DOBERMANNS_AFTER_SEX_DOWNSTAIRS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You head back down the narrow staircase to the tavern's ground floor, before wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- SEATING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SEATING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Around the edge of the tavern there are several recessed seating areas, all of which are currently occupied by groups of rough-looking bounty hunters.
		#IF(game.getCharactersPresent().contains(silence))
			 In this particular area, however, you see that one of the recessed seating areas is occupied by the lone, familiar figure of Silence, the albino rat-girl whom you first met serving as one of Vengar's bodyguards. There's no sign of her companion, Shadow, although you're certain that she must be lurking somewhere nearby. You could always head over and say something to the mute rat-girl, or instead simply turn around and head back into the main section of the tavern...
		#ELSE
			 As you don't have any business with any of them, there's not much else you can do here but turn around and head back into the main section of the tavern...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- STAIRS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="STAIRS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		At the back of the tavern, a narrow, twisting staircase leads up to the first floor. A wooden sign reading 'Rooms for hire. Ask at bar.' has been fixed to the wall beside this staircase. Unfortunately for anyone looking for accommodation to rent, a paper note has been nailed to the bottom of this sign, which declares there to be 'No vacancies.'
	</p>
	<p>
		Although you have no business up there, there's nothing to stop you from heading up the stairs and having a look around the first floor of the tavern...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="STAIRS_UPSTAIRS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you want to take a look at the tavern's first floor, you travel up the narrow staircase and prepare to explore...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BOUNTY_BOARD -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BOUNTY_BOARD"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Positioned near to the tavern's entrance, a large wooden bounty board has been fixed to the wall, onto which dozens of pieces of paper have been tacked. Standing before this board, you see that most of the bounties have had the seals of one or more groups of bounty hunters imprinted onto them, signalling that there are already people out hunting for the requested fugitive.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking over the entire board, you see that there are some bounties which haven't yet been claimed. A promising poster fixed to the wall beside this bounty board declares that anyone is able to register as an official bounty hunter at the bar, and you wonder whether that sort of work is something you'd be interested in... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- BAR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The tavern's focal point takes the form of a long, wooden bar, behind which several barmaids and barmen are fulfilling the never-ending orders from the many patrons desperate for another drink. From their slurred, drunken speech and seemingly-unquenchable thirst, you can safely assume that most of the bounty hunters here end up spending a significant portion of their income on alcohol.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getRace()==RACE_DEMON)
			Noticing that you're a demon, the crowd parts to let you [pc.step] up to the bar.
		#ELSE
			Although it's not easy, you manage to push your way through the crowd and [pc.step] up to the bar.
		#ENDIF
		 While the menu hung up on the wall lists several different types of alcoholic beverage, the only item of food on offer is a bag of bar nuts. As you wonder whether to order something or not, you can't help but notice the fact that there's a rusty old slave collar hung up on the wall behind the bar, which you assume must be the tavern's namesake.
	</p>
	<p>
		Noticing you standing there, a rabbit-boy barman steps forwards and asks, [style.speechMasculine(So, what can I get for you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_NUTS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Placing an order for one bag of bar nuts, you hand over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, before receiving the small bag of [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]. Opening the pack, you quickly munch down the contents, before wondering whether or not to order a drink to help wash them down...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_BEER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Placing an order for a bottle of beer, you hand over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, before receiving the bottle of [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]. After the barman's popped off the cap and placed it down on the bar, you quickly lift the bottle to your waiting [pc.lips], before tilting your head back and drinking all of its delicious contents...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_CIDER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Placing an order for a bottle of cider, you hand over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you, before receiving the bottle of [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]. After the barman's popped off the cap and placed it down on the bar, you quickly lift the bottle to your waiting [pc.lips], before tilting your head back and drinking all of its delicious contents...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_VODKA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Placing an order for a glass of vodka, you hand over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you. After the barman's placed a glass down on the bar and filled it with [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1], you quickly lift your drink to your waiting [pc.lips], before tilting your head back and downing it in one large gulp...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_WHISKEY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Placing an order for a glass of whiskey, you hand over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you. After the barman's placed a glass down on the bar and filled it with [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1], you quickly lift your drink to your waiting [pc.lips], before tilting your head back and downing it in one large gulp...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="BAR_RUM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Placing an order for a glass of rum, you hand over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames asked of you. After the barman's placed a glass down on the bar and filled it with [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1], you quickly lift your drink to your waiting [pc.lips], before tilting your head back and downing it in one large gulp...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- UPSTAIRS_CORRIDOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="UPSTAIRS_CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Old, wooden floorboards creak underfoot as you [pc.walk] down the narrow, twisting corridor which links the rooms of the tavern's first floor. Although there are numerous arcane candles attached to the walls, their flickering light does little to illuminate the dark, wooden wall panels, giving this passageway a gloomy, creepy atmosphere.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- UPSTAIRS_STAIRS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="UPSTAIRS_STAIRS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself at the top of the narrow, twisting staircase, you wonder whether you should make use of it and travel back down to the ground floor, or instead set out to explore the tavern's first floor...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="UPSTAIRS_STAIRS_DOWNSTAIRS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to head back down to the tavern's ground floor, you descend the narrow staircase...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- UPSTAIRS_ROOM -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="UPSTAIRS_ROOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The wooden door before you, like all of the others up here on the tavern's first floor, has sign on it which declares the room to be occupied. With no reason to disturb the occupants, there's nothing for you to do here except turn around and head back down the corridor...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
