<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- OUTSIDE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="OUTSIDE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you navigate through the labyrinthine passageways of Dominion's back-alleys, you start to hear the faint murmur of voices coming from somewhere up ahead. Proceeding with caution, you slowly make your way around the next corner, and find yourself [pc.stepping] into a well-kept courtyard, which is paved over in clean, grey cobblestones. Positioned in the very centre of this small square, there stands a finely-carved stone figure, depicting a beautiful human slave bowing her head in submission.
	</p>
	<p>
		Continuing to move forwards, you see that multiple narrow entrances link three of this area's walled sides to the surrounding alleyways, while on the fourth there's a huge, open gateway, through which the sounds of a busy marketplace can be heard. The words 'Slaver Alley' have been cast into this gate's dull iron framing, while to either side of it, posters advertising a multitude of different slave traders have been plastered all over the weathered brick walls. A pair of muscular horse-boys are standing guard a little way inside, and from the fact that their attention is fixed entirely on looking inwards towards Slaver Alley, you suspect that their only job is to make sure that no runaway slaves slip past them.
	</p>
	#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
		<p>
			There doesn't seem to be any sign that these horse-boys are affected by the ongoing arcane storm, and as a particularly large bolt of pink lightning flashes across the sky, you see the faint shimmer of a vast arcane shield protecting both them and all of Slaver Alley from its effects.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			While it's nowhere near as busy as the main streets of Dominion, this area still sees a relatively high level of foot traffic. As you've been standing here, several shoppers, often accompanied by one or more slaves, have already crossed the courtyard, heading either to or from the heavily-patrolled alleyway which leads back out to the city's busy boulevard.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		If you wanted to, you could pass through the gateway and enter Slaver Alley right now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- GATEWAY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GATEWAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing in the gateway which links Slaver Alley to the rest of Dominion. On either side of this entrance, two horse-boy private security guards are keeping a watchful eye on anyone who passes through here; they're mostly focused on looking inwards towards Slavery Alley, as their primary duty is being on the lookout for any runaway slaves.
	</p>
	<p>
		The brick walls to either side of this gateway have been plastered with promotional posters, and while the vast majority of them are advertising stores within Slaver Alley itself, you see plenty of others promoting everything from soft drinks to brothels in Dominion's red-light district.
		#IF(pc.isQuestProgressGreaterThan(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_HELENA, QUEST_ROMANCE_HELENA_6_ADVERTISING))
			 True to their word, the guards have prevented anyone from pasting adverts over the six enchanted posters of Helena which you put up in this area. As customers to Slaver Alley pass you by, you hear some of them commenting on the harpy matriarch's beautiful appearance.
		#ELSE
			 A large sign near to where the guards are standing declares that <i>'Permission must be obtained before putting up any advertisements!'</i>.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		The only place not plastered with these promotional posters is the spot where a touristy-looking information board has been screwed to the wall, and upon reading it, you discover that a powerful arcane shield has been erected over the entire area, which protects everyone beneath it from the lust-inducing effects of any ongoing arcane storm. True enough, as you glance up at the sky, you see the faint pink crackle of the shield's arcane energy, reassuring you that you needn't worry about attacks from any horny citizens.
	</p>
	<p>
		Continuing to skim over the information board, you read that a person must be in possession of a slaver license before being able to buy or sell slaves. According to the next paragraph, these slaver licenses may be obtained from the 'Slaver Administration' building, which is apparently only a short distance away from where you're currently standing.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GATEWAY_POSTERS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		<i>You'd better speak to the guards before starting to put up Helena's posters...</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- GATEWAY_POSTER_PERMISSION -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GATEWAY_POSTER_PERMISSION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that Helena is expecting you to immediately get on with your task, you [pc.walk] directly over to the entrance of Slaver Alley, where you see that two horse-boy guards are standing on duty. A large sign fixed to one of the nearby walls declares that <i>'Permission must be obtained before putting up any advertisements!'</i>, and as the two guards are keeping a close watch on you, there'd be no way to put up Helena's posters without being seen and stopped by them. Realising that you have no choice but to first obtain their permission, you step up to the older-looking of the two, who you assume to be the one in charge, and ask him if you could put your six posters up.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculineStrong(More posters, huh?)] he grunts, [style.speechMasculineStrong(Sure, you can put them up, but it's going to cost you a hundred flames.)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasBreasts())
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isCoverableAreaExposed(CA_NIPPLES))
				[style.speechMasculine(If you don't want to pay, you could let us get a good feel of your tits instead!)]
			#ELSE
				[style.speechMasculine(If you don't want to pay, you could flash us your tits instead!)]
			#ENDIF
			 the second, younger horse-boy interjects, [style.speechMasculine(That'll keep me going until the end of my shift!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			The older horse-boy grunts in approval at this suggestion, letting you know that if you wanted to avoid paying the hundred flame fee, you could always do as his subordinate suggests...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			From their stern glares, you realise that there wouldn't be much point in trying to convince them to waive the fee, and so you're left with the choice of either paying up now, or returning to give them their money at another time...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GATEWAY_POSTER_PERMISSION_PAID"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Producing the hundred flames asked of you, you hand them over to the senior of the two horse-boys. With an approving grunt and nod of his head he says, [style.speechMasculineStrong(Right, go on then, you can put your posters up.)] 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GATEWAY_POSTER_PERMISSION_GROPED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to do as the younger guard suggests, you step forwards and push your [pc.breastSize] breasts out towards him, [pc.speech(Go on then, get a good feel!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not hesitating for a moment, the horse-boy greedily reaches out and grabs your tits, letting out a horny grunt as he playfully squeezes your [pc.nipples] between his rough fingers. Not wanting to miss out on the action, the second horse-boy steps over and joins the first in groping your breasts, grinning lecherously at your exposed [pc.nipples] as you unwittingly let out [pc.a_moan+]. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculine(Fucking nice... That'll do for me!)] the younger horse-boy declares, giving your tits one final squeeze before stepping back to his post.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculineStrong(Yeah, that'll keep me going until I can get a good fuck once my shift's over,)] his superior says, similarly giving your [pc.nipples+] one last pinch before stepping back. Waving his hand at the walls, he declares, [style.speechMasculineStrong(Go on then, you can put your posters up now!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GATEWAY_POSTER_PERMISSION_FLASH_BREASTS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to do as the younger guard suggests, you shift aside your clothing so that your [pc.breastSize] breasts and [pc.nipples+] are fully exposed. Pointing them in the direction of the two guards, you ask, [pc.speech(Is this what you wanted to see?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculine(Oh yeah, those're fucking nice!)] the younger horse-boy declares, grinning lustfully at your tits.
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculineStrong(Yeah, that'll keep me going until I can get a good fuck once my shift's over,)] his superior says while starting hungrily at your [pc.nipples]. Letting out a satisfied sigh, he waves his hand at the walls and declares, [style.speechMasculineStrong(Go on then, you can put your posters up now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving your clothing back into their previous position, you prepare to do as the guard says...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GATEWAY_POSTER_PERMISSION_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking a look at the walls on either side of the gateway, you see that they're already completely plastered with advertisements, and there's not a single free spot available where you can put up yours. Sensing what it is you're thinking, the younger of the two horse-boy guards says, [style.speechMasculine(Just paste them over some other poster; someone else will be along to do the same to yours before too long anyway.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hoping that that doesn't turn out to be the case, you unroll the first of the posters, and relying on its enchantment to stick itself to the wall, you press it down over the top of an advertisement for Starr cigarettes. Sure enough, the poster adheres to the wall without need for any glue, and after [pc.stepping] back and admiring the moving image of Helena posing in her bikini, you move over and get started on putting up the next one. Before you're able to do so, however, the senior horse-boy lets out a low whistle and comments, [style.speechMasculineStrong(Damn... I'm sure I've seen her on the cover a magazine before. Is she one of those harpy queens or something?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Replying in the affirmative, you finish putting up the next poster, which causes the younger of the two horse-boys to excitedly comment, [style.speechMasculine(Woah! This one's in a different pose to the last! Look at her tits! Harpies don't usually have them that big!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Sure enough, this second poster you've just put up shows Helena in a different pose to the first; provocatively leaning forwards towards the viewer, she's gently swaying her body from side-to-side, which is causing her [helena.cupSize]-cup breasts to ponderously swing back and forth. Urged to continue by the two horse-boys, you put up the third poster beside the second, before [pc.stepping] over to the opposite wall and putting up the remaining three on that side. Each of the six posters turns out to display a bikini-clad Helena in a unique pose, and as you finish putting up the last one, the senior horse-boy comments, [style.speechMasculineStrong(There's no way I'm letting anyone put their posters over the top of these! Damn... This job suddenly became a lot more bearable!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can respond to this, you suddenly notice a dark figure quickly approaching from one side, and you turn to see that it's none other than Scarlett herself. With the usual scowl on her face, she's making her way directly towards you, and you wonder what it is she wants...
	</p>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GATEWAY_POSTER_PERMISSION_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling the guards that you'll come back to put up the posters another time, you step back and prepare to continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- GATEWAY_POSTER_PERMISSION_END_RETURN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="GATEWAY_POSTER_PERMISSION_END_RETURN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Completely ignoring the two horse-boy guards, Scarlett walks up right in front of you and flatly states, [scarlett.speech(You're finally done with putting those stupid fucking posters up? Helena's got something else for you to do now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[style.speechMasculine(I'd hardly call them stupid,)] the younger horse-boy comments as he hears what it is that Scarlett's saying.
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speech(How about you shut the fuck up, you dumb fucking cunt? I wasn't fucking talking to you!)] the foul-mouthed harpy snaps, before turning back to you and ordering, [scarlett.speech(Follow me back to the store.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can ask any further questions, the rude harpy simply turns her back on you and marches off. Leaving the younger horse-boy guard complaining to his senior about the mannerisms of harpies, you prepare to follow Scarlett back to Helena's Boutique...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- ALLEYWAY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="ALLEYWAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself walking down one of Slaver Alley's numerous interconnected passageways. Lined with clean, grey cobblestone, and being almost as wide as a normal street, they're quite unlike the regular sort of passages that make up the rest of Dominion's back-alleys.
		#IF(game.isDayTime())
			 Colourful canvas awnings have been unfurled from the sides of the surrounding buildings, and, looking up through the gap in the middle, you see a faint pink crackle evidence of the shield that protects Slaver Alley from arcane storms.
		#ELSE
			 A series of arcane-powered lights cast a flickering glow over the area, and as you look up at the night sky, you see a faint pink crackle evidence of the shield that protects Slaver Alley from arcane storms.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Although not as busy as Dominion's main streets, there are still a significant amount of people wandering about, and you often have to push your way through small crowds that inexplicably decide to loiter right in the middle of the path. The close proximity of the surrounding buildings echoes and amplifies the crowd's inane chatter, making Slaver Alley feel more alive than any other part of the city you've wandered through.
	</p>
	<p>
		The most striking feature of this area is the manner of goods that are sold here. Down each passageway, multiple wooden stands have been erected, and on top each one, slaves of all different races and sexes are being publicly displayed. You see that information boards have been attached to each one of these stands, giving you instructions as to which shop you need to visit in order to negotiate the purchase of the wares on display.
	</p>
	<p>
		Glancing up at the slaves as you pass, you notice that the one thing they all have in common is that they're all wearing metal collars of some sort or another. Apart from that peculiar accessory, the vast majority of them are completely naked, although you do see a few that have been dressed in skimpy pieces of highly-revealing clothing.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- DESERTED_ALLEYWAY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="DESERTED_ALLEYWAY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With its concealed entrance originally revealed to you by [sean.name], this hidden alleyway is once again completely deserted. Even if its location were widely known, you can't imagine why anyone would willingly come back here, as there's absolutely nothing to see except dilapidated brickwork and the odd weed poking up through the cracked concrete path.
	</p>
	<p>
		There really isn't anything to do here except turn around and leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL_FEMALE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_FEMALE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In the far right corner of Slaver Alley's main square, sits the slaver shop, 'A Woman's Touch'. The delicate pink lettering which proudly displays this establishment's name is painted over the dark purple silhouette of an hourglass-shaped woman.
	</p>
	<p>
		Just like all the other slaver stores, large glass windows are set into the frontage, allowing passers-by to check out what goods are on offer as they walk past. As you find yourself approaching the entrance, a very delicate-looking cat-girl, who you assume to be one of the shop assistants, steps out in front of you and curtsies. [genericFemale.speech(Please excuse me, [pc.Sir], but would you be interested in browsing our stock? We have new slaves finishing our training regimen every day, who are then ready for purchasing. You won't find girls anywhere else who are as well-trained and obedient as the ones we offer.)]
	</p>
	#IF pc.isHasSlaverLicense()
	#THEN
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Alright,)] you reply, [pc.speech(I can take a look around.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Smiling at you in delight, the cat-girl leads you inside the store, and as you're shown around, you notice a few slaves on offer that you might be interested in...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Can anyone buy these slaves, then?)] you ask.
		</p>
		<p>
			[genericFemale.speech(Oh, please forgive me, [pc.Sir]! I assumed you had a slaver license. Please do come back if you were ever to obtain one,)] the cat-girl hastily explains, curtsying once more before disappearing back into the shop.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL_MALE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_MALE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In the far left corner of Slaver Alley's main square, there's a slave shop that's quite unlike most of the others. Whereas all the other buildings that you've passed have had ornately-painted signs and decorative frontages, the one before you is of a plain wooden finish, and has its name, 'Iron & Steel', burnt into the framework.
	</p>
	<p>
		Most of the other shops have large glass windows by which to show off their goods to passers-by, but this one goes a step further, and the whole wooden frontage is actually a series of cleverly-designed sliding panels, about half of which have been pulled to one side. Looking into the open store, you see that all the slaves within appear to be males, and as you pass, a bulky bull-boy steps out and blocks your way, before cheerfully booming, [genericMale.speech(Taking a good look at our stock, I see! Why not come on in?! I'm sure we've got the right guy for you! Breeding studs, manual labourers, even pretty-boy models! We've got it all!)]
	</p>
	#IF pc.isHasSlaverLicense()
	#THEN
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Maybe a quick look,)] you reply, stepping forwards alongside the smiling bull-boy into the store...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I don't have a licence, I'm afraid,)] you reply, continuing on past the salesman.
		</p>
		<p>
			[genericMale.speech(Well, if you ever get one, then you know where to visit for the best male slaves in the city!)] the bull-boy shouts after you, before disappearing back into his shop.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL_ANAL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_ANAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		On one of the three sides of the square, a shop proudly displays an ass-shaped sign bearing the words, 'The Rear Entrance'. Knowing exactly what sort of slaves must be sold in there, you take a look through the large glass windows as you pass. Sure enough, you see that the slaves on display are all making sure to show off their asses, each of which is decorated by either a plain or jewelled butt-plug.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you walk past the front door, a short cat-boy darts out to block your path, before placing his hands on his hips and grinning cheekily at you. [genericMale.speech(You like butts, right?! Come on inside! We've got the best asses in all of Dominion, and each and every one of our slaves have been specially trained to love anal sex!)]
	</p>
	#IF pc.isHasSlaverLicense()
	#THEN
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Ok,)] you reply, stepping forwards alongside the diminutive cat-boy into his store...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I don't have a licence, I'm afraid,)] you reply, continuing on past the salesman.
		</p>
		<p>
			[genericMale.speech(Well, you know where to visit as soon as you get one!)] the cat-boy squeaks, before rushing back into his shop.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL_VAGINAL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_VAGINAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		On the far side of the square, a slave shop has had its frontage painted all in white, and in flowing pink lettering, the name 'White Lilies' is painted beside an artistic depiction of a bunch of the very same flowers. It's quite clear from the feminine decor, as well as the fact that all of the naked slaves in the windows are showing off their well-kept pussies, that this particular store specialises in slaves who are in possession of female genitals.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you walk past the front door, a beautiful white-furred rabbit-girl steps out towards you, and in a refined tone she asks, [genericFemale.speech(Why hello there, would you be interested at all in browsing some of my wares? I can assure you that all of the slaves sold in my establishment are virgins, and have undergone specialist training so as to desire nothing more than to have their feminine sex broken in by their new owner. Would you like to be their first, I wonder?)]
	</p>
	#IF pc.isHasSlaverLicense()
	#THEN
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I've got a few minutes to spare,)] you reply, stepping forwards alongside the regal rabbit-girl into her store...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I don't have a licence, I'm afraid,)] you reply, continuing on past the salesman.
		</p>
		<p>
			[genericFemale.speech(Ah, that is a shame. Well, if you ever do acquire one, then please visit us again,)] the rabbit-girl says, smiling politely at you before stepping back into her shop.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL_ORAL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		On one side of the square, a rather shabby-looking slave store bears a mouth-shaped sign displaying the words, 'Viva Voce'. Beneath this, someone's scrawled some graffiti, and as you step forwards to take a closer look, you see that whoever wrote it wasn't the best at spelling, as it reads: 'It meens speakin fanci'.
	</p>
	<p>
		Having satisfied your curiosity, you turn to leave, but find that a very shady-looking rat-boy is blocking your path. Before you can say anything, he grins and steps forwards, before nodding at the sign. [genericMale.speech(It's Latin, ain't it? I kinda inherited this place from me old man, an' he was the one who gave it that name. He was real smart, see, an' I kept on forgettin' what it meant, so I 'ad to leave meself that note there!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ah, so you're the owner,)] you say, but before you can continue, the rat-boy laughs and steps over towards the door.
	</p>
	<p>
		[genericMale.speech(Yeah, tha's me! I kinda wanted to keep me old man's vision goin', see, so all me slaves fer sale 'ave been trained to love kissin', sucking cocks, eatin' girls out, all that kinda' stuff. We even 'ave a deal with some shady demon guy who give us these potions wot makes their lips all big and juicy! You comin' in to take a looksie? Y'won't regret it!)]
	</p>
	#IF pc.isHasSlaverLicense()
	#THEN
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Ok, sure, why not)] you reply, stepping forwards into the rat-boy's store...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I don't have a licence,)] you reply. [pc.speech(Maybe another time.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[genericMale.speech(Ah, yeah, no worries. You jus' make sure to come 'ere once ya got one, alright?)] the rat-boy replies, letting out a cackling laugh as he steps back into the shadows.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL_STATUE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_STATUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		In the middle of a small square on one side of Slaver Alley, there sits a very striking statue. Made completely out of jet-black obsidian, and standing at least twelve feet from head-to-toe, it's a masterfully-crafted depiction of what appears to be a buxom female fallen angel, with wide hips and massive, GG-cup breasts.
	</p>
	<p>
		Her huge, feathered wings reach up to the sky behind her, and, linked by heavy chains, bracers have been clasped around her delicate wrists and ankles. One of her hands is reaching down between her legs, where she's lewdly spreading her
		#IF(game.isGapeContentEnabled())
			 tentacled, gaping pussy
		#ELSE
			 tentacled pussy
		#ENDIF
		 for all to see, while the other is reaching around behind her back in order to dig her slender fingers into her exposed asshole.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking up at her face, you see that her beautiful features are contorted into an orgasmic scream, and, as evidence that her corruption has manifested itself into physical transformations other than just the one between her legs, an abnormally long tongue drops down out of her open mouth to push its way into one of her lip-shaped nipples, which appears in turn to be desperately sucking on the wet, squirming muscle.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.getOccupation()==OCCUPATION_TOURIST)
		<p>
			Letting out a low whistle, you remark to yourself, [pc.speech(
			[game.random(This must be one of them Baroque pieces I read about...
			| Europeans sure are blasé about nudity...)]
			)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		This lewd statue sits upon a squat, stone pedestal, no higher than six feet or so, and as you approach, you see these words appear: 'My name is Marlel, once the humblest of all angels; Look upon my form, ye enemies of Lilith, and despair.'
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_STATUE_IGNORANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Nobody in the square seems to be paying much attention to the statue, and you doubt that there's anybody here who would know of the creator or what this piece of their art is meant to represent, other than what's apparent from the words inscribed upon the base. Letting out a sigh, you take one last look at the lewd visage of the fallen angel before you, before continuing on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_STATUE_TRUTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		From what Lyssieth told you, this is no ordinary statue, and is in fact the petrified form of the corrupted archangel Marlel. Lyssieth's eldest sister, Lirecea, is responsible for her current situation, and you wonder if you'll be able to force the elder lilin to revert the petrification process when you inevitably end up confronting her. Possessing no way to release Marlel from her stone prison, you let out a sigh, and, taking one last look at her lewd visage, you continue on your way...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL_EXCLUSIVE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_EXCLUSIVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to take a look inside one of the many shops that fill Slaver Alley, you approach the entrance to the nearest building. In order to display yet more slaves to passing customers, you see that a series of large glass windows have been installed into the walls before you. As you walk up to the entrance, some of the slaves standing behind these windows glance your way; no doubt wondering if you'll be their next owner.
	</p>
	<p>
		Pushing open the door, you step inside the shop, and find that the interior is surprisingly clean, well-lit, and airy. Yet more slaves line the walls around you, and in the middle of the room, the shop's owner calls out to you from behind a circular wooden desk, [style.speechMasculine(Good [style.afternoon]! Are you here to hire some slaves for your business?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After answering in the negative, the shop owner informs you that his store is one of several throughout Slaver Alley which specialises in renting slaves to businesses. Apparently, most of his clients are managers of companies here in Dominion who occasionally have to rent slaves to cover for temporary labour shortages.
	</p>
	<p>
		As this store is of no use to you, there's not much for you to do except say goodbye and [pc.step] back out into the street...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL_BULK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_BULK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Flanked on both sides by a pair of huge warehouses, the store you find yourself standing in front of is without doubt the largest in all of Slaver Alley. Looking up at the large lettering that's printed across all three of these large buildings, you see that they're part of something called the 'Zaibatsu Exchange'.
	</p>
	<p>
		While the warehouses are quite clearly not open to the public, you can see through the store's large windows that there are dozens of slaves on sale within. Wondering if you should go inside and take a look around, you [pc.walk] nearer to the front entrance, but as you approach, a wolf-girl guard steps forwards to bar your way and roughly growls, [style.speechFeminine(Hey! I don't recognise your face! You're not a member, are you?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that it would be far more trouble than it's worth to lie to this aggressive wolf-girl, you truthfully reply in the negative. Letting out a deep, throaty growl, she says, [style.speechFeminine(Then you'd better not be thinking about trying to go inside. This place is for members only.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing no reason to cause a scene, you turn your back on the wolf-girl and [pc.walk] off back into Slaver Alley...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL_CAFE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You find yourself standing in front of one of the cosy cafés which are scattered throughout Slaver Alley. Open twenty-four hours a day, seven days of the week, these establishments offer a place in which weary members of the public can rest and recuperate. From the advertisement posters which have been placed in the windows, this particular café seems to be associated with the shop
		#IF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE)
			 'Viva Voce'. The poster nearest to the door states that you can <i>'Ask the café staff for a demonstration of our slaves' oral abilities'</i>.
		#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_2)
			 'Iron & Steel'. The poster nearest to the door states that you can <i>'Ask the café staff for a demonstration of our slaves' strength and virility'</i>.
		#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_3)
			 'The Rear Entrance'. The poster nearest to the door states that you can <i>'Ask the café staff for a demonstration of our slaves' anal abilities'</i>.
		#ELSE
			 'A Woman's Touch'. The poster nearest to the door states that you can <i>'Ask the café staff for a demonstration of our slaves' obedience and desire to please'</i>.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			Looking through the front windows, you see that the café is currently very busy, with almost all of the tables being occupied. Despite this, however, you think that you'd be able to find a seat if you wanted to go inside and get something to eat or drink...
		#ELSE
			Looking through the front windows, you see that the café is currently very quiet, with almost all of the tables being empty. If you wanted to, you could go inside and get something to eat or drink...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL_CAFE_INTERIOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_INTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to take a break, you push open the door to the café and step inside. Looking around the roomy interior, you see that there are about two dozen tables, most of which
		#IF(game.isExtendedWorkTime())
			 are occupied.
		#ELSE
			 are unoccupied.
		#ENDIF
		 Over on one side of the room, there's a long counter, and behind a layer of protective glass you see all sorts of cakes and snacks on display.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE)
		<p>
			Noticing your entry, [npc.a_race] waitress, who's wearing a light blue maid's outfit, and who has a heavy metal collar around her neck, hurries over to where you're standing. Her [npc.lips+] are covered in a thick layer of golden lipstick, and as they turn up into a shy smile, she curtsies and says in a soft voice,
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCafe1Visited))
				 [npc.speech(Welcome to our café, [pc.sir]; it's good to see you again. Please follow me and I'll show you to your table.)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc.speech(Welcome to our café, [pc.sir]. My name is [npc.name]; I'm a slave from the shop 'Viva Voce', and if you're impressed by my service then you can find many slaves like me for sale there. Please follow me and I'll show you to your table.)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF(pc.getTotalTimesHadSex(npc)>0)
			<p>
				Doing as the maid-waitress asks, you follow her as she leads you over to an empty table next to one of the windows. Handing you a menu, she states, [npc.speech(All food and drink must be paid for at the moment of order. Please call me over once you've made your selection.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCafe1DailyDemonstrated))
					After pausing to let out a slightly frustrated sigh, the [npc.race] whines, [npc.speech(I'm sorry, but if you want another demo, you'll have to come back tomorrow; I'm only allowed to give one demo per customer per day...)]
				#ELSE
					After pausing to flash you a shy smile, the [npc.race] lets out an excited giggle and says, [npc.speech(If you want another demo, just call me over and let me know...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				With that, the waitress blushes and rushes over to another table which requires her attention, leaving you to decide what you'd like to order...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Doing as the maid-waitress asks, you follow her as she leads you over to an empty table next to one of the windows. Handing you a menu, she states, [npc.speech(All food and drink must be paid for at the moment of order. Please call me over once you've made your selection. Oh, and if you'd like a demonstration of what slaves from 'Viva Voce' can do, then please let me know... I'll be happy to show you...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				With that, the waitress flashes you a sunny smile and rushes over to another table which requires her attention, leaving you to decide what you'd like to order...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_2)
		<p>
			Noticing your entry, a muscular, [npc.race] waiter, who's wearing black crotchless chaps and a navy blue t-shirt, and who has a heavy metal collar around his neck, confidently strides over to where you're standing. Thanks to his choice of leg-wear, you can see that there's a huge bulge pressing out from beneath his black briefs,
			#IF(pc.isAttractedTo(npc))
				 and you can't help but glance at it as he grins and declares,
			#ELSE
				 and you try to avoid looking at it again as he grins and declares,
			#ENDIF
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCafe2Visited))
				 [npc.speech(Welcome to our café, [pc.sir]; thanks for coming back again. Please follow me and I'll show you to your table.)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc.speech(Welcome to our café, [pc.sir]. My name is [npc.name]; I'm a slave from the shop 'Iron & Steel', and if you're impressed by my service then you can find many slaves like me for sale there. Please follow me and I'll show you to your table.)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF(pc.getTotalTimesHadSex(npc)>0)
			<p>
				Doing as the waiter asks, you follow him as he leads you over to an empty table next to one of the windows. Handing you a menu, he states, [npc.speech(All food and drink must be paid for at the moment of order. Please call me over once you've made your selection.)]
			</p>
			#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(npc))
				<p>
					Looking down at your pregnant belly, [npc.name] grins and asks,
					#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(npc))
						 [npc.speech(Looks like I really gave you the full breeding demo experience, huh?)]
					#ELSE
						 [npc.speech(You're still pregnant from the breeding demo I gave you, huh?)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					After you've replied to confirm that he's the father, [npc.name] lets out a satisfied grunt and states,
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCafe2DailyDemonstrated))
						 [npc.speech(If you want another demo, you'll have to come back tomorrow; I'm only allowed to give one demo per customer per day.)]
					#ELSE
						 [npc.speech(If you want another demo, just call me over and let me know.)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCafe2DailyDemonstrated))
						After pausing to let out a slightly frustrated grunt, the [npc.race] states, [npc.speech(If you want another demo, you'll have to come back tomorrow; I'm only allowed to give one demo per customer per day.)]
					#ELSE
						After pausing to flash you a knowing look, the [npc.race] grins and states, [npc.speech(If you want another demo, just call me over and let me know.)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Doing as the waiter asks, you follow him as he leads you over to an empty table next to one of the windows. Handing you a menu, he states, [npc.speech(All food and drink must be paid for at the moment of order. Please call me over once you've made your selection. Oh, and if you'd like a demonstration of what slaves from 'Iron & Steel' can do, then please let me know; I'll be more than happy to give you a full demonstration.)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			With that, the waiter flashes you a grin and strides over to another table which requires his attention, leaving you to decide what you'd like to order...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_3)
		<p>
			Noticing your entry, [npc.a_race] waiter, who's wearing a smart, black butler's uniform, and who has a heavy metal collar around his neck, gracefully steps over to where you're standing. Respectfully bowing to you, he states,
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCafe3Visited))
				 [npc.speech(Welcome to our café again, [pc.sir]; we're grateful that you've chosen to visit us again. Please follow me and I'll show you to your table.)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc.speech(Welcome to our café, [pc.sir]. My name is [npc.name]; I'm a slave from the shop 'The Rear Entrance', and if you're impressed by my service then you can find many slaves like me for sale there. Please follow me and I'll show you to your table.)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF(pc.getTotalTimesHadSex(npc)>0)
			<p>
				Doing as the waiter asks, you follow him as he leads you over to an empty table next to one of the windows. Handing you a menu, he states, [npc.speech(All food and drink must be paid for at the moment of order. Please call me over once you've made your selection.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCafe3DailyDemonstrated))
					After pausing to let out a soft sigh, the [npc.race] apologises, [npc.speech(I'm sorry, [pc.sir], but if you want another demo, you'll have to come back tomorrow; I'm only permitted to give one demo per customer per day.)]
				#ELSE
					After pausing to flash you a subtle smile, the [npc.race] says, [npc.speech(If you want another demo, then please don't hesitate to call me over and let me know.)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Doing as the waiter asks, you follow him as he leads you over to an empty table next to one of the windows. Handing you a menu, he states, [npc.speech(All food and drink must be paid for at the moment of order. Please call me over once you've made your selection. Oh, and if you'd like a demonstration of what slaves from 'The Rear Entrance' can do, then please let me know so that I can arrange a demonstration for you.)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			With that, the waiter bows to you once more, before gliding over to another table which requires his attention, leaving you to decide what you'd like to order...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Noticing your entry, a beautiful, [npc.race] waitress, who's wearing a burgundy virgin-killer sweater, black stockings and gloves, and who has a heavy metal collar around her neck, struts over to where you're standing. Provocatively biting her [npc.lip] and crossing her arms to push her [npc.cupSize]-cup breasts up, she says in a seductive tone,
			#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCafe3Visited))
				 [npc.speech(Welcome to our café again, [pc.sir]; I'm happy to see you here again. Please follow me and I'll show you to your table.)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc.speech(Welcome to our café, [pc.sir]. My name is [npc.name]; I'm a slave from the shop 'A Woman's Touch', and if you're impressed by my service then you can find many slaves like me for sale there. Please follow me and I'll show you to your table.)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF(pc.getTotalTimesHadSex(npc)>0)
			<p>
				Doing as the waitress asks, you follow her as she leads you over to an empty table next to one of the windows. Handing you a menu, she states, [npc.speech(All food and drink must be paid for at the moment of order. Please call me over once you've made your selection.)]
			</p>
			#IF(npc.isVisiblyPregnant() && npc.getPregnantLitter().getFather().equals(pc))
				<p>
					Rubbing her [npc.hands] over her [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)], [npc.name] grins
					#IF(!npc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
						 and reveals, [npc.speech(Yeah, you were the one to knock me up. No worries though; I kind of like being pregnant. Oh, and don't worry about anything; my owner is handling all of my needs.)]
					#ELSE
						 and says, [npc.speech(Yeah, I'm still pregnant, thanks to you. No worries though; I kind of like it. Oh, and don't worry about anything; my owner is handling all of my needs.)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					Not giving you much time in which to respond, the [npc.race]
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCafe4DailyDemonstrated))
						 sighs and states, [npc.speech(If you want another demo, you'll have to come back tomorrow; I'm only allowed to give one demo per customer per day.)]
					#ELSE
						 flashes you a seductive smile and states, [npc.speech(If you want another demo, just call me over and let me know.)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					#IF(flags.hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCafe2DailyDemonstrated))
						After pausing to let out a slightly frustrated sigh, the [npc.race] states, [npc.speech(If you want another demo, you'll have to come back tomorrow; I'm only allowed to give one demo per customer per day.)]
					#ELSE
						After pausing to flash you a seductive smile, the [npc.race] states, [npc.speech(If you want another demo, just call me over and let me know.)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Doing as the waitress asks, you follow her as she leads you over to an empty table next to one of the windows. Handing you a menu, she states, [npc.speech(All food and drink must be paid for at the moment of order. Please call me over once you've made your selection. Oh, and if you'd like a demonstration of what slaves from 'A Woman's Touch' can do, then please let me know... I'll be happy to show you...)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			With that, the waitress bats her eyelashes at you, and then after flashing one last smile, she struts over to another table which requires her attention, leaving you to decide what you'd like to order...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_INTERIOR_ORDER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Calling over the #IF(npc.isFeminine())waitress#ELSEwaiter#ENDIF, you place an order for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1], before handing over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_2] flames [npc.she] asks of you. Having received the payment, [npc.she] sets off into the kitchen, before swiftly returning to your table and placing the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] down in front of you.
		#IF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE)
			 Flashing you a cheery smile, she then quickly turns around and hurries off to another table which requires her attention.
		#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_2)
			 Flashing you a grin, he then turns around and strides off to another table which requires his attention.
		#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_3)
			 Giving you a small bow, he then turns around and steps over to another table which requires his attention.
		#ELSE
			 Flashing you a seductive smirk, she then quickly turns around and hurries off to another table which requires her attention.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Relaxing in your comfortable chair, you make small-talk with [com.name] as you [#SPECIAL_PARSE_3] your [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]...
		#ELSE
			Relaxing in your comfortable chair, you gaze out of the café's window and do some people-watching as you [#SPECIAL_PARSE_3] your [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_INTERIOR_ORDER_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Calling over the #IF(npc.isFeminine())waitress#ELSEwaiter#ENDIF, you place an order for [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1], before handing over the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_2] flames [npc.she] asks of you. Having received the payment, [npc.she] sets off into the kitchen, before returning to your table and placing the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1] down in front of [com.name].
		#IF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE)
			 Flashing the two of you a cheery smile, she then quickly turns around and hurries off to another table which requires her attention.
		#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_2)
			 Flashing the two of you a grin, he then turns around and strides off to another table which requires his attention.
		#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_3)
			 Giving the two of you a small bow, he then turns around and steps over to another table which requires his attention.
		#ELSE
			 Flashing the two of you a seductive smirk, she then quickly turns around and hurries off to another table which requires her attention.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Relaxing in your comfortable chair, you make small-talk with [com.name] as [com.she] [#SPECIAL_PARSE_3] [com.her] [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_DEMONSTRATION_EXPLANATION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE)
		<p>
			Wanting to know exactly what [npc.namePos] demonstration involves, you call over the waitress, before putting the question to her.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Oh, well, you know...)] she shyly responds, before slowly running her [npc.tongue] over her [npc.lips+] and revealing, [npc.speech(My owner's shop specialises in orally-trained slaves... I can take you around back and show you just how thorough my training has been... We'll keep going until you cum, then the demo's over...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly worried that she hasn't been clear enough, the [npc.race] blushes as she 
			#IF(pc.hasPenis() && pc.isCoverableAreaVisible(CA_PENIS))
				 looks down at your [pc.cock+] and declares, [npc.speech(I'll give you the best blowjob of your life! Just say the word, and you can be balls-deep down my throat in a few minutes...)]
			#ELSEIF(pc.hasVagina() && pc.isCoverableAreaVisible(CA_VAGINA))
				 looks down at your [pc.pussy+] and declares, [npc.speech(I'll give you the best cunnilingus of your life! Just say the word, and I'll be eating you out in a few minutes...)]
			#ELSE
				 declares, [npc.speech(I give the best blowjobs and cunnilingus in all of slaver alley! Just say the word, and I'll be showing you how good I am in a few minutes...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			At that moment, another customer calls for [npc.NamePos] attention. Before dashing off to see to them, she declares, [npc.speech(Just call me over if you want a demo!)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_2)
		<p>
			Wanting to know exactly what [npc.namePos] demonstration involves, you call over the muscular waiter, before putting the question to him.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(You get to feel how good my cock is,)] he confidently responds, before reaching down to squeeze the massive bulge between his legs and revealing, [npc.speech(My owner's shop specialises in strong, virile slaves. I'll take you around back and get you stuffed full of my fat cock to show you how good it is to own a slave like me. I'll fuck you until you cum, then the demo's over.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			At that moment, another customer calls for [npc.NamePos] attention. Before striding off to see to them, he declares, [npc.speech(Just call me over if you want a demo; I'll get you [pc.moaning] and orgasming in no time.)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_3)
		<p>
			Wanting to know exactly what [npc.namePos] demonstration involves, you call over the waiter, before putting the question to him.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Well, [pc.sir], my owner's store specialises in anally-trained slaves,)] he politely responds, before turning to one side and slightly pushing his [npc.ass+] out towards you. Flashing you a smile, he states, [npc.speech(You can use my ass however you'd like, or, if you prefer, I'll show you how much I love performing rimjobs.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			At that moment, another customer calls for [npc.NamePos] attention. Before striding off to see to them, he bows to you and says, [npc.speech(Please call me over if you want a demo; I promise that my ass won't disappoint you.)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to know exactly what [npc.namePos] demonstration involves, you call over the waitress, before putting the question to her.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Why, you get to fuck my pussy, of course!)] she confidently responds, before biting her [npc.lip] and teasing, [npc.speech(Or, if you'd prefer, I'll spread my legs and let you eat me out. My pussy tastes great, I promise!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			At that moment, another customer calls for [npc.NamePos] attention. Before strutting off to see to them, she winks at you and declares, [npc.speech(Just call me over if you want a demo!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_ORAL_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to put [npc.namePos] mouth to the test, you call over the waitress and tell her that you want to have a demonstration of her blowjob skills.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Yes, [pc.sir],)] she replies, before letting out an excited little moan and beckoning you to follow her. Skipping off to the far side of the café with you in tow, she blushes as she playfully teases, [npc.speech(I hope you don't mind getting your cock marked by my lipstick... My owner makes me wear a lot of it so that you can see how deep I can take you down my throat...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leading you into a small, carpeted office at the rear of the café, [npc.name] closes the door behind you, before wasting no time in dropping to her knees before you. Expertly gaining access to your cock before you even have time to say anything, she lets out a hungry moan and declares, [npc.speech(Oh yes, this'll do nicely! Remember, the demo ends once I make you orgasm...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning forwards, she darts out her [npc.tongue+] and delivers a long, slow lick up the length of your rapidly-hardening shaft, before dropping her head down and taking your [pc.cock+] into her mouth. Bobbing her head up and down, she starts making lewd, wet gargling noises as she starts giving you an enthusiastic blowjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_ORAL_CUNNILINGUS_RECEIVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to put [npc.namePos] tongue to the test, you call over the waitress and tell her that you want to have a demonstration of her cunnilingus skills.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Yes, [pc.sir],)] she replies, before letting out an excited little moan and beckoning you to follow her. Skipping off to the far side of the café with you in tow, she blushes as she playfully teases, [npc.speech(I hope you don't mind getting your pussy marked by my lipstick... My owner makes me wear a lot of it so clients can see how deep I can take their cocks...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leading you into a small, carpeted office at the rear of the café, [npc.name] closes the door behind you, before wasting no time in dropping to her knees before you. Expertly gaining access to your pussy before you even have time to say anything, she lets out a hungry moan and declares, [npc.speech(Oh yes, this'll do nicely! Remember, the demo ends once I make you orgasm...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning forwards, she darts out her [npc.tongue+] and delivers a long, slow lick over your [pc.labia+], before pushing her head forwards and pressing her [npc.lips+] against your [pc.pussy+]. Darting out her tongue and thrusting it into your cunt, she starts making lewd, wet kissing noises as she starts enthusiastically eating you out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_MASCULINE_BLOWJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get a taste of [npc.namePos] massive cock, you call him over and say that you want to get a demonstration of how good he is at face-fucking.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Hungry for this, are you?)] he grunts in amusement as he grabs hold of his massive bulge and hefts it up and down a couple of times. Replying in the positive, you can't help but let out an eager [pc.moan] as he dominantly takes you by the [pc.arm] and leads you over towards the back of the café, saying as he goes, [npc.speech(I'll have you choking and gargling on my fat cock in just a minute. You're going to love it, aren't you, you horny thing?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Once again replying in the positive, you happily allow the muscular [npc.race] to take you into a small, carpeted office that's located at the rear of the café. As [npc.name] closes the door and turns to face you, you eagerly drop down before him, and after quickly shifting his briefs to one side, you let out [pc.a_moan+] as his [npc.cock+] flops free.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Go on, get me hard,)] [npc.name] grunts, and you eagerly oblige by leaning forwards and planting a big, wet kiss on his [npc.cockHead+]. After licking and kissing his [npc.cock+] to get him hard, you open wide, allowing him to grab the sides of your head and thrust his [npc.cock+] into your mouth and down your throat. With lewd, wet gargling noises coming out of your throat with each one of his thrusts, the [npc.race] grunts, [npc.speech(I'll make you cum from this... ~Mmm!~ Remember, after you've orgasmed once, the demo's over...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_MASCULINE_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to feel [npc.namePos] massive cock pumping deep in and out of your [pc.pussy+], you call him over and say that you want to get a demonstration of how virile and hungry for sex he is.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Wanting to get rutted by this, huh?)] he grunts in amusement as he grabs hold of his massive bulge and hefts it up and down a couple of times. Replying in the positive, you can't help but let out an eager [pc.moan] as he dominantly takes you by the [pc.arm] and leads you over towards the back of the café, saying as he goes, [npc.speech(I'll have you stuffed full of my fat cock in just a minute. You're going to love it, aren't you, you horny thing?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Once again replying in the positive, you happily allow the muscular [npc.race] to take you into a small, carpeted office that's located at the rear of the café. As [npc.name] closes the door and turns to face you,
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 you eagerly turn around and drop down before him, presenting him with your hind-quarters in the process. Watching the muscular [npc.race] quickly shift his briefs to one side, you let out [pc.a_moan+] as you see his [npc.cock+] flopping free.
		#ELSE
			 you eagerly lie back before him, and after gaining access to your groin, you spread your [pc.legs] and present him with your [pc.pussy+].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You want it like that, huh?)] [npc.name] hungrily grunts.
		#IF(pc.isTaur())
			 Stepping forwards, he strokes his cock a few times, and thanks to the sight of your [pc.pussy+], he's rock-hard in just a moment. Wasting no time, he lines his [npc.cock+] up to your cunt, and after sliding the [npc.cockHead+] up and down over your [pc.labia+] a couple of times, he thrusts forwards, sinking his [npc.cock+] into your [pc.pussy+]. Pushing forwards, he fills you with his massive shaft, grunting as he does so, [npc.speech(I'll make you cum in no time! ~Mmm!~ Remember, after you've orgasmed once, the demo's over...)]
		#ELSE
			 Stepping forwards, he strokes his cock a few times, and thanks to the sight of your submissive posture and exposed [pc.pussy], he's rock-hard in just a moment. Wasting no time, he drops down over the top of you, grabbing your [pc.legs] and pushing them up and back towards your head as he does so. Locking you in the mating press position, he lets out another deep grunt as he lines his [npc.cock+] up to your cunt, and after sliding the [npc.cockHead+] up and down over your [pc.labia+] a couple of times, he drops down, sinking his [npc.cock+] into your [pc.pussy+] in the process. Ignoring your lewd squeals as he fills you with his massive shaft, he declares, [npc.speech(I'll make you cum in no time! ~Mmm!~ Remember, after you've orgasmed once, the demo's over...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_MASCULINE_ANAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to feel [npc.namePos] massive cock pumping deep in and out of your [pc.ass+], you call him over and say that you want to get a demonstration of how virile and hungry for anal sex he is.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Wanting your ass to get rutted by this, huh?)] he grunts in amusement as he grabs hold of his massive bulge and hefts it up and down a couple of times. Replying in the positive, you can't help but let out an eager [pc.moan] as he dominantly takes you by the [pc.arm] and leads you over towards the back of the café, saying as he goes, [npc.speech(I'll have you stuffed full of my fat cock in just a minute. You're going to love it, aren't you, you horny thing?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Once again replying in the positive, you happily allow the muscular [npc.race] to take you into a small, carpeted office that's located at the rear of the café. As [npc.name] closes the door and turns to face you, you eagerly turn around and drop down before him, presenting him with your [pc.ass+] in the process. Watching the muscular [npc.race] quickly shift his briefs to one side, you let out [pc.a_moan+] as you see his [npc.cock+] flopping free.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(You want it like that, huh?)] [npc.name] hungrily grunts. Stepping forwards, he strokes his cock a few times, and thanks to the sight of your exposed asshole, he's rock-hard in just a moment. Wasting no time, he lines his [npc.cock+] up to your rear entrance, and after sliding the [npc.cockHead+] up and down over your [pc.ass+] a couple of times, he thrusts forwards, sinking his [npc.cock+] into your [pc.asshole+]. Pushing forwards, he fills you with his massive shaft, grunting as he does so, [npc.speech(I'll make you cum in no time! ~Mmm!~ Remember, after you've orgasmed once, the demo's over...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_ANAL_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to fuck [npc.namePos] ass, you call over the waiter and tell him that you want a demo of how much he loves getting his ass rutted.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Of course, [pc.sir],)] he replies, before letting out a quiet, excited moan and gesturing for you to follow him. Walking over to the far side of the café with you in tow, he drops his professional mannerisms a little as he teases, [npc.speech(I can't wait to feel your cock pounding my butt... I love getting fucked in the ass so much...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leading you into a small, carpeted office at the rear of the café, [npc.name] closes the door behind you, before wasting no time in pulling down his trousers and bending over the office's desk, exposing his [npc.asshole+] to you in the process. Quickly gaining access to your cock, you [pc.step] forwards and rub the [pc.cockHead+] over the [npc.race]'s ass, causing him to moan, [npc.speech(Oh yes! ~Mmm!~ Please, [pc.sir], fuck my ass! Oh, and please remember that the demo ends once you cum...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wasting no more time, you line your [pc.cock+] up to [npc.namePos] rear entrance, before thrusting forwards and sinking your [pc.cock+] into his [npc.asshole+]. Pushing forwards, you fill the waiter's ass with your throbbing shaft, before pulling back and then thrusting forwards once more, causing him to moan and groan in delight as you fuck his [npc.ass+]...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_ANAL_ANILINGUS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get a rimjob from [npc.name], you call over the waiter and tell him that you want a demo of how much he loves performing anilingus.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Of course, [pc.sir],)] he replies, before letting out a quiet, excited moan and gesturing for you to follow him. Walking over to the far side of the café with you in tow, he drops his professional mannerisms a little as he teases, [npc.speech(I can't wait to get a taste of your ass...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling him that he'll get what he wants in just a moment, you happily allow the [npc.race] to take you into a small, carpeted office that's located at the rear of the café. As [npc.name] closes the door and turns to face you, you eagerly expose your [pc.asshole+] and lean forwards over the office's desk, presenting your [pc.ass+] to the waiter in the process. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Let's get started then!)] he happily exclaims, before dropping down behind you and leaning forwards to plant a big, wet kiss on your [pc.asshole+]. Pulling back for a moment, he moans, [npc.speech(Oh, please remember that the demo ends once you cum...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, [npc.name] buries his face between your [pc.assSize] ass cheeks, and after giving your rear entrance another passionate kiss, he darts out his tongue and starts to give you an enthusiastic rimjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_ANAL_TASTING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get a taste of [npc.namePos] ass, you call over the waiter and tell him that you want a demo of how much he loves to receive anilingus.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(Of course, [pc.sir],)] he replies, before letting out a quiet, excited moan and gesturing for you to follow him. Walking over to the far side of the café with you in tow, he drops his professional mannerisms a little as he teases, [npc.speech(I can't wait to get a rimjob from you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling him that he'll get what he wants in just a moment, you happily allow the [npc.race] to take you into a small, carpeted office that's located at the rear of the café. After he's closed the door, he wastes no time in pulling down his trousers and bending over the office's desk, exposing his [npc.asshole+] to you in the process. Quickly [pc.stepping] forwards, you drop down behind the [npc.race] and plant a big, wet kiss on his [npc.asshole+], causing him to moan, [npc.speech(Oh yes! ~Mmm!~ Please, [pc.sir], enjoy my ass! Oh, and please remember that the demo ends once you cum...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eager to get started, you bury your face between [npc.namePos] [npc.assSize] ass cheeks, and after giving his rear entrance another passionate kiss, you dart out your [pc.tongue+] and start to give him an enthusiastic rimjob...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_FEMININE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to fuck [npc.name], you call over the waitress and tell her that you want a demonstration of how good her pussy feels.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(~Mmm!~ You want to pound my little cunt, huh?)] she moans, before winking and beckoning you to follow her. Strutting off to the far side of the café with you in tow, she bites her lip as she looks back over her shoulder and playfully teases, [npc.speech(My owner said that clients can finish inside of me if they want, so don't worry about pulling out once I make you cum...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leading you into a small, carpeted office at the rear of the café, [npc.name] closes the door behind you, before wasting no time in pulling up her virgin-killer sweater and lying back over the office's desk. Spreading her legs, she exposes her [npc.pussy+] to you, before reaching down and using her [npc.fingers+] to spread her pussy lips. Quickly gaining access to your cock, you [pc.step] forwards and rub the [pc.cockHead+] over the [npc.race]'s [npc.labia+], causing her to excitedly squeal and moan, [npc.speech(Oh yes! ~Mmm!~ Come on, fuck me good and hard! Oh, and please remember that the demo ends once you cum...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wasting no more time, you line your [pc.cock+] up to [npc.namePos] [npc.pussy+], before thrusting forwards and sinking your [pc.cock+] into her hungry cunt. Pushing forwards, you fill the waitress's pussy with your throbbing shaft, before pulling back and then thrusting forwards once more, causing her to moan in delight...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_ORAL_CUNNILINGUS_GIVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to get a taste of [npc.namePos] pussy, you call over the waitress and tell her that you want a demonstration of how much she loves to be eaten out.
	</p>
	<p>
		[npc.speech(~Mmm!~ You want to get your tongue into my hot little cunt, huh?)] she moans, before winking and beckoning you to follow her. Strutting off to the far side of the café with you in tow, she bites her lip as she looks back over her shoulder and playfully teases, [npc.speech(You know, I'm something of a squirter, so apologies in advance if I end up making a mess all over your face...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leading you into a small, carpeted office at the rear of the café, [npc.name] closes the door behind you, before wasting no time in pulling up her virgin-killer sweater and sitting down on a nearby chair. Spreading her legs, she exposes her [npc.pussy+] to you, before reaching down and using her [npc.fingers+] to spread her pussy lips. Wanting to get started as soon as possible, you [pc.step] forwards and drop down between the [npc.race]'s legs, before planting a big, wet kiss on her [npc.labia+]. Stroking the top of your head, she loudly moans, [npc.speech(Oh yes! ~Mmm!~ Go on, get your tongue in there and have a good taste! Oh, and please remember that the demo ends once you cum...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Eager to get started, you bury your face between [npc.namePos] [npc.legs] and give her [npc.clit+] a passionate kiss. With the [npc.race] continuing to let out a stream of horny moans, you dart out your [pc.tongue+] and thrust it into her cunt, before starting to enthusiastically eat her out...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE)
		<p>
			As you've reached your climax, [npc.name] gently pushes you away from her and sighs, [npc.speech(Sorry, but my owner has ordered that I have to stop after my partner's first orgasm...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Although still horny and wanting to do more with the [npc.race], you realise from the tone of her voice that there's no room for negotiation, and so you [pc.step] back and set about getting your things back in order. Cleaning herself up with a few wet wipes, [npc.name] gets her uniform back in order and steps over to the door, asking, [npc.speech(Are you ready to head back to your table now, [pc.sir]?)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_2)
		<p>
			As you've reached your climax, [npc.name] takes a step back and grunts, [npc.speech(Sorry, babe, but my owner has ordered that I have to stop after your first orgasm. Come back tomorrow and we can do this again.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Although still horny and wanting to do more with the [npc.race], you realise from the tone of his voice that there's no room for negotiation, and so you [pc.step] back and set about getting your things back in order. Cleaning himself up with a few wet wipes, [npc.name] gets his uniform back in order and steps over to the door, asking, [npc.speech(Are you ready to head back to your table now?)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(pc.getLocationPlaceType()==PLACE_TYPE_SLAVER_ALLEY_CAFE_3)
		<p>
			As you've reached your climax, [npc.name] takes a step back and sighs, [npc.speech(I'm sorry, [pc.sir], but my owner has ordered that I have to stop after your first orgasm...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Although still horny and wanting to do more with the [npc.race], you realise from the tone of his voice that there's no room for negotiation, and so you [pc.step] back and set about getting your things back in order. Cleaning himself up with a few wet wipes, [npc.name] gets his uniform back in order and steps over to the door, asking, [npc.speech(Are you ready to head back to your table now, [pc.sir]?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As you've reached your climax, [npc.name] gently pushes you away from her and sighs, [npc.speech(Sorry, babe, but my owner has ordered that I have to stop after my partner's first orgasm...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Although still horny and wanting to do more with the [npc.race], you realise from the tone of her voice that there's no room for negotiation, and so you [pc.step] back and set about getting your things back in order. Cleaning herself up with a few wet wipes, [npc.name] gets her uniform back in order and steps over to the door, asking, [npc.speech(Are you ready to head back to your table now?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL_CAFE_AFTER_SEX_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Replying in the positive, you head back out into the café and allow [npc.name] to lead you back over to your table. Before departing, [npc.she] states, [npc.speech(Please call for me if you want to order anything. Oh, and I can't give you another demonstration until tomorrow at the earliest.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment, another customer calls for [npc.namePos] attention, and as the [npc.race] heads over to see what they want, you're left wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MARKET_STALL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MARKET_STALL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to take a look inside one of the shops, you approach the entrance to the nearest building. In order to display yet more slaves to passing customers, you see that a series of large glass windows have been installed into the walls before you. As you walk up to the entrance, some of the slaves standing behind these windows glance your way; no doubt wondering if you'll be their next owner.
	</p>
	<p>
		Pushing open the door, you step inside the shop, and find that the interior is surprisingly clean, well-lit, and airy. Yet more slaves line the walls around you, and in the middle of the room, the shop's owner cries out a greeting from behind a circular wooden desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		After browsing the wares for a moment, you decide that you've had enough. After all, without a permit, you're unable to buy anything.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUCTION_BLOCK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUCTION_BLOCK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you walk towards Slaver Alley's central courtyard, the excited buzz of hundreds of voices grows louder and louder. The source of this incessant din is hard to miss, and takes the form a huge, bustling crowd, which has surrounded a raised wooden platform. Several noticeboards, elevated above the heads of the energetic mob by means of tall poles, declare this area to be for 'Public Auctions'.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isHasSlaverLicense())
			Being in possession of a slaver's license, you wonder if you should approach the stage and participate in the next auction.
		#ELSE
			The noticeboards also declare that you'd need a slaver license in order to participate in any auctions, so, not being in possession of one yourself, there'd be no point in approaching the stage.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUCTION_BLOCK_LIST -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUCTION_BLOCK_LIST_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You make your way through the pressing crowds and take your place on the outskirts of the main bidding area. The information boards in this section seem to carry quite a lot more detail than those on the outskirts of the courtyard, and upon reading one, you discover a little more about the slaves that are on offer here.
	</p>
	<p>
		According to the notice board, the vast majority of slaves are bought and sold by through the stores that scattered throughout slaver alley, but in the cases of a slave owner's assets being seized, or if a slave owner somehow ends up being enslaved themselves, all slaves that they owned are put up for public auction. It also states that some slaves willingly sell themselves in order to pay off their debts, and offering themselves up at a public auction is apparently a popular choice for those individuals.
	</p>
	<p>
		Attached to the bottom of each of the noticeboards is a list of the slaves that are up next for the public auction. After reading through the list of names, you wonder if you should stick around to place a bid on any of them...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUCTION_IMPORT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUCTION_IMPORT_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You can import any of your previously exported characters in order to add them to the auctioning list. Once imported, this character will show up in the auction list, and by bidding on them you can purchase them and add them as one of your slaves.
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>You can export any character in the game by viewing their character sheet and pressing the little export button in the bottom-right of the screen.</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AUCTION_BIDDING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUCTION_BIDDING_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you'd like to try and bid on [npc.name], you hang around the area until [npc.sheIs] up for auction. Thankfully, you don't have to wait long, and soon enough you see the [npc.race], stark naked except for the slave collar around [npc.her] neck, being led up onto the platform.
	</p>
	<p>
		Within moments, the bidding starts, and [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] quickly matches the starting price, muttering, [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>The current bid is [#SPECIAL_PARSE_2], which means that you'll need to bid [#SPECIAL_PARSE_3] to get in the lead for buying [npc.name].</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUCTION_IMPORT_VICTORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] backs out of the bidding, sighing, [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]
	</p>
	<p>
		Nobody else in the crowd offers another bid, leaving the auctioneer to call out, [maleNPC.speech(Going once... Going twice... Sold! To the [pc.race] at the back!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Walking towards the stage, you pay the auctioneer's assistant the amount that you bid, totalling [#SPECIAL_PARSE_2]. She informs you that your new slave will be ready for collection from the Slavery Administration building, before handing over the paperwork which proves your ownership of [npc.name].
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUCTION_IMPORT_DEFEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You back out of the bidding, which allows the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] you were competing with to win the auction.
	</p>
	<p>
		Nobody else in the crowd offers another bid, leaving the auctioneer to call out, [maleNPC.speech(Going once... Going twice... Sold! To the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] near the back!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] walks towards the stage to finalise their purchase of [npc.name], you hear them mutter, [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AUCTION_IMPORT_CONTINUE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] continues to bid against someone else, taking [npc.namePos] asking price up to [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1].
	</p>
	<p>
		<i>The current bid is [#SPECIAL_PARSE_1], which means that you'll need to bid [#SPECIAL_PARSE_2] to get in the lead for buying [npc.name].</i>
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The collection of twenty-or-so public stocks, positioned right in the middle of a wide courtyard, is the first thing anyone sees when entering Slaver Alley. Used as a means of punishment for disobedient slaves, each one of the devices consists of a wooden frame, with holes for securing the occupant's arms and head. A small sign positioned next to each one informs members of the public as to what kinds of use have been permitted by the slave's owner.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although more than half of the stocks are currently occupied, most of the slaves are locked up just as a means of humiliating them, and are clearly marked as being unavailable for public use. Not all of the slaves are so lucky, however, as you see that a few of them are marked as being publicly available for one type of penetration or another.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_FREED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		The collection of twenty-or-so public stocks, positioned right in the middle of a wide courtyard, is the first thing anyone sees when entering Slaver Alley. Used as a means of punishment for disobedient slaves, each one of the devices consists of a wooden frame, with holes for securing the occupant's arms and head. A small sign positioned next to each one informs members of the public as to what kinds of use have been permitted by the slave's owner.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although quite a few of the stocks are currently occupied, all of the slaves have been marked as unavailable for public use. Knowing that this is thanks to your earlier actions, you can't help but smile to yourself as you pass by...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_ENFORCER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_seanIntroduced))
			Over on one side of the square, you see the familiar figure of [sean.name] leaning back against a brick wall. He looks to be incredibly bored, and you wonder if you should give him something to do by walking up to him and making conversation.
		#ELSE
			Over on one side of the square, you see a [sean.race] Enforcer leaning back against a brick wall. He looks to be incredibly bored, and you wonder if you should give him something to do by walking up to him and making conversation.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEX_SOLO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Deciding that you'd like to have some fun with [npc.race] in the stocks nearest to you, you tell [com.name] to stand back and watch as you walk up behind the slave. [npc.She] lets out a little [npc.moan] as [npc.she] hears you approach, and shifts [npc.her] [npc.hips+] in anticipation of what's about to happen...
		#ELSE
			Deciding that you'd like to have some fun with the [npc.race] in the stocks nearest to you, you walk up behind [npc.herHim]. [npc.She] lets out a little [npc.moan] as [npc.she] hears you, and shifts [npc.her] [npc.hips+] in anticipation of what's about to happen...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEX_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(!npc2.isAttractedTo(pc) || !npc2.isAttractedTo(npc))
			Deciding that you'd like to have some fun with [npc.race] in the stocks nearest to you, you tell [npc2.name] to join you as you walk up behind the slave. Clearly not at all wanting to do this, [npc2.she] mutters, [npc2.speech(Eugh... If I <i>have</i> to...)]
		#ELSE
			Deciding that you'd like to have some fun with [npc.race] in the stocks nearest to you, you tell [npc2.name] to join you as you walk up behind the slave. Clearly happy to be joining in on the fun, [npc2.she] exclaims, [npc2.speech(Oh, this is going to be good!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping up behind [npc.name], you give [npc.her] [npc.ass+] a little slap, causing [npc.herHim] to let out [npc.a_moan+]. Seeing that you've taken [npc.her] behind, [npc2.name] steps around in front of the slave and prepares to use [npc.her] mouth...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_STOCKS_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_STOCKS_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			#IF(sex.getNumberOfOrgasms(npc)>0)
				Having had your fun, you and [com.name] step back, grinning as you hear [npc.name] let out a satisfied [npc.moan]. Several members of the public who stopped to watch the two of you using the helpless [npc.race] compliment you both on your performance, and as you move away, one of them steps forwards to have a turn with the [npc.race] themselves...
			#ELSE
				Having had your fun, you and [com.name] step back, grinning as you hear [npc.name] let out a frustrated [npc.moan]. Several members of the public who stopped to watch the two of you using the helpless [npc.race] comment on your performance, and as you move away, one of them steps forwards to have a turn with the [npc.race] themselves...
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(sex.getNumberOfOrgasms(npc)>0)
				Having had your fun with [npc.name], you step back, grinning as you hear [npc.herHim] out a satisfied [npc.moan]. Several members of the public who stopped to watch you using the helpless [npc.race] compliment you on your performance, and as you move away, one of them steps forwards to have a turn with the [npc.race] themselves...
			#ELSE
				Having had your fun with [npc.name], you step back, grinning as you hear [npc.herHim] let out a frustrated [npc.moan]. Several members of the public who stopped to watch you using the helpless [npc.race] comment on your performance, and as you move away, one of them steps forwards to have a turn with the [npc.race] themselves...
			#ENDIF

		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_seanIntroduced))
		<p>
			Deciding that you'd like to speak with [sean.name] again, you walk past the public stocks and head directly towards him. As you approach, you once again take note of the fact that he's [sean.a_raceStage] [sean.race], who stands at [sean.heightValue] in height. His fur is a washed-out, sandy shade of yellowy-orange, and he has a brilliant pair of light blue eyes, which lock onto you as you come to a halt in front of him.
		</p>
		#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant() && pc.isCharacterPossiblyFather(sean))
			#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(sean))
				<p>
					Looking down at your visibly-swollen belly, [sean.name] cheekily grins and remarks in his soft Irish accent, [sean.speech(Looks like you might have a few of my buns in your oven, hmm? Stay still a moment; let's find out!)]
				</p>
				#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(sean.getId()))
					<p>
						Doing as [sean.name] asks, you stand still as he produces an Arcane Pregnancy Tester out of one of his pockets, before swiping it over your belly and then stepping back to take a look at the results. As you see his face lighting up, you already know what he's going to say, but remain quiet to let him happily exclaim, [sean.speech(Yes! I'm the one that got you knocked up! Be a good mother to our kids now, won't you?)]
					</p>
					<p>
						Reassuring the excited [sean.race] that you will, you can't help but smile as the father of your children steps forwards and gently rubs his hand over your pregnant bump. Flashing you a cheeky grin, he says, [sean.speech(While I'm happy to let you know that I'm the dad, I think I'll leave the number of kids you're carrying as a nice surprise for you!)]
					</p>
				#ELSE
					<p>
						Doing as [sean.name] asks, you stand still as he produces an Arcane Pregnancy Tester out of one of his pockets, before swiping it over your belly and then stepping back to take a look at the results. As you see his excited smile quickly turn into a frown, you already know what he's going to say, but remain quiet to let him reveal, [sean.speech(So, I'm not the father... Oh well, maybe there'll be a next time...)]
					</p>
				#ENDIF
			#ELSEIF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(sean.getId()))
				<p>
					Looking down at your visibly-swollen belly, [sean.name] cheekily grins and remarks in his soft Irish accent, [sean.speech(You're still pregnant with our kids, hmm? I bet you're wondering how many are in there, but don't worry, you'll find out soon enough!)]
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			#IF(com.equals(brax))
				#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_seanSeenBrax))
					<p>
						#IF(brax.getRace()==RACE_WOLF_MORPH && !brax.isFeminine())
							Looking across to [brax.name], [sean.namePos] eyes suddenly open wide in shock. Furrowing his eyebrows, the [sean.race] asks, [sean.speech(Brax?! Is that you?! What are you doing out here?)]
						#ELSE
							Looking across to [brax.name], [sean.namePos] eyes suddenly open wide in shock. Furrowing his eyebrows, the [sean.race] mutters, [sean.speech(You know, you somehow remind me of Brax... Wait, that <i>is</i> you, isn't it?! What happened to you?!)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
					<p>
						#IF(brax.getName().equals("Brax"))
							[pc.speech([brax.Name] is my slave,)] you reveal, [pc.speech(I take it you know [brax.herHim]?)]
						#ELSE
							[pc.speech(<i>[brax.Name]</i> is my slave,)] you reveal, [pc.speech(I take it you know [brax.herHim]?)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
					<p>
						#IF(brax.isFeminine())
							[sean.speech(Do I know '[brax.herHim]', [pc.she] asks!)]
						#ELSE
							[sean.speech(Do I know [brax.herHim], [pc.she] asks!)]
						#ENDIF
						 [sean.name] exclaims in disbelief, throwing his arms up in the air and quickly pacing around in a tight circle. Turning back to face you, he reveals, [sean.speech(Of course I know [brax.herHim]; [brax.sheIs] the one who demoted me and assigned me to this wretched post!)]
					</p>
					<p>
						Addressing your [com.companion], [sean.name] continues,
						#IF(brax.isFeminine())
							 [sean.speech(So, you're a slave now?! And [brax.a_genderAppears] on top of that! Well, what goes around, comes around; it couldn't have happened to a more deserving person!)]
						#ELSE
							 [sean.speech(So, you're a slave now?! Well, what goes around, comes around; it couldn't have happened to a more deserving person!)]
						#ENDIF
					</p>
					<p>
						#IF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
							#IF(brax.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false))
								[brax.speech(Fuck you, [sean.surname],)] [brax.name] angrily replies, [brax.speech(I'm not surprised to see that you haven't managed to work your way out of this post; you always were a lazy fuck.)]
							#ELSE
								Narrowing [brax.her] eyes, [brax.name] makes an angry growling noise, letting [sean.name] know that the animosity is mutual.
							#ENDIF
						#ELSEIF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
							#IF(brax.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false))
								[brax.speech(I'm sorry for demoting you,)] [brax.name] mutters, submissively shuffling [brax.her] [brax.feet].
							#ELSE
								Casting [brax.her] [brax.eyes] to the floor, [brax.name] makes a submissive whining noise while simultaneously shuffling [brax.her] [brax.feet].
							#ENDIF
						#ELSE
							#IF(brax.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false))
								[brax.speech(What's done is done,)] [brax.name] says, crossing [brax.her] [brax.arms] and letting out a sigh.
							#ELSE
								crossing [brax.her] [brax.arms], [brax.name] makes a dismissive humming noise, letting [sean.name] know that [brax.she] isn't bothered by his animosity.
							#ENDIF
						#ENDIF
					</p>
					<p>
						[sean.speech(Well, whatever. I may just be <i>Constable</i> [sean.surname] thanks to you, but I guess there's no point in hating you for it,)]  [sean.name] sighs, before turning his gaze back to you and asking, [sean.speech(Now, what do you want?)]
					</p>
				#ELSEIF(com.isVisiblyPregnant() && com.isCharacterPossiblyFather(sean))
					#IF(!com.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(sean))
						<p>
							#IF(com.getName().equals("Brax"))
								Looking across to [com.name], [sean.name] grins and comments on [com.her] swollen belly, [sean.speech(Well, well, well. You wondering if it was me who got you pregnant, eh, [com.name]? You just say right there and we'll find out together!)]
							#ELSE
								Looking across to [com.name], [sean.name] grins and comments on [com.her] swollen belly, [sean.speech(Well, well, well. You wondering if it was me who got you pregnant, eh, <i>'Brax'</i>? Oh, sorry, that's '[com.name]' now, isn't it? You just say right there and we'll find out together!)]
							#ENDIF
						</p>
						#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(sean.getId()))
							#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
								<p>
									Letting out a rumbling growl, [com.name] nevertheless does as [sean.name] asks, and remains still as he swipes an Arcane Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] swollen belly. Stepping back and looking at the results, the [sean.race] smirks and announces, [sean.speech(It <i>was</i> me who got you knocked up! You know, I always wanted to get Candi pregnant, but I'd never have imagined that you'd be the one who'd be the mother of my kids instead!)]
								</p>
								<p>
									[com.speech(Don't think that this changes anything!)] [com.name] snarls, [com.speech(Just because I was horny and wanted a good fuck, doesn't mean I like you!)]
								</p>
							#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
								<p>
									Letting out a submissive whine, [com.name] does as [sean.name] asks, and remains still as he swipes an Arcane Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] swollen belly. Stepping back and looking at the results, the [sean.race] smirks and announces, [sean.speech(It <i>was</i> me who got you knocked up! You know, I always wanted to get Candi pregnant, but I'd never have imagined that you'd be the one who'd be the mother of my kids instead!)]
								</p>
								<p>
									[com.speech(Well, I'll do a good job of caring for them,)] [com.name] replies, shuffling [com.her] feet and blushing.
								</p>
							#ELSE
								<p>
									Letting out an impatient sigh, [com.name] does as [sean.name] asks, and remains still as he swipes an Arcane Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] swollen belly. Stepping back and looking at the results, the [sean.race] smirks and announces, [sean.speech(It <i>was</i> me who got you knocked up! You know, I always wanted to get Candi pregnant, but I'd never have imagined that you'd be the one who'd be the mother of my kids instead!)]
								</p>
								<p>
									[com.speech(It's not like I ever imagined that this would happen either,)] [com.name] replies, crossing [com.her] [com.arms] and rolling [com.her] eyes.
								</p>
							#ENDIF
						#ELSE
							<p>
								Letting out a sigh, [com.name] does as [sean.name] asks, and remains still as [sean.name] swipes an Arcane Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] swollen belly. Stepping back and looking at the results, the [sean.race] furrows his eyebrows and exclaims, [sean.speech(Damn! It was someone else who got you knocked up! Oh well, maybe there'll be a next time...)]
							</p>
						#ENDIF
					#ELSEIF(com.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(sean.getId()))
						<p>
							Looking across to [com.name], [sean.name] grins and comments on [com.her] swollen belly, [sean.speech(I hope you're enjoying carrying our kids around, [com.name]! You look better as an expectant mother than you ever did as an Inspector!)]
						</p>
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(com.isVisiblyPregnant() && com.isCharacterPossiblyFather(sean))
					#IF(!com.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(sean))
						<p>
							Looking across to [com.name], [sean.name] grins and comments on [com.her] swollen belly, [sean.speech(Well, well, well. You wondering if it was me who got you pregnant? You just say right there and we'll find out together!)]
						</p>
						#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(sean.getId()))
							<p>
								Letting out a sigh, [com.name] does as [sean.name] asks, and remains still as he swipes an Arcane Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] swollen belly. Stepping back and looking at the results, the [sean.race] smirks and announces, [sean.speech(It <i>was</i> me who got you knocked up! I think I'll leave the number of buns in your oven as a surprise for you to find out later, though!)]
							</p>
						#ELSE
							<p>
								Letting out a sigh, [com.name] does as [sean.name] asks, and remains still as he swipes an Arcane Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] swollen belly. Stepping back and looking at the results, the [sean.race] furrows his eyebrows and exclaims, [sean.speech(Damn! It was someone else who got you knocked up! Oh well, maybe there'll be a next time...)]
							</p>
						#ENDIF
					#ELSEIF(com.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(sean.getId()))
						<p>
							Looking across to [com.name], [sean.name] grins and comments on [com.her] swollen belly, [sean.speech(I hope you're enjoying carrying our kids around, [com.name]! You look great as an expectant mother!)]
						</p>
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			Leaning back against the wall behind him, [sean.name] asks in his soft Irish accent, [sean.speech(So, what can I do for you?)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Deciding that you'd like to speak with the Enforcer on duty in this area, you walk past the public stocks and head directly towards him. As you approach, you take note of the fact that he's [sean.a_raceStage] [sean.race], who stands at [sean.heightValue] in height. His fur is a washed-out, sandy shade of yellowy-orange, and he has a brilliant pair of light blue eyes, which lock onto you as you come to a halt in front of him.
		</p>
		<p>
			Obviously thinking that you're here to present some kind of problem to him, the Enforcer looks you up and down in a suspicious manner, before cautiously asking in a soft Irish accent, [sean.speech(Is there something I can help you with?)]
		</p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions() && com.equals(brax))
			<p>
				#IF(brax.getRace()==RACE_WOLF_MORPH && !brax.isFeminine())
					Before you can offer an answer, the Enforcer's eyes shift over to look at [brax.name], before opening wide in shock. Furrowing his eyebrows, the [sean.race] asks, [sean.speech(Brax?! Is that you?! What are you doing out here?)]
				#ELSE
					Before you can offer an answer, the Enforcer's eyes shift over to look at [brax.name], before opening wide in shock. Furrowing his eyebrows, the [sean.race] mutters, [sean.speech(You know, you somehow remind me of Brax... Wait, that <i>is</i> you, isn't it?! What happened to you?!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(brax.getName().equals("Brax"))
					[pc.speech([brax.Name] is my slave,)] you reveal, [pc.speech(I take it you know [brax.herHim]?)]
				#ELSE
					[pc.speech('[brax.Name]' is my slave,)] you reveal, [pc.speech(I take it you know [brax.herHim]?)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(brax.isFeminine())
					[sean.speech(Do I know '[brax.herHim]', [pc.she] asks!)]
				#ELSE
					[sean.speech(Do I know [brax.herHim], [pc.she] asks!)]
				#ENDIF
				 [sean.name] exclaims in disbelief, throwing his arms up in the air and quickly pacing around in a tight circle. Turning back to face you, he reveals, [sean.speech(Of course I know [brax.herHim]; [brax.sheIs] the one who demoted me and assigned me to this wretched post!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Addressing your [com.companion], [sean.name] continues,
				#IF(brax.isFeminine())
					 [sean.speech(So, you're a slave now?! And [brax.a_genderAppears] on top of that! Well, what goes around, comes around; it couldn't have happened to a more deserving person!)]
				#ELSE
					 [sean.speech(So, you're a slave now?! Well, what goes around, comes around; it couldn't have happened to a more deserving person!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					#IF(brax.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false))
						[brax.speech(Fuck you, [sean.surname],)] [brax.name] angrily replies, [brax.speech(I'm not surprised to see that you haven't managed to work your way out of this post; you always were a lazy fuck.)]
					#ELSE
						Narrowing [brax.her] eyes, [brax.name] makes an angry growling noise, letting [sean.name] know that the animosity is mutual.
					#ENDIF
				#ELSEIF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					#IF(brax.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false))
						[brax.speech(I'm sorry for demoting you,)] [brax.name] mutters, submissively shuffling [brax.her] [brax.feet].
					#ELSE
						Casting [brax.her] [brax.eyes] to the floor, [brax.name] makes a submissive whining noise while simultaneously shuffling [brax.her] [brax.feet].
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					#IF(brax.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, false))
						[brax.speech(What's done is done,)] [brax.name] says, crossing [brax.her] [brax.arms] and letting out a sigh.
					#ELSE
						crossing [brax.her] [brax.arms], [brax.name] makes a dismissive humming noise, letting [sean.name] know that [brax.she] isn't bothered by his animosity.
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Well, whatever. I may just be <i>Constable</i> [sean.surname] thanks to you, but I guess there's no point in hating you for it,)]  [sean.name] sighs, before turning his gaze back to you and asking, [sean.speech(Now, who are you and what do you want?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Seeing no reason not to give the Enforcer your name, you do so, and then wonder what to say next...
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				As you prepare to answer, you look down to see the surname '[sean.Surname]' displayed on this Enforcer's stabproof vest. Catching your eye, the [sean.race] impatiently says, [sean.speech(Yeah, the name's [sean.surname]. <i>Constable</i> [sean.surname] to you, mind. Now, who are you and what do you want?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Seeing no reason not to give the Enforcer your name, you do so, and then wonder what to say next...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTalked))
			Wanting to know a little more about [sean.namePos] duties, you ask him why he's guarding the stocks when there's already private security watching over the area from the nearby entrance.
		#ELSE
			Wanting to find out about [sean.namePos] duties again, you ask him why he's guarding the stocks when there's already private security watching over the area from the nearby entrance.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions() && com.equals(brax))
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTalkedBraxReveal))
			<p>
				#IF(com.getName().equals("Brax"))
					Looking over and glaring at [brax.name], [sean.name] says, [sean.speech(Well, if you remember what I said last time, it's your slave here who's the one responsible for me being demoted and stationed at this pointless post. Isn't that right, [brax.name]?)]
				#ELSE
					Looking over and glaring at [brax.name], [sean.name] says, [sean.speech(Well, if you remember what I said last time, it's your slave here who's the one responsible for me being demoted and stationed at this pointless post. Isn't that right, <i>'[brax.name]'</i>?)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					[brax.speech(You've only got yourself to blame,)] [brax.name] growls out in reply to the [sean.race]'s accusation.
				#ELSEIF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					[brax.speech(Yes... Sorry about that,)] [brax.name] replies, submissively shuffling [brax.her] feet.
				#ELSE
					[brax.speech(I guess,)] [brax.name] sighs, crossing [brax.her] [brax.arms].
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Let me tell you again what happened,)] [sean.name] says, turning back to face you, [sean.speech(So you already know that the receptionist at the Enforcer HQ, Candi, is complete slut. She sucks off pretty much any Enforcer who has a higher rank than her, and seeing as I was a Sergeant, she'd be down on her knees before I could even say hello. Anyway, one day I convinced her to let me fuck her instead of just getting a blowjob, but she made me promise that I'd pull out.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					[brax.speech(But you didn't, and you even tricked her into taking one of those [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getNamePlural(false)],)] [brax.name] interjects in an angry tone.
				#ELSEIF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					[brax.speech(Yes, but you didn't, did you? You even tricked her into taking one of those [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getNamePlural(false)]...)] [brax.name] interjects in a soft tone.
				#ELSE
					[brax.speech(But you didn't, and you even tricked her into taking one of those [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getNamePlural(false)],)] [brax.name] interjects in a disapproving tone.
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Yeah, but come on, I didn't even end up getting her pregnant!)] [sean.name] objects, before continuing, [sean.speech(So anyway, Candi actually filed a formal complaint to [brax.name] here, who wasted no time in demoting me and assigning me to this pointless post. Apparently, the private security guys here wanted an official Enforcer presence to remind everyone that the law's on their side. You know, I wouldn't have cared so much about the demotion, but it's the fact that I'm bored out of my mind that's the real punishment. I never have anything to do!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				#IF(com.getName().equals("Brax"))
					Looking over and glaring at [brax.name], [sean.name] reveals, [sean.speech(It's your slave here who's the one responsible for me being demoted and stationed at this pointless post. Isn't that right, [brax.name]?)]
				#ELSE
					Looking over and glaring at [brax.name], [sean.name] reveals, [sean.speech(It's your slave here who's the one responsible for me being demoted and stationed at this pointless post. Isn't that right, <i>'[brax.name]'</i>?)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					[brax.speech(You've only got yourself to blame,)] [brax.name] growls out in reply to the [sean.race]'s accusation.
				#ELSEIF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					[brax.speech(Yes... Sorry about that,)] [brax.name] replies, submissively shuffling [brax.her] feet.
				#ELSE
					[brax.speech(I guess,)] [brax.name] sighs, crossing [brax.her] [brax.arms].
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				[sean.speech(I don't know if [brax.name] has told you anything about it, but in any case, let me tell you what really happened,)] [sean.name] says, turning back to face you, [sean.speech(If you've been to the Enforcer HQ, then I'm sure you've met that cat-girl secretary, Candi?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Nodding in confirmation, you listen as [sean.name] continues, [sean.speech(So you know that she's a complete slut. She sucks off pretty much any Enforcer who has a higher rank than her, and seeing as I was a Sergeant, she'd be down on her knees before I could even say hello. Anyway, one day I convinced her to let me fuck her instead of just getting a blowjob, but she made me promise that I'd pull out.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					[brax.speech(But you didn't, and you even tricked her into taking one of those [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getNamePlural(false)],)] [brax.name] interjects in an angry tone.
				#ELSEIF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					[brax.speech(Yes, but you didn't, did you? You even tricked her into taking one of those [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getNamePlural(false)]...)] [brax.name] interjects in a soft tone.
				#ELSE
					[brax.speech(But you didn't, and you even tricked her into taking one of those [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getNamePlural(false)],)] [brax.name] interjects in a disapproving tone.
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Hey now, come on, [brax.name]. I didn't even end up getting her pregnant!)] [sean.name] objects, before continuing, [sean.speech(So yeah, anyway, Candi actually filed a formal complaint to [brax.name] here, who wasted no time in demoting me and assigning me to this pointless post. Apparently, the private security guys here wanted an official Enforcer presence to remind everyone that the law's on their side. You know, I wouldn't have cared so much about the demotion, but it's the fact that I'm bored out of my mind that's the real punishment. I never have anything to do!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTalkedBraxReveal))
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Well, you already know that it was your slave, [brax.name], who's the one that's responsible for me being here,)] [sean.name] says, before taking a moment to collect his thoughts and explaining, [sean.speech(So, as I said last time, I used to be a Sergeant, but ended up being demoted and then stationed here as an additional punishment by [brax.name]. It all started with Candi over at the HQ being a complete slut. As you know, she sucks off pretty much any Enforcer who has a higher rank than her, and seeing as I was a Sergeant, she'd be down on her knees before I could even say hello. Anyway, one day I convinced her to let me fuck her instead of just getting a blowjob, but she made me promise that I'd pull out.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Oh yeah, and you didn't,)] you say, remembering what [sean.name] told you the last time you asked him about this.
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Heh, yeah, I sort of got carried away, and tricked her into taking a [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getName(false)] and then finished inside of her. The thing is, I didn't even end up getting her pregnant, but she still filed a formal complaint to [brax.name], who wasted no time in demoting me and assigning me to this pointless post,)] [sean.name] sighs, before explaining, [sean.speech(Apparently, the private security guys here wanted an official Enforcer presence to remind everyone that the law's on their side. You know, I wouldn't have cared so much about the demotion, but it's the fact that it's absolutely pointless me being here that's the real punishment. I never have anything to do!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTalked))
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Well, I don't mind telling you the story again,)] [sean.name] says, before taking a moment to collect his thoughts and explaining, [sean.speech(So, as you might recall me saying before, I used to be a Sergeant, but ended up being demoted and then stationed here as an additional punishment by my superior. It all started with this cat-girl Enforcer over at the HQ being a complete slut. She'd suck off pretty much any Enforcer who had a higher rank than her, and seeing as I was a Sergeant at the time, she'd be down on her knees before I could even say hello. Anyway, one day I convinced her to let me fuck her instead of just getting a blowjob, but she made me promise that I'd pull out.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(And then you didn't,)] you recall.
			</p>
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Yeah, that's right, I sort of got carried away, and tricked her into taking a [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getName(false)] and then finished inside of her. The thing is, I didn't even end up getting her pregnant, but she still filed a formal complaint to my superior, who wasted no time in demoting me and assigning me to this pointless post,)] [sean.name] sighs, before explaining, [sean.speech(Apparently, the private security guys here wanted an official Enforcer presence to remind everyone that the law's on their side. You know, I wouldn't have cared so much about the demotion, but it's the fact that it's absolutely pointless me being here that's the real punishment. I never have anything to do!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Well, I don't see a reason not to tell you about how I ended up being posted here,)] [sean.name] says, before taking a moment to collect his thoughts and explaining, [sean.speech(So, I used to be a Sergeant, but ended up being demoted and then stationed here as an additional punishment by my superior. It all started with this cat-girl Enforcer over at the HQ being a complete slut. She'd suck off pretty much any Enforcer who had a higher rank than her, and seeing as I was a Sergeant at the time, she'd be down on her knees before I could even say hello. Anyway, one day I convinced her to let me fuck her instead of just getting a blowjob, but she made me promise that I'd pull out.)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(And you didn't?)] you guess.
			</p>
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Heh, yeah, I sort of got carried away, and tricked her into taking a [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getName(false)] and then finished inside of her. The thing is, I didn't even end up getting her pregnant, but she still filed a formal complaint to my superior, who wasted no time in demoting me and assigning me to this pointless post,)] [sean.name] sighs, before explaining, [sean.speech(Apparently, the private security guys here wanted an official Enforcer presence to remind everyone that the law's on their side. You know, I wouldn't have cared so much about the demotion, but it's the fact that it's absolutely pointless me being here that's the real punishment. I never have anything to do!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You mean nobody ever causes any trouble here?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyComplained))
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleySlavesFreed))
				[sean.speech(Apart from you? No,)] the [sean.race] replies with a grin, [sean.speech(You're the most interesting thing that's ever happened here. You should come back and complain about the slaves again tomorrow. That'd give me something to do...)]
			#ELSE
				[sean.speech(Apart from you? No,)] the [sean.race] replies with a grin, [sean.speech(You're the most interesting thing that's ever happened here. So, are you wanting to complain about the slaves again? It'd at least give me something to do...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			[sean.speech(No,)] the [sean.race] sighs, [sean.speech(but I kind of wish they would; it'd at least give me something to do. So, are you wanting anything else?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN_TALK_FREED_SLAVES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTalkedFreedSlaves))
			Turing to glance at the deserted stocks, you once again ask [sean.name] if [sean.sheIs] going to get in trouble for allowing the slaves to escape on his watch.
		#ELSE
			Turing to glance at the deserted stocks, you ask [sean.name] if [sean.sheIs] going to get in trouble for allowing the slaves to escape on his watch.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Not likely,)] the [sean.race] replies with a smirk on his face, [sean.speech(These private security goons always act like they're more important than us Enforcers, so even if they go and complain to my superiors, it's not like any of them will care. And anyway, the security guards are meant to be the ones actually preventing slave escapes; I'm just here to remind everyone that the law is on their side.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(And you're not going to reveal that it was me who freed them?)] you ask in a hushed tone.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Heh, not likely; that would get me in huge trouble as well, and besides, I wouldn't want to do anything that might remove my only source of fun,)] [sean.name] replies, grinning at you. [sean.speech(There'll be more slaves in the stocks tomorrow, so if you want to come back and complain, you know where to find me!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN_SEDUCE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN_SEDUCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Putting on your most seductive voice, you step up to [sean.name] and start teasing him with the offer of spending some alone time with you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Quickly getting excited by your behaviour, the [sean.race] impatiently replies, [sean.speech(That's it, I'm taking a break right now! So, what did you want to do together?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN_SEDUCE_ALLEYWAY"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyVisitedHiddenAlleyway))
		<p>
			Knowing of only one place nearby where you could have sex in private, you suggest to [sean.name] that the two of you could take a visit to the hidden alleyway. Eager to fuck you again, the [sean.race] readily agrees, and, grabbing hold of your [pc.hand], he hastily leads you down the road and into the narrow passageway.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to go somewhere where you can have sex in private, you ask [sean.name] if he knows a suitable location nearby. Eager to fuck you again, the [sean.race] quickly replies, [sean.speech(I know just the place! Follow me; there's an alleyway nearby where we can have some privacy.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Grabbing hold of your [pc.hand], [sean.name] hastily leads you down the main street a short distance, before veering off to the right and stepping up to a weathered wooden door set into an otherwise featureless brick wall. Grabbing the handle and giving it a forceful push, the [sean.race] demonstrates that this door is kept unlocked, and as it swings open, he strides through to the other side. Being dragged along with him, you step through the doorway and take a look at your new surroundings.
		</p>
		<p>
			Although the brick wall had given the impression that this door would lead into a building's enclosed interior, you instead discover that it was nothing more than a deceptive façade, as you now find yourself standing in a relatively wide alleyway, with the open sky above your head. Turning to face you, [sean.name] says, [sean.speech(Nobody knows about this place, and those that do have no reason to come here, as all it leads to is a dead end. Now, let's get down to business!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Although [com.name] follows the two of you along, [com.she] hangs back a little once you've entered the alley, and looks on as [sean.name] steps up to you and pulls you into a passionate kiss.
		</p>
		<p>
			After making out with one another for a minute or two, the [sean.race] pulls back, before grinning and declaring, [sean.speech(I can't spend too much time away from my post, so let's get started!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyVisitedHiddenAlleyway))
			As soon as you're out of sight of Slaver Alley's main pathway, [sean.name] steps up to you and pulls you into a passionate kiss.
		#ELSE
			Wasting no more time, [sean.name] impatiently steps up to you and pulls you into a passionate kiss.
		#ENDIF
		 Continuing to make out with one another for a minute or two, the [sean.race] eventually pulls back, before grinning and declaring, [sean.speech(I can't spend too much time away from my post, so let's get started!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN_SEDUCE_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling like you want to do something a little more exciting than just having sex in an alleyway, you step up close to [sean.name] and seductively suggest that he lock you in the stocks and publicly breed you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(You're a really kinky [pc.girl], you know that, right?)] the [sean.race] asks as he hears your suggestion. Asking him if he's willing to do it or not, you can't help but grin as he replies, [sean.speech(Of course I'll do it! If you're looking to get bred, though, then you're going to be wanting to take a [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getName(false)]; it'll make your womb nice and fertile.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Producing a small purple pill from out of one of his pockets, [sean.name] pops it out of its protective wrapper and holds it up to your mouth. Leaning forwards and opening your mouth, you allow the [sean.race] to place it onto your outstretched tongue, and with a quick smile, you gulp it down.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Good [pc.girl]! Now, let's have you put on a show for the public!)] [sean.name] exclaims, before helping you to strip out of your clothes. Leading you over to the nearest set of stocks, the [sean.race] quickly locks you in, before stepping around behind you and teasing, [sean.speech(Mmm, that's one fine-looking pussy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can reply to that, you suddenly feel [sean.namePos] fingers tracing their way up and down over your [pc.labia+], which causes you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan]. Bucking your [pc.hips] back against his touch, you plead, [pc.speech(Please, breed me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The scene which the two of you have created very quickly attracts the attention of some passersby, and as [sean.name] reaches down to expose his cock, a stranger shouts,
		[style.random(
		[style.speechMasculine(Go on, fuck that slut and give [pc.herHim] a nice big creampie!)]
		|
		[style.speechMasculine(Give that slut what she wants! Go on, pound [pc.her] cunt and make [pc.herHim] a mother!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Go on, fuck that slut and give [pc.herHim] a nice big creampie!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Give that slut what she wants! Go on, pound [pc.her] cunt and make [pc.herHim] a mother!)]
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning forwards over the top of you, [sean.name] teases, [sean.speech(Go on, beg me to fuck your pussy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		By now absolutely desperate to get fucked by [sean.name], you can't help but [pc.moanVerb] in excitement as you feel him start to tease the head of his [sean.cockSize] cock up and down between your [pc.labia+]. Pushing your hips back, you beg, [pc.speech(Please! Fuck my pussy! Give me your cock! Please!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a deep grunt, the [sean.name] finally gives you what you want, and thrusts forwards to drive his [sean.cock+] into your [pc.pussy+]. A high-pitched [pc.moan] bursts out of your mouth as you feel your [pc.labia+] spread lewdly around [sean.namePos] thick cock, and with the gathering crowd cheering him on, the [sean.race] starts rapidly pounding your greedy cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN_SEDUCE_ALLEYWAY_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyVisitedHiddenAlleyway))
		<p>
			Knowing of only one place nearby where you could have sex in private, you suggest to [sean.name] that the three of you could take a visit to the hidden alleyway. Eager to fuck you and [com.name], the [sean.race] readily agrees, and, grabbing hold of each of your [pc.hands], he hastily leads you and your [com.companion] down the road and into the narrow passageway.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to go somewhere where you can have sex in private, you ask [sean.name] if he knows a suitable location nearby. Eager to fuck you again, the [sean.race] quickly replies, [sean.speech(I know just the place! Follow me; there's an alleyway nearby where we can have some privacy.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Grabbing hold of you and [com.name] by the [pc.hand], [sean.name] hastily leads the two of you down the main street a short distance, before veering off to the right and stepping up to a weathered wooden door set into an otherwise featureless brick wall. Grabbing the handle and giving it a forceful push, the [sean.race] demonstrates that this door is kept unlocked, and as it swings open, he strides through to the other side. Being dragged along with him, you step through the doorway and take a look at your new surroundings.
		</p>
		<p>
			Although the brick wall had given the impression that this door would lead into a building's enclosed interior, you instead discover that it was nothing more than a deceptive façade, as you now find yourself standing in a relatively wide alleyway, with the open sky above your head. Turning to face you and [com.name], [sean.name] says, [sean.speech(Nobody knows about this place, and those that do have no reason to come here, as all it leads to is a dead end. Now, let's get down to business!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyVisitedHiddenAlleyway))
			As soon as you're out of sight of Slaver Alley's main pathway, [sean.name] steps up to you and pulls you into a passionate kiss.
		#ELSE
			Wasting no more time, [sean.name] impatiently steps up to you and pulls you into a passionate kiss.
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions() && com.equals(brax))
			 Continuing to make out with one another for a minute or two, the [sean.race] eventually pulls back, before moving over to [com.name]. Despite the fact that the two of them have some bad history with one another, all seems to be forgotten in the heat of the moment, and [com.name] enthusiastically leans into [sean.name] as he starts groping and kissing [com.herHim].
		#ELSE
			 Continuing to make out with one another for a minute or two, the [sean.race] eventually pulls back, before moving over to [com.name]. Just as eager to have sex as you are, [com.name] enthusiastically leans into [sean.name] as he starts groping and kissing [com.herHim].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After giving your [com.companion] a taste of what's to come, the [sean.race] pulls away, before grinning and declaring to the two of you, [sean.speech(I can't spend too much time away from my post, so let's get started!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN_SEDUCE_BREEDING_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Feeling like you want to do something a little more exciting than just having sex in an alleyway, you step up close to [sean.name] and seductively suggest that he lock you and [com.name] in the stocks and publicly breed the two of you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(You're a really kinky [pc.girl], you know that, right?)] the [sean.race] asks as he hears your suggestion. Asking him if he's willing to do it or not, you can't help but grin as he replies, [sean.speech(Of course I'll do it! If you're looking to get bred, though, then you're both going to want to take a [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getName(false)]; it'll make your wombs nice and fertile.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Producing two small purple pills from out of one of his pockets, [sean.name] pops them out of their protective wrappers and holds them up to you and [com.name]. Leaning forwards and opening your mouth, you allow the [sean.race] to place one of them onto your outstretched tongue, and with a quick smile, you gulp it down. Following your lead, your [com.companion] does the same thing, and lets out an exited [com.moan] as [com.she] swallows down the fertility-enhancing pill.
	</p>
	#IF(com.equals(brax))
		<p>
			Grinning at [com.name], the [sean.race] remarks, [sean.speech(Whoever would have guessed that my old Inspector would be moaning in excitement at the prospect of being bred by me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				[brax.speech(Don't think that this makes me like you!)] [brax.name] snaps, but from the way [com.her] cheeks are flushing, you can tell that [com.sheIs] desperately looking forward to what's to come.
			#ELSEIF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
				[brax.speech(I can't wait to feel you inside of me,)] [brax.name] submissively teases, tracing [com.her] [com.fingers] down between [com.her] [com.legs].
			#ELSE
				[brax.speech(Well, stranger things have happened, I'm sure!)] [brax.name] quickly retorts, [com.her] cheeks flushing red from a mixture of excitement and embarrassment.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Come on then, let's have the two of you put on a show for the public!)] [sean.name] exclaims, before helping you and [com.name] to strip out of your clothing. Leading you over to the nearest pair of stocks, the [sean.race] quickly locks you and your [com.companion] in, before stepping around behind the two of you and teasing, [sean.speech(Mmm, those are some fine-looking pussies! I wonder which one of you I'll breed first?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before either of you can reply to that, you suddenly feel [sean.namePos] fingers tracing their way up and down over your [pc.labia+], which causes you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan]. Bucking your [pc.hips] back against his touch, you plead, [pc.speech(Please, choose me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The scene which the three of you have created very quickly attracts the attention of some passersby, and as [sean.name] reaches down to expose his cock, a stranger shouts,
		[style.random(
		[style.speechMasculine(Go on, fuck those sluts and give them some nice big creampies!)]
		|
		[style.speechMasculine(Give those sluts what they want! Go on, pound their cunts and make them into mothers!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Go on, fuck those sluts and give them some nice big creampies!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Give that sluts what they want! Go on, pound their cunts and make them into mothers!)]
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Leaning forwards over the top of you, [sean.name] teases, [sean.speech(I think I'll knock you up first! Go on, beg me to fuck your pussy!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		By now absolutely desperate to get fucked by [sean.name], you can't help but [pc.moanVerb] in excitement as you feel him start to tease the head of his [sean.cockSize] cock up and down between your [pc.labia+]. Pushing your hips back, you beg, [pc.speech(Please! Fuck my pussy! Give me your cock! Please!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a deep grunt, the [sean.name] finally gives you what you want, and thrusts forwards to drive his [sean.cock+] into your [pc.pussy+]. A high-pitched [pc.moan] bursts out of your mouth as you feel your [pc.labia+] spread lewdly around [sean.namePos] thick cock, and with the gathering crowd cheering him on, the [sean.race] starts rapidly pounding your greedy cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN_SEDUCE_BACK_OUT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_SEAN_SEDUCE_BACK_OUT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having second thoughts about what you're doing, you step away from [sean.name] and admit that you're not ready to have sex with him right now. Letting out a frustrated sigh, the [sean.race] complains, [sean.speech(Don't go leading me on like that! I was getting really fired up there...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Making a quick apology, you wonder what you should say to [sean.name] next... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_ALLEYWAY_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_ALLEYWAY_THREESOME_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(com.equals(brax))
		<p>
			Letting out a satisfied sigh, [sean.name] disentangles himself from you and [com.name]. As the three of you start to get your things back in order, the [sean.race] comments, [sean.speech(Getting to spend time with the two of you certainly makes this assignment not seem so bad after all! You know, you're a lot easier to like now that you're not my boss, [com.name].)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				[brax.speech(Don't get cocky!)] [brax.name] snaps, [com.speech(Just because I sometimes need a good fuck, doesn't make us friends!)]
			#ELSEIF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
				[brax.speech(Thanks, [sean.surname],)] [brax.name] softly replies, blushing.
			#ELSE
				[brax.speech(You're easier to get on with like this as well,)] [brax.name] admits, blushing a little.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Grinning at [com.namePos] comment, you turn to face [sean.name] as he finishes getting dressed and states, [sean.speech(I need to get back to my post now; I hope to see the pair of you again soon!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the [sean.race] dashes off, leaving you to finish getting your things together...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Letting out a satisfied sigh, [sean.name] disentangles himself from you and [com.name]. As the three of you start to get your things back in order, the [sean.race] comments, [sean.speech(Getting to spend time with the two of you certainly makes this assignment not seem so bad after all!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Grinning at [sean.namePos] comment, you and [com.name] turn to face him as he finishes getting dressed and continues, [sean.speech(I need to get back to my post now; I hope to see the pair of you again soon!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the [sean.race] dashes off, leaving you to finish getting your things together...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_ALLEYWAY_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a satisfied sigh, you and [sean.name] disentangle yourselves from one another. As the two of you start to get your things back in order, the [sean.race] comments, [sean.speech(Getting to spend time with you certainly makes this assignment not seem so bad after all!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Grinning at [sean.namePos] comment, you turn to face him as he finishes getting dressed and continues, [sean.speech(I need to get back to my post now; I hope to see you again soon!)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			#IF(com.isFeminine())
				Looking over at [com.name], the [sean.race] cheekily adds, [sean.speech(Maybe you'll join in next time, [com.name]! Anyway, see you!)]
			#ELSE
				Looking over at [com.name], the [sean.race] cheekily adds, [sean.speech(I hope you had fun too! Anyway, see you!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, [sean.name] dashes off, leaving you and your [com.companion] to finish getting your things together...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With that, [sean.name] dashes off, leaving you to finish getting your things together...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_ALLEYWAY_SEX_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			As soon as you're ready to go, you and [com.name] head back out of the hidden alleyway, and once again find yourselves standing in Slaver Alley, wondering what to do next...
		#ELSE
			As soon as you're ready to go, you head back out of the hidden alleyway, and once again find yourself standing in Slaver Alley, wondering what to do next...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_STOCKS_BREEDING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_STOCKS_BREEDING_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As [sean.name] steps back, the members of the crowd that's gathered to watch start discussing amongst themselves whether or not the cum dripping out of your well-fucked pussy will be enough to get you pregnant. Hearing what it is they're saying, the [sean.race] reaches down to grab your [pc.ass+] with both hands, before pulling to each side and spreading your pussy for all to see. [sean.speech(Take a look at all that spunk I stuffed inside of [pc.herHim]! There's no way [pc.she] hasn't been knocked up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getFetishDesire(FETISH_EXHIBITIONIST).isPositive())
			Feeling extremely turned on from being exposed in such a lewd manner, you can't help but let out a long, horny moan, which draws laughter and yet more comments from the members of the crowd gathered around your rear end.
		#ELSE
			Feeling your cheeks burn with embarrassment, you can't help but let out a high-pitched whimper, which draws laughter and yet more comments from the members of the crowd gathered around your rear end.
		#ENDIF
		 Giving your [pc.ass] an affectionate slap, [sean.name] reminds the crowd, [sean.speech(You can look, but you can't touch! Now, if you want, you can watch me knock up this other one as well!)]
	</p>
	#IF(com.equals(brax))
		<p>
			As the [sean.race] steps up behind [com.name] and begins teasing his cock up and down between [com.her] [com.labia+], you hear him tease, [sean.speech(Never would have imagined we'd be in this situation, eh, <i>Inspector</i>? Now go on, beg me to breed you!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				[com.speech(S-Shut up and just fuck me already!)] [com.name] impatiently snaps, but, wanting to hear your [com.companion] beg to be bred, [sean.name] refuses to penetrate [com.herHim] until [com.she] relents and [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Fine! J-Just breed me already! Give me your cum and knock me up! Please!)]
			#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
				[com.speech(Please, fuck me!)] [com.name] desperately [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Breed me! Give me your cum and knock me up!)]
			#ELSE
				[com.speech(Go on then, fuck me!)] [com.name] blushes as [com.she] [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Breed me! Give me your cum and knock me up!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(That's a good [com.girl]!)] [sean.name] says, before thrusting forwards and filling [com.namePos] hungry pussy with his [sean.cockSize] cock. Getting a good grip on your [com.companion]'s hips, the [sean.race] leans forwards over the top of [com.name] and starts frantically humping [com.herHim].
		</p>
		<p>
			Due to the stocks which you're locked in being parallel to the ones which are restraining [com.name], you aren't able to get a good view of what's happening, but from the frantic wet slapping sounds, combined with all manner of lewd moans and comments coming out of your [com.companion]'s mouth, you can tell that [sean.name] is giving [com.herHim] just as thorough a fucking as the one you've just received. Soon enough, the [sean.race]'s steady grunts start to get deeper and louder, but before he orgasms, [com.name] lets out a shuddering moan and exclaims, [com.speech(~Ooh!~ Fuck! Yes! ~Mmm!~ I-I'm cumming!)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			The wet slapping sounds of [sean.namePos] cock repeatedly slamming into [com.namePos] quivering pussy get faster and faster as your [com.companion] climaxes, and then, just a few moments later, they come to a stop with one final wet squelch, which is followed by a deep, desperate grunt from the [sean.race], [sean.speech(~Aah!~ That's it! Take it all, [com.name]! ~Aah!~ Fuck!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Panting and moaning, [com.name] fully capitulates to [com.her] one-time subordinate, and exclaims, [com.speech(~Ooh!~ Yes! Fill my pussy with your cum! ~Aah!~ Breed me, yes!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With the surrounding crowd cheering him on, [sean.name] does as [com.name] asks, and, keeping his [sean.cockGirth] cock hilted in [com.her] dripping pussy, the [sean.race]'s balls tense up and unload their virile seed deep into [com.her] fertile womb. Continuing to pant, moan, and groan, they stay locked together like this for a short while, until [sean.namePos] thick cum backs up and seeps out around his still-throbbing cock.
		</p>
		<p>
			Having finally emptied his balls, first into you, and now into your [com.companion], [sean.name] slides his cock out of [com.namePos] well-fucked pussy, before standing to one side and letting the crowd see the fresh creampie he's given [com.herHim]. Just as he did to you, [sean.name] affectionately slaps [com.namePos] ass, before remarking, [sean.speech(You're far better like this than you ever were as an Enforcer. I mean, fuck... You've no idea how good your pussy feels!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a deep, long moan, [com.name] admits, [com.speech(Your cock felt great too... I wonder if you've got me pregnant...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(We'll find out soon enough,)] [sean.name] replies. Putting away his by-now soft cock and then zipping up his trousers, the [sean.race] walks around in front of you and [com.name] to say, [sean.speech(I'm going to leave the two of you like this for a while. I want to give my seed time to find your eggs, and plus, the public seems to be enjoying the view from behind.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a chuckle, the [sean.race] walks off to somewhere behind you and [com.name], leaving your creampied cunts on full display...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As the [sean.race] steps up behind [com.name] and begins teasing his cock up and down between [com.her] [com.labia+], you hear him tease, [sean.speech(Now it's your turn! Go on, beg me to breed you!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[com.speech(Please, fuck me!)] [com.name] obediently [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Breed me! Give me your cum and knock me up!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(That's a good [com.girl]!)] [sean.name] says, before thrusting forwards and filling [com.namePos] hungry pussy with his [sean.cockSize] cock. Getting a good grip on your [com.companion]'s hips, the [sean.race] leans forwards over the top of [com.name] and starts frantically humping [com.herHim].
		</p>
		<p>
			Due to the stocks which you're locked in being parallel to the ones which are restraining [com.name], you aren't able to get a good view of what's happening, but from the frantic wet slapping sounds, combined with all manner of lewd moans and comments coming out of your [com.companion]'s mouth, you can tell that [sean.name] is giving [com.herHim] just as thorough a fucking as the one you've just received. Soon enough, the [sean.race]'s steady grunts start to get deeper and louder, but before he orgasms, [com.name] lets out a shuddering moan and exclaims, [com.speech(~Ooh!~ Fuck! Yes! ~Mmm!~ I-I'm cumming!)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			The wet slapping sounds of [sean.namePos] cock repeatedly slamming into [com.namePos] quivering pussy get faster and faster as your [com.companion] climaxes, and then, just a few moments later, they come to a stop with one final wet squelch, which is followed by a deep, desperate grunt from the [sean.race], [sean.speech(~Aah!~ That's it! Take it all! ~Aah!~ Fuck!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Panting and moaning, [com.name] desperately exclaims, [com.speech(~Ooh!~ Yes! Fill my pussy with your cum! ~Aah!~ Breed me, yes!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With the surrounding crowd cheering him on, [sean.name] does as [com.name] asks, and, keeping his [sean.cockGirth] cock hilted in [com.her] dripping pussy, the [sean.race]'s balls tense up and unload their virile seed deep into [com.her] fertile womb. Continuing to pant, moan, and groan, they stay locked together like this for a short while, until [sean.namePos] thick cum backs up and seeps out around his still-throbbing cock.
		</p>
		<p>
			Having finally emptied his balls, first into you, and now into your [com.companion], [sean.name] slides his cock out of [com.namePos] well-fucked pussy, before standing to one side and letting the crowd see the fresh creampie he's given [com.herHim]. Just as he did to you, [sean.name] affectionately slaps [com.namePos] ass, before remarking, [sean.speech(Your pussy sure felt good to fuck!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a deep, long moan, [com.name] pants, [com.speech(I wonder if you've got me pregnant...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(We'll find out soon enough,)] [sean.name] replies. Putting away his by-now soft cock and then zipping up his trousers, the [sean.race] walks around in front of you and [com.name] to say, [sean.speech(I'm going to leave the two of you like this for a while. I want to give my seed time to find your eggs, and plus, the public seems to be enjoying the view from behind.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a chuckle, the [sean.race] walks off to somewhere behind you and [com.name], leaving your creampied cunts on full display...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_STOCKS_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As [sean.name] steps back, the members of the crowd that's gathered to watch start discussing amongst themselves whether or not the cum dripping out of your well-fucked pussy will be enough to get you pregnant. Hearing what it is they're saying, the [sean.race] reaches down to grab your [pc.ass+] with both hands, before pulling to each side and spreading your pussy for all to see. [sean.speech(Take a look at all that spunk I stuffed inside of [pc.herHim]! There's no way [pc.she] hasn't been knocked up!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a deep, long moan, you settle into panting out loud as [sean.name] lets go of your ass and puts away his by-now soft cock. Zipping up his trousers, the [sean.race] walks around in front of you to say, [sean.speech(I'm going to leave you like this for a while. I want to give my seed time to find your eggs, and plus, the public seems to be enjoying the view from behind.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a chuckle, the [sean.race] walks off to somewhere behind you, leaving your creampied cunt on full display...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_STOCKS_BREEDING_FINISHED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_STOCKS_BREEDING_THREESOME_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although [sean.name] has left you and [com.name] locked up in the stocks awaiting his return, you're by no means alone, as several members of the crowd which gathered to watch you both being fucked are still lingering around in the nearby area.
		#IF(pc.getFetishDesire(FETISH_EXHIBITIONIST).isPositive())
			 You can't help but feel extremely turned on as you realise that they're watching the cum slowly drip from your pussy, and you let out a quiet moan as you hear one of them comment,
		#ELSE
			 You can't help but feel extremely embarrassed as you realise that they're watching the cum slowly drip from your pussy, and you let out an anguished groan as you hear one of them comment,
		#ENDIF
		 [style.random(
		[style.speechMasculine(Look at that dirty cunt! Did you hear how [pc.she] was moaning as that rabbit emptied his balls in [pc.herHim]?)]
		|
		[style.speechMasculine(That rabbit sure pounded [pc.her] pussy! I bet [pc.her] belly'll soon be swollen with a big litter of bunnies!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Look at that dirty cunt! Did you hear how [pc.she] was moaning as that rabbit emptied his balls in [pc.herHim]?)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(That rabbit sure pounded [pc.her] pussy! I bet [pc.her] belly'll soon be swollen with a big litter of bunnies!)]
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		From somewhere else behind you, another stranger loudly comments on the state of [com.namePos] exposed genitals,
		 [style.random(
		[style.speechMasculine(Did you hear how this one was begging to be bred? By the looks of how much cum that rabbit stuffed into [com.her] cunt, [com.she]'ll be getting what [com.she] wanted!)]
		|
		[style.speechMasculine(This one sure is a dirty slut! Did you hear how [com.she] was begging that rabbit to finish inside [com.her] pussy?)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Did you hear how this one was begging to be bred? By the looks of how much cum that rabbit stuffed into [com.her] cunt, [com.she]'ll be getting what [com.she] wanted!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(This one sure is a dirty slut! Did you hear how [com.she] was begging that rabbit to finish inside [com.her] pussy?)]
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After enduring several more minutes of hearing these sorts of comments, you finally hear the last remnants of the crowd walk off, leaving you and [com.name] alone. Another ten or so minutes after that, and only after you've felt the last few drops of cum drip out of your pussy, [sean.name] finally returns. Walking around in front of you and [com.name], he grins and holds up a pair of Arcane Pregnancy Testers, before declaring, [sean.speech(Let's see if I succeeded in breeding you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isPregnant())
			Walking around to swipe the first one over your belly, [sean.name] takes a look at the readout and happily declares, [sean.speech(Yes! I got you pregnant! You'll have a nice big swollen belly soon enough!)]
		#ELSE
			Walking around to swipe the first one over your belly, [sean.name] takes a look at the readout and sighs in frustration, [sean.speech(Damn it! I didn't get you pregnant, even after all that?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(com.equals(brax))
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Now, lets see if my old Inspector is going to be the mother to my kids,)] [sean.name] teases, walking up beside [com.name] and swiping the second Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] belly.
			#IF(com.isPregnant())
				 Taking a look at the digital readout, the [sean.race] excitedly declares, [sean.speech(Oh, yes! I got you pregnant, all right! How does it feel, [com.name], knowing that the guy you demoted is now the father to the kids growing in your womb?)]
			#ELSE
				 Taking a look at the digital readout, the [sean.race] whines, [sean.speech(Well, that sucks... I didn't get you pregnant after all...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				#IF(com.isPregnant())
					[com.speech(Shut up, [sean.name]!)] [com.name] snaps, [com.speech(I may have asked for it, but don't think that this gives you the right to take the piss!)]
				#ELSE
					[com.speech(You can't do anything right, can you, [sean.name]?)] [com.name] snaps.
				#ENDIF
			#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
				#IF(com.isPregnant())
					[com.speech(It feels good,)] [com.name] softly moans, [com.speech(I'll be a good mother to our children!)]
				#ELSE
					[com.speech(Aww,)] [com.name] whines, [com.speech(maybe there'll be a next time?)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				#IF(com.isPregnant())
					[com.speech(Well, I don't know, it's kind of fun, I guess,)] [com.name] replies in a fluster, [com.speech(Regardless, I'll be a good mother to our children...)]
				#ELSE
					[com.speech(Hmm, I expected more from you, [sean.name],)] [com.name] hums in disapproval, [com.speech(Maybe there'll be a next time?)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Now, lets see if you're going to be the mother to my kids,)] [sean.name] teases, walking up beside [com.name] and swiping the second Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] belly.
			#IF(com.isPregnant())
				 Taking a look at the digital readout, the [sean.race] excitedly declares, [sean.speech(Oh, yes! I got you pregnant, all right! I knew I'd have no problems knocking you up!)]
			#ELSE
				 Taking a look at the digital readout, the [sean.race] whines, [sean.speech(Well, that sucks... I didn't get you pregnant after all...)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_STOCKS_BREEDING_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although [sean.name] has left you locked up in the stocks awaiting his return, you're by no means alone, as several members of the crowd which gathered to watch you being fucked are still lingering around in the nearby area.
		#IF(pc.getFetishDesire(FETISH_EXHIBITIONIST).isPositive())
			 You can't help but feel extremely turned on as you realise that they're watching the cum slowly drip from your pussy, and you let out a quiet moan as you hear one of them comment,
		#ELSE
			 You can't help but feel extremely embarrassed as you realise that they're watching the cum slowly drip from your pussy, and you let out an anguished groan as you hear one of them comment,
		#ENDIF
		 [style.random(
		[style.speechMasculine(Look at that dirty cunt! Did you hear how [pc.she] was moaning as that rabbit emptied his balls in [pc.herHim]?)]
		|
		[style.speechMasculine(That rabbit sure pounded [pc.her] pussy! I bet [pc.her] belly'll soon be swollen with a big litter of bunnies!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Look at that dirty cunt! Did you hear how [pc.she] was moaning as that rabbit emptied his balls in [pc.herHim]?)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(That rabbit sure pounded [pc.her] pussy! I bet [pc.her] belly'll soon be swollen with a big litter of bunnies!)]
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			After enduring several more minutes of hearing these sorts of comments, you finally hear the last remnants of the crowd walk off, leaving you alone with just [com.name] hanging around nearby.
		#ELSE
			After enduring several more minutes of hearing these sorts of comments, you finally hear the last remnants of the crowd walk off, leaving you alone.
		#ENDIF
		 Another ten or so minutes after that, and only after you've felt the last few drops of cum drip out of your pussy, [sean.name] finally returns. Walking around in front of you, he grins and holds up an Arcane Pregnancy Tester, before declaring, [sean.speech(Let's see if I succeeded in breeding you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isPregnant())
			Walking around to swipe it over your belly, [sean.name] takes a look at the readout and happily declares, [sean.speech(Yes! I got you pregnant! You'll have a nice big swollen belly soon enough!)]
		#ELSE
			Walking around to swipe it over your belly, [sean.name] takes a look at the readout and sighs in frustration, [sean.speech(Damn it! I didn't get you pregnant, even after all that?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_STOCKS_BREEDING_THREESOME_FINISHED_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With you and [com.name] having been told the results of having your pussies stuffed with his cum, [sean.name] moves to unlock each of you from the stocks. As the two of you stand up and stretch, he says, [sean.speech(If you want to have some more fun together, just come back any time and ask!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, the [sean.race] moves back over to his post, leaving you and your [com.companion] to get dressed and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_SEDUCE_STOCKS_BREEDING_FINISHED_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having been told the result of having your pussy stuffed with his cum, [sean.name] moves to unlock you from the stocks. As you stand up and stretch, he says, [sean.speech(If you want to have some more fun together, just come back any time and ask!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			With that, the [sean.race] moves back over to his post, leaving you to get dressed and meet back up with [com.name], before wondering what to do next...
		#ELSE
			With that, the [sean.race] moves back over to his post, leaving you to get dressed and wonder what to do next...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again wanting to voice your objection to the idea of slaves being locked into stocks and then being publicly used, and with [sean.name] being the only authority figure that you can see, you start repeating your argument for why they should be freed.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although he once again displays his annoyance by sighing and rolling his eyes as he hears what it is you're saying, the [sean.race] allows you to finish voicing your opinion without interruption. As you finish repeating your case for why the slaves shouldn't be subjected to such humiliating treatment, [sean.name] asks,
		#IF(sean.getFoughtPlayerCount()>0)
			[sean.speech(So, we're doing this again, are we? You want to keep on complaining and get me to challenge you, is that it? Or are you going to just drop it?)]
		#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTookPlace))
			[sean.speech(So, we're doing this again, are we? You want to keep on complaining and then take up my offer of swapping places with the slaves? Or are you going to just drop it?)]
		#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyBribed))
			[sean.speech(So, we're doing this again, are we? You want to keep on complaining and then pay the 'official sponsored break' fee? Or are you going to just drop it?)]
		#ELSE
			[sean.speech(So, what do you want now? Let me guess, you've got more complaining to do?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You really don't like the idea of slaves being locked into stocks and then being publicly used, and with [sean.name] being the only authority figure that you can see, you decide to voice your objections to him.
	</p>
	<p>
		Although he displays his annoyance by sighing and rolling his eyes as he hears what it is you're saying, the [sean.race] allows you to finish voicing your opinion without interruption. As you finish making your case for why the slaves shouldn't be subjected to such humiliating treatment, [sean.name] asks, [sean.speech(Why do you even care what happens to them? By their very nature of being slaves, they're either criminals or people who willingly sold themselves into slavery. How about you just drop it and go and find some other cause to champion.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking a moment to consider [sean.namePos] words, you decide that it would indeed be for the best if you were to drop your complaint. Telling the [sean.race] that you still don't like what's going on in this place, you step away from him and move off into the square.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you head off, [sean.name] calls out after you, [sean.speech(If you've any other business, come back and let me know!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_PERSIST -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_PERSIST_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ignoring [sean.namePos] comment, you once again persist with your old argument, pointing out that even if slaves are criminals or have been willingly enslaved, they should still be treated with dignity. Ignoring the fact that [sean.name] looks increasingly annoyed with each passing moment, you go on to blame not only Lilith's governance for this egregious assault on each slave's basic rights, but also the people responsible for upholding these unjust slavery laws, including [sean.name] himself.
	</p>
	<p>
		Having patiently listened this whole time, [sean.name] lets out a deep sigh as you finally come to the end of your argument. With a knowing look on his face, he says,  [sean.speech(Let's cut the bullshit, ok? My offer from before still stands; if you're willing to fight me, and you win, I'll give you the keys to the stocks and stay out of your way for fifteen minutes or so. You lose, however, and I lock you up in the stocks alongside the slaves to show you that getting fucked by random members of the public isn't as bad as you're imagining.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting a grin settle on his face, the [sean.race] waits to hear your answer. You could always agree to do as he says, and duel him in the nearby alleyway, but then again, there might be another way to get what you want. You could try to bribe him to get the keys to the stocks, or, if you really wanted to, offer to temporarily swap places with one of the slaves in order to give them an opportunity to escape...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_PERSIST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ignoring [sean.namePos] comment, you persist with your argument, pointing out that even if slaves are criminals or have been willingly enslaved, they should still be treated with dignity. Ignoring the fact that [sean.name] looks increasingly annoyed with each passing moment, you go on to blame not only Lilith's governance for this egregious assault on each slave's basic rights, but also the people responsible for upholding these unjust slavery laws, including [sean.name] himself.
	</p>
	<p>
		Having patiently listened this whole time, [sean.name] lets out a deep sigh as you finally come to the end of your argument. With a stern look on his face, he says, [sean.speech(You're really going too far, calling out Lilith herself like that. If I still gave a shit about this job, I'd have more than half a mind to arrest you right now for what you've just said. Lucky for you, you're the only interesting thing that's happened to me while stationed here, so I'm not about to get rid of you so easily.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So are you going to do something about these slaves or not?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Am <i>I</i> going to do anything? No I'm not,)] [sean.name] replies, before mischievously grinning and continuing, [sean.speech(but perhaps if you were to offer me some more entertainment, I'd give you the chance to free them yourself.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(What kind of entertainment?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(The kind we can make a bet on,)] [sean.name] replies, [sean.speech(I know of a hidden alleyway near here in which we could play a sort of game. I've not had the opportunity to hone my combat skills for a good long while now, so if you're willing to fight me, and you win, I'll give you the keys to the stocks and stay out of your way for fifteen minutes or so. You lose, however, and I lock you up in the stocks alongside the slaves to show you that getting fucked by random members of the public isn't as bad as you're imagining.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a big grin on his face, the [sean.race] waits to hear your answer. You could always agree to do as he says, and duel him in the nearby alleyway, but then again, there might be another way to get what you want. You could try to bribe him to get the keys to the stocks, or, if you really wanted to, offer to temporarily swap places with one of the slaves in order to give them an opportunity to escape...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_PERSIST_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Taking a moment to consider your options, you decide that it would be best if you were to refuse [sean.namePos] challenge. Telling him that perhaps you'll consider his offer and be back another time, you step away and move off into the square.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you head off, [sean.name] calls out after you, [sean.speech(See you around!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that the best way to free the slaves is to accept [sean.namePos] offer, you tell him that you're once again willing to fight him. As he hears you say this, the [sean.race] grins and says, [sean.speech(Great! Let's head to that hidden alleyway again.)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Doing as [sean.name] suggests, the three of you head down the main street a short distance, before veering off to the right and stepping up to the weathered wooden door that's set into the brick wall façade. Grabbing the handle and forcefully pushing the door open, the [sean.race] leads the way through into the wide, open-air alleyway. Turning to face you and your [com.companion], [sean.name] says, [sean.speech(I told you that nobody ever comes here; look, it's completely deserted again. So, are you two ready to fight? I'm not going to go easy on the pair of you!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Doing as [sean.name] suggests, you follow on as he heads down the main street a short distance, before veering off to the right and stepping up to the weathered wooden door that's set into the brick wall façade. Grabbing the handle and forcefully pushing the door open, the [sean.race] leads the way through into the wide, open-air alleyway. Turning to face you, he says, [sean.speech(I told you that nobody ever comes here; look, it's completely deserted again. So, are you ready to fight? I'm not going to go easy on you!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Taking off his utility belt, stabproof vest, and beret, [sean.name] rests his hands on his pistols, ready to engage you in combat. This seems to be your final opportunity to back out, although the [sean.race] will undoubtedly think less of you for wasting his time if you choose to do so...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that the best way to free the slaves is to accept [sean.namePos] offer, you tell him that you're willing to fight him. As he hears you say this, the [sean.race] grins and says, [sean.speech(Great! Follow me; the alleyway where we can do it isn't too far from here.)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Doing as [sean.name] instructs, you and [com.name] follow him down the main street a short distance, before veering off to the right and stepping up to a weathered wooden door set into an otherwise featureless brick wall. Grabbing the handle and giving it a forceful push, the [sean.race] demonstrates that this door is kept unlocked, and as it swings open, he strides through to the other side. Continuing to follow in [sean.namePos] footsteps, you and [com.name] step through the doorway.
		</p>
		<p>
			Although the brick wall had given the impression that this door would lead into a building's enclosed interior, you instead discover that it was nothing more than a deceptive façade, as you now find yourselves standing in a relatively wide alleyway, with the open sky above your heads. Turning to face you and your [com.companion], [sean.name] says, [sean.speech(Nobody knows about this place, and those that do have no reason to come here, as all it leads to is a dead end. It's the perfect place for a fight, so, are you two ready to do it? I'm not going to go easy on the pair of you!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Doing as [sean.name] instructs, you follow him down the main street a short distance, before veering off to the right and stepping up to a weathered wooden door set into an otherwise featureless brick wall. Grabbing the handle and giving it a forceful push, the [sean.race] demonstrates that this door is kept unlocked, and as it swings open, he strides through to the other side. Continuing to follow in [sean.namePos] footsteps, you step through the doorway.
		</p>
		<p>
			Although the brick wall had given the impression that this door would lead into a building's enclosed interior, you instead discover that it was nothing more than a deceptive façade, as you now find yourself standing in a relatively wide alleyway, with the open sky above your head. Turning to face you, [sean.name] says, [sean.speech(Nobody knows about this place, and those that do have no reason to come here, as all it leads to is a dead end. It's the perfect place for a fight, so, are you ready to do it? I'm not going to go easy on you!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		#IF(!sean.isPlayerKnowsName())
			[sean.speech(Seeing as I'm not exactly following Enforcer guidelines with you anymore, I guess you can call me [sean.name(true)] from now on,)] he continues, before taking off his utility belt, stabproof vest, and beret, and then resting his hands on his pistols, ready to engage you in combat.
		#ELSE
			Taking off his utility belt, stabproof vest, and beret, [sean.name] rests his hands on his pistols, ready to engage you in combat.
		#ENDIF
		 This seems to be your final opportunity to back out, although the [sean.race] will undoubtedly think less of you for wasting his time if you choose to do so...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_BRIBE_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that there's a way in which you can free the slaves without having to resort to violence, you slyly ask [sean.name] if you're still able to make an 'official' payment to sponsor him taking a fifteen minute coffee break. Obviously happy to hear what it is you're suggesting, the [sean.race] grins and replies, [sean.speech(Yeah, we're still trialling that, and it'll be five-thousand flames again.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Happy to hear that [sean.name] is still willing to take bribes, you produce another five-thousand flames, before handing it over to him. With a grin still on his face, the [sean.race] gives you his keys to the stocks once again, saying, [sean.speech(You don't mind looking after these for a while, do you? They open all of the stocks, so make sure they don't fall into the wrong hands, ok? I'll be back in fifteen minutes, and I'm hoping that you won't be handed over to me by the private security guards when I get back, understand?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Assuring [sean.name] that you won't get caught, you watch as he ambles off down the street and out of sight. With just fifteen minutes before he returns, you realise that you'd better make haste in releasing the slaves...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_BRIBE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that there must be a way in which you can free the slaves without having to resort to violence, you slyly ask [sean.name] if there's some kind of 'official' payment you can make that would allow to him go and take a break and leave the stocks unattended for a while. Instantly catching on to what it is you're suggesting, the [sean.race] grins and replies, [sean.speech(Yeah, there's something like that which we're trialling at the moment. You can pay... hmm... I think five-thousand flames, and that sponsors an Enforcer to take a fifteen minute coffee break. Is that the sort of thing you were thinking of?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Replying in the affirmative, you produce the five-thousand flames which [sean.name] is asking for, before questioning whether or not you can pay it directly to him. With a grin still on his face, the [sean.race] takes the money out of your [pc.hands], before saying, [sean.speech(Of course, I'll take this and make sure it goes into the 'offical' fund. Oh, and I suppose you were wanting to help out by taking care of these for a while as well?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing exactly what it is you were after, and obviously hoping that by helping you out he'll get more bribes in the future, [sean.name] produces a set of keys and hands them over to you. Pocketing the cash you've just handed over, he continues,
		#IF(!sean.isPlayerKnowsName())
			 [sean.speech(Those open all of the stocks, so make sure they don't fall into the wrong hands, ok? I'll be back in fifteen minutes, and I'm hoping that you won't be handed over to me by the private security guards when I get back, understand? Oh, and seeing as you're such a good friend to us Enforcers by doing this, you can just call me '[sean.name(true)]' from now on.)]
		#ELSE
			 [sean.speech(Those open all of the stocks, so make sure they don't fall into the wrong hands, ok? I'll be back in fifteen minutes, and I'm hoping that you won't be handed over to me by the private security guards when I get back, understand?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Assuring [sean.name] that you won't get caught, you watch as he ambles off down the street and out of sight. With just fifteen minutes before he returns, you realise that you'd better make haste in releasing the slaves...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_TAKE_PLACE_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight if at all possible, but still wanting to do something to help the slaves in the stocks, you ask [sean.name] if you can trade places with one of them again, thereby giving them at least a few hours of rest from their ordeal. Grinning as he hears that you want to spend some time in the stocks again, [sean.name] says, [sean.speech(Sure thing; it's pretty entertaining having you take a slave's place for a while. You go ahead and choose which one of them you want to replace.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking around at the dozen or so slaves locked up in the square, your eyes settle on [npc.a_race] who looks to be particularly worn-out and over-used. A short queue of random members of the public has formed behind [npc.herHim], waiting for the guy who's currently roughly fucking [npc.herHim] to be done so that they can have a turn. Pointing to this unfortunate slave, you tell [sean.name] that you'd like to give [npc.herHim] the opportunity to take a break.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Sure thing,)] the [sean.race] replies, leading you over to the stocks in which the [npc.race] is locked. Shouting out for the members of the public to clear off, [sean.name] tells the guy currently pounding the [npc.race] from behind to hurry up and finish. A few moments, and one huge load of spunk later, and the weary, cum-stuffed [npc.race] is being swiftly released from [npc.her] restraints. Taking [npc.her] place, you allow [sean.name] to strip you and lock you into the stocks, telling yourself all the while that this is the right thing to do in order to help out the slave.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_TAKE_PLACE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight if at all possible, but still wanting to do something to help the slaves in the stocks, you ask [sean.name] if you can trade places with one of them, thereby giving them at least a few hours of rest from their ordeal. Opening his eyes wide in surprise as he hears what it is you're suggesting, the [sean.race] nevertheless replies in agreement,
		#IF(!sean.isPlayerKnowsName())
			 [sean.speech(Well, if that's the sort of thing you're into, then sure, why not? It'll give me some entertainment, at least. You choose which slave you want to replace. Oh, and by the way, I can tell that you're going to be a familiar face around here, so you might as well get to calling me '[sean.name(true)]' from now on.)]
		#ELSE
			 [sean.speech(Well, if that's the sort of thing you're into, then sure, why not? It'll give me some entertainment, at least. You choose which slave you want to replace.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking around at the dozen or so slaves locked up in the square, your eyes settle on [npc.a_race] who looks to be particularly worn-out and over-used. A short queue of random members of the public has formed behind [npc.herHim], waiting for the guy who's currently roughly fucking [npc.herHim] to be done so that they can have a turn. Pointing to this unfortunate slave, you tell [sean.name(true)] that you'd like to give [npc.herHim] the opportunity to take a break.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Sure thing,)] the [sean.race] replies, leading you over to the stocks in which the [npc.race] is locked. Shouting out for the members of the public to clear off, [sean.name(true)] tells the guy currently pounding the [npc.race] from behind to hurry up and finish. A few moments, and one huge load of spunk later, and the weary, cum-stuffed [npc.race] is being swiftly released from [npc.her] restraints. Taking [npc.her] place, you allow [sean.name(true)] to strip you and lock you into the stocks, telling yourself all the while that this is the right thing to do in order to help out the slave.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_TAKE_PLACE_BOTH_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight if at all possible, but still wanting to do something to help the slaves in the stocks, you ask [sean.name] if you and [com.name] can trade places with two of them again, thereby giving them at least a few hours of rest from their ordeal. Grinning as he hears that you want to spend some time in the stocks again, [sean.name] says, [sean.speech(Sure thing; it's pretty entertaining having the two of you take a couple of slaves' places for a while. You go ahead and choose which of them you want to replace.)]
	</p>
	#IF(com.equals(brax))
		<p>
			As you turn to look at the stocks, [sean.name(true)] steps closer to [com.name] and teases, [sean.speech(You never told anyone at the station that you were into this sort of thing, [com.name], or did you get into public humiliation after becoming a slave?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				[com.speech(Fuck off, [sean.surname],)] [com.name] snaps, [com.speech(The sort of stuff I'm into is none of your damn business.)]
			#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
				[com.speech(Well, I guess I came to like it later on, yeah,)] [com.name] mutters, blushing as [com.she] submissively shuffles [com.her] [com.feet].
			#ELSE
				[com.speech(I guess I came to like it later on, yeah,)] [com.name] admits, blushing a little and crossing [com.her] [com.arms].
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Looking around at the dozen or so slaves locked up in the square, your eyes settle on
		#IF(npc.getRace()==npc2.getRace())
			 a pair of [npc.races],
		#ELSE
			 [npc.a_race] and [npc2.a_race],
		#ENDIF
		 who not only are locked up beside one another, but who also look to be particularly worn-out and over-used. A short queue of random members of the public has formed behind the two of them, waiting for the guys who are currently roughly fucking them to be done so that they can have a turn. Pointing to these unfortunate slaves, you tell [sean.name(true)] that you'd like to give them the opportunity to take a break.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Sure thing,)] the [sean.race] replies, leading you over to the stocks in which the slaves are locked. Shouting out for the members of the public to clear off, [sean.name(true)] tells the guys currently pounding the slaves from behind to hurry up and finish. A few moments, and a couple of huge loads of spunk later, and the weary, cum-stuffed
		#IF(npc.getRace()==npc2.getRace())
			 [npc.races]
		#ELSE
			 [npc.race] and [npc2.race]
		#ENDIF
		 are being swiftly released from their restraints. Taking their place, you and [com.name] allow [sean.name(true)] to strip the two of you and lock you into the stocks, telling yourself all the while that this is the right thing to do in order to help out the slaves.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_TAKE_PLACE_BOTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to avoid a fight if at all possible, but still wanting to do something to help the slaves in the stocks, you ask [sean.name] if you and [com.name] can trade places with two of them, thereby giving them at least a few hours of rest from their ordeal. Opening his eyes wide in surprise as he hears what it is you're suggesting, the [sean.race] nevertheless replies in agreement,
		#IF(!sean.isPlayerKnowsName())
			 [sean.speech(Well, if that's the sort of thing you're both into, then sure, why not? It'll give me some entertainment, at least. You choose which slaves you want to replace. Oh, and by the way, I can tell that you're going to be a familiar face around here, so you might as well get to calling me '[sean.name(true)]' from now on.)]
		#ELSE
			 [sean.speech(Well, if that's the sort of thing you're both into, then sure, why not? It'll give me some entertainment, at least. You choose which slaves you want to replace.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(com.equals(brax))
		<p>
			As you turn to look at the stocks, [sean.name(true)] steps closer to [com.name] and teases, [sean.speech(You never told anyone at the station that you were into this sort of thing, [com.name], or did you get into public humiliation after becoming a slave?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				[com.speech(Fuck off, [sean.surname],)] [com.name] snaps, [com.speech(The sort of stuff I'm into is none of your damn business.)]
			#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
				[com.speech(Well, I guess I came to like it later on, yeah,)] [com.name] mutters, blushing as [com.she] submissively shuffles [com.her] [com.feet].
			#ELSE
				[com.speech(I guess I came to like it later on, yeah,)] [com.name] admits, blushing a little and crossing [com.her] [com.arms].
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Looking around at the dozen or so slaves locked up in the square, your eyes settle on
		#IF(npc.getRace()==npc2.getRace())
			 a pair of [npc.races],
		#ELSE
			 [npc.a_race] and [npc2.a_race],
		#ENDIF
		 who not only are locked up beside one another, but who also look to be particularly worn-out and over-used. A short queue of random members of the public has formed behind the two of them, waiting for the guys who are currently roughly fucking them to be done so that they can have a turn. Pointing to these unfortunate slaves, you tell [sean.name(true)] that you'd like to give them the opportunity to take a break.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Sure thing,)] the [sean.race] replies, leading you over to the stocks in which the slaves are locked. Shouting out for the members of the public to clear off, [sean.name(true)] tells the guys currently pounding the slaves from behind to hurry up and finish. A few moments, and a couple of huge loads of spunk later, and the weary, cum-stuffed
		#IF(npc.getRace()==npc2.getRace())
			 [npc.races]
		#ELSE
			 [npc.race] and [npc2.race]
		#ENDIF
		 are being swiftly released from their restraints. Taking their place, you and [com.name] allow [sean.name(true)] to strip the two of you and lock you into the stocks, telling yourself all the while that this is the right thing to do in order to help out the slaves.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE_BACK_OUT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having second thoughts about this whole endeavour, you take a step back and explain to [sean.name] that you don't want to fight him after all. Letting out a disappointed sigh, the [sean.race] grabs his stabproof vest, utility belt, and beret, and while putting them back on, complains, [sean.speech(Damn it, you got me really fired up here! You shouldn't do that to folks!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Apologising for leading him on, you move aside as [sean.name] heads back out into Slaver Alley, before quickly marching off back to his post. Following on, you and [com.name] step out through the doorway, closing the weathered door behind you as you wonder where to go to next...
		#ELSE
			Apologising for leading him on, you move aside as [sean.name] heads back out into Slaver Alley, before quickly marching off back to his post. Following on, you step out through the doorway, closing the weathered door behind you as you wonder where to go to next...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE_VICTORY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE_VICTORY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Staggering back against one wall of the alleyway, [sean.name] calls out, [sean.speech(Wait! No more! Y-You got me...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			#IF(com.equals(brax))
				Stepping forwards, you and [com.name] watch as the [sean.race] holsters his pistols, before reaching into one of his pockets and producing a set of keys. Throwing them over to you, he sighs, [sean.speech(Damn it... I really am rusty after all this time doing nothing... I'll be back at my post in fifteen minutes, so make the most of your time. Those keys will unlock the stocks, but please try not to get caught while doing it; I don't know how I'd explain all this... Oh, and well fought, you two... I guess you're still as sharp as you always were, [com.name]...)]
			#ELSE
				Stepping forwards, you and [com.name] watch as the [sean.race] holsters his pistols, before reaching into one of his pockets and producing a set of keys. Throwing them over to you, he sighs, [sean.speech(Damn it... I really am rusty after all this time doing nothing... I'll be back at my post in fifteen minutes, so make the most of your time. Those keys will unlock the stocks, but please try not to get caught while doing it; I don't know how I'd explain all this... Oh, and well fought, you two... You really got me...)]
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			Stepping forwards, you watch as the [sean.race] holsters his pistols, before reaching into one of his pockets and producing a set of keys. Throwing them over to you, he sighs, [sean.speech(Damn it... I really am rusty after all this time doing nothing... I'll be back at my post in fifteen minutes, so make the most of your time. Those keys will unlock the stocks, but please try not to get caught while doing it; I don't know how I'd explain all this... Oh, and well fought... You really got me...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isFeminine())
			Looking down at the keys in your [pc.hand], you wonder whether you should go and free the slaves, or perhaps take this opportunity to make a move on [sean.name]. From the look in his eyes, you can tell that he's attracted to you, so it shouldn't take much to convince him to have sex with you...
		#ELSE
			Looking down at the keys in your [pc.hand], you resolve to go and free the slaves right away...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE_VICTORY_FREE_SLAVES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			Exiting the alleyway through the same door by which you entered, you and [com.name] hurry back to where the public stocks are located. 
		#ELSE
			Exiting the alleyway through the same door by which you entered, you hurry back to where the public stocks are located. 
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE_VICTORY_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to miss this opportunity to have sex with [sean.name], you step up to him and seductively suggest that he let you take good care of him. Although worn out from the fight you just had, [sean.name] manages to summon the energy to stand up, and with a mischievous grin on his face, he replies, [sean.speech(You know, there are easier ways to get into my pants than having to fight me first...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing that [sean.name] is more than happy to have sex with you, you step forwards and pull him into a passionate kiss. Continuing to make out with one another for a minute or two, you eventually pull back, before grinding up against the [sean.race]'s body. Realising that you're about to really get started with having sex with him, [sean.name] happily sighs, [sean.speech(I guess I don't mind losing to you if this is what I get out of it!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE_VICTORY_SEX_BOTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to miss this opportunity to have sex with [sean.name], you step up to him and seductively suggest that he let you and [com.name] take good care of him. Although worn out from the fight you just had, [sean.name] manages to summon the energy to stand up, and with a mischievous grin on his face, he replies, [sean.speech(You know, there are easier ways to get into my pants than having to fight me first...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(com.equals(brax))
			Seeing that the [sean.race] is more than happy to have sex with you and [com.name], you step forwards and pull him into a passionate kiss. Continuing to make out with one another for a minute or two, you eventually pull back, before letting [com.name] step forwards and have a turn. Despite the fact that the two of them have some bad history with one another, all seems to be forgotten in the heat of the moment, and [com.name] enthusiastically leans into [sean.name] as the two of them start groping and kissing one another.
		#ELSE
			Seeing that the [sean.race] is more than happy to have sex with you and [com.name], you step forwards and pull him into a passionate kiss. Continuing to make out with one another for a minute or two, you eventually pull back, before letting [com.name] step forwards and have a turn. Just as eager to have sex as you are, [com.name] enthusiastically leans into [sean.name] as the two of them start groping and kissing one another.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After your [com.companion] has spent a few moments making out with [sean.name], [com.she] pulls back, allowing you to step up right beside [com.herHim]. Realising that the two of you are about to really get started with having sex with him, [sean.name] happily sighs, [sean.speech(I guess I don't mind losing to the two of you if this is what I get out of it!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_SEAN_ALLEYWAY_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_ALLEYWAY_SEX_THREESOME"><![CDATA[
	#IF(com.equals(brax))
		<p>
			Letting out a satisfied sigh, [sean.name] disentangles himself from you and [com.name]. As the three of you start to get your things back in order, the [sean.race] comments, [sean.speech(Getting to spend time with the two of you certainly makes this assignment not seem so bad after all! You know, you're a lot easier to like now that you're not my boss, [com.name].)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				[brax.speech(Don't get cocky!)] [brax.name] snaps, [com.speech(Just because I sometimes need a good fuck, doesn't make us friends!)]
			#ELSEIF(brax.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
				[brax.speech(Thanks, [sean.surname],)] [brax.name] softly replies, blushing.
			#ELSE
				[brax.speech(You're easier to get on with like this as well,)] [brax.name] admits, blushing a little.
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Grinning at [com.namePos] comment, you turn to face [sean.name] as he finishes getting dressed and states, [sean.speech(I need to get back to my post now; I guess the time for you freeing those slaves has passed...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Telling [sean.name] that you're sure there will be more opportunities to free them in the future, you hand his keys back over to him. Telling you to come and visit him again soon, the [sean.race] dashes off, leaving you to finish getting your things together...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Letting out a satisfied sigh, [sean.name] disentangles himself from you and [com.name]. As the three of you start to get your things back in order, the [sean.race] comments, [sean.speech(Getting to spend time with the two of you certainly makes this assignment not seem so bad after all!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Grinning at [sean.namePos] comment, you and [com.name] turn to face him as he finishes getting dressed and continues, [sean.speech(I need to get back to my post now; I guess the time for you freeing those slaves has passed...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Telling [sean.name] that you're sure there will be more opportunities to free them in the future, you hand his keys back over to him. Telling you to come and visit him again soon, the [sean.race] dashes off, leaving you to finish getting your things together...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_ALLEYWAY_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a satisfied sigh, you and [sean.name] disentangle yourselves from one another. As the two of you start to get your things back in order, the [sean.race] comments, [sean.speech(Getting to spend time with you certainly makes this assignment not seem so bad after all!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Grinning at [sean.namePos] comment, you turn to face him as he finishes getting dressed and continues, [sean.speech(I need to get back to my post now; I guess the time for you freeing those slaves has passed...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Telling [sean.name] that you're sure there will be more opportunities to free them in the future, you hand his keys back over to him. Telling you to come and visit him again soon, the [sean.race] dashes off, leaving you to finish getting your things together...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEAN_ALLEYWAY_SEX_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
			As soon as you're ready to go, you and [com.name] head back out of the hidden alleyway, and once again find yourselves standing in Slaver Alley, wondering what to do next...
		#ELSE
			As soon as you're ready to go, you head back out of the hidden alleyway, and once again find yourself standing in Slaver Alley, wondering what to do next...
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE_DEFEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_CHALLENGE_DEFEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stumbling back against the nearest of the alleyway's walls, you let out an exhausted groan and slump to the floor, defeated. Having proven to be more than a match for you, [sean.name] holsters his pistols and proudly declares, [sean.speech(I thought I was getting rusty, but it looks like I've still got it!)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions())
		<p>
			Striding forwards to where you and [com.name] have fallen, the [sean.race] looks down and continues, [sean.speech(A deal's a deal! I won, so now the two of you get to provide me with some more entertainment in the stocks! Come on!)]
		</p>
		#IF(game.isInvoluntaryNTREnabled())
			<p>
				Clearly still possessing a large amount of energy, [sean.name] half-drags, half-carries you and [com.name] all the way back to the square in which the public stocks are located. Attracted by the commotion, a small crowd starts to gather around you and [com.name] as [sean.name] strips the two of you naked and then locks you into a free pair of stocks. As he slides the bolts shut, the [sean.race] declares, [sean.speech(There we go! All ready to have some fun with members of the public!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Clearly still possessing a large amount of energy, [sean.name] half-drags, half-carries you and [com.name] all the way back to the square in which the public stocks are located. Taking a look around, the [sean.race] sighs in annoyance, [sean.speech(Damn... There's only one free set of stocks...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Clearly having decided that you're more deserving of a place in the stocks than [com.name], [sean.name] leaves your companion to recover their strength and watch as he strips you naked and then locks you into the free set of stocks. Attracted by the commotion, a small crowd starts to gather around as the [sean.race] slides the bolts shut and declares, [sean.speech(There we go! All ready to have some fun with members of the public!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Striding forwards to where you've fallen, the [sean.race] looks down and continues, [sean.speech(A deal's a deal! I won, so now you get to provide me with some more entertainment in the stocks! Come on!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly still possessing a large amount of energy, [sean.name] half-drags, half-carries you all the way back to the square in which the public stocks are located. Attracted by the commotion, a small crowd starts to gather around as [sean.name] strips you naked and then locks you into a free pair of stocks. As he slides the bolts shut, the [sean.race] declares, [sean.speech(There we go! All ready to have some fun with members of the public!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_FREE_SLAVES -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_FREE_SLAVES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Now that [sean.name] is out of the way, you see that the only people in a position to stop you from freeing the slaves are the two private security guards standing watch at the main entrance to Slaver Alley. Thankfully, they seem to be only interested in making sure no runaways slip past them, and so you're able to get started on unlocking the stocks without them noticing.
	</p>
	<p>
		Slipping quickly from slave to slave and freeing them from their restraints, you inform each one that they should take this opportunity to escape. Where you encounter one or more members of the public having sex with one of the slaves, you dismiss them by telling them that you're the slave's owner and that you're taking them back home. In this manner, you're able to release every slave in a matter of minutes, all the while managing to avoid detection.
	</p>
	<p>
		Quickly retreating to one side of the square so as to not be seen when the alarm is inevitably raised, you look back and see that almost half of the slaves you've just freed are refusing to leave their stocks. The other half, however, start running off into Slaver Alley, and one by one, they disappear out of sight. It's at this moment that the guards at the entrance to Slaver Alley suddenly notice what's going on, and, rushing forwards, they shout out for the escapees to halt.
	</p>
	<p>
		Refusing to obey the orders given to them, the slaves continue running off, and some of them even slip around the guards to rush out of the entrance and escape into Dominion's alleyways. Drawn by the large commotion that's breaking out, several more guards soon rush into the area, and set about trying to track down and recapture the runaway slaves. As they try to figure out what's going on, they command all the members of the public to stand back, and, not wanting to stand out and be identified as the cause of the slaves' escape, you do as they say.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_FREE_SLAVES_END -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_COMPLAIN_FREE_SLAVES_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping away from the square in which the public stocks are positioned, you watch as the guards frantically try to figure out how the slaves were released from their restraints. It's at this moment that you hear the familiar voice of [sean.name] behind you, and you spin around to see the [sean.race] grinning as he says, [sean.speech(Looks like you got what you wanted, huh? I'll have to shut the place down while we 'investigate', but don't worry, I'll make sure they don't find out what really happened. Now, you got my keys?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Handing over [sean.namePos] keys, you step aside as he strides forwards into the square and takes charge of the situation. From what you can make out of the snippets of conversation you overhear between the [sean.race] and the private security guards, the public stocks are to be closed for the remainder of the day, and it's to be assumed that some kind of saboteur snuck in and picked the locks on all the stocks, before disappearing without a trace.
	</p>
	<p>
		A few minutes later, and the guards once again allow traffic to pass through the square once more. As you amble forwards amongst the crowds, you're pleased to see that the stocks which contain the slaves who refused to escape have all been marked as unavailable for public use. With your work here being done, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_DEAL_BOTH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Walking around in front of you and [com.name], [sean.name] grins and says, [sean.speech(Now, I was thinking of giving the two of you a choice as to what happens to you. I can always mark you both as being available for public use, or, if you'd like, I could spare you that and keep you all to myself instead.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Fishing around in his pocket, the [sean.race] produces a pair of small purple pills, and holds them up in front of you and [com.name] as he explains, [sean.speech(Of course, if you want me to keep the public away from you, you'll have to swallow these [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getNamePlural(false)] and beg for me to breed you. You'd like me to pound your pussies and fill you with my virile seed, wouldn't you?)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionAcceptedDeal))
		#IF(com.equals(brax))
			<p>
				Quick to reply, [com.name] shuffles about a little in [com.her] stocks and admits, [com.speech(Yes, I'd like that...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Hah! Who would ever have guessed that one day you'd be admitting that you want me to breed you, eh, <i>Inspector</i>?)] [sean.name] teases.
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					[com.speech(Just give me the pill and get started already,)] [com.name] snaps, [com.speech(Better that you knock me up than having a bunch of strangers use me like this...)]
				#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					[com.speech(Please, give me the pill already!)] [com.name] impatiently whines, opening [com.her] mouth.
				#ELSE
					[com.speech(Come on, just give me the pill and stop teasing me already!)] [com.name] whines, opening [com.her] mouth.
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				Doing as [com.she] asks, [sean.name] pops one of the purple pills out of its protective wrapper, before placing it on [com.namePos] outstretched tongue and then teasing, [sean.speech(Go on then, [com.name], beg for me to breed you!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Quickly swallowing down the fertility-enhancing pill, your [com.companion] obediently whines,
				#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					[com.speech(Fuck... I can't believe I'm doing this... Please, [sean.surname], I need your cock! J-Just breed me already!)]
				#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					[com.speech(Please, I need your cock! Just breed me already!)]
				#ELSE
					[com.speech(Please, I need your cock! Just breed me already!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Quick to reply, [com.name] shuffles about a little in [com.her] stocks and admits, [com.speech(Yes, I'd like that... Please, give me the pill and then breed me!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Doing as [com.she] asks, [sean.name] pops one of the purple pills out of its protective wrapper, before placing it on [com.namePos] outstretched tongue. Quickly swallowing it down, your [com.companion] whines, [com.speech(Please, I need your cock! Just breed me already!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Don't worry, you'll be getting it soon enough!)] [sean.name] replies, chuckling at [com.namePos] eager request. Turning to face you, he continues, [sean.speech(First, however, I need to hear your friend's answer!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(!com.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isPositive())
				As [com.she] doesn't have a positive desire towards the pregnancy fetish, [com.name] shuffles about a little in [com.her] stocks and exclaims, [com.speech(There's no way I'm agreeing to that!)]
			#ELSE
				Quick to reply, [com.name] shuffles about a little in [com.her] stocks and exclaims, [com.speech(There's no way I'm agreeing to that!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out an annoyed grunt, [sean.name] puts one of the pills back in his pocket. Turning to face you, he asks, [sean.speech(So, what about you? You want to be bred my me, right?)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_DEAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Walking around in front of you, [sean.name] grins and says, [sean.speech(Now, I was thinking of giving you a choice as to what happens to you. I can always mark you as being available for public use, or, if you'd like, I could spare you that and keep you all to myself instead.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Fishing around in his pocket, the [sean.race] produces a small purple pill, and holds it up in front of you as he explains, [sean.speech(Of course, if you want me to keep the public away from you, you'll have to swallow this [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getName(false)] and beg for me to breed you. You'd like me to pound your pussy and knock you up, wouldn't you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_DEAL_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Walking around in front of [com.name], [sean.name] grins and says, [sean.speech(Now, I was thinking of giving you a choice as to what happens to you. I can always mark you as being available for public use, or, if you'd like, I could spare you that and keep you all to myself instead.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Fishing around in his pocket, the [sean.race] produces a small purple pill, and holds it up in front of your [com.companion] he explains, [sean.speech(Of course, if you want me to keep the public away from you, you'll have to swallow this [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getName(false)] and beg for me to breed you. You'd like me to pound your pussy and knock you up, wouldn't you?)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionAcceptedDeal))
		#IF(com.equals(brax))
			<p>
				Quick to reply, [com.name] shuffles about a little in [com.her] stocks and admits, [com.speech(Yes, I'd like that...)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Hah! Who would ever have guessed that one day you'd be admitting that you want me to breed you, eh, <i>Inspector</i>?)] [sean.name] teases.
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					[com.speech(Just give me the pill and get started already,)] [com.name] snaps, [com.speech(Better that you knock me up than having a bunch of strangers use me like this...)]
				#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					[com.speech(Please, give me the pill already!)] [com.name] impatiently whines, opening [com.her] mouth.
				#ELSE
					[com.speech(Come on, just give me the pill and stop teasing me already!)] [com.name] whines, opening [com.her] mouth.
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				Doing as [com.she] asks, [sean.name] pops one of the purple pills out of its protective wrapper, before placing it on [com.namePos] outstretched tongue and then teasing, [sean.speech(Go on then, [com.name], beg for me to breed you!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Quickly swallowing down the fertility-enhancing pill, your [com.companion] obediently whines,
				#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					[com.speech(Fuck... I can't believe I'm doing this... Please, [sean.surname], I need your cock! J-Just breed me already!)]
				#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					[com.speech(Please, I need your cock! Just breed me already!)]
				#ELSE
					[com.speech(Please, I need your cock! Just breed me already!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Quick to reply, [com.name] shuffles about a little in [com.her] stocks and admits, [com.speech(Yes, I'd like that... Please, give me the pill and then breed me!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Doing as [com.she] asks, [sean.name] pops one of the purple pills out of its protective wrapper, before placing it on [com.namePos] outstretched tongue. Quickly swallowing it down, your [com.companion] whines, [com.speech(Please, I need your cock! Just breed me already!)]
			</p>
			<p>
		#ENDIF
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Don't worry, you'll be getting it soon enough!)] [sean.name] replies, walking around behind [com.name] and giving [com.her] exposed pussy a gentle slap. Laughing in response to the horny moan which [com.name] makes, he moves over to mark your set of stocks as being fully available for public use, before walking off and calling over his shoulder, [sean.speech(I'll be back to give you a good breeding once I've seen your friend here get fucked!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(!com.getFetishDesire(FETISH_PREGNANCY).isPositive())
				As [com.she] doesn't have a positive desire towards the pregnancy fetish, [com.name] shuffles about a little in [com.her] stocks and exclaims, [com.speech(There's no way I'm agreeing to that!)]
			#ELSE
				Quick to reply, [com.name] shuffles about a little in [com.her] stocks and exclaims, [com.speech(There's no way I'm agreeing to that!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out an annoyed grunt, [sean.name] put the pill back in his pocket. Marking both of your stocks as being fully available for public use, he then walks off, calling over his shoulder, [sean.speech(I'll be back to let you go once you've both had a good fucking!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.hasCompanions() && game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionInStocks))
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Right, so I'll get both your stocks marked up as being fully available for public use,)] [sean.name] says, moving between you and [com.name] as he carries out his task. Once he's done, he steps around in front of you and cheekily asks, [sean.speech(A deal's a deal, so there are no hard feelings, right?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Taking the defeated whines which you and [com.name] make as confirmation that you're not angry with him, [sean.name] smiles and walks off, calling over his shoulder as he goes, [sean.speech(I'll be back to let you go once you've both had a good fucking! I'm sure it won't take long before some strangers decide to use you!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Right, so I'll get your stocks marked up as being fully available for public use,)] [sean.name] says, moving forwards and quickly carrying out his task. Once he's done, he steps around in front of you and cheekily asks, [sean.speech(A deal's a deal, so there are no hard feelings, right?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Taking the defeated whine which you let out as confirmation that you're not angry with him, [sean.name] smiles and walks off, calling over his shoulder as he goes, [sean.speech(I'll be back to let you go once you've had a good fucking! I'm sure it won't take long before some strangers decide to use you!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_ACCEPTED_DEAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that it would be preferable to get bred by [sean.name] rather than having an unknown number of strangers fuck you, you tell the [sean.race] that you accept his deal. Opening your mouth, you allow him to slide the purple pill past your [pc.lips], before gulping it down and opening wide to show him that you've swallowed it.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Now, tell me that you want me to breed you,)] [sean.name] says, reminding you of the other part of his deal.
	</p>
	<p>
		By now starting to feel extremely turned on by this whole situation, you eagerly moan, [pc.speech(Please, breed me! Pump me full of your seed!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(Well, how could I refuse that?)] [sean.name] laughs, before stepping around behind you and declaring, [sean.speech(There's no point in waiting; I'll give you a good fucking right away!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_REFUSED_DEAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You don't like the idea of being publicly bred by [sean.name], and so you tell him that you're not willing to accept his deal.
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionAcceptedDeal))
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Right, well if that's how it's going to be, I'll just get your stocks marked up as being fully available for public use!)] [sean.name] exclaims in a frustrated tone, before moving forwards and quickly carrying out his task. Once he's done, he steps around in front of you and cheekily states, [sean.speech(A deal's a deal, so there are no hard feelings, right?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Taking the defeated whine which you let out as confirmation that you're not angry with him, [sean.name] smiles and walks around behind [com.name] again. Giving [com.her] exposed pussy a gentle slap, he laughs as your [com.companion] lets out a horny moan, before walking off and calling over his shoulder, [sean.speech(I'll be back to give you a good breeding once I've seen your friend here get fucked!)]
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionInStocks))
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Right, well if that's how it's going to be, I'll just get both of your stocks marked up as being fully available for public use!)] [sean.name] exclaims in a frustrated tone, before moving forwards and quickly carrying out his task. Once he's done, he steps around in front of you and cheekily asks, [sean.speech(A deal's a deal, so there are no hard feelings, right?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Taking the defeated whines which you and [com.name] make as confirmation that you're not angry with him, [sean.name] smiles and walks off, calling over his shoulder as he goes, [sean.speech(I'll be back to let you go once you've both had a good fucking! I'm sure it won't take long before some strangers decide to use you!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Right, well if that's how it's going to be, I'll just get your stocks marked up as being fully available for public use!)] [sean.name] exclaims in a frustrated tone, before moving forwards and quickly carrying out his task. Once he's done, he steps around in front of you and cheekily asks, [sean.speech(A deal's a deal, so there are no hard feelings, right?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Taking the defeated whine which you let out as confirmation that you're not angry with him, [sean.name] smiles and walks off, calling over his shoulder as he goes, [sean.speech(I'll be back to let you go once you've had a good fucking! I'm sure it won't take long before some strangers decide to use you!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_RANDOMS_APPROACH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With [sean.name] having returned to his post, and being locked securely into the stocks, you're left feeling extremely exposed and vulnerable. Knowing that you're completely at the mercy of any passing stranger who wants to use you, you remain still and wait to see what will happen next...
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTwoPartners))
		<p>
			About ten minutes later, and having already heard several members of the public comment on your situation as they pass by, a pair of strangers decide that you're just what they're looking for, and quickly step up in front of you before starting to comment on your appearance.
			#IF(npc.isFeminine()==npc2.isFeminine() && npc.getRaceStage()==npc2.getRaceStage() && npc.getRace()==npc2.getRace())
				 Looking up, you see that both of these strangers are [npc.fullRaces(true)].
			#ELSE
				 Looking up, you see that the one making most of the lewd comments is [npc.a_fullRace(true)], while the other is [npc2.a_fullRace(true)].
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(You ready for a good fucking, slut?)] [npc.name] asks as [npc.she] sees you looking up at [npc.herHim]. Not waiting for an answer, [npc.she] moves around behind you and slaps your [pc.ass+], causing you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan].
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Oh yeah, this one's ready to go!)] [npc2.name] excitedly exclaims, stepping up in front of you.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			About ten minutes later, and having already heard several members of the public comment on your situation as they pass by, [npc.a_fullRace(true)] decides that you're just what they're looking for, and quickly [npc.steps] up in front of you to declare, [npc.speech(You look like you'll be a good fuck, you dirty slut!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Not waiting for a response,
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_ORAL_RECEIVING))
				 [npc.she] [npc.steps] forwards and pushes [npc.her] groin into your face, before sneering,
				#IF(npc.hasVagina())
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love eating me out!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love sucking my cock!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSEIF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
				 [npc.she] moves around behind you and slaps your [pc.ass+], causing you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan]. Laughing at your reaction, [npc.she] then sneers, [npc.speech(Oh yeah, I'm going to fuck your ass so good!)]
			#ELSEIF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_VAGINAL_GIVING))
				 [npc.she] moves around behind you and slaps your [pc.ass+], causing you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan]. Laughing at your reaction, [npc.she] then sneers, [npc.speech(Oh yeah, I'm going to fuck your pussy so good!)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc.she] [npc.steps] forwards and pushes [npc.her] groin against one of your [pc.hands], before sneering,
				#IF(npc.hasVagina())
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love fingering my cunt!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love stroking my cock!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FIRST_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FIRST_SEX_START_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		With [sean.name] now standing behind you, you're unable to see what's going on, resulting in you letting out a surprised [pc.moan] as you suddenly feel his fingers tracing their way up and down over your [pc.labia+]. Leaning in over the top of you, the [sean.race] teases, [sean.speech(That's right; let everyone know that you're my little slut! Beg for me to breed you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Bucking your [pc.hips] back against his touch, you eagerly do as [sean.name] asks, and once again loudly [pc.moan], [pc.speech(Please, fuck me! I want you to breed me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The scene which the two of you are creating very quickly attracts the attention of some passersby, and as [sean.name] reaches down to expose his cock, a stranger shouts,
		[style.random(
		[style.speechMasculine(Go on, fuck that slut and give [pc.herHim] a nice big creampie!)]
		|
		[style.speechMasculine(Give that slut what she wants! Go on, pound [pc.her] cunt and make [pc.herHim] a mother!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Go on, fuck that slut and give [pc.herHim] a nice big creampie!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Give that slut what she wants! Go on, pound [pc.her] cunt and make [pc.herHim] a mother!)]
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Delivering a quick slap to your exposed [pc.ass], [sean.name] teases, [sean.speech(Don't stop begging for it, slut!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		By now absolutely desperate to get fucked by [sean.name], you can't help but [pc.moanVerb] in excitement as you feel him start to tease the head of his [sean.cockSize] cock up and down between your [pc.labia+]. Frantically pushing your hips back, you whine, [pc.speech(Please! Fuck my pussy! I want to feel your cock inside of me! Please!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a deep grunt, the [sean.name] finally gives you what you want, and thrusts forwards to drive his [sean.cock+] into your [pc.pussy+]. A high-pitched [pc.moan] bursts out of your mouth as you feel your [pc.labia+] spread lewdly around [sean.namePos] thick cock, and with the gathering crowd cheering him on, the [sean.race] starts rapidly pounding your greedy cunt...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_RANDOMS_START_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTwoPartners))
		<p>
			From behind, you hear [npc.name] shuffling around to displace [npc.her] clothing, and then just a moment later you suddenly feel the [npc.cockHead+] of [npc.her] cock rubbing up and down over your [pc.ass+]. Shifting your [pc.hips] a little in response, you can't help but whine as [npc.name] teases, [npc.speech(Looking forwards to being fucked, slut?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Copying [npc2.her] friend's lead, [npc2.name] similarly displaces [npc2.her] clothing, presenting you with [npc2.her]
			#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
				#IF(npc2.hasVagina())
					 [npc2.cock+] and [npc2.pussy+].
				#ELSE
					 [npc2.cock+].
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				 [npc2.pussy+].
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out an excited [npc2.moan], [npc2.she] joins [npc.name] in teasing you, [npc2.speech(I hope you're ready to have some fun!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With no way to free yourself, you realise that there's absolutely nothing you can do to stop these two strangers from fucking you...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_ORAL_RECEIVING))
				Eager to get started, [npc.name] displaces [npc.her] clothing, presenting you with [npc.her]
				#IF(npc.hasPenis())
					#IF(npc.hasVagina())
						 [npc.cock+] and [npc.pussy+].
					#ELSE
						 [npc.cock+].
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					 [npc.pussy+].
				#ENDIF
				 Letting out an excited [npc.moan], [npc.she] bucks [npc.her] [npc.hips] forwards and teases, [npc.speech(Let's see what that mouth of yours can do!)]
			#ELSEIF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
				Over the noise of the small crowd which rapidly starts to form around you, you hear the [npc.race] quickly moving to displace [npc.her] clothing, and then just a moment later, you suddenly feel the [npc.cockHead+] of [npc.her] [npc.cock+] start to rub up and down over your [pc.asshole+]. Letting out a hungry [npc.moan], the [npc.race] teases, [npc.speech(I hope you're ready for this, you dirty little buttslut!)]
			#ELSE
				Over the noise of the small crowd which rapidly starts to form around you, you hear the [npc.race] quickly moving to displace [npc.her] clothing, and then just a moment later, you suddenly feel the [npc.cockHead+] of [npc.her] [npc.cock+] start to rub up and down between your [pc.labia+]. Letting out a hungry [npc.moan], the [npc.race] teases, [npc.speech(I hope you're ready for this, you dirty little slut!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			With no way to free yourself, you realise that there's absolutely nothing you can do to stop this stranger from using you...
		<p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_AFTER_FIRST_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_AFTER_FIRST_SEX_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having achieved his objective of filling your pussy with his virile seed, [sean.name] steps back and takes a good look at what he's just done. Letting out a low whistle, he remarks, [sean.speech(Now that's a fine looking creampie! There's no way you aren't getting knocked up from that!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You let out a long, deep [pc.moan] in response to the [sean.race]'s comment, causing him to let out a chuckle and say, [sean.speech(I'll give my seed a few hours to fertilise your womb, then I'll be back to give you another filling, just to make sure you're definitely getting pregnant from this.)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionInStocks))
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionAcceptedDeal))
			#IF(com.equals(brax))
				<p>
					Leaving your dripping creampie to be admired by the crowd still lingering around behind you, [sean.name] steps over to [com.name]. Playfully slapping [com.her] ass, he teases, [sean.speech(So, <i>Inspector</i>, are you ready to get a feel of my cock?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
						[com.speech(Just give it to me already,)] [com.name] impatiently snaps, [com.speech(You already made me wait and listen while [pc.name] had [pc.her] turn, now it's mine!)]
					#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
						[com.speech(Yes, please, breed me!)] [com.name] eagerly replies, lifting [com.her] ass and swaying it back and forth to entice [sean.name] to fuck [com.herHim].
					#ELSE
						[com.speech(Just stop teasing and give it to me!)] [com.name] eagerly begs, lifting [com.her] ass and swaying it back and forth to entice [sean.name] to fuck [com.herHim].
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					[sean.speech(That's what I like to hear!)] the [sean.race] replies, before moving forwards and getting ready to start fucking your [com.companion].
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Leaving your dripping creampie to be admired by the crowd still lingering around behind you, [sean.name] steps over to [com.name]. Playfully slapping [com.her] ass, he teases, [sean.speech(So, are you ready for your turn?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[com.speech(Yes, please, breed me!)] [com.name] eagerly replies, lifting [com.her] ass and swaying it back and forth to entice [sean.name] to fuck [com.herHim].
				</p>
				<p>
					[sean.speech(That's what I like to hear!)] the [sean.race] replies, before moving forwards and getting ready to start fucking your [com.companion].
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Leaving your dripping creampie to be admired by the crowd still lingering around behind you, [sean.name] moves off and returns to his post. The sight of your cum-stuffed pussy doesn't hold their attention for too long, however, and one of them quickly notices that your [com.companion] is not only marked for public use, but is also currently not being used by anyone. As they walk around to inspect [com.name] from every angle, you're able to look across and see that they're [npc.a_raceFull(true)].
			</p>
			<p>
				Finishing [npc.her] inspection and stepping up close behind [com.name], you hear the [npc.race] declare, [npc.speech(I'm going to enjoy fucking you, slut!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Leaving your dripping creampie to be admired by the members of the public still lingering around behind you, [sean.name] moves off and returns to his post. The sight of your cum-stuffed pussy doesn't hold their attention for too long, however, and the crowd quickly dissipates, leaving you with little else to do but wait for the [sean.race] to return and fill you up a second time...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_AFTER_FIRST_SEX_RANDOMS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTwoPartners))
		<p>
			Having had their fun, the two strangers step back and start making lewd comments on your performance to one another. Although you're too tired from the double fucking you just received to fully pay attention to what it is they're saying, you're still vaguely aware that they're talking about you as though you're nothing but a worthless sex toy, which, combined with the mocking comments from the crowd that gathered to watch your performance, makes you feel more humiliated than ever.
		</p>
		<p>
			Delivering one last swift slap to your [pc.ass+], the [npc.race] steps around to where [npc.her] [npc2.race] companion is still standing in front of you, and without giving you even one last look, they walk off together.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having had [npc.her] fun, the stranger steps back and starts making lewd comments on your performance. Although you're too tired from the fucking you just received to fully pay attention to what it is [npc.sheIs] saying, you're still vaguely aware that [npc.sheIs] talking about you as though you're nothing but a worthless sex toy, which, combined with the mocking comments from the crowd that gathered to watch your performance, makes you feel more humiliated than ever.
		</p>
		<p>
			Delivering one last swift slap to your [pc.ass+], the [npc.race] makes one last disparaging comment, before [npc.walking] off into the crowd.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionInStocks))
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionAcceptedDeal))
			#IF(com.equals(brax))
				<p>
					Seeing that the strangers have finally finished with you, [sean.name] returns and steps over to [com.name]. Playfully slapping [com.her] ass, he teases, [sean.speech(So, <i>Inspector</i>, are you ready to get a feel of my cock?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
						[com.speech(Just give it to me already,)] [com.name] impatiently snaps, [com.speech(You already made me wait and listen while [pc.name] got fucked, now I want my turn!)]
					#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
						[com.speech(Yes, please, breed me!)] [com.name] eagerly replies, lifting [com.her] ass and swaying it back and forth to entice [sean.name] to fuck [com.herHim].
					#ELSE
						[com.speech(Just stop teasing and give it to me!)] [com.name] eagerly begs, lifting [com.her] ass and swaying it back and forth to entice [sean.name] to fuck [com.herHim].
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					[sean.speech(That's what I like to hear!)] the [sean.race] replies, before moving forwards and getting ready to start fucking your [com.companion].
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Seeing that the strangers have finally finished with you, [sean.name] returns and steps over to [com.name]. Playfully slapping [com.her] ass, he teases, [sean.speech(So, are you ready for your turn?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[com.speech(Yes, please, breed me!)] [com.name] eagerly replies, lifting [com.her] ass and swaying it back and forth to entice [sean.name] to fuck [com.herHim].
				</p>
				<p>
					[sean.speech(That's what I like to hear!)] the [sean.race] replies, before moving forwards and getting ready to start fucking your [com.companion].
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			While the sight of you being fucked proved to be entertaining enough to draw a moderately-sized crowd, the members of the public who gathered to watch quickly start to lose interest. As they quickly wander off, you find yourself with little else to do but wait and see if you're going to be used for a second time...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_AFTER_FIRST_SEX_COMPANION_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	#IF(com.equals(brax))
		<p>
			As the [sean.race] steps up behind [com.name] and begins teasing his cock up and down between [com.her] [com.labia+], you hear him tease, [sean.speech(Never would have imagined we'd be in this situation, eh, <i>Inspector</i>? Now go on, beg me to breed you again! I'll never tire of hearing you say it!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				[com.speech(S-Shut up and just do it already!)] [com.name] impatiently snaps, but, wanting to hear your [com.companion] beg to be bred, [sean.name] refuses to penetrate [com.herHim] until [com.she] relents and [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Fine! J-Just breed me already! Give me your cum and knock me up! Please!)]
			#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
				[com.speech(Please, fuck me!)] [com.name] desperately [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Breed me! Give me your cum and knock me up!)]
			#ELSE
				[com.speech(Go on then, fuck me!)] [com.name] blushes as [com.she] [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Breed me! Give me your cum and knock me up!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(That's a good [com.girl]!)] [sean.name] says, before thrusting forwards and filling [com.namePos] hungry pussy with his [sean.cockSize] cock. Getting a good grip on your [com.companion]'s hips, the [sean.race] leans forwards over the top of [com.herHim] and starts frantically humping [com.her] [com.pussy].
		</p>
		<p>
			Due to the stocks which you're locked in being parallel to the ones which are restraining [com.name], you aren't able to get a good view of what's happening, but from the frantic wet slapping sounds, combined with all manner of lewd moans and comments coming out of your [com.companion]'s mouth, you can tell that [sean.name] is giving [com.herHim] a thorough fucking. Soon enough, the [sean.race]'s steady grunts start to get deeper and louder, but before he orgasms, [com.name] lets out a shuddering moan and exclaims, [com.speech(~Ooh!~ Fuck! Yes! ~Mmm!~ I-I'm cumming!)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			The wet slapping sounds of [sean.namePos] cock repeatedly slamming into [com.namePos] quivering pussy get faster and faster as your [com.companion] climaxes, and then, just a few moments later, they come to a stop with one final wet squelch, which is followed by a deep, desperate grunt from the [sean.race], [sean.speech(~Aah!~ That's it! Take it all, [com.name]! ~Aah!~ Fuck!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Panting and moaning, [com.name] fully capitulates to [com.her] one-time subordinate, and exclaims, [com.speech(~Ooh!~ Yes! Fill my pussy with your cum! ~Aah!~ Breed me, yes!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With the surrounding crowd cheering him on, [sean.name] does as [com.name] asks, and, keeping his [sean.cockGirth] cock hilted in [com.her] dripping pussy, the [sean.race]'s balls tense up and unload their virile seed deep into [com.her] fertile womb. Continuing to pant, moan, and groan, they stay locked together like this for a short while, until [sean.namePos] thick cum backs up and seeps out around his still-throbbing cock.
		</p>
		<p>
			Having finally emptied his balls, [sean.name] slides his cock out of [com.namePos] well-fucked pussy, before standing to one side and letting the crowd see the fresh creampie he's given [com.herHim]. Affectionately slapping [com.namePos] ass, the [sean.race] remarks, [sean.speech(You're far better like this than you ever were as an Enforcer. I mean, fuck... You've no idea how good your pussy feels!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a deep, long moan, [com.name] admits, [com.speech(Your cock felt great too... I wonder if you've got me pregnant...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(We'll find out later,)] [sean.name] replies. Putting away his by-now soft cock and then zipping up his trousers, the [sean.race] starts to walk off, calling over his shoulder as he goes, [sean.speech(I'll be back to give you another filling in a few hours!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As the [sean.race] steps up behind [com.name] and begins teasing his cock up and down between [com.her] [com.labia+], you hear him tease, [sean.speech(Now it's your turn! Go on, beg me to breed you!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[com.speech(Please, fuck me!)] [com.name] obediently [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Breed me! Give me your cum and knock me up!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(That's a good [com.girl]!)] [sean.name] says, before thrusting forwards and filling [com.namePos] hungry pussy with his [sean.cockSize] cock. Getting a good grip on your [com.companion]'s hips, the [sean.race] leans forwards over the top of [com.name] and starts frantically humping [com.herHim].
		</p>
		<p>
			Due to the stocks which you're locked in being parallel to the ones which are restraining [com.name], you aren't able to get a good view of what's happening, but from the frantic wet slapping sounds, combined with all manner of lewd moans and comments coming out of your [com.companion]'s mouth, you can tell that [sean.name] is giving [com.herHim] a thorough fucking. Soon enough, the [sean.race]'s steady grunts start to get deeper and louder, but before he orgasms, [com.name] lets out a shuddering moan and exclaims, [com.speech(~Ooh!~ Fuck! Yes! ~Mmm!~ I-I'm cumming!)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			The wet slapping sounds of [sean.namePos] cock repeatedly slamming into [com.namePos] quivering pussy get faster and faster as your [com.companion] climaxes, and then, just a few moments later, they come to a stop with one final wet squelch, which is followed by a deep, desperate grunt from the [sean.race], [sean.speech(~Aah!~ That's it! Take it all! ~Aah!~ Fuck!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Panting and moaning, [com.name] desperately exclaims, [com.speech(~Ooh!~ Yes! Fill my pussy with your cum! ~Aah!~ Breed me, yes!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With the surrounding crowd cheering him on, [sean.name] does as [com.name] asks, and, keeping his [sean.cockGirth] cock hilted in [com.her] dripping pussy, the [sean.race]'s balls tense up and unload their virile seed deep into [com.her] fertile womb. Continuing to pant, moan, and groan, they stay locked together like this for a short while, until [sean.namePos] thick cum backs up and seeps out around his still-throbbing cock.
		</p>
		<p>
			Having finally emptied his balls into your [com.companion], [sean.name] slides his cock out of [com.namePos] well-fucked pussy, before standing to one side and letting the crowd see the fresh creampie he's given [com.herHim]. Affectionately slapping [com.namePos] ass, the [sean.race] remarks, [sean.speech(Your pussy sure felt good to fuck!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a deep, long moan, [com.name] pants, [com.speech(I wonder if you've got me pregnant...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(We'll find out later,)] [sean.name] replies. Putting away his by-now soft cock and then zipping up his trousers, the [sean.race] starts to walk off, calling over his shoulder as he goes, [sean.speech(I'll be back to give you another filling in a few hours!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_RANDOMS_START_SEX_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTwoPartners))
		<p>
			As the crowd which gathered to watch you starts to dissipate, several members of the public start to look for some other form of entertainment, and it's not long before one of them  points out that your [com.companion] is available for public use. A couple of members of the crowd quickly rush forwards to take advantage of the fact that nobody's currently using [com.herHim], and as they walk around to inspect [com.name] from every angle, you're able to look across and see that
			#IF(npc.isFeminine()==npc2.isFeminine() && npc.getRaceStage()==npc2.getRaceStage() && npc.getRace()==npc2.getRace())
				 they're both [npc.fullRaces(true)].
			#ELSE
				 Looking up, you see that the more dominant-looking of the two is [npc.a_fullRace(true)], while the other is [npc2.a_fullRace(true)].
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Finishing [npc.her] inspection, the more dominant [npc.race] steps around behind [com.name] and teases, [npc.speech(I'm going to enjoy fucking you, slut!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Oh yeah, this is going to be fun!)] the [npc2.race] [npc2.moansVerb] as [npc2.she] steps up in front of [com.name], before quickly displacing [npc2.her] clothing and presenting your [com.companion] with [npc2.her]
			#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
				#IF(npc2.hasVagina())
					 [npc2.cock+] and [npc2.pussy+].
				#ELSE
					 [npc2.cock+].
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				 [npc2.pussy+].
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out an excited [npc2.moan], [npc2.she] doesn't hesitate for a moment longer, and instantly starts to use [com.name]...
		</p>
		<p>
			[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
		</p>
		<p>
			While this is happening, you hear [npc.name] shuffling around behind [com.name] as [npc.she] quickly seeks to displace [com.her] clothing. As soon as [npc.sheIs] done, [npc.she] steps forwards and teases the [npc.cockHead+] of [npc.her] cock up and down over your [com.companion]'s [com.ass+]. Shifting [npc.her] [com.hips] a little in response, [com.name] can't help but whine as [npc.name] teases, [npc.speech(Time to give you a good fucking, slut!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eventually having had enough fun with [com.name], the two strangers get their clothing back in order and walk off, leaving your [com.companion] panting and quietly moaning as [com.she] recovers from the experience...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			While the sight of you being fucked proved to be entertaining enough to draw a moderately-sized crowd, the members of the public who gathered to watch quickly start to lose interest. As they start to wander off, one of them suddenly notices that your [com.companion] is not only marked for public use, but is also currently not being used by anyone. As they walk around to inspect [com.name] from every angle, you're able to look across and see that they're [npc.a_raceFull(true)].
		</p>
		<p>
			Although you can't see [npc.herHim] from your position in the stocks, you're still able to hear the [npc.race] as [npc.she] steps around behind [com.name] and slaps ass, before teasing, [npc.speech(Come on, slut, beg me to fuck you! I'll keep this going until you do it!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As the sound of another slap rings out, you hear your [com.companion] relent and beg, [com.speech(Please, fuck me! I need you to fuck me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			A small crowd quickly gathers to watch the upcoming entertainment, and as they start to loudly comment on your [com.companion]'s display of submission, the [npc.race] lets out an excited [npc.moan] and prepares to start fucking [com.herHim]...
		</p>
		<p>
			[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having had [npc.her] fun, [npc.name] steps away from [com.name], and without so much as a backwards glance, walks off and leaves your [com.companion] panting and quietly [npc.moaning] in the stocks. The crowd which gathered to watch the lewd display quickly dissipates, leaving both you and [com.name] with little else to do but wait and see what will happen to you next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_SECOND_SEX_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		For the next couple of hours, you're left locked up in the stocks with nothing to do except concentrate on the feeling of [sean.namePos] cum slowly dripping out of your pussy. Except for the occasional stranger who stops in their tracks to make a degrading comment on your appearance, nothing of interest happens during your time in captivity, but then, just as you feel the last of the [sean.race]'s cum leak out of your cunt, you hear someone approaching from behind.
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(You're looking awfully empty back here,)] [sean.name] remarks, revealing his presence, [sean.speech(and I bet you're getting pretty bored by now. Would you like me to fix both of those problems for you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You can't contain your excitement at the prospect of finally getting to have some more fun, and desperately call out, [pc.speech(Yes, please! Fuck me again! I want to feel your cock inside of me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[sean.speech(That's what I like to hear!)] [sean.name] replies as he steps up behind you and prepares to give you what you're asking for...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_SECOND_SEX_RANDOMS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTwoPartners))
		<p>
			For the next couple of hours, you're left locked up in the stocks with nothing to do except think about how you were publicly fucked by those two strangers. Except for the occasional member of the public who stops in their tracks to make a degrading comment on your appearance, nothing of interest happens during your time in captivity, but then, just as you're wondering if anyone will stop and use you again, a couple of strangers move forwards to stand in front of you.
			#IF(npc.isFeminine()==npc2.isFeminine() && npc.getRaceStage()==npc2.getRaceStage() && npc.getRace()==npc2.getRace())
				 Looking up, you see that both of them are [npc.fullRaces(true)].
			#ELSE
				 Looking up, you see that the more dominant-looking of the pair is [npc.a_fullRace(true)], while the other is [npc2.a_fullRace(true)].
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(This slut's used goods; you sure you don't want to wait for a fresh slave to be locked up?)] [npc.name] asks [npc.her] companion.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Yeah, I want some action right now!)] [npc2.name] excitedly replies, before [npc2.stepping] forwards and dominantly rubbing [npc2.her] groin over your face.
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(Fine. I guess I'll just have to make do with sloppy seconds,)] [npc.name] says, before moving around behind you and slapping your [pc.ass+], which causes you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan].
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			For the next couple of hours, you're left locked up in the stocks with nothing to do except think about how you were publicly fucked by those two strangers. Except for the occasional member of the public who stops in their tracks to make a degrading comment on your appearance, nothing of interest happens during your time in captivity, but then, just as you're wondering if anyone will stop and use you again, [npc.a_fullRace(true)] suddenly [npc.steps] up in front of you and declares, [npc.speech(You're just what I was looking for!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Not waiting for a response,
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_ORAL_RECEIVING))
				 [npc.she] [npc.steps] forwards and pushes [npc.her] groin into your face, before sneering,
				#IF(npc.hasVagina())
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love eating me out!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love sucking my cock!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSEIF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
				 [npc.she] moves around behind you and slaps your [pc.ass+], causing you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan]. Laughing at your reaction, [npc.she] then sneers, [npc.speech(Oh yeah, I'm going to fuck your ass so good!)]
			#ELSEIF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_VAGINAL_GIVING))
				 [npc.she] moves around behind you and slaps your [pc.ass+], causing you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan]. Laughing at your reaction, [npc.she] then sneers, [npc.speech(Oh yeah, I'm going to fuck your pussy so good!)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc.she] [npc.steps] forwards and pushes [npc.her] groin against one of your [pc.hands], before sneering,
				#IF(npc.hasVagina())
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love fingering my cunt!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love stroking my cock!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_SECOND_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_SECOND_SEX_START_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Like the first time, [sean.name] quickly unzips his trousers, before pulling both them and his boxers down to gain access to his [sean.cockSize] cock. Taking hold of his rapidly-hardening shaft, he starts rubbing the [sean.cockHead+] up and down between your [pc.labia+], teasing, [sean.speech(You want this, don't you? Go on, beg for me to breed you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Desperate to get bred by the [sean.race], you once more find yourself begging, [pc.speech(Please, [sean.name]! I need your cock! Pound me and empty your balls in my fertile womb!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not needing to be told twice, the [sean.race] thrusts forwards, parting your [pc.labia+] around his [sean.cock+] as he plunges into your [pc.pussy+]. Letting out a delighted [pc.moan], you continue desperately begging [sean.name] to breed you, which encourages him to pick up the pace and start to rapidly pound your hungry pussy.
	</p>
	<p>
		Attracted by the loud, lewd noises which you're making, a small crowd starts to form around you, and as [sean.name] continues to drive his cock in and out of your cunt, the members of the public start commenting on your performance...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_AFTER_SECOND_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_AFTER_SECOND_SEX_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Stepping back a little, [sean.name] grabs your ass cheeks with both hands, before pulling them apart and showing off your creampied pussy to the crowd that's formed behind you. As you feel the [sean.race]'s cum oozing out of your quivering cunt, you can't help but let out a satisfied [pc.moan], which spurs [sean.name] into remarking, [sean.speech(You like that, huh?! I've stuffed so much cum into your pussy that there's no way you're not getting pregnant!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Members of the crowd start to call out lewd comments in response to the [sean.race]'s comment, which causes him to let go of your ass and give it a little slap, before turning to them and declaring, [sean.speech(I'll leave [pc.her] pussy on display like this for half an hour or so. You can look as much as you want, but no touching!)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionInStocks))
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionAcceptedDeal))
			#IF(com.equals(brax))
				<p>
					Once again leaving your leaking creampie to be admired and commented on by the strangers still lingering around behind you, [sean.name] steps over to [com.name]. Lustfully groping [com.her] ass, he asks, [sean.speech(So, <i>Inspector</i>, you ready to take another load of my cum?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
						[com.speech(Stop teasing me!)] [com.name] snaps, before continuing, [com.speech(Just give me your cock already; I want to be bred like [pc.name]!)]
					#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
						[com.speech(Yes, I need your cock!)] [com.name] eagerly replies, lifting [com.her] [com.hips+] and moaning, [com.speech(Come on! Breed me!)]
					#ELSE
						[com.speech(Just stop teasing and give it to me!)] [com.name] eagerly begs, lifting [com.her] [com.hips+] and moaning, [com.speech(Come on! Breed me!)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					[sean.speech(That's a good [com.girl]!)] the [sean.race] replies, before stepping up right behind your [com.companion] and preparing to fuck [com.herHim].
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Once again leaving your leaking creampie to be admired and commented on by the strangers still lingering around behind you, [sean.name] steps over to [com.name]. Lustfully groping [com.her] ass, he asks, [sean.speech(So, you ready to take another load of my cum?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[com.speech(Yes, I need your cock!)] [com.name] eagerly replies, lifting [com.her] [com.hips+] and moaning, [com.speech(Come on! Breed me!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[sean.speech(That's a good [com.girl]!)] the [sean.race] replies, before stepping up right behind your [com.companion] and preparing to fuck [com.herHim].
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Once again leaving your leaking creampie to be admired and commented on by the strangers still lingering around behind you, [sean.name] heads off and returns to his post. Just like the last time, your dripping pussy doesn't hold their attention for long, and within moments, your [com.companion] is noticed as being available for public use. A couple of members of the crowd quickly rush forwards to take advantage of the fact that nobody's currently using [com.herHim], and as they walk around to inspect [com.name] from every angle, you're able to look across and see that
				#IF(npc.isFeminine()==npc2.isFeminine() && npc.getRaceStage()==npc2.getRaceStage() && npc.getRace()==npc2.getRace())
					 they're both [npc.fullRaces(true)].
				#ELSE
					 Looking up, you see that the more dominant-looking of the two is [npc.a_fullRace(true)], while the other is [npc2.a_fullRace(true)].
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				Finishing [npc.her] inspection, the more dominant [npc.race] steps around behind [com.name] and teases, [npc.speech(I'm going to enjoy fucking you, slut!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Following the [npc.race]'s lead, [npc.name] moves up in front of your [com.companion] and [npc2.moansVerb], [npc.speech(This is going to be fun!)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Once again leaving your leaking creampie to be admired and commented on by the strangers still lingering around behind you, [sean.name] heads off and returns to his post. Just like the last time, your dripping pussy doesn't hold their attention for long, and the crowd quickly dissipates, leaving you with little else to do but wait for the [sean.race] to return and release you...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_AFTER_SECOND_SEX_RANDOMS"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTwoPartners))
		<p>
			Having had their fun, the two strangers step back, and as you start to let out a satisfied sigh, the [npc.race] behind you delivers one final slap to your [pc.ass+]. As you let out a startled [pc.moan], [npc.she] rudely comments, [npc.speech(You were an ok fuck, you dumb slut! See you around!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You can't but feel extremely humiliated as the stranger tells you this, and as [npc.she] joins [npc.her] companion in walking off without even a backwards glance, you hear several members of the public loudly commenting on what a dirty slut you are. Feeling your cheeks burning in shame, you wonder how long it's going to be before you're released from the stocks...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having had [npc.his] fun, the [npc.race] steps back and delivers one final slap to your [pc.ass+]. As you let out a startled [pc.moan], [npc.she] rudely comments, [npc.speech(You were an ok fuck, you dumb slut! See you around!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			You can't but feel extremely humiliated as the stranger tells you this, and as [npc.she] walks off without even a backwards glance, you hear several members of the public loudly commenting on what a dirty slut you are. Feeling your cheeks burning in shame, you wonder how long it's going to be before you're released from the stocks...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionInStocks))
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionAcceptedDeal))
			#IF(com.equals(brax))
				<p>
					Having been standing nearby and watching you this whole time, you hear [sean.name] step over to [com.name], before lustfully groping [com.her] ass and asking, [sean.speech(So, <i>Inspector</i>, you ready to take another load of my cum?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
						[com.speech(Stop teasing me!)] [com.name] snaps, before continuing, [com.speech(Just give me your cock already; I want you to breed me!)]
					#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
						[com.speech(Yes, I need your cock!)] [com.name] eagerly replies, lifting [com.her] [com.hips+] and moaning, [com.speech(Come on! Breed me!)]
					#ELSE
						[com.speech(Just stop teasing and give it to me!)] [com.name] eagerly begs, lifting [com.her] [com.hips+] and moaning, [com.speech(Come on! Breed me!)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					[sean.speech(That's a good [com.girl]!)] the [sean.race] replies, before stepping up right behind your [com.companion] and preparing to fuck [com.herHim].
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					Having been standing nearby and watching you this whole time, you hear [sean.name] step over to [com.name], before lustfully groping [com.her] ass and asking, [sean.speech(So, you ready to take another load of my cum?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[com.speech(Yes, I need your cock!)] [com.name] eagerly replies, lifting [com.her] [com.hips+] and moaning, [com.speech(Come on! Breed me!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[sean.speech(That's a good [com.girl]!)] the [sean.race] replies, before stepping up right behind your [com.companion] and preparing to fuck [com.herHim].
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_AFTER_SECOND_SEX_COMPANION_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	#IF(com.equals(brax))
		<p>
			Stepping up behind [com.name] once again, [sean.name] gently teases the [sean.cockHead+] of his cock up and down between [com.her] [com.labia+]. Starting to push forwards, the [sean.race] tricks your [com.companion] into thinking [com.sheIs] about to be penetrated, before suddenly pulling back and chuckling at the desperate whining noise [com.name] makes, [sean.speech(Come on now, [com.name]! You know I want to hear you beg for it! And this time, how about you call me 'Sir'? I always wanted you to one day call me that...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
				[com.speech(Just fuck me, [sean.surname]!)] [com.name] commands, but the [sean.name] refuses to do so, continuing to tease [com.her] pussy until [com.she] relents and exclaims, [com.speech(Ok, fine! Please... <i>Sir</i>... Fuck me already!)]
			#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
				[com.speech(Please, sir, fuck me!)] [com.name] desperately [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(I want to be sure you've knocked me up, so please, pump another load of your cum into my dirty pussy!)]
			#ELSE
				[com.speech(Ok... S-Sir...)] [com.name] blushes as [com.she] replies, [com.speech(Please, sir, fuck me and pump another load of your cum into my dirty pussy!)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Clearly wanting to draw this moment out as long as possible, [sean.name] still refuses to penetrate [com.name], and demands, [sean.speech(Say it again! Call me 'Sir' and beg for me to knock you up!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			By now clearly being absolutely desperate to be fucked, [com.name] [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Please, Sir! Give me your cum and knock me up! Fuck me, please! Fuck me, Sir!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a deep, approving grunt, [sean.name] thrusts forwards and fills [com.namePos] [com.pussy+] with his [sean.cockSize] cock. Overwhelmed with passion, the [sean.race] grabs your [com.companion]'s hips, before leaning forwards over the top of [com.herHim] and starting to rapidly hammer his [sean.cockGirth], throbbing shaft in and out of [com.her] [com.pussy].
		</p>
		<p>
			Just as it was the last time, the positioning of your stocks is preventing you from getting a good view of what's happening, but from the deep grunts and frantic wet slapping sounds coming from behind [com.name], you can tell that [sean.name] is relentlessly pounding [com.her] pussy. The rapid pace at which your [com.companion] is being fucked proves to be too much for [com.herHim] to bear, and [com.her] desperate moans quickly increase in both volume and frequency, before [com.she] suddenly wails, [com.speech(Fuck! ~Aah!~ So good! ~Ooh!~ I'm- ~Aah!~ I'm cumming!)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			With an ear-splitting scream, and with [sean.namePos] [sean.cock+] still incessantly slamming in and out of [com.her] trembling pussy, [com.name] reaches [com.her] climax. The repetitive slapping sounds coming from between [com.her] legs suddenly sound noticeably wetter, before suddenly coming to an abrupt halt with one final wet squelch. Letting out a deep, desperate grunt, the [sean.race], who's now balls-deep in your [com.companion]'s cunt, exclaims, [sean.speech(That's it! ~Aah!~ Take my load, slut! ~Mmm!~ Feel my cum claiming your womb!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Panting and moaning, [com.name] once again proves to be willing to fully capitulate to [com.her] one-time subordinate, and loudly [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Yes, Sir! ~Ooh!~ Please, Sir, empty your balls in my pussy and womb! ~Aah!~ Knock me up and make me yours!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With the surrounding crowd cheering him on, [sean.name] does as [com.name] asks, and, keeping his [sean.cockGirth] cock hilted in [com.her] still-quivering pussy, he lets out a series of deep grunts in time with his virile seed spurting deep into [com.her] fertile womb. Continuing to make all manner of lewd noises, they stay locked together like this for a short while, until [sean.namePos] thick cum backs up and seeps out around his still-throbbing cock.
		</p>
		<p>
			Having finally emptied his balls into the [com.race] who he once called <i>Inspector</i>, [sean.name] slides his cock out of [com.her] tired pussy, before standing to one side and letting the crowd see the huge creampie he's given [com.herHim]. Grabbing hold of [com.namePos] ass cheeks, the [sean.race] pulls them apart to really show off how much cum he's stuffed into [com.her] pussy, remarking, [sean.speech(If only you could see what your cunt looks like now! There's no way you're not going to be a mother after this!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a deep, long moan, [com.name] lifts [com.her] hips to help show off [com.her] pussy, sighing, [com.speech(Thank you, Sir...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Now to leave you for a while, to make sure that my seed has enough time to get you pregnant,)] [sean.name] says, releasing his grip on [com.namePos] ass. Putting away his softening cock and then zipping up his trousers, the [sean.race] starts to walk off, calling over his shoulder as he goes, [sean.speech(I'll be back in about thirty minutes!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Stepping up behind [com.name] once again, [sean.name] gently teases the [sean.cockHead+] of his cock up and down between [com.her] [com.labia+]. Starting to push forwards, the [sean.race] tricks your [com.companion] into thinking [com.sheIs] about to be penetrated, before suddenly pulling back and chuckling at the desperate whining noise [com.name] makes, [sean.speech(Come on, you know I want to hear you beg for it!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[com.speech(Please, fuck me!)] [com.name] desperately [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(I want to be sure you've knocked me up, so please, pump another load of your cum into my dirty pussy!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a deep, approving grunt, [sean.name] thrusts forwards and fills [com.namePos] [com.pussy+] with his [sean.cockSize] cock. Overwhelmed with passion, the [sean.race] grabs your [com.companion]'s hips, before leaning forwards over the top of [com.herHim] and starting to rapidly hammer his [sean.cockGirth], throbbing shaft in and out of [com.her] [com.pussy].
		</p>
		<p>
			Just as it was the last time, the positioning of your stocks is preventing you from getting a good view of what's happening, but from the deep grunts and frantic wet slapping sounds coming from behind [com.name], you can tell that [sean.name] is relentlessly pounding [com.her] pussy. The rapid pace at which your [com.companion] is being fucked proves to be too much for [com.herHim] to bear, and [com.her] desperate moans quickly increase in both volume and frequency, before [com.she] suddenly wails, [com.speech(Fuck! ~Aah!~ So good! ~Ooh!~ I'm- ~Aah!~ I'm cumming!)] 
		</p>
		<p>
			With an ear-splitting scream, and with [sean.namePos] [sean.cock+] still incessantly slamming in and out of [com.her] trembling pussy, [com.name] reaches [com.her] climax. The repetitive slapping sounds coming from between [com.her] legs suddenly sound noticeably wetter, before suddenly coming to an abrupt halt with one final wet squelch. Letting out a deep, desperate grunt, the [sean.race], who's now balls-deep in your [com.companion]'s cunt, exclaims, [sean.speech(That's it! ~Aah!~ Take my load, slut! ~Mmm!~ Feel my cum claiming your womb!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Panting and moaning, [com.name] once again proves to be willing to fully capitulate to [sean.name], and loudly [com.moansVerb], [com.speech(Yes! ~Ooh!~ Please, empty your balls in my pussy and womb! ~Aah!~ Knock me up and make me yours!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With the surrounding crowd cheering him on, [sean.name] does as [com.name] asks, and, keeping his [sean.cockGirth] cock hilted in [com.her] still-quivering pussy, he lets out a series of deep grunts in time with his virile seed spurting deep into [com.her] fertile womb. Continuing to make all manner of lewd noises, they stay locked together like this for a short while, until [sean.namePos] thick cum backs up and seeps out around his still-throbbing cock.
		</p>
		<p>
			Having finally emptied his balls into your [com.companion], [sean.name] slides his cock out of [com.her] tired pussy, before standing to one side and letting the crowd see the huge creampie he's given [com.herHim]. Grabbing hold of [com.namePos] ass cheeks, the [sean.race] pulls them apart to really show off how much cum he's stuffed into [com.her] pussy, remarking, [sean.speech(If only you could see what your cunt looks like now! There's no way you're not going to be a mother after this!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Letting out a deep, long moan, [com.name] lifts [com.her] hips to help show off [com.her] pussy, sighing, [com.speech(That feels so good...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[sean.speech(Now to leave you for a while, to make sure that my seed has enough time to get you pregnant,)] [sean.name] says, releasing his grip on [com.namePos] ass. Putting away his softening cock and then zipping up his trousers, the [sean.race] starts to walk off, calling over his shoulder as he goes, [sean.speech(I'll be back in about thirty minutes!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FINISHED_BREEDING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having been left locked up in the stocks, there's nothing you can do but wait for [sean.namePos] return. As you wonder to yourself how long he'll be, you realise that the sight of the [sean.race]'s cum slowly dripping out of your creampied pussy is attracting the attention of an occasional passer-by. While most of these strangers soon move on without passing comment, one of them stops and loudly remarks, 
		[style.random(
		[style.speechMasculine(Look at this dirty slut! Someone's turned her cunt into a cum-dump!)]
		|
		[style.speechMasculine(What a filthy pussy! I bet this slut's going to get pregnant from all that cum stuffed in there!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Look at this dirty slut! Someone's turned her cunt into a cum-dump!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(What a filthy pussy! I bet this slut's going to get pregnant from all that cum stuffed in there!)]
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After enduring several more similarly lewd comments over the next half an hour, and once all of the cum has dripped out of your well-used cunt, you eventually hear [sean.name] walking up behind you. Stepping around in front of the stocks, he grins down at you and shows you that he's holding an Arcane Pregnancy Tester, before declaring, [sean.speech(Let's see if I succeeded in breeding you!)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isPregnant())
		<p>
			Walking around to swipe it over your belly, the [sean.race] takes a look at the readout and happily declares, [sean.speech(Yes! I got you pregnant! You'll have a nice big swollen belly soon enough!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With a big grin still on his face, [sean.name] quickly unlocks your stocks, allowing you to stand upright once again. Handing you your clothes, he says, [sean.speech(Come and see me again soon! You're the only interesting thing that ever happens to me here!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the [sean.race] walks back over to his post, leaving you to get dressed and continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Walking around to swipe it over your belly, the [sean.race] takes a look at the readout and sighs in frustration, [sean.speech(Damn it! I didn't get you pregnant, even after all that?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With a disappointed look on his face, [sean.name] quickly unlocks your stocks, allowing you to stand upright once again. Handing you your clothes, he says, [sean.speech(I hope you'll come and see me again soon... You're the only interesting thing that ever happens to me here.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the [sean.race] walks back over to his post, leaving you to get dressed and continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having been left locked up in the stocks, there's nothing you can do but wait for [sean.namePos] return. As you wonder to yourself how long he'll be, you realise that the sight of your exposed body is attracting the attention of an occasional passer-by. While most of these strangers soon move on without passing comment, one of them stops and loudly remarks, 
		[style.random(
		[style.speechMasculine(Look at this dirty slut! I wonder how many times [pc.sheHas] been used today?!)]
		|
		[style.speechMasculine(What a filthy slut! I bet [pc.sheHas] been fucked loads of times already!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Look at this dirty slut! I wonder how many times [pc.sheHas] been used today?!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(What a filthy slut! I bet [pc.sheHas] been fucked loads of times already!)]
		)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After enduring several more similarly lewd comments over the next half an hour, you eventually hear [sean.name] walking up behind you. Stepping around in front of the stocks, he grins down at you and declares, [sean.speech(I think you've had enough for one day!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With a smile on his face, [sean.name] steps forwards and prepares to unlock your stocks...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_COMPANION_SECOND_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FINISHED_BREEDING_WITH_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having been left locked up in the stocks, there's nothing which you and [com.name] can do but wait for [sean.namePos] return. As you wonder to yourself how long he'll be, you realise that the sight of the [sean.race]'s cum slowly dripping out of your creampied pussy is attracting the attention of an occasional passer-by. While most of these strangers soon move on without passing comment, one of them stops and loudly remarks, 
		[style.random(
		[style.speechMasculine(Look at this dirty slut! Someone's turned her cunt into a cum-dump!)]
		|
		[style.speechMasculine(What a filthy pussy! I bet this slut's going to get pregnant from all that cum stuffed in there!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Look at this dirty slut! Someone's turned her cunt into a cum-dump!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(What a filthy pussy! I bet this slut's going to get pregnant from all that cum stuffed in there!)]
		)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionAcceptedDeal))
		<p>
			After enduring several more similarly lewd comments over the next half an hour, and once all of the cum has dripped out of both your and [com.namePos] well-used cunts, you eventually hear [sean.name] walking up behind you. Stepping around in front of the stocks, he grins down at you and your [com.companion] and shows you that he's holding a pair of Arcane Pregnancy Testers, before declaring, [sean.speech(Let's see if I succeeded in breeding you!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			#IF(pc.isPregnant())
				Walking around to swipe the first one over your belly, [sean.name] takes a look at the readout and happily declares, [sean.speech(Yes! I got you pregnant! You'll have a nice big swollen belly soon enough!)]
			#ELSE
				Walking around to swipe the first one over your belly, [sean.name] takes a look at the readout and sighs in frustration, [sean.speech(Damn it! I didn't get you pregnant, even after all that?)]
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		#IF(com.equals(brax))
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Now, lets see if my old Inspector is going to be the mother to my kids,)] [sean.name] teases, walking up beside [com.name] and swiping the second Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] belly.
				#IF(com.isPregnant())
					 Taking a look at the digital readout, the [sean.race] excitedly declares, [sean.speech(Oh, yes! I got you pregnant, all right! How does it feel, [com.name], knowing that the guy you demoted is now the father to the kids growing in your womb?)]
				#ELSE
					 Taking a look at the digital readout, the [sean.race] whines, [sean.speech(Well, that sucks... I didn't get you pregnant after all...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					#IF(com.isPregnant())
						[com.speech(Shut up, [sean.name]!)] [com.name] snaps, [com.speech(I may have asked for it, but don't think that this gives you the right to take the piss!)]
					#ELSE
						[com.speech(You can't do anything right, can you, [sean.name]?)] [com.name] snaps.
					#ENDIF
				#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					#IF(com.isPregnant())
						[com.speech(It feels good,)] [com.name] softly moans, [com.speech(I'll be a good mother to our children!)]
					#ELSE
						[com.speech(Aww,)] [com.name] whines, [com.speech(maybe there'll be a next time?)]
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					#IF(com.isPregnant())
						[com.speech(Well, I don't know, it's kind of fun, I guess,)] [com.name] replies in a fluster, [com.speech(Regardless, I'll be a good mother to our children...)]
					#ELSE
						[com.speech(Hmm, I expected more from you, [sean.name],)] [com.name] hums in disapproval, [com.speech(Maybe there'll be a next time?)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				[sean.speech(Now, lets see if you're going to be the mother to my kids,)] [sean.name] teases, walking up beside [com.name] and swiping the second Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] belly.
				#IF(com.isPregnant())
					 Taking a look at the digital readout, the [sean.race] excitedly declares, [sean.speech(Oh, yes! I got you pregnant, all right! I knew I'd have no problems knocking you up!)]
				#ELSE
					 Taking a look at the digital readout, the [sean.race] whines, [sean.speech(Well, that sucks... I didn't get you pregnant after all...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			After enduring several more similarly lewd comments over the next half an hour, and once all of the cum has dripped out of your well-used cunt, you eventually hear [sean.name] walking up behind you. Stepping around in front of the stocks, he grins down at you and shows you that he's holding an Arcane Pregnancy Tester, before declaring, [sean.speech(Let's see if I succeeded in breeding you!)]
		</p>
		#IF(pc.isPregnant())
			<p>
				Walking around to swipe it over your belly, the [sean.race] takes a look at the readout and happily declares, [sean.speech(Yes! I got you pregnant! You'll have a nice big swollen belly soon enough!)]
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				Walking around to swipe it over your belly, the [sean.race] takes a look at the readout and sighs in frustration, [sean.speech(Damn it! I didn't get you pregnant, even after all that?)]
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Stepping forwards, [sean.name] prepares to unlock your stocks and set you and [com.name] free...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FINISHED_WITH_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having been left locked up in the stocks, there's nothing you and [com.name] can do but wait for [sean.namePos] return. As you wonder to yourself how long he'll be, you realise that the sight of your exposed body is attracting the attention of an occasional passer-by. While most of these strangers soon move on without passing comment, one of them stops and loudly remarks, 
		[style.random(
		[style.speechMasculine(Look at this dirty slut! I wonder how many times [pc.sheHas] been used today?!)]
		|
		[style.speechMasculine(What a filthy slut! I bet [pc.sheHas] been fucked loads of times already!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(Look at this dirty slut! I wonder how many times [pc.sheHas] been used today?!)]
		|
		[style.speechFeminine(What a filthy slut! I bet [pc.sheHas] been fucked loads of times already!)]
		)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionAcceptedDeal))
		#IF(com.equals(brax))
			<p>
				After enduring several more similarly lewd comments over the next half an hour, you eventually hear [sean.name] walking up behind you. Stepping around in front of the stocks, he grins down at [com.name] and shows [com.herHim] that he's holding an Arcane Pregnancy Tester, before declaring, [sean.speech(Now, lets see if my old Inspector is going to be the mother to my kids!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				With that, the [sean.race] walks up beside your [com.companion], before reaching down to swipe the Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] belly.
				#IF(com.isPregnant())
					 Taking a look at the digital readout, [sean.name] excitedly declares, [sean.speech(Oh, yes! I got you pregnant, all right! How does it feel, [com.name], knowing that the guy you demoted is now the father to the kids growing in your womb?)]
				#ELSE
					 Taking a look at the digital readout, [sean.name] whines, [sean.speech(Well, that sucks... I didn't get you pregnant after all...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_DOMINANT))
					#IF(com.isPregnant())
						[com.speech(Shut up, [sean.name]!)] [com.name] snaps, [com.speech(I may have asked for it, but don't think that this gives you the right to take the piss!)]
					#ELSE
						[com.speech(You can't do anything right, can you, [sean.name]?)] [com.name] snaps.
					#ENDIF
				#ELSEIF(com.hasFetish(FETISH_SUBMISSIVE))
					#IF(com.isPregnant())
						[com.speech(It feels good,)] [com.name] softly moans, [com.speech(I'll be a good mother to our children!)]
					#ELSE
						[com.speech(Aww,)] [com.name] whines, [com.speech(maybe there'll be a next time?)]
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					#IF(com.isPregnant())
						[com.speech(Well, I don't know, it's kind of fun, I guess,)] [com.name] replies in a fluster, [com.speech(Regardless, I'll be a good mother to our children...)]
					#ELSE
						[com.speech(Hmm, I expected more from you, [sean.name],)] [com.name] hums in disapproval, [com.speech(Maybe there'll be a next time?)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				After enduring several more similarly lewd comments over the next half an hour, you eventually hear [sean.name] walking up behind you. Stepping around in front of the stocks, he grins down at [com.name] and shows [com.herHim] that he's holding an Arcane Pregnancy Tester, before declaring, [sean.speech(Now, lets see if you're going to be the mother to my kids!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				With that, the [sean.race] walks up beside your [com.companion], before reaching down to swipe the Pregnancy Tester over [com.her] belly.
				#IF(com.isPregnant())
					 Taking a look at the digital readout, [sean.name] excitedly declares, [sean.speech(Oh, yes! I got you pregnant, all right! I knew I'd have no problems knocking you up!)]
				#ELSE
					 Taking a look at the digital readout, [sean.name] whines, [sean.speech(Well, that sucks... I didn't get you pregnant after all...)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			After enduring several more similarly lewd comments over the next half an hour, you eventually hear [sean.name] walking up behind you. Stepping around in front of the stocks, he grins down at you and [com.name] and declares, [sean.speech(I think you've had enough for one day!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		Stepping forwards, [sean.name] prepares to unlock your stocks and set you and [com.name] free...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FINISHED_END"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionInStocks))
		<p>
			Moving quickly between you and [com.name], [sean.name] quickly unlocks your stocks, allowing the two of you to stand upright once again. Handing you your clothes, he says, [sean.speech(I hope you'll come and see me again soon! You're the only interesting thing that ever happens to me here.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the [sean.race] walks back over to his post, leaving you and [com.name] to get dressed and continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Now that you've finished being used, [sean.name] steps forwards and quickly unlocks your stocks, allowing you to stand upright once again. Handing you your clothes, he says, [sean.speech(Come and see me again soon! You're the only interesting thing that ever happens to me here!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the [sean.race] walks back over to his post, leaving you to get dressed and continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FINISHED_REPEAT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FINISHED_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not yet satisfied by the public fucking you've received so far, you tell [sean.name] to leave you locked up in the stocks for a little while longer. Letting out an amused laugh, he turns and marches off back to his post, calling over his shoulder as he goes, [sean.speech(Fine, I'll be back later to see if you've had enough!)]
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTwoPartners))
		<p>
			About fifteen minutes later, and having already heard several members of the public comment on your situation as they pass by, a pair of strangers decide that you're just what they're looking for, and quickly step up in front of you before starting to comment on your appearance.
			#IF(npc.isFeminine()==npc2.isFeminine() && npc.getRaceStage()==npc2.getRaceStage() && npc.getRace()==npc2.getRace())
				 Looking up, you see that both of these strangers are [npc.fullRaces(true)].
			#ELSE
				 Looking up, you see that the one making most of the lewd comments is [npc.a_fullRace(true)], while the other is [npc2.a_fullRace(true)].
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc.speech(You ready for a good fucking, slut?)] [npc.name] asks as [npc.she] sees you looking up at [npc.herHim]. Not waiting for an answer, [npc.she] moves around behind you and slaps your [pc.ass+], causing you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan].
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Oh yeah, this one's ready to go!)] [npc2.name] excitedly exclaims, stepping up in front of you.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			About fifteen minutes later, and having already heard several members of the public comment on your situation as they pass by, [npc.a_fullRace(true)] decides that you're just what they're looking for, and quickly [npc.steps] up in front of you to declare, [npc.speech(You look like you'll be a good fuck, you dirty slut!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Not waiting for a response,
			#IF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_ORAL_RECEIVING))
				 [npc.she] [npc.steps] forwards and pushes [npc.her] groin into your face, before sneering,
				#IF(npc.hasVagina())
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love eating me out!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love sucking my cock!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ELSEIF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_ANAL_GIVING))
				 [npc.she] moves around behind you and slaps your [pc.ass+], causing you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan]. Laughing at your reaction, [npc.she] then sneers, [npc.speech(Oh yeah, I'm going to fuck your ass so good!)]
			#ELSEIF(npc.hasFetish(FETISH_VAGINAL_GIVING))
				 [npc.she] moves around behind you and slaps your [pc.ass+], causing you to let out an involuntary [pc.moan]. Laughing at your reaction, [npc.she] then sneers, [npc.speech(Oh yeah, I'm going to fuck your pussy so good!)]
			#ELSE
				 [npc.she] [npc.steps] forwards and pushes [npc.her] groin against one of your [pc.hands], before sneering,
				#IF(npc.hasVagina())
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love fingering my cunt!)]
				#ELSE
					 [npc.speech(Oh yeah, you're going to love stroking my cock!)]
				#ENDIF
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FINISHED_REPEAT_AFTER_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FINISHED_REPEAT_AFTER_SEX"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTwoPartners))
		<p>
			Having had their fun, the two strangers step back and start making lewd comments on your performance to one another. Although you're too tired from the double fucking you just received to fully pay attention to what it is they're saying, you're still vaguely aware that they're talking about you as though you're nothing but a worthless sex toy, which, combined with the mocking comments from the crowd that gathered to watch your performance, makes you feel more humiliated than ever.
		</p>
		<p>
			Delivering one last swift slap to your [pc.ass+], the [npc.race] steps around to where [npc.her] [npc2.race] companion is still standing in front of you, and without giving you even one last look, they walk off together.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Having had [npc.her] fun, the stranger steps back and starts making lewd comments on your performance. Although you're too tired from the fucking you just received to fully pay attention to what it is [npc.sheIs] saying, you're still vaguely aware that [npc.sheIs] talking about you as though you're nothing but a worthless sex toy, which, combined with the mocking comments from the crowd that gathered to watch your performance, makes you feel more humiliated than ever.
		</p>
		<p>
			Delivering one last swift slap to your [pc.ass+], the [npc.race] makes one last disparaging comment, before [npc.walking] off into the crowd.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionInStocks) || !game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyCompanionAcceptedDeal))
		<p>
			While the sight of you being fucked proved to be entertaining enough to draw a moderately-sized crowd, the members of the public who gathered to watch quickly start to lose interest. As they quickly wander off, you find yourself with little else to do but wait for [sean.name] to return and offer to set you free once again...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PUBLIC_STOCKS_LOCKED_UP_FINISHED_REPEAT_AFTER_SEX_START_SEX_COMPANION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_slaverAlleyTwoPartners))
		<p>
			As the crowd which gathered to watch you starts to dissipate, several members of the public start to look for some other form of entertainment, and it's not long before one of them  points out that your [com.companion] is available for public use. A couple of members of the crowd quickly rush forwards to take advantage of the fact that nobody's currently using [com.herHim], and as they walk around to inspect [com.name] from every angle, you're able to look across and see that
			#IF(npc.isFeminine()==npc2.isFeminine() && npc.getRaceStage()==npc2.getRaceStage() && npc.getRace()==npc2.getRace())
				 they're both [npc.fullRaces(true)].
			#ELSE
				 Looking up, you see that the more dominant-looking of the two is [npc.a_fullRace(true)], while the other is [npc2.a_fullRace(true)].
			#ENDIF
		</p>
		<p>
			Finishing [npc.her] inspection, the more dominant [npc.race] steps around behind [com.name] and teases, [npc.speech(I'm going to enjoy fucking you, slut!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[npc2.speech(Oh yeah, this is going to be fun!)] the [npc2.race] [npc2.moansVerb] as [npc2.she] steps up in front of [com.name], before quickly displacing [npc2.her] clothing and presenting your [com.companion] with [npc2.her]
			#IF(npc2.hasPenis())
				#IF(npc2.hasVagina())
					 [npc2.cock+] and [npc2.pussy+].
				#ELSE
					 [npc2.cock+].
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				 [npc2.pussy+].
			#ENDIF
			 Letting out an excited [npc2.moan], [npc2.she] doesn't hesitate for a moment longer, and instantly starts to use [com.name]...
		</p>
		<p>
			[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
		</p>
		<p>
			While this is happening, you hear [npc.name] shuffling around behind [com.name] as [npc.she] quickly seeks to displace [com.her] clothing. As soon as [npc.sheIs] done, [npc.she] steps forwards and teases the [npc.cockHead+] of [npc.her] cock up and down over your [com.companion]'s [com.ass+]. Shifting [npc.her] [com.hips] a little in response, [com.name] can't help but whine as [npc.name] teases, [npc.speech(Time to give you a good fucking, slut!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[#SPECIAL_PARSE_1]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eventually having had enough fun with [com.name], the two strangers get their clothing back in order and walk off, leaving your [com.companion] panting and quietly moaning as [com.she] recovers from the experience...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			While the sight of you being fucked proved to be entertaining enough to draw a moderately-sized crowd, the members of the public who gathered to watch quickly start to lose interest. As they start to wander off, one of them suddenly notices that your [com.companion] is not only marked for public use, but is also currently not being used by anyone. As they walk around to inspect [com.name] from every angle, you're able to look across and see that they're [npc.a_raceFull(true)].
		</p>
		<p>
			Although you can't see [npc.herHim] from your position in the stocks, you're still able to hear the [npc.race] as [npc.she] steps around behind [com.name] and slaps ass, before teasing, [npc.speech(Come on, slut, beg me to fuck you! I'll keep this going until you do it!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As the sound of another slap rings out, you hear your [com.companion] relent and beg, [com.speech(Please, fuck me! I need you to fuck me!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			A small crowd quickly gathers to watch the upcoming entertainment, and as they start to loudly comment on your [com.companion]'s display of submission, the [npc.race] lets out an excited [npc.moan] and prepares to start fucking [com.herHim]...
		</p>
		<p>
			[#SPECIAL_PARSE_0]
		</p>
		<p>
			Having had [npc.her] fun, [npc.name] steps away from [com.name], and without so much as a backwards glance, walks off and leaves your [com.companion] panting and quietly [npc.moaning] in the stocks. The crowd which gathered to watch the lewd display quickly dissipates, leaving both you and [com.name] with little else to do but wait and see what will happen to you next...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
</dialogue>
