<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- SCARLETTS_SHOP_EXTERIOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SCARLETTS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_CLOSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Tucked away in one corner of Slaver Alley, you see a shop that's quite unlike all the others. Looking down from the words 'Scarlett's Shop' painted in fancy gold lettering above the door, you see that there's a sign hanging in one of the large glass windows, which reads, [style.italicsMinorBad('Open every day, [unit.time(6)]-[unit.time(22)]')].
	</p>
	#IF(pc.getQuest(QUEST_LINE_MAIN) == QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA)
		<p>
			As the shop is currently [style.colourBad(closed)], there's nothing more for you to do here except turn around and leave. You also haven't yet gone to report to Scarlett's matriarch, [helena.name], so there wouldn't be much for you to do here even if the shop was open. Scarlett said that you can find [helena.name] up in the Harpy Nests...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As the shop is currently [style.colourBad(closed)], there's nothing more for you to do here except turn around and leave. If you wanted to talk to Scarlett, you'll have to come back at some time after six in the morning...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SCARLETTS_SHOP_EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Tucked away in one corner of Slaver Alley, you see a shop that's quite unlike all the others. Looking down from the words 'Scarlett's Shop' painted in fancy gold lettering above the door, you see that there's a sign hanging in one of the large glass windows, which reads, [style.italicsMinorGood('Open every day, [unit.time(6)]-[unit.time(22)]')].
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite the fact that this shop should be [style.colourGood(open)] for business at this time, you don't see any sign of activity inside. Furthermore, while the other shops in Slaver Alley use the area in front of their premises to proudly display advertisement boards and platforms upon which to display their goods, the area in front of 'Scarlett's Shop' is noticeably barren; yet further proof that this particular store must have fallen upon hard times.
	</p>
	#IF(pc.getQuest(QUEST_LINE_MAIN) == QUEST_MAIN_1_E_REPORT_TO_HELENA)
		<p>
			You haven't yet gone to report to Scarlett's matriarch, [helena.name], and you don't really want to have to talk to the rude harpy again until you've done as she's asked. Scarlett said that you can find [helena.name] up in the Harpy Nests, so you'll need to go there report to her before stepping foot inside this shop again.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- SCARLETTS_SHOP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SCARLETTS_SHOP_INTRO"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Pushing open the door and stepping inside, you quickly discover that the interior of 'Scarlett's Shop' is just as bare as it appeared to be from the outside. There isn't a single slave for sale in sight, and the only sign of life is a rather defeated-looking, black-feathered harpy slouched down behind a counter at the far end of the shop.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking up as she hears you enter the shop, the harpy lets out an annoyed huff, before shouting out, [scarlett.speech(If you aren't here to donate any slaves, then you'd better turn around and fuck right off! I'm not in the mood to deal with any fucking morons like you today.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she's quite clearly the shop's owner, this extremely rude harpy must be 'Scarlett', who's the exact person you're looking for. As she rudely repeats her demand for you to get out of her store, you wonder if you should ask her about Arthur right now, or do as she says and come back at another time.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SCARLETTS_SHOP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Pushing open the door and stepping inside, you quickly discover that the interior of 'Scarlett's Shop' is just as bare as it appeared to be from the outside. There isn't a single slave for sale in sight, and the only sign of life is a rather defeated-looking harpy slouched down behind a counter at the far end of the shop.
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking up as she hears you enter the shop, the harpy lets out an annoyed huff, before shouting out, [scarlett.speech(If you aren't here to donate any slaves, then you'd better turn around and fuck right off! I'm not in the mood to deal with any fucking morons like you today.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You're quite taken aback at Scarlett's rude words, and deciding that it's probably best not to get involved with someone like that, you turn around and head for the exit.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- SCARLETT_IS_A_BITCH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SCARLETT_IS_A_BITCH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Letting out a defeated sigh as you wonder why everything has to be so difficult, you walk towards the front desk where Scarlett is sitting.
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speech(Did you not hear what I just said?! Fuck off already!)] the rude harpy shouts, sitting up in her chair and throwing a menacing sneer your way.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I just need to know if you've got a slave for sale going by the name of 'Arthur',)] you explain, hoping that you can resolve your business with the harpy as quickly as possible.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you mention the name 'Arthur', Scarlett stands up from behind her desk, and her cheeks flush red as she rants, [scarlett.speech(If I hear that fucking name one more time, I swear I'm going to kill someone! Are you working with them?! Huh?! Those fucking cunts who fucked me over?! Tell me who the fuck you are, right fucking now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isCowardly())
			Although she looks as though she's lacking the physical strength required in order to follow through on any of her threats, Scarlett's foul language and aggressive posturing are more than enough to scare you. Wanting to escape from this threatening situation as quickly as possible, you answer the harpy,
		#ELSE
			Despite her foul language and aggressive posturing, you find Scarlett's outburst to be more embarrassing than intimidating. She clearly lacks the physical strength required in order to follow through on any of her threats, so it's more out of a desire to calm her down rather than due to feeling threatened that you start to answer her,
		#ENDIF
		 [pc.speech(Don't worry, I'm not working with 'them', whoever they might be. I'm just a friend of Arthur's who's been trying to track him down. I found out from the Enforcers that he was meant to have been given to you. If you're still in possession of him, I'd like to see if I can buy his freedom, and if not, then could you [style.italics(please)] just tell me who you sold him to?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speech(Is that so?)] Scarlett huffs as she sits back down, [scarlett.speech(I guess you really are as stupid as you look. Can't you see that I've got no slaves for sale? Of course I'm not fucking still in possession of him. I'm fucking finished. <i>Finished!</i> And it's all thanks to your 'friend'...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Hoping that this annoying harpy is about to tell you what you want to know, you listen as she continues, [scarlett.speech(There might be a way for both of us to profit here... Yeah, I know what happened to Arthur, <i>and</i> I know where he is right now, but hopefully even a fucking idiot like yourself can understand that I'm not going to be giving that information away for free. You want to know what I know? Then you're going to be fucking doing something to help me out first.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Wondering how many different people you're going to have to deal with before finally finding Arthur, you sigh, [pc.speech(So what do you need my help with?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speech(Even a dumb cunt like you can see that this business is a complete failure, and my matriarch is [style.italics(not)] going to be happy when she finds out about it,)] the foul-mouthed harpy grumbles as she leans back in her chair, [scarlett.speech(If you want to know what happened to your stupid fucking friend, you're going to go up to the Harpy Nests, find a matriarch called '[helena.name]', tell her that my business is bust, and take whatever punishment she'll decide upon on my behalf. There's no fucking way I'm going to be the one who tells her about this.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You realise that if you ever want to find out what happened to Arthur, you're going to have to agree to Scarlett's demands, even if you don't plan on taking any 'punishment' on her behalf...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- SCARLETT_IS_A_SUPER_BITCH -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SCARLETT_IS_A_SUPER_BITCH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to agree with the insufferable harpy for now, you respond, [pc.speech(Fine, I'll do it, but you'd better keep your end of the bargain. When I get back, you're going to tell me exactly what's happened to Arthur, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speech(Just fuck off and do it already! Fuck, you're a real asshole to try and talk to, you know?!)] Scarlett shouts, looking just as infuriated as you feel right now. [scarlett.speech(Don't bother coming back here until you've taken [helena.namePos] punishment! And don't let her go easy on you; I'm gonna enjoy hearing what she did to you when you get back!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting to waste any more time talking to her, you turn your back on Scarlett and walk out of her shop. As the door swings shut behind you, you find yourself wondering if you've ever met anyone as rude as she is. You seriously hope that this matriarch, '[helena.name]', is nothing like Scarlett, and as you set off in the direction of the Harpy Nests, you wonder how many more hurdles you'll be presented with before finally finding Arthur...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_HELENA_RETURNS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Once again you find yourself standing before 'Scarlett's Shop', but unlike the last time you were here, all of the blinds have been pulled down, preventing you from seeing into the store's interior. As you walk towards the front entrance, you pass a couple of gossiping wolf-girls, and you can't help but overhear a snippet of their conversation, [npcFemale.speech(...I'm telling you, I saw <i>the</i> [helena.name] going in there! You know, they say she's the most beautiful harpy in all of Lilith's Realm...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Curious to find out what's become of Scarlett, you wonder if you should enter the shop now, or come back at another time...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_ROMANCE_FAILED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After you refused to sell Scarlett to her, Helena gave up on her plans of making this slave shop into a successful business. Now lying completely abandoned, the only hint of the matriarch's involvement in the refurbishment of these premises is the name 'Helena's Boutique' painted over the front entrance.
	</p>
	<p>
		After spending a moment to reflect on the fact that it's extremely unlikely that this place will ever open its doors to customers again, there's nothing left for you to do except turn around and continue on your way elsewhere...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_PAINTING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(pc.getQuest(QUEST_LINE_ROMANCE_HELENA)==QUEST_ROMANCE_HELENA_3_C_EXTERIOR_DECORATOR)
			Thanks to you, the entire frontage of Helena's shop has been repainted in a brilliant white, and is really starting to stand out from those around it. Looking around, you see that most people are at least glancing in its direction as they walk past. Unfortunately for the more curious of these passersby, however, Helena has replaced the sign displaying the shop's opening times with one that simply reads: 'Closed for renovations.'
		#ELSE
			Thanks to you, all of the paint has been stripped from the front of Helena's store, including the name 'Scarlett's Shop'. With just the bare woodwork left exposed, the frontage is starting to stand out from those around it, and you notice that a few members of the public are starting to look in its direction as they walk past. Unfortunately for the more curious of these passersby, however, Helena has replaced the sign displaying the shop's opening times with one that simply reads: 'Closed for renovations.'
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_GONE_HOME"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you know that this sign wouldn't normally apply to you, Helena has gone home early for the day. As such, you'll be unable to enter the shop and speak with her again until
		#IF(game.getDayOfWeek()==DOW_FRIDAY)
			 [style.colourMinorBad(Monday morning at the earliest)].
		#ELSE
			 [style.colourMinorBad(tomorrow morning at the earliest)].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_PAINTING_OPEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that this sign doesn't apply to you, and seeing through the front windows that Helena is sitting behind the counter, you could enter the shop and talk to her right now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_PAINTING_CLOSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you know that this sign wouldn't normally apply to you, Helena is only present from [style.italicsMinorBad([unit.time(9)]-[unit.time(17)] on weekdays, or up until [unit.time(21)] on Friday)]. As such, the store is currently [style.colourBad(closed)] even to you, and the harpy matriarch won't be present until 
		#IF(game.getDayOfWeek()==DOW_FRIDAY)
			 [style.colourMinorBad(Monday morning at the earliest)].
		#ELSE
			 [style.colourMinorBad(tomorrow morning at the earliest)].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_FINISHED_OPEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As a result of your hard work, the entire frontage of Helena's Boutique has not only been repainted in a brilliant white, but also proudly bears the words 'Helena's Boutique' in bright gold lettering over the entrance. Thanks to all of your efforts, the harpy matriarch's store is by far the most popular in all of Slaver Alley, and while the initial excitement of Helena's unexpected presence has by now worn off, there still several fans loitering around nearby in the hopes of getting an autograph or a kind word from Helena herself.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_FINISHED_CLOSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As a result of your hard work, the entire frontage of Helena's Boutique has not only been repainted in a brilliant white, but also proudly bears the words 'Helena's Boutique' in bright gold lettering over the entrance. Thanks to all of your efforts, the harpy matriarch's store is by far the most popular in all of Slaver Alley, and even though it's currently closed, there are still a few dedicated fans loitering around nearby as they wait for the chance to get an autograph or a kind word from Helena herself.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_PAINTED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As a result of your hard work, the entire frontage of Helena's shop has not only been repainted in a brilliant white, but also proudly bears the words 'Helena's Boutique' in bright gold lettering over the entrance. Thanks to this, word of the harpy matriarch's presence in Slaver Alley has finally started to spread, which is clearly evidenced by the small crowd loitering around in front of its large glass windows. Unfortunately for these people hoping to catch a glimpse of Helena, however, the shop's blinds have all been pulled down, concealing the interior from their curious gaze. To further dash their hopes of meeting the harpy matriarch, there's a sign hanging in the window which reads: 'Closed until grand reopening.'
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_PAINTED_OPEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing both that this sign doesn't apply to you, and that Helena will be inside the shop at this time of day, you could step inside and talk to her right now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_PAINTED_CLOSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although you know that this sign wouldn't normally apply to you, Helena is only present from [style.italicsMinorBad([unit.time(9)]-[unit.time(17)] on weekdays, or up until [unit.time(21)] on Friday)]. As such, the store is currently [style.colourBad(closed)] even to you, and the harpy matriarch won't be present until 
		#IF(game.getDayOfWeek()==DOW_FRIDAY)
			 [style.colourMinorBad(Monday morning at the earliest)].
		#ELSE
			 [style.colourMinorBad(tomorrow morning at the earliest)].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Although the name 'Scarlett's Shop' is still painted in fancy gold lettering above its front entrance, you know that the store in front of you is no longer managed by the rude harpy who bears that name. Instead, it's now run by Helena, but despite the fact that this beautiful harpy matriarch is a well-known figure throughout Dominion, her store doesn't seem to be any more popular than it was when under Scarlett's management. In fact, not a single member of the public seems to be even glancing in its direction, and you can only image that it must be because none of them are aware of Helena's takeover.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_OPEN"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unlike the days when Scarlett was in charge, Helena's shop has rather limited opening times, which are clearly displayed for all to see on a sign hanging in the front window which reads: [style.italicsMinorGood('Open weekdays, [unit.time(9)]-[unit.time(17)]. Open until [unit.time(21)] on Friday.')]
	</p>
	<p>
		As her shop is currently [style.colourGood(open)] for business, you could always step inside and see Helena again right now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_EXTERIOR_CLOSED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Unlike the days when Scarlett was in charge, Helena's shop has rather limited opening times, which are clearly displayed for all to see on a sign hanging in the front window which reads: [style.italicsMinorBad('Open weekdays, [unit.time(9)]-[unit.time(17)]. Open until [unit.time(21)] on Friday.')]
	</p>
	<p>
		As her shop is currently [style.colourBad(closed)], there's nothing more for you to do here except turn around and leave. If you wanted to talk to [helena.name], you'll have to come back at a time when her shop is open...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_SHOP -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_INTRODUCTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Pushing open the front door and entering the shop, you're greeted by the sight of the beautiful figure of [helena.name] sitting down behind the shop's counter. With a delightful smile on her face, she greets you in her calm, regal voice, [helena.speech(What a pleasure it is to see you once again. May I enquire as to the reason for you following me here?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Seeing absolutely no sign of the raven-harpy you need to have a word with, you ask, [pc.speech(Is Scarlett still around here somewhere? I really need to talk to her.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Covering her mouth with one of her flawless, white-feathered wings, Helena lets out a soft, delicate laugh. Beckoning you forwards with her free hand, she looks down to one side of her and says, [helena.speech(My dear Scarlett, this [pc.race] is asking after you. Be a good girl and greet your friend.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speechNoEffects(~Mrph!~)] comes a quiet, muffled groan from somewhere behind the counter, and then a moment later, the submissive form of Scarlett obediently crawls out to kneel down in front of you. You can't help but stare as you see that she's wearing nothing except for a pink ball gag in her mouth and a heavy steel slave collar around her neck. With her groin fully on display, you're able to see that Scarlett's genitals consist solely of [scarlett.a_penisSize], light-skinned cock and accompanying pair of vestigial balls.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Good girl,)] [helena.name] says, standing up from behind the counter and stepping forwards to stroke Scarlett's plume of dark black head-feathers. With an underlying icy tone to her otherwise melodic voice, the matriarch calmly states, [helena.speech(As you can no doubt see, I've had to enslave my dear Scarlett so that she can use her body to pay me back for all the flames she's wasted while mismanaging this business I'd entrusted to her. I'm afraid that if you were hoping to speak with her about something, then you'll have to buy her from me first.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		It seems as though yet another obstacle has been put in your way towards finding Arthur. No matter what your views on slavery might be, it looks as though you only have one option. You'll have to buy Scarlett, then demand that she tell you what happened to Arthur.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_OFFER_SCARLETT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Pushing open the front door and entering the shop, you're greeted once again by the sight of the beautiful figure of [helena.name] sitting down behind the shop's counter. With a delightful smile on her face, she calls out in her calm, regal voice, [helena.speech(Good [style.evening]. Perchance have you returned to complete your purchase of my dear Scarlett?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speechNoEffects(~Mrph!~)] Scarlett groans from the other side of the counter as she hears [helena.name] talk about selling her.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Pushing open the front door and entering the shop, you're greeted once again by the sight of the beautiful figure of [helena.name] sitting down behind the shop's counter. With a delightful smile on her face, she calls out in her calm, regal voice,
		#IF(helena.hasSlaves())
			 [helena.speech(Good [style.evening], [pc.name]. You're fast becoming a regular visitor to my humble shop. Perchance are you here to purchase a slave?)]
		#ELSE
			 [helena.speech(Good [style.evening], [pc.name]. Unfortunately, I must inform you that I have no slaves for sale at this time. I am expecting another couple to be delivered here tomorrow morning, so may I suggest that you return then?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	#IF(helena.hasSlaves())
		<p>
			#IF(helena.getSlavesOwned().size()==2)
				Looking across to one side of the barren store, you see a pair of slaves obediently standing to attention. Wearing nothing but the slave collars locked in place around their necks, you're able to see that one is [npc.a_raceFull], while the other is [npc2.a_raceFull].
			#ELSE
				Looking across to one side of the barren store, you see a slave obediently standing to attention. Wearing nothing but the slave collar locked in place around [npc.her] neck, you're able to see that [npc.she] is [npc.a_raceFull].
			#ENDIF
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		#IF(pc.hasCompanion(scarlett))
			After glancing across at [scarlett.name], the beautiful harpy courteously smiles at you and patiently waits to see what it is you'll do next.
		#ELSE
			Courteously smiling at you, the beautiful harpy patiently waits to see what it is you'll do next.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_SCARLETT_FOR_SALE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(If that's what it takes, I'll buy Scarlett,)] you say.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(What an excellent decision,)] [helena.name] calmly replies,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_punishedByHelena))
			 [helena.speech(Now, taking into consideration the fact that you took that little punishment of mine on Scarlett's behalf, I'm willing to give you a discount. Although she is unquestionably loyal to me, I must inform you that Scarlett can be quite unpleasant towards others, and so would need a good deal of training to make her into a good slave. Taking this into account, I'd value Scarlett at fifteen thousand flames, but with the discount I'm willing to give you, you may purchase her for ten thousand.)]
		#ELSE
			 [helena.speech(Although she is unquestionably loyal to me, I must inform you that Scarlett can be quite unpleasant towards others, and so would need a good deal of training to make her into a good slave. Taking this into account, I'd value Scarlett at fifteen thousand flames. I'm not one for haggling over prices, so you can either pay the full fifteen thousand, or else I'll find someone else to buy her.)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'll pay that much for her,)] you readily agree, not wanting [helena.name] to sell Scarlett to anyone else.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(As you were so kind as to come up to my nest and inform me of Scarlett's failure, I'll reserve her for you,)] [helena.name] says, [helena.speech(Simply let me know whenever you're ready to complete your purchase. Oh, and please do remember to bring your slaver license; as I'm sure you already know, it's required in order to complete any slave transaction.)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isHasSlaverLicense())
		<p>
			[pc.speech(Of course,)] you reply, [pc.speech(I'll have that ready for you.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[helena.speech(Most excellent. Please do let me know when you're ready to complete your purchase,)] the beautiful white-feathered harpy replies.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			[pc.speech(My slaver license...)] you muse out loud, wondering where you could obtain one.
		</p>
		<p>
			[helena.speech(If you've misplaced yours, then I believe you should be able to fill out some forms and get a replacement at the Slavery Administration building,)] [helena.name] helpfully explains, [helena.speech(It's the same building as the one where you would have first obtained your license. In case you cannot remember, that would be the large one next to the square where all those public stocks are kept.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Thanking Helena for the information, and concealing the fact that you don't have a license lest the matriarch change her mind about reserving Scarlett for you, you prepare to set off and enquire about obtaining one at this 'Slavery Administration' building...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_BUYING_SCARLETT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Producing both your slaver license and the [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames which Helena is asking for, you place them down on the counter in front of her, saying that you'd like to purchase Scarlett without any further delay. After quickly checking your license and the money to make sure that everything's in order, [helena.name] smiles at you and softly says, [helena.speech(Thank you for your custom. Please wait one moment while I prepare your slave.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning to one side, [helena.name] leans down to where Scarlett is sitting behind the counter, before unfastening and removing her ballgag. Sitting back upright, she orders, [helena.speech(Go on, Scarlett, say hello to your new owner.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As she sulkily stands up and walks around from the other side of the counter, you see that Scarlett is still completely naked except for the metal collar around her neck. Upon seeing you waiting to take ownership of her, the gravity of her situation suddenly hits her, and with her cheeks flushing bright red, she turns back to her matriarch and screams, [scarlett.speech(You fucking bitch! You can't seriously be selling me to [pc.herHim]! You ugly whore, I'll make you pay for this!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The pleasant smile on [helena.namePos] face instantly vanishes as she hears Scarlett calling her ugly, and as the feathers on her head and wings bristle up, you can almost physically feel the icy rage she's about to unleash on your new slave. You'd better do something to silence Scarlett before this escalates any further.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- HELENAS_SHOP_SCARLETT_PURCHASED -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_SCARLETT_PURCHASED_GENTLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Thinking that it would best to show Scarlett some kindness, you reach up and place [pc.a_hand] on her shoulder, smiling reassuringly at her as she snaps back around to scowl angrily at you. Speaking in the softest tone you can manage, you say, [pc.speech(Calm down, Scarlett. It's going to be ok. Just take a deep breath and try to relax.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The raven-harpy's face flushes bright red, and for a moment you think that she's about to unleash yet another barrage of foul language, but instead she simply glares into your [pc.eyes] without saying a word. Sharply yanking her shoulder back, she wriggles out of your grip and steps away from you. Realising that any more physical contact is likely to send her into another fit of rage, you simply smile at the angry harpy with as much warmth as you can muster. Seeing that Helena is still on the edge of launching into a furious rage of her own, you ask your new slave, [pc.speech(Could you please apologise to Helena?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she's quick to anger, Scarlett isn't stupid, and quickly realises that as she's your slave, she'd better do as you say. Turning to face Helena, she mutters, [scarlett.speech(Sorry, Helena...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although the smile doesn't return to her face, Helena's head-feathers flatten back down, and she icily states, [helena.speech(Don't you <i>ever</i> speak to me like that again.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that both harpies have calmed down, you ask Scarlett, [pc.speech(Now, do you think you can finally tell me where Arthur is?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_SCARLETT_PURCHASED_SHOUT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to put Scarlett in her place, you angrily berate her, [pc.speech(You insolent bitch! How <i>dare</i> you?! You're only to speak when spoken to, and if I hear <i>one more</i> insult come out of that filthy mouth of yours, you're going to be sorry!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The raven-harpy's face flushes bright red, and for a moment you think that she's about to unleash yet another barrage of foul language, but instead she simply glares into your [pc.eyes] without saying a word. You hold her gaze, and after angrily staring at one another for a moment, Scarlett casts her eyes down to the floor. Seeing that Helena is still on the edge of launching into a furious rage of her own, you tell your new slave, [pc.speech(You're to apologise to Helena, right now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she's quick to anger, Scarlett isn't stupid, and quickly realises that as she's your slave, she'd better do as you say. Turning to face Helena, she mutters, [scarlett.speech(Sorry, Helena...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although the smile doesn't return to her face, Helena's head-feathers flatten back down, and she icily states, [helena.speech(Don't you <i>ever</i> speak to me like that again.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that both harpies have calmed down, you turn to face your new slave and order her, [pc.speech(Now, tell me where Arthur is!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_SCARLETT_PURCHASED_SLAP"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to put your insolent slave in her place, you step forwards, before quickly reaching up and delivering a sharp slap across her face. As she recoils back from your blow, you shout, [pc.speech(You insolent bitch! How <i>dare</i> you?! You're only to speak when spoken to, and if I hear <i>one more</i> insult come out of that filthy mouth of yours, you're going to be sorry!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With her mouth open wide in shock, the raven-harpy's face flushes bright red, and for a moment you think that she's about to unleash yet another barrage of foul language, but instead she simply glares into your [pc.eyes] without saying a word. You hold her gaze, and after angrily staring at one another for a moment, Scarlett casts her eyes down to the floor. Seeing that Helena is still on the edge of launching into a furious rage of her own, you tell your new slave, [pc.speech(You're to apologise to Helena, right now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although she's quick to anger, Scarlett isn't stupid, and quickly realises that as she's your slave, she'd better do as you say. Turning to face Helena, she mutters, [scarlett.speech(Sorry, Helena...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Although the smile doesn't return to her face, Helena's head-feathers flatten back down, and she icily states, [helena.speech(Don't you <i>ever</i> speak to me like that again.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Now that both harpies have calmed down, you turn to face your new slave and order her, [pc.speech(Now, tell me where Arthur is!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_SCARLETT_PURCHASED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You see a flicker of defiance deep down in Scarlett's [scarlett.eyeColour] [scarlett.eyes], but she simply lets out a little huff, before rudely answering, [scarlett.speech(I don't have any fucking choice, do I? I'm guessing you know that Arthur was enslaved by the Enforcers. Well, through a random lottery, I was the 'lucky' person who ended up taking possession of him. Not five minutes after he was delivered here, some <i>bastard incubus</i> came by and demanded that I give Arthur over to him, without any payment!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You notice Scarlett fidgeting around as she starts getting angry at the thought of what happened to her, and she angrily curses, [scarlett.speech(That fucking cunt had all these official documents of minor infractions I'd committed while running this shop, and he made me fucking choose between being shut down or handing over Arthur! Obviously, I chose the latter option.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Do you know the name of this incubus? Or where he lives?)] you ask, desperate to finally find out where Arthur is being held.
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speech(I don't know, it was some stupid fucking name beginning with 'Z'... Hmm... 'Zaranix', I think it was,)] Scarlett growls, the very thought of his name making her cheeks flush red with rage, [scarlett.speech(The cunt's not hard to miss; after all, how many demons do you see choosing to stay in their male form? If you want to know where he lives, then you can find his address on a piece of paper in my drawer over there... I had to verify the fucker's slaver license, and made a note of where he lived so that I could go and get my revenge later...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having overheard your conversation, [helena.name] pulls open the drawers beneath her counter until she finds the scrap of paper Scarlett's talking about. Helpfully walking over to where you're standing and handing it over to you, she then returns to sit in her chair once more. After taking a moment to decipher Scarlett's barely-legible handwriting, you groan as you realise that you're going to have to travel back over to Demon Home; the address where he's being kept is just a short way down the street from where his apartment building is.
	</p>
	<p>
		Your thoughts about how you're going to deal with Zaranix are suddenly interrupted by Scarlett's impatient shuffling, and you realise that you're going to have to decide what you're going to do with her before anything else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_BUYING_SCARLETT_KEEP_HER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you're going to keep Scarlett, you turn towards [helena.name] and ask, [pc.speech(Can I get Scarlett transferred somewhere? I don't have the time to escort her around right now.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Well, of course. All newly-bought slaves have to be processed through the Slavery Administration first; now that you've concluded your business with Scarlett, she can be held there until you're ready to collect her,)] [helena.name] responds, before motioning with her wing to one side of the shop, [helena.speech(Please wait over there, Scarlett, I'll take you down to the Slavery Administration building once [pc.name] has departed.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You thank Helena for her cooperation and prepare to exit her store, but before you can leave, the harpy matriarch calls out, [helena.speech(I've decided to personally take over the management of this shop, so if you ever need to buy or sell any slaves, please keep me in mind!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="HELENAS_SHOP_BUYING_SCARLETT_FREE_HER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not liking the idea of keeping Scarlett as a slave, you turn towards [helena.name] and ask, [pc.speech(Do I need to fill out some kind of form to set Scarlett free?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Oh my, it looks like today's your lucky day,)] [helena.name] calmly says to Scarlett, before turning to you and replying, [helena.speech(All that needs to be done is to inform the Slavery Administration of your intention to set Scarlett free. As all newly-bought slaves have to be processed at the same building, I'll fill out the necessary forms for you at the same time.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speech(You're really setting me free?)] Scarlett asks, and as you reply in the affirmative, she mumbles, [scarlett.speech(Thank you... I guess...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(Wait for me over there,)] [helena.name] calls out to Scarlett, using her wing to motion towards one side of the shop, [helena.speech(Once [pc.name] has left, I'll have you set free, and then you can return to my nest. Oh, and don't think that I've forgotten about your silly little outburst earlier; I'll make sure that you're punished for insulting me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[scarlett.speech(Yes, [helena.name]...)] Scarlett mumbles, walking over to one side of the shop and obediently waiting there.
	</p>
	<p>
		[helena.speech(I suppose I must thank you for returning a member of my flock to me,)] [helena.name] says, turning towards you with a smug smile on her face. Thanking Helena for her cooperation, you prepare to exit her store, but before you can leave, the harpy matriarch calls out, [helena.speech(I've decided to personally take over the management of this shop, so if you ever need to buy or sell any slaves, please keep me in mind!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
