<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="SLAVERY_ADMINISTRATION_EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A large metal sign, bearing the words 'Slavery Administration', is prominently displayed above the entrance to the building before you. Its clean, white-washed walls and heavy oak doors set this particular establishment apart from the rest of the stores in Slaver Alley.
	</p>
	<p>
		Noticing a little information board attached to one side of the entrance, you walk up and read what it says. From what you can gather, it appears as though this is an official government building, in which all matters relating to the ownership of slaves, licenses, and businesses dealing in slave-trading are handled. A little piece of paper has been stuck to the bottom of the board, which reads; <i>'Slaver licenses are not being issued!'</i>
	</p>
	<p>
		To one side of this information board, a dozen posters have been plastered over the side of the building. You could take a closer look at these posters,
		#IF(pc.isHasSlaverLicense())
			 or, as you're in possession of a slaver license, you could enter the Slavery Administration building and make use of its services.
		#ELSE
			 or, even though it's doubtful that you'd be able to make use of any of its services, you could enter the Slavery Administration building.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLAVERY_ADMINISTRATION_POSTERS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to take a closer look at the posters which are plastered over the wall of the Slavery Administration building, you [pc.step] over to stand in front of them. It immediately becomes apparent why these posters have been allowed to remain on the side of a government building, for all except one of them are declarations of victory for the state.
	</p>
	<p>
		As you casts your gaze over the posters, you find yourself looking at mug shots of dangerous-looking criminals. Their crimes are listed below their portraits, and range from theft and public disorder to #IF(game.isNonConEnabled())rape#ELSEassault#ENDIF and treason. The punishment for every one of these individuals is listed as lifetime enslavement, and as the capitalised words 'JUSTICE SERVED' have been stamped in purple letters over each one, you realise that these criminals have all been caught and enslaved.
	</p>
	<p>
		The only poster which isn't of this format is one that displays an idyllic scene of a happy family living in the countryside. The writing beneath promises a better life for anyone willing to leave Dominion and take the voyage over the 'Endless Sea' to the land beyond.
		#IF(game.isPlotDiscovered())
			 Knowing that this land must be mainland Europe, you can't help but doubt that the emigrating citizens of Dominion will have a life there similar to the one shown on the poster.
		#ELSE
			 Taking another look at the scene displayed upon the poster, you can't help but wonder what this promised land is like in reality.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Having seen all there is, you [pc.step] away from the posters and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLAVERY_ADMINISTRATION"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.isHasSlaverLicense())
		<p>
			The heavy oak doors of the 'Slavery Administration' building are wide open, and, stepping through the inviting entranceway, you find yourself standing in a cavernous entrance hall. Rows of marble pillars line the edges of the room, with little wooden benches interspersed between them. Two doors are set into the wall opposite you, with signs labelling them as 'Holding pens' and 'Offices'. The only other piece of furniture to be seen is a long, black-marble desk, behind which the black-haired cat-boy, [finch.name], is grinning at you with mischievous eyes.
		</p>
		<p>
			[finch.speech(Ah, if it isn't my <i>favourite</i> customer, [pc.name]!)] he shouts, beckoning you over to the desk. [finch.speech(What can I help you with today?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Walking forwards, you return [finch.namePos] greeting, [pc.speech(Hi, [finch.name].)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[finch.speech(As an owner of a slaver license, I'm pleased to offer you my services,)] he says, standing up to reveal his tiny feline cock. [finch.speech(I've got slave collars, with the appropriate paperwork already completed, as well as a large selection of clothing suitable for your slaves!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			As you come to a halt in front of the black marble desk, [finch.name] grins expectantly at you, [finch.speech(Or, if you'd like, we can discuss the management and handling of your property. Remember, any new slaves you capture will be delivered here first. All the costs of collection and transport are covered in the cost of each slave collar, so just let me know if you want to have your slaves moved elsewhere.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Thanking [finch.name], you wonder what you do next...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_finchIntroduced))
		<p>
			The heavy oak doors of the 'Slavery Administration' building are wide open, and, stepping through the inviting entranceway, you find yourself standing in a large, cavernous entrance hall. Rows of marble pillars line the edges of the room, with little wooden benches interspersed between them. Two doors are set into the wall opposite you, with signs labelling them as 'Holding pens' and 'Offices'. The only other piece of furniture to be seen is a long, black-marble desk, behind which a black-haired cat-boy is grinning at you with mischievous eyes.
		</p>
		<p>
			[finch.speech(Welcome!)] he shouts, beckoning you over to the desk. [finch.speech(Can I help you with anything?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Walking forwards, you return the cat-boy's greeting, [pc.speech(Hello, I was just looking around.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[finch.speech(I'm afraid that there's not really much to see here. All the <i>fun</i> happens in the holding cells, and they're off-limits. Unless you've got a slaver license, there's really not much I can offer you, except for a good day!)] he says, standing up and bowing a little. [finch.speech(Oh, where are my manners?! I'm [finch.name], the manager of the Slavery Administration. I keep petitioning my superiors to have the name changed to something a little more <i>exciting</i>, but they're quite set in their ways.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[pc.speech(I'm [pc.name],)] you answer, returning the cat-boy's disarming smile. As [finch.name] continues grinning at you, your eyes are drawn down to his groin, where you see that his choice of crotchless chaps and briefs have left his tiny cat-like cock completely exposed.
		</p>
		<p>
			Noticing your downwards glance, [finch.name] lets out a little laugh, and you can't help but notice that there's a slightly unsettling edge to his voice, [finch.speech(I like having easy access! You never know when a disobedient slave needs to be put in their place...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Due to your lack of a slaver license, [finch.name] is unable to offer you any services. As he sits back down, concealing his exposed groin behind the desk once more, you wonder if you should ask him about how to obtain one.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			The heavy oak doors of the 'Slavery Administration' building are wide open, and, stepping through the inviting entranceway, you find yourself standing in a large, cavernous entrance hall. Rows of marble pillars line the edges of the room, with little wooden benches interspersed between them. Two doors are set into the wall opposite you, with signs labelling them as 'Holding pens' and 'Offices'. The only other piece of furniture to be seen is a long, black-marble desk, behind which the black-haired cat-boy, [finch.name], is grinning at you with mischievous eyes.
		</p>
		<p>
			[finch.speech(Hello again!)] he shouts, beckoning you over to the desk. [finch.speech(Can I help you with anything?)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Walking forwards, you return [finch.namePos] greeting, [pc.speech(Hello, I was just looking around.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			[finch.speech(I'm afraid that there's not really much to see here. All the <i>fun</i> happens in the holding cells, and they're off-limits. Unless you've got a slaver license, there's really not much I can offer you, except for a good day!)] he says, standing up to reveal his tiny feline cock.
		</p>
		<p>
			Due to your lack of a slaver license, [finch.name] is unable to offer you any services. Throwing a grin your way, he sits back down, concealing his exposed groin behind the desk once more.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLAVERY_ADMINISTRATION_ASK_ABOUT_SLAVER_LICENSE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Walking up to [finch.namePos] desk, you ask, [pc.speech(How do I get a slaver license? Is there some kind of form I need to fill out?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.Name] leans back in his chair, grinning up at you. [finch.speech(Yeah, there's a form to fill out, <i>and</i> a fee of five-thousand flames to pay, but slaver licenses aren't handed out to just anyone. If you're looking to apply for one, you're going to have to join the waiting list. Last time I looked, I think the estimated wait time for new applicants is just over four years...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Four years?!)] you exclaim in disbelief. [pc.speech(Is there no other way to get one?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.speech(Well, unless you can get a letter of recommendation from someone who's already got a slaver license, then no, there's no other way. And if you had that, you wouldn't be asking, would you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.Name] grins up at you, and you can't help but notice the slightly threatening look in his [finch.eyeColour] cat-like eyes. You thank him for the information and step away from the desk, determined to go and ask for a letter of recommendation from Lilaya, the one person you know that can help you out.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLAVERY_ADMINISTRATION_SLAVER_LICENSE_OBTAINED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Walking up to [finch.namePos] desk, you place the letter of recommendation down in front of him. [pc.speech(I got a letter of recommendation from my aunt, so can I get that license now?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.speech(Hah! It's not quite as easy as that, this just means that you're on the priority list, not that-)] [finch.name] starts explaining, but as he reads the signature at the bottom of your letter, he stops talking.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Is something wrong?)] you ask, noticing that all the colour has drained from his face.
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.speech(Your aunt is <i>Lilaya</i>?)] he asks, putting the letter to one side. [finch.speech(Why didn't you say so earlier?! If you've got the five-thousand flame fee, I'll process your license right now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Oh, great!)] you cheerily reply, handing over the money. [pc.speech(You know Lilaya then?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.Name] pulls out a large stack of forms from under his desk, and as he starts filling them out, he replies, [finch.speech(Of course! Anyone in any sort of business which deals with demons should know of all the elder lilin's recognised children. Lilaya is an especially notable individual, as she's one of only two half-demons to ever have been recognised by her elder lilin mother. Anyway, it's going to take me about fifteen minutes to fill out these forms, so you can wait on one of the benches if you'd like.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thankful for Finch's knowledge of, and apparent respect for, your demonic aunt, you walk over to one of the wooden benches at the edge of the room and take a seat. True to his word, [finch.name] takes just under fifteen minutes to work his way through the pile of forms, and once he's finished, he calls you back over to his desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.speech(Right, I just need your name and signature here, here, and here,)] he says, pointing to three different places on the forms. [finch.speech(Once you're done, I'll talk you through the rules and regulations.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Quickly skimming over the forms to make sure that you're not signing your life away by mistake, you then sign in the places that [finch.name] points to. Once you're done, the cat-boy files the papers away beneath his desk, before producing a little checklist, titled <i>'Slavery rules & regulations'</i>.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLAVERY_ADMINISTRATION_SLAVER_LICENSE_OBTAINED_RULES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[finch.speech(So, before you run off and try to enslave the first person you meet, you need to be aware of the basics,)] [finch.name] states, pointing down at the checklist in front of him. [finch.speech(First of all, slaves are meant to wear a piece of enchanted clothing in order to clearly designate them as someone else's property. Slave collars are most regularly used for this purpose, and can only be purchased from here, at the Slavery Administration building. Although some slave owners allow their slaves to work without wearing a piece of enslavement clothing, we strongly advise against this. Runaway slaves who don't have their collars on are almost impossible to track down without great expense, so if you decide to take theirs off, don't come crying to me when they run away!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Understood,)] you reply, nodding for Finch to continue.
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.speech(Now, you won't need to worry about this if you're only planning on buying and selling slaves, but if you're hoping to enslave people, then there are some <i>strict</i> limitations. You can only enslave two sorts of people; those who are willing, and those who have been marked for enslavement by Enforcers. Slave collars have a special enchantment in them that detects if the wearer falls into either one of those categories, so don't try and run around making just anyone into your slave!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(That makes sense,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.speech(Good. Now, assuming you're interested in enslaving people, the last thing you need to be aware of is what happens once you make your slave-to-be wear the enslavement clothing. As soon as you fit whatever clothing it may be into place, the collar's special enchantment will activate,)] [finch.name] says, grinning, [finch.speech(and if they're a suitable enslavement target, they'll be teleported right into the holding cells in this very building! Now, normally teleportation spells are limited to only the most powerful of arcane users, so you might be shocked the first time you see it!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(So I have to come here and pick up everyone I enslave?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.speech(That's right, but I'm sure someone as important as you can simply send a messenger to come and collect them from the comfort of your own home. Although this system is a little inconvenient for all involved, we had to implement it a few years ago to counteract some nasty illegal enslavement practices. With this new system, we're making sure that all new slaves go through the proper channels.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.Name] picks up the last piece of paper you signed and holds it out for you to take. [finch.speech(That's all there really is to it. With this license, you're able to buy and sell slaves in any manner you like. The only restriction is on enslavement, which, as I said, can only be done to those who are willing, or those who are wanted by the Enforcers. Oh, and on that last note, there's usually no point in trying to enslave any demons you run into, as Enforcers only sign off on an enslavement order for the most troublesome and destitute demons in the city. Any demon with even a shred of respectability could, for all any Enforcer knows, be a lilin's favoured son or daughter, and before they know it, they'd be the one ending up in my cells instead of the demon!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I see,)] you say, wondering if any demons prowling the alleyways of Dominion have been marked for enslavement.
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.speech(Normally, non-demons wouldn't even be permitted to own demonic slaves, but as you're related to Lilaya herself, I've gone ahead and marked your license as the extended coverage type, meaning that you'll get no trouble from any Enforcers if you do end up owning some demon slaves,)] Finch states, giving you a friendly wink before leaning back and crossing his arms. [finch.speech(One last thing; if you get soft and want to set your slave free, you're going to need a 'Freedom Certification' to do so. That's basically an official document that allows you to declare one of your slaves as being freed. Now, they don't come cheap, as we can't have criminals coming along to easily buy their convicted friends out of their punishment. If you can cough up enough flames, then you can buy them from me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Thanking him for explaining things to you, you put your new slaver license safely away, but before you're able to turn and leave, the cat-boy has some final words, [finch.speech(Now that you've got that license, I can sell you some slave collars if you'd like. I've also got a few more fun things in stock...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- SLAVE_FREEDOM_TALK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLAVE_FREEDOM_TALK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to know what sort of process you'd have to go through to set a slave free, you ask Finch if you're able to simply let your slaves go if you don't want them anymore.
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.speech(That's not how it works,)] the cat-boy replies, [finch.speech(If you let your slave go, they're still registered with us as being a slave, so if an Enforcer patrol bumps into them, they're going to have a collar clasped around their neck and returned to you, along with a bill for their time and effort. Anyway, unless you've managed to convince someone to enter into a willing slave contract, your slaves are going to be criminals or other scum. You really want to set people like that free?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Finch lets out a disapproving grunt as you reply by saying that it's a possibility, but despite his reaction, he tells you what you want to know, [finch.speech(Getting a slave freed requires you to go through the courts and get a Freedom Certification issued to the slave in question. Unless your slave's an important demon, that process is going to take at least a year to get through, and at the end of it you're more likely than not to have your request for your slave's freedom rejected. The state can't afford to be letting criminals back onto the streets all the time, can it? What would happen to society if that were to happen...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		While he's been explaining this to you, Finch has been repeatedly glancing over at a nearby dog-boy who's been loitering within earshot of your conversation. As this stranger turns around and leaves, Finch's final sentence trails off, and he lowers his voice and hisses, [finch.speech(You want to free your slaves? I can get all the paperwork done right here from behind my desk, <i>and</i> register everything as being one-hundred percent official and legit. Of course, skipping over the whole judicial process isn't exactly legal, but if you rat me out then you'll be even more screwed than I will be; you'll have Lilaya's mother, an elder lilin, pissed at you for bringing shame to her family...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that this is the only realistic way in which you'll be able to set any of your slaves free, you ask Finch how much it'll cost you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[finch.speech(You're a sharp one,)] Finch replies with a big grin on his face. Still keeping his voice down to barely louder than a whisper, he reveals, [finch.speech(I've got to grease some palms every time I do this, so these Freedom Certifications aren't going to come cheap. It's going to be at least [#SPECIAL_PARSE_0] flames, and that's not even including my cut. I'm not running a charity here, so you can add about fifty percent on top of that.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		At that moment, Finch's eyes flick over to track another stranger who's just entered the building, and he raises his voice to a normal volume to say, [finch.speech(Yeah, so anyway, just let me know if you want to buy anything. Is there anything else I can do for you?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLAVE_FREEDOM_TALK_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that you can now purchase Freedom Certifications from Finch, you wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SLAVE_FREEDOM_TALK_END_START_ACCOMMODATION_QUEST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that you can now purchase Freedom Certifications from Finch, you wonder whether you'd be able to convince any slaves to stay with you as your guest after freeing them. Of course, that would require Lilaya's permission to house guests in her mansion, so you make a mental note to bring that up with her before wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
