<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	
	<htmlContent tag="APE_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Ape-morphs tend to stay anywhere there is lush vegetation, towering trees, or rolling plains next to the former, and will mainly be found in the jungles and savannah in the south of Lilith's Realm; some larger varieties make their homes in the mountains. While uncommon, some tend to find their way to Dominion, often becoming lost and finding their way to areas of interest such as gambling dens and nightclubs. Rounded, furry ears, large round eyes, powerful bodies, and a lack of tail distinguish most ape-morphs from other morphs.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	<htmlContent tag="APE_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While the individual personalities of ape-morphs vary greatly from one individual to another, ape-morphs in general have a well-earned reputation for being curious, constantly seeking new knowledge, and an almost prepubescent temper. In the wild, ape-morphs live in troops, frollicking in the trees, rivers, and plains of the jungles and savannahs. Though they vary vastly in size and demeanor, most ape-morphs tend to stay close to their families, with only a small few individuals venturing out to cities or on their own adventures.
	</p>
	<p>
		Ape-morphs are split into a few distinct subspecies, the most common of which are chimpanzee-morphs who live in the jungles and savannahs of Dominion. They are distinguishable by their large, round ears, lack of a tail, and coarse solid fur. The largest ape-morphs, gorilla-morphs, inhabit the jungles and mountains of Dominion. Gorilla-morphs are by and far the largest primates in Dominion. They are known for their gigantic upper torsos, enormous arms, curved backs, and protuding asses. Between chimpanzee and gorilla-morphs in size, are the orangutan-morphs. Different from the rest of their ape cousins, organgutan-morphs tend to be docile in temprement; though younger adult males have a tendency toward forcibly loving the opposite sex of any species near them. Legends tell of a much rarer species, one which seems nearly human though possessing superhuman strength and abilities, with a prehensile tail other ape-morphs do not possess; these stories have yet to be proven true.
	</p>	
	<p>
		Like most other races, ape-morphs are greatly affected by arcane storms. However, due to the fact that many of them live far away from Dominion's epicentre of such storms, they typically only experience mild effects. Ape-morphs caught near enough to arcane lightning become extremely aggressive while their innate curiosity becomes extremely deviant; often they will force themselves upon much larger victims, their uncanny strength used to great effect. Many a survivor has told stories of being ravaged by an entire troop of horny ape-morphs during a storm. More than one has told the same story twice with a smile on their face.
	</p>
	<p>
		An ape-morph's offspring will be a mixture of ape-morphs and offspring of their partner's race.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</bookText>
