<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<bookText>
	
	<htmlContent tag="SALAMANDER_BASIC"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Salamander-morphs live in the thermal extremes of Lilith's Realm. Flame salamander-morphs generally roam near the desert and volcano to the south while their icy cousins keep to the mountains in the west. Reptilian eyes, frilled ears, and a bright flame or frosty aura at the tip of their tail are indicative of a salamander-morph.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<htmlContent tag="SALAMANDER_ADVANCED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		While the individual personalities of salamander-morphs vary greatly from one individual to another, most have a penchant for being wilful and competitive. Though not generally predatory towards others, any challenge made towards a salamander-morph will be met with extreme ardour more often than not.
	</p>
	<p>
		There are two distinct subspecies of salamander-morphs; the main difference lies at the end of their tails. Frost salamanders have small clouds of cold, arcane mist surrounding the tip of their tails. Flame salamander-morphs, unsurprisingly, have an arcane flame burning at the end of theirs. Similarly to elementals, both phenomenon are not harmful unless willed to be.
	</p>
	<p>
		Despite their geographical and physiological differences, members of both subspecies often occupy similar societal niches. Their resilience and independent nature generally lead most salamander-morphs to live off the land, though a decent number pursue careers as mercenaries.
	</p>
	<p>
		Salamander-morphs are often theorized to be natural conduits of the arcane due to their tails. Despite (or, perhaps, because of) this, they are just as susceptible to arcane storms as most other races. That being said, most rarely experience the full effects due to their large distance from the storms' epicentre in Dominion.
	</p>
	<p>
		A salamander-morph's offspring will be a mixture of salamander-morphs and offspring of their partner's race.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
</bookText>
