<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<!-- EXTERIOR -->

	<htmlContent tag="EXTERIOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Being built in an extremely imposing example of brutalist architecture, the vast structure before you is strikingly different from the usual residential buildings which Dominion is mostly comprised of. A wide courtyard, paved in drab, grey flagstones and cordoned off with chain bollards, separates the street on which you're standing from this unusual property. Looking up at the façade, which is made almost entirely out of sheets of reflective glass and thick pillars of grey concrete, you see that there's a sign bearing the words "Enforcer Headquarters, Blackhall'.
	</p>
	<p>
		As if the sign wasn't enough to reveal this establishment's purpose to any passersby, there are also a half-dozen or so groups of smartly-dressed
		#IF(game.getCurrentWeather()==WEATHER_MAGIC_STORM)
			 demon
		#ENDIF
		 Enforcers loitering about the courtyard, with several more standing guard at each of the three main entrances. While the signs beside two of these doorways inform you that they're for Enforcer use only, the third bears the words 'Public Inquiries, open 24/7'. If you had any sort of business to conduct here, then this would be the door for you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- CORRIDOR -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="CORRIDOR"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A series of doors line either side of this rather ordinary-looking corridor, each one marked with a different name and title. You scan each one for the name '[brax.name]' as you walk along, smiling in your most disarming manner at any enforcers that you pass along the way.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- ENTRANCE -->

	<htmlContent tag="ENTRANCE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		A pair of glass doors link the outside world to the small entrance hall that you find yourself standing in. There's a noticeboard hanging from a nearby wall, covered in posters and information leaflets of all kinds. Other than that, however, this room is completely empty, and you'll have to proceed through another set of internal doors if you wanted to enter the building proper.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- WAITING_AREA -->

	<htmlContent tag="WAITING_AREA"><![CDATA[
	#IF(pc.getCharactersEncountered().contains(candi.getId()))
		<p>
			Several rough-looking members of the local community are lounging about on the many low sofas littered around this waiting area. A reception desk is built into the left-hand wall, and you see Candi, the cat-girl bimbo, sitting behind it. She has long, bleach-blonde hair, a beautiful face that's been completely plastered in makeup, and a massive pair of G-cup breasts that threaten to spill out of her half-buttoned-up shirt at any moment. Her cute cat-like ears twitch this way and that as she stares into a little mirror on her desk, and you notice that she's busy applying a layer of bright pink lipstick to her plump lips.
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Several rough-looking members of the local community are lounging about on the many low sofas littered around this waiting area. A reception desk sits off to one side of the room, and you see a lesser cat-girl, wearing an enforcer's uniform, sitting behind it. She has long, bleach-blonde hair, a beautiful face that's been completely plastered in makeup, and a massive pair of G-cup breasts that threaten to spill out of her half-buttoned-up shirt at any moment. Her cute cat-like ears twitch this way and that as she stares into a little mirror on her desk, and you notice that she's busy applying a layer of bright pink lipstick to her plump, bimbo-like lips.
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	<p>
		The only other person you can see takes the form of a muscular horse-boy Enforcer, who's standing guard beside the door which leads to the rest of the building's interior.
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_accessToEnforcerHQ))
			 His watchful gaze sweeps the room, making sure that nobody is able to sneak past him.
		#ELSE
			 From the moment you entered the waiting area, he hasn't taken his eyes off of you, and you realise that there's absolutely no possibility of being able to sneak through the door he's guarding. If you wanted to get access to the HQ's interior, you'll have to negotiate with the bimbo cat-girl receptionist.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- GUARDED_DOOR -->

	<htmlContent tag="GUARDED_DOOR"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.isBraxMainQuestComplete())
		<p>
			You flash the pass that Candi gave to you at the horse-boy guard, but he refuses to step aside. [style.speechMasculine(Those passes aren't valid anymore, don't waste my time.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			It looks like he's not going to let you pass, and you don't really have any business back there anyway...
		</p>
	#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_accessToEnforcerHQ))
		<p>
			You flash the pass that Candi gave to you at the horse-boy guard, and, with a grunt, he steps aside to let you pass.
		</p>
		<p>
			 As you walk through the doors, you hear him muttering,  [style.speechMasculine(That slut's gonna get in trouble with [brax.name] again... Giving out passes like she does blowjobs...)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			As you walk up to the horse-boy guard, he crosses his arms and frowns at you. [style.speechMasculine(I don't know what you're thinking, but there's no way you're getting through here, understood? Unless you want to be thrown out, you'd better back off. Now.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			It looks like he means business, and it probably wouldn't be the smartest idea to start a fight in the middle of the Enforcer HQ. If you had any business with one of the enforcers here, you might be able to get a pass from the cat-girl receptionist, which would allow you to get past these guarded doors...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="GUARDED_DOOR_STEP_BACK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Realising that you'd stand no chance in a fight against all of the enforcers that would soon arrive as backup, you decide not to try and force your way through into the interior of the building. Agreeing to do as the horse-boy says, you step back into the waiting room...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- RECEPTION_DESK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_DESK"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.isBraxMainQuestComplete())
		#IF(!game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_seenBraxAfterQuest))
			<p>
				You walk over to Candi, smiling as you see her totally engrossed in the little mirror sitting on her desk. Curiously, there's another placard next to hers, and as you come to a halt in front of Candi, your eyes go wide as you read the words '[brax.name], Candi's assistant'.
			</p>
			<p>
				[pc.speech(Hi, Candi,)] you greet her, continuing to smile as she looks up from her mirror, [pc.speech(how are you and [brax.name] doing? I see his name here, but where is he?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[candi.speechNoEffects(Like, omigosh! Heya, I recognise you!)] she cries out, her voice bubbling with excitement. [candi.speechNoEffects(You, like, know my little pet? Come say hello [brax.name]!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Candi reaches down to tug on something, and you hear a familiar voice respond, [brax.speech(Candi, please, I don't wa-)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[brax.namePos] protest is cut off as Candi stands up, sharply yanking on what you now see to be a pink leash. [candi.speechNoEffects(Bad pet! Bad! You, like, have to do as I say! The chief said so, remember?!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Letting out another groan, [brax.name] crawls out from under Candi's desk and stands up to face you. A look of shock crosses his face, and he desperately pulls on his leash as he shouts out, [brax.speech(That's [pc.herHim]! Candi! That's the one who took the documents! Call the chie- ~Aargh!~)]
			</p>
			<p>
				[brax.namePos] leash is suddenly and violently yanked backwards, immediately interrupting his accusation and causing him to choke and splutter. Candi's face has gone bright red, and she looks absolutely furious as she starts to shout, [candi.speechNoEffects(Bad pet! Bad, bad, <b>bad</b>! How <i>dare</i> you treat a visitor like that! Like, [pc.sheIs] even a friend of yours, remember?! If you say <i>one more word</i>, I'm going to, like, get the ballgag out, and no more talking for a week!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				With [brax.name] suitably subdued, Candi turns back to face you. [candi.speechNoEffects(Like, I am soooo sorry! [brax.name] is kinda stupid, don't mind him! He gave away some kind of really important paper or something, and the chief said I could, like, have him as a pet. I even have, like, permission to punish him and stuff. Hey! You know what would be fun! How about you get to punish him for being so super mean to you?!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Candi finally stops talking, giving you a moment to process what's going on. It looks like [brax.name] got demoted for giving you that information about Arthur, and is now Candi's pet. She's far too stupid to understand what [brax.name] is trying to tell her, and you see a look of intense frustration cross over the unfortunate wolf-boy's face as his owner silences him.
			</p>
			<p>
				You could take up Candi's offer and have some fun with [brax.name] in her office. As you're deciding what to do, you notice a little cardboard box, marked '[brax.namePos] junk', sitting on a shelf behind Candi's desk.
				#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_braxTransformedPlayer))
					 The neck of a very familiar-looking bottle is poking out of the top, and an interesting idea runs through your mind...
				#ELSE
					 The neck of a delicate-looking bottle is poking out of the top, and, remembering Candi's warning about [brax.name] having a wolf-girl transformation potion, an interesting idea runs through your mind...
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			#IF(pc.isQuestCompleted(QUEST_LINE_SIDE_BUYING_BRAX))
				#IF(game.getSecondsPassed()-game.getDialogueFlags().candiSexTimer>60*60*12)
					<p>
						You walk over to the reception desk, and, coming to a halt just before it, you look down to see that the cat-girl secretary hasn't even noticed your approach. While at first it looked as though she was completely engrossed in doing her makeup, you now see that she has in fact angled the mirror in front of her in such a way that she's looking down into her own lap. Following her gaze, you see that her skirt has been pulled up, and her right hand is frantically rubbing away at her exposed pussy. The sound of your approach was masked by the lewd little 'oohs' and 'aahs' she's making, but as Candi leans back in her chair a little, she suddenly notices you standing before her.
					</p>
					<p>
						[candi.speechNoEffects(Oh, like, it's you again!)] she exclaims, quite clearly unperturbed by your presence as she continues brazenly masturbating while talking, [candi.speechNoEffects(Like, fuck, those lollipops really got me super horny and stuff, y'know? Like, I keep on masturbating, but it's not going away! Y'know, this is kinda partly your fault for giving these to me. You need to, like, get round here and help me out! Come on, you wanna fuck, don't you?)]
					</p>
					<p>
						After asking this, the horny bimbo cat-girl bites her lip, and, putting on the most pleading and desperate look she can muster, lets out a long, imploring whine. Gazing into your eyes, she begs, [candi.speechNoEffects(Like, please?!)]
					</p>
				#ELSE
					<p>
						You walk over to the reception desk, and, coming to a halt just before it, you look down to see that the cat-girl secretary hasn't even noticed your approach. She's completely engrossed in doing her makeup, and faint little 'oohs' and 'aahs' drift out her open mouth as she vacantly gazes into a little mirror that's sitting on her desk. Before you can say anything to get her attention, she reaches up to tuck a loose strand of bleach-blonde hair back behind her cat-like ears, and as she does so, she suddenly notices you standing before her.
					</p>
					<p>
						[candi.speechNoEffects(Oh, hey, like, you're back!)] she happily exclaims, [candi.speechNoEffects(Thanks for, like, helping me to cum! Y'know, I'm feeling all super duper and normal again now, but I know it's only gonna be, like, a half-day at most before my pussy starts gettin' wet and all I can think of is sex! You gotta come back and help me out again when that happens, ok?)]
					</p>
					<p>
						Flashing you a big smile, Candi then turns back to her mirror and continues with her never-ending quest to get her makeup just right...
					</p>
				#ENDIF
			#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_bimbofiedBrax))
				<p>
					You walk over to Candi, smiling as you see her totally engrossed in the little mirror sitting on her desk. As you come to a halt in front of her, you look down over the top of the desk to see [brax.name] furiously masturbating on the floor.
				</p>
				<p>
					[pc.speech(Hi again, Candi,)] you say, continuing to smile as she looks up from her mirror, [pc.speech(it looks like [brax.namePos] having fun down there!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[candi.speechNoEffects(Like, omigosh! Heya!)] she cries out, her voice bubbling with excitement, [candi.speechNoEffects(and, like, eugh! I know right?! [brax.Name], like, won't stop masturbating, even after I've told [brax.him] to like a million times! I'm, like, far too busy to punish [brax.him] properly as well!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					As she speaks, Candi reaches down to tug [brax.namePos] [brax.arms] away from [brax.her] [brax.pussy], causing the horny bimbo to cry out,
					 [brax.speechNoEffects(Awww! Candi! Please! I, like, <i>need</i> this! You gotta let m- ~Aah!~)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[brax.NamePos] pathetic whining is cut off as Candi stands up, sharply yanking on [brax.his] pink leash. [candi.speechNoEffects(Like, try to control yourself pet! Lucky for you, your super best friend is, like, here to play!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[brax.name] immediately jumps to [brax.his] feet, and as [brax.he] catches sight of you, [brax.he] lets out a delighted squeal, [brax.speechNoEffects(Yes! Heya! Please, like, can we play together?! I'm, like, thinking of you all the time and stuff!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					As [brax.name] drops [brax.his] hands back down to [brax.her] groin and starts masturbating, Candi turns back to face you. [candi.speechNoEffects(You'd be, like, doin' me a huuuge favour if you'd, like, help out with [brax.namePos] horniness! How about, like, you take [brax.him] into my office, and, like, give [brax.him] a good fucking?!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					You could take up Candi's offer and have some fun with [brax.name] in her office, or walk away and leave [brax.name] alone...
				</p>
			#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_feminisedBrax))
				<p>
					You walk over to Candi, smiling as you see her totally engrossed in the little mirror sitting on her desk. As you come to a halt in front of her, you read the words on the placard next to hers; '[brax.name], Candi's assistant'.
				</p>
				<p>
					[pc.speech(Hi again, Candi,)] you greet her, continuing to smile as she looks up from her mirror, [pc.speech(how are you and [brax.name] doing?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[candi.speechNoEffects(Like, omigosh! Heya!)] she cries out, her voice bubbling with excitement. [candi.speechNoEffects([brax.namePos] been, like, super disobedient! [brax.He], like, refused to suck my friend's cock earlier! Can you believe that?!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					As she speaks, Candi reaches down to tug on something, and you hear a familiar whimper in response, [brax.speech(Sorry, Cand-)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[brax.namePos] apology is cut off as Candi stands up, sharply yanking on [brax.his] pink leash. [candi.speechNoEffects(Like, come on pet! Stand up and say hello to your friend again!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[brax.name] obediently crawls out from under Candi's desk and stands up to face you. [brax.speech(Hello...)]
				</p>
				<p>
					With [brax.name] displaying an acceptable level of submission, Candi turns back to face you. [candi.speechNoEffects(Hey, like, [brax.name] still hasn't been punished for disobeying me earlier! How about, like, you punish [brax.him] for me?!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					You could take up Candi's offer and have some fun with [brax.name] in her office, or walk away and leave [brax.name] alone. As you're making up your mind, you take another look at Candi, wondering if you could ask her to make [brax.name] a little more like her...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					You walk over to Candi, smiling as you see her totally engrossed in the little mirror sitting on her desk. As you come to a halt in front of her, you read the words on the placard next to hers; '[brax.name], Candi's assistant'.
				</p>
				<p>
					[pc.speech(Hi again, Candi,)] you greet her, continuing to smile as she looks up from her mirror, [pc.speech(how are you and [brax.name] doing?)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[candi.speechNoEffects(Like, omigosh! Heya!)] she cries out, her voice bubbling with excitement. [candi.speechNoEffects([brax.namePos] been, like, super disobedient! [brax.He], like, refused to lick my shoes clean earlier! Can you believe that?!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					As she speaks, Candi reaches down to tug on something, and you hear a familiar whimper in response, [brax.speech(Sorry, Cand-)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[brax.namePos] apology is cut off as Candi stands up, sharply yanking on [brax.his] pink leash. [candi.speechNoEffects(Like, come on pet! Stand up and say hello to your friend again!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					[brax.name] reluctantly crawls out from under Candi's desk and stands up to face you. [brax.speech(Eugh, not you aga- Aah!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					Candi yanks on [brax.namePos] leash once again, before starting to furiously scold [brax.him]. After a few minutes, she's forced [brax.name] to apologise to you, and turns back to face you. [candi.speechNoEffects(Hey, like, I'm pretty sure you'll agree that [brax.name] <i>really</i> needs to be punished again! How about, like, you take [brax.him] into my office and show [brax.him] how to behave?!)]
				</p>
				<p>
					You could take up Candi's offer and have some fun with [brax.name] in her office, or walk away and leave [brax.name] alone.
					#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_braxTransformedPlayer))
						 As you're deciding what to do, you notice a little cardboard box, marked '[brax.namePos] junk', sitting on a shelf behind Candi's desk. The neck of a very familiar-looking bottle is poking out of the top, and an interesting idea runs through your head...
					#ELSE
						 As you're deciding what to do, you notice a little cardboard box, marked '[brax.namePos] junk', sitting on a shelf behind Candi's desk. The neck of a delicate-looking bottle is poking out of the top, and, remembering Candi's warning about [brax.name] having a wolf-girl transformation potion, an interesting idea runs through your head...
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		<p>
			You walk over to the reception desk, and, coming to a halt just before it, you look down to see that the cat-girl secretary hasn't even noticed your approach. She's completely engrossed in doing her makeup, and faint little 'oohs' and 'aahs' drift out her open mouth as she vacantly gazes into a little mirror that's sitting on her desk. Every now and then, she has to tuck loose strands of bleach-blonde hair back behind her cat-like ears, interrupting her sighs with an annoyed tutting sound each time she does so.
		</p>
		<p>
			In amongst her messy collection of beauty products scattered all over the desk, you see a little placard with the name 'Candi' on it.
			 It seems as though Candi is completely oblivious to the world outside of her mirror, so you'll need to raise your voice in order to get her attention if you wanted to ask anything of her.
		</p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(DialogueFlagValue.accessToEnforcerHQ))
			<p>
				<i>You've already got a pass from Candi, so there's no point interrupting her again...</i>
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_DESK_PUNISH_BRAX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sure thing, Candi, I can punish [brax.name] for you!)] you respond, stepping around to the other side of the desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Thanks, I've got, like, loads of work and stuff to do, so you're really helping me out here!)] Candi replies, handing you [brax.namePos] pink leash as she returns to applying makeup in her little mirror.
	</p>
	<p>
		With a tug, you get [brax.name] to follow you into Candi's little office. Closing the door behind you, you turn to face the [brax.race], smiling as you unclip the leash from [brax.his] collar.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I bet you're pretty angry right now, huh [brax.name]?)] you tease, laughing as [brax.he] lets out a low growl. [pc.speech(You'd better quiet down, unless you want Candi to know how bad you've been!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[brax.Name] shuffles [brax.his] feet, looking down at the ground as [brax.he] lets out an annoyed grunt. Stepping forwards, you take hold of [brax.his] shoulders, and with a forceful shove, you push [brax.him] down onto [brax.his] knees before you.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Good [brax.boy]! Now, time for your punishment!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_DESK_PUNISH_BREE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sure thing, Candi, I can punish [brax.name] for you!)] you respond, stepping around to the other side of the desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Thanks, I've got, like, loads of work and stuff to do, so you're really helping me out here!)] Candi replies, handing you [brax.namePos] pink leash as she returns to applying makeup in her little mirror.
	</p>
	<p>
		With a tug, you get [brax.name] to follow you into Candi's little office. Closing the door behind you, you turn to face the [brax.race], smiling as you unclip the leash from [brax.his] collar.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(You're going to do as you're told, aren't you [brax.name]?)] you tease, laughing as [brax.he] lets out a meek little whimper. [pc.speech(Don't worry, I'll be sure to let Candi know how good you've been!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Knowing what's expected of [brax.herHim], [brax.name] drops to [brax.her] knees before you. Stepping forwards, you reach down to stroke the top of [brax.her] head.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Good [brax.girl]! Now, time for your punishment!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_DESK_PUNISH_BRANDI"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sure thing, Candi, I can punish [brax.name] for you!)] you respond, stepping around to the other side of the desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Thanks, I've got, like, loads of work and stuff to do, so you're really helping me out here!)] Candi replies, handing you [brax.namePos] pink leash as she returns to applying makeup in her little mirror.
	</p>
	<p>
		With a tug, you get [brax.name] to follow you into Candi's little office. Closing the door behind you, you turn to face the [brax.race], smiling as you unclip the leash from [brax.his] collar.
	</p>
	<p>
		[brax.Name] immediately drops to [brax.her] knees, shuffling forwards as [brax.she] begs, [brax.speechNoEffects(Please! I, like, <i>need</i> to be punished! Please use me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(What a good [brax.girl]!)] you say, grinning as [brax.he] lets out a desperate, hungry whimper. [pc.speech(Seeing as you asked so nicely, I'll give you what you want!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="RECEPTION_DESK_PUNISHED_BY_BRAX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sure thing, Candi, I can punish [brax.name] for you!)] you respond, stepping around to the other side of the desk.
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Thanks, I've got, like, loads of work and stuff to do, so you're really helping me out here!)] Candi replies, handing you [brax.namePos] pink leash as she returns to applying makeup in her little mirror.
	</p>
	<p>
		With a tug, you get [brax.name] to follow you into Candi's little office. Closing the door behind you, you turn to face the [brax.race], smiling as you unclip the leash from [brax.his] collar.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I bet you're pretty angry right now, huh [brax.name]?)] you tease, laughing as [brax.he] lets out a low growl. [pc.speech(Mmm, you want to be the one punishing me, don't you?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[brax.speech(If I wasn't on the verge of being enslaved, I'd give you a hard fuck to teach you a lesson right now!)] [brax.name] growls as [brax.he] steps up to you.
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a playful giggle, you trace [pc.a_finger] over [brax.his] chest. [pc.speech(Well, I won't tell if you won't... Or is Candi's pet too submissive to try anyth- eek!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Obviously having had enough of your teasing, and with a clear invitation to fuck you, [brax.name] grabs you by the shoulders and throws you to the floor. You let out a delighted [pc.moan] as [brax.he] manhandles you into a doggystyle position. Leaning down over your back, [brax.name] growls into your [pc.ear], [brax.speech(Remember, bitch, <i>I'm</i> the real alpha here!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="START_SEX_CANDI"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to leave Candi after she's asked you for help, you tell her that you'll sort her problem out for her, before stepping around behind the reception counter. Letting out an excited whine, the horny cat-girl immediately leaps to her feet, and after placing a little 'Be back soon' sign on the desk, she grabs you by the [pc.hand] and pulls you through the nearby door into her small office.
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Oh yeah, like, fuck me, right now!)] she demands, slamming the door closed before leaping forwards into your [pc.arms]... 
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_SEX_CANDI -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_SEX_CANDI"><![CDATA[
	#IF(candi.isSatisfiedFromLastSex())
		<p>
			With a deeply satisfied sigh, Candi moans, [candi.speechNoEffects(~Mmm!~ Fuck, that was, like, sooo good... I, like, super needed that.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the two of you gather your things and head out of her office. Moving back around to the correct side of the desk, you prepare to continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			With an immensely frustrated sigh, Candi moans, [candi.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Fuck, that was, like, super not satisfying! I, like, need someone to finish me off!)]
		</p>
		<p>
			With that, the still-desperately-horny cat-girl grabs her clothes and runs off out of the office, clearly with nothing on her mind but finding someone willing to help her orgasm. Collecting your things, you soon follow her out of the office, and prepare to continue on your way...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- BUYING_BRAX_INITIAL -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BUYING_BRAX_INITIAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As [brax.name] is now registered as a slave, you realise that this means you'd potentially be able to own [brax.herHim], if only you can convince Candi to sell [brax.herHim] to you. With this on your mind, you inform the bimbo cat-girl that you're in possession of a slaver's license, and ask how much she'd be willing to consider selling [brax.name] for.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_bimbofiedBrax))
			Upon hearing you ask this, the bimbo wolf-girl exclaims in a bubbly voice, [brax.speechNoEffects(Hey, like, you wanna be my owner? That'd be kinda fun! I'm, like, desperate to get fucked in some place other than behind this desk, y'know?)]
			</p>
			<p>
			[candi.speechNoEffects(Like, you don't get to decide who owns you, bitch!)] Candi exclaims, giving [brax.namePos] leash a sharp yank before continuing, [candi.speechNoEffects(So, you wanna buy my little slave, huh? She's, like, apparently super into you already...)]
		#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_feminisedBrax))
			Upon hearing you ask this, the wolf-girl mutters, [brax.speech(C-Candi, please, you can't sell me... Who knows what [pc.she]'ll do to me?)]
			</p>
			<p>
			[candi.speechNoEffects(Like, you don't get to decide what I can and can't do, bitch!)] Candi exclaims, giving [brax.namePos] leash a sharp yank before continuing, [candi.speechNoEffects(So, you wanna buy my little slave, huh? Even though she's, like, pretty disobedient and stuff?)]
		#ELSE
			Upon hearing you ask this, the wolf-boy angrily shouts, [brax.speech(You seriously think you can just buy me?! Candi, tell [pc.herHim] to fuck off alread- ~Aargh!~)]
			</p>
			<p>
			[candi.speechNoEffects(Like, shut up, bitch!)] Candi exclaims, yanking on [brax.namePos] leash to quieten him down. [candi.speechNoEffects(So, you wanna buy my little slave, huh? Even though he's, like, super disobedient and stuff?)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Reaffirming that you would indeed like to buy [brax.name] from her, you again ask how much she'd be willing to sell [brax.herHim] for. Leaning back in her chair, Candi lets out a long sigh, before saying, [candi.speechNoEffects(Like, I dunno... I mean, it's kinda annoying having to care for a slave, but, like, it's also kinda fun to get [brax.herHim] to do what I say... I'll tell ya what; I'll, like, really think about if I wanna sell [brax.herHim] to you, but you gotta do something for me first.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After asking Candi what that 'something' would be, she smiles and places a small bag of coins on the desk in front of her, before saying, [candi.speechNoEffects(I, like, ordered some perfume and stuff from this nice succubus lady a week or something ago, and, like, I just haven't had the time to go and pick it up yet, y'know? You just, like, take this money, go pay for my perfume, and bring it back to me, and I'll, like, let you know if [brax.name] is for sale or not. Deal?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_kateIntroduced))
			As it sounds like an easy enough task, you agree to do as Candi asks, and after taking the bag of flames, you're informed that the perfume is waiting at none other than Kate's shop, 'Succubi's Secrets', over in the Shopping Arcade.
		#ELSE
			As it sounds like an easy enough task, you agree to do as Candi asks, and after taking the bag of flames, you're informed that the shop at which the perfume is waiting is named 'Succubi's Secrets', and is located in one corner of the Shopping Arcade.
		#ENDIF
		 Telling Candi that you'll have no trouble retrieving her perfume for her, you wonder if you should head off to the Shopping Arcade right away, or hang around here for a little while longer...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- BUYING_BRAX_PERFUME_DELIVERY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BUYING_BRAX_PERFUME_DELIVERY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Telling Candi that you've done as she asked, you place the bottles of perfume on the desk before her. The cat-girl's eyes light up as she sees what it is you're delivering to her, and in a happy voice, she exclaims, [candi.speechNoEffects(Wohoo! Like, that succubus lady who works there really knows her stuff! She knew, like, exactly what brands I was talking about! This is, like, the real good stuff, y'know?!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reminding Candi about her end of the deal, you ask her if she's decided whether she'll sell [brax.name] to you or not. Putting the bottles of perfume away beneath her desk, the cat-girl straightens back up and smiles at you as she answers, [candi.speechNoEffects(Like, I was thinking no, but after you've gone and got me these super duper perfumes, there's, like, no way I could refuse! I'll sell [brax.herHim] to you, but I gotta think about how much [brax.sheIs] worth...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_bimbofiedBrax))
			[brax.speechNoEffects(So, like, I'm gonna belong to [pc.herHim] soon?)] [brax.name] asks, playfully eyeing you up and down before suggestively winking at you.
			</p>
			<p>
			[candi.speechNoEffects(Yeah, like, probably,)] Candi answers, [candi.speechNoEffects(I gotta, like, think about how much to sell you for first, y'know?)]
		#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_feminisedBrax))
			[brax.speechNoEffects(Y-You're really going to sell me?)] [brax.name] asks, glancing worriedly in your direction.
			</p>
			<p>
			[candi.speechNoEffects(Yeah, like, probably,)] Candi answers, [candi.speechNoEffects(I gotta, like, think about how much to sell you for first, y'know?)]
		#ELSE
			[brax.speechNoEffects(You can't be serious!)] [brax.name] shouts, [brax.speech(You can't sell me! And to <i>[pc.herHim]</i>, of all people?! The chief will never allow- ~Eugh!~)]
			</p>
			<p>
			[candi.speechNoEffects(Shut up already! Fuck! You're, like, the worst fuckin' slave ever! I'm gonna be glad to be rid of you!)] Candi screeches, yanking harshly on [brax.namePos] leash to shut [brax.herHim] up. Glaring angrily at [brax.herHim], she then continues, [candi.speechNoEffects(And the chief, like, had all your papers signed to me personally, so, like, if I wanna sell you, that's up to me! Now, like, try to be a good bitch for once and stay quiet while I, like, think about how much to sell you for!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning back towards you, Candi then says, [candi.speechNoEffects(So, um, I'm gonna need some time to think. If you're really serious about buying my bitch here, then I'm gonna need you to prove it. While I'm thinkin' about what to charge ya, I want you to do something for me, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Realising that you have little choice but to do as she asks, you agree to help Candi once again, and ask her what it is she needs you to do. Glancing around to make sure that nobody else is nearby, the bimbo cat-girl leans forwards over her desk, and in an overly-dramatic manner, places a finger over her lips and makes a shushing noise, before whispering, [candi.speechNoEffects(You, like, can't tell anyone about this, ok, but, like, I overheard some talk about these extra special lollipops being confiscated up in the Harpy Nests. I, um, really love sucking on things like that, so you're gonna, like, go and fetch them for me, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You almost put a quick end to Candi's entire plan as you point out that the Enforcers are unlikely to simply hand over contraband lollipops to a member of the public, but after letting out a particularly long 'umming' noise, she exclaims, [candi.speechNoEffects(Oh, you can just use the super secret password that, like, only enforcers are allowed to know! Just tell them it's a 'priority thunder', and then they'll know you must be a friend! Lucky I'm so smart I could think of that for you, huh? So anyway, go up to those Harpy Nests, and, like, tell them that the 'contraband lollipops' are needed here at the enforcer headquarters for, um, testing or something, I dunno, you'll think of something.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After getting Candi's assurance that she'll have put a price on [brax.name] by the time you return with these lollipops, you wonder if you should head on up to the Harpy Nests right away, or do something else here first...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- BUYING_BRAX_LOLLIPOP_DELIVERY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BUYING_BRAX_LOLLIPOP_DELIVERY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Placing the box down on the desk before Candi, you tell her that it contains the contraband lollipops she was after. Although you relay the warning that the dog-boy Enforcer gave you about the lollipops containing a dangerous, permanent aphrodisiac, the bimbo cat-girl doesn't seem to take much notice, and dismisses the message with a wave of her hand, [candi.speechNoEffects(Yeah, yeah, dangerous lollipops, sure, like, whatever.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Reminding her that she'd promised to put a price on [brax.name] by the time you returned with these lollipops, you ask Candi how much she's willing to sell the [brax.race] for. Stopping half-way through impatiently opening the box, Candi sighs and says, [candi.speechNoEffects(Yeah, like, I really tried to think hard, y'know, but I just don't think I can put a price on [brax.herHim]... Maybe I can't sell [brax.herHim] after all?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		After expressing your displeasure at having the cat-girl go back on her word, and throwing out the casual observation that she would get into a lot of trouble if it was known that she'd obtained these lollipops for her own personal use, you once again ask Candi what price she's going to put on [brax.name]. This time, with the thought of getting into trouble over these lollipops clearly in her head, she says, [candi.speechNoEffects(Well, like, I don't think I could, um, ask for flames for [brax.herHim]... There is one thing I'd be, like, willing to trade [brax.herHim] for, though. There was this super rare, super exclusive, limited-edition set of lipsticks put out by, like, the best brand out there a few months ago, right? Like, obviously, they were all bought by super rich demons and stuff, but I heard from a friend's cousin's girlfriend that there's still one set for sale over in the Shopping Arcade. You, like, get that for me, and I'll trade you [brax.name] for it.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Finally having got a price set on [brax.namePos] head, you ask Candi where exactly this lipstick set is for sale, and how you're supposed to tell it apart from any others.
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Well, like, I heard it's being sold in that 'Ralph's Snacks' place, but you, like, have to ask for it all special-like and stuff, y'know? It's not displayed to the public. Oh, and the set's called 'A Hundred Kisses', so you just need to ask for that, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Agreeing to retrieve this special lipstick set in order to trade it for [brax.name], you wonder if you should head over to 'Ralph's Snacks' right away, or do something else first...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	<!-- BUYING_BRAX_LIPSTICK_DELIVERY -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="BUYING_BRAX_LIPSTICK_DELIVERY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to finally become the owner of [brax.name], you place the lipstick set 'A Hundred Kisses', down on the desk in front of Candi. Seeing what it is you've brought her, the bimbo cat-girl lets out an excited squeal, [candi.speechNoEffects(~Aah!~ Like, no way! You actually got it! I, like, totally can't even!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Bouncing up and down in excitement, Candi reaches forwards to take the box, but, not wanting to hand it over until you know that she's going to keep her end of the bargain, you pull it away from her. Responding to her protestations with the simple demand that she produce the paperwork for signing over [brax.name], you soon manage to get her to do as you ask. Once the correct forms for a slave transfer are laid out before you, you allow Candi to take the lipsticks.
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_bimbofiedBrax))
			[brax.speechNoEffects(So, like, I'm getting you as my new owner?)] [brax.name] asks, biting her lip and batting her eyelids at you.
		#ELSEIF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_feminisedBrax))
			[brax.speechNoEffects(So... Y-You're going to be the one owning me now?)] [brax.name] asks, nervously shuffling her feet as she wonders how you're going to be treating her.
		#ELSE
			[brax.speechNoEffects(I can't believe this!)] [brax.name] exclaims, [brax.speech(<i>[pc.SheIs]</i> going to be my... my <i>owner</i>?! ~Eugh!~)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Responding in the affirmative, you sign the papers laid out in front of you, before asking Candi to do the same. Despite all that you've done for her, she seems very reluctant to go through with it, and it takes some pointed reminders of her promises to finally get her to sign off on the transfer. Being infused with a special arcane enchantment, the documents immediately react to both party's signatures, and with a bright purple flash, the enslavement collar around [brax.namePos] next activates, teleporting [brax.herHim] to the slaver administration building's holding cells.
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Well, like, there ya go,)] candi pouts, clearly upset at having lost her slave, [candi.speechNoEffects(I guess these lipsticks are, like, pretty good, but I feel like you cheated me outta something!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Not wanting an enforcer with a grudge on your back, you remind Candi that you also retrieved her perfume, as well as the box of contraband lollipops, and that by all accounts it was a fair deal. As you mention this, her eyes suddenly light up, and she happily exclaims, [candi.speechNoEffects(Oh, that's right! I, like, forgot about those! I was saving them for when this happened to make me feel better!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Before you can even think about stopping her, the bimbo cat-girl reaches down beneath her desk, and, producing a glowing-pink lollipop, she wraps her plump lips around it and starts sucking. Immediately, you see her cheeks flush red, and with complete indifference to your presence before her, she drops her hands down between her legs, before pulling her skirt up and reaching down into her thong to start masturbating. 
	</p>
	<p>
		[candi.speechNoEffects(Fuck, like, the<i>sh</i>e thing<i>sh</i> are pretty good,)] she slurps around the lollipop in her mouth, before looking up into your eyes and pleading, [candi.speechNoEffects(I'm <i>sh</i>o horny! Like, plea<i>sh</i>e! Come round here and fuck me!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With any animosity towards you seemingly forgotten, Candi continues desperately pleading for you to fuck her, and you wonder if you should take her up on her offer, or simply take your leave and see to the arrangements for your new slave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>

	
	
</dialogue>
