<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<dialogue>

	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		At the far end of the atrium, a long wooden counter has been set into the wall. A sign hanging above this opening reads 'Epona's Pregnancy Roulette', and, standing behind the desk, you see a brown-haired horse girl. As you approach, the horse-girl catches your eye, and, beckoning you over, she calls out, [epona.speech(Hey there! You got a moment?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Deciding to see what it is this she wants, you walk up to the counter, and as you come to a halt before her, the horse-girl beams at you in delight. [epona.speech(Hello there! I haven't seen you around here before. Are you interested in pregnancy at all? Y'know, getting knocked up, knocking some fertile sluts up, all that good stuff?)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_NO_FETISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Maybe. What's this about?)] you ask.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Well, to keep it brief, the name's Epona, and I'm the one in charge of our special game, 'Pregnancy Roulette'!)] Epona happily explains. [epona.speech(Basically, if you pay the buy-in of ten thousand flames, you can join five other breeders in trying to knock a volunteer up, or, if you'd rather be the one to get preggers, you can put in the same buy-in and guess which of the six studs is gonna be the father of your kids!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_PREGNANCY_FETISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You feel your heart start to race at the mention of getting bred, and, unable to contain your enthusiasm, you blurt out, [pc.speech(Yes! You mean this is a game about getting knocked up?! Can I have a go?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Haha! You got a thing for being a Mommy, huh? Well, to keep it brief, the name's Epona, and I'm the one in charge of our special game, 'Pregnancy Roulette'!)] Epona happily explains. [epona.speech(Basically, if you pay the buy-in of ten thousand flames, you can join five other breeders in trying to knock a volunteer up, or, if you'd rather be the one to get preggers, you can put in the same buy-in and guess which of the six studs is gonna be the father of your kids! I'm guessing you're going to be more interested in that second option.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_IMPREGNATION_FETISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You feel your heart start to race at the mention of impregnation, and, unable to contain your enthusiasm, you blurt out, [pc.speech(Yes! You mean this is a game about knocking people up?! Can I have a go?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Haha! You got a thing for making Mommys, huh? Well, to keep it brief, the name's Epona, and I'm the one in charge of our special game, 'Pregnancy Roulette'!)] Epona happily explains, [epona.speech(Basically, if you pay the buy-in of ten thousand flames, you can join five other breeders in trying to knock a volunteer up, or, if you'd rather be the one to get preggers, you can put in the same buy-in and guess which of the six studs is gonna be the father of your kids! I'm guessing you're going to be more interested in that first option.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_BOTH_FETISH"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You feel your heart start to race at the mention of breeding, and, unable to contain your enthusiasm, you blurt out, [pc.speech(Yes! You mean this is a game all about breeding?! Can I have a go?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Haha! You got a thing for pregnancies, huh? Well, to keep it brief, the name's Epona, and I'm the one in charge of our special game, 'Pregnancy Roulette'!)] Epona happily explains. [epona.speech(Basically, if you pay the buy-in of ten thousand flames, you can join five other breeders in trying to knock a volunteer up, or, if you'd rather be the one to get preggers, you can put in the same buy-in and guess which of the six studs is gonna be the father of your kids!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ten thousand flames? That's a lot more expensive than the other games in here,)] you observe.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Yeah, well, this is kind of the premium game here in the Gambling Den. But with a big buy-in comes the chance of a big reward! If you get a girl pregnant, you win double your money back! Oh, and if you're the one getting knocked up, and you guess the father correctly, you win fifty thousand flames! Just let me know if you're interested, or want me to go over the rules with you.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ok, thanks, Epona,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Oh, and I almost forgot!)] Epona exclaims, [epona.speech(I've got a little customer loyalty thing going. Basically, each time you have a go at my game, I'll give you a stamp. Collect six stamps, and you can take me for a ride!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Epona steps back from the counter, before laughing and pulling her skirt up to flash her black panties at you. Looking down at the sudden movement, you see the unmistakable bulge of a huge horse-cock between her legs.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Haha!)] Epona laughs, [epona.speech(I've got the full package down here, so you get to choose whether you're the one riding me, or I'm the one riding you!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Epona lets her skirt fall back down to cover her panties, and steps forwards to lean on the counter. [epona.speech(So, just let me know if you want to play!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		At the far end of the atrium, a long wooden counter has been set into the wall. A sign hanging above this opening reads 'Epona's Pregnancy Roulette', and, standing behind the desk, you see the sign's namesake waiting for another game to start. As you walk towards the counter, Epona notices you and calls out, [epona.speech(Heya, [pc.name]!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_EPONA_IMPREGNATED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		At the far end of the atrium, a long wooden counter has been set into the wall. A sign hanging above this opening reads 'Epona's Pregnancy Roulette', and, standing behind the desk, you see the sign's namesake waiting for another game to start. As you walk towards the counter, Epona notices you and calls out, [epona.speech(Ah, [pc.name]! Look! Look!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		As you walk up to the counter to find out what it is Epona wants you to see, the horse-girl steps back and points down at her stomach. Looking down at the horse-girl's tummy, you see that she's sporting a round, pregnant bump. She lets out a little laugh as she sees you looking down at her stomach, and starts stroking her belly as she happily sighs, [epona.speech(Look what you did... Isn't it fantastic? I'm going to be a Mommy...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You can't help but smile as you see how pleased Epona is, and spend the next few minutes leaning over the counter to stroke her tummy while listening to her tale of how happy she was when she found out she'd been impregnated by you. Soon enough, however, Epona reminds you that she's still at work, and, as you step back from the counter, she sighs once more, [epona.speech(So, just let me know if you want to play a game of Pregnancy Roulette. I bet you want to share your potent seed with all the girls...)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<!-- Responses: -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_GREETING_UTIL_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having now been introduced to Epona, you wonder if you should take up her offer of paying to join a game of pregnancy roulette, or instead do something else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_GREETING_UTIL_PREG_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having seen that Epona is pregnant with your child, you now wonder if you should take up her offer of paying to join a game of pregnancy roulette, or instead do something else...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EPONA_START_SEX_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I think it's time I cash those stamps in,)] you say, grinning at Epona.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Yes! I thought you'd never ask!)] the horse-girl eagerly replies, before stepping to one side and lifting up the counter-top. [epona.speech(Come around here, we can do this in the back room. Oh, and are you wanting to ride me, or shall I take charge?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'm going to be the one in charge,)] you reply, stepping around behind the counter before moving up next to Epona and giving her [epona.ass+] a firm squeeze.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(~Mmm!~ Excellent! Right this way!)] the horse-girl squeals, placing a 'Be back soon' sign on the counter, before quickly leading you towards a door marked 'Staff Room'. Hurriedly opening it and stepping inside, Epona pulls you after her, and you suddenly find yourself standing in a rather plain-looking staff room, furnished with a couple of leather sofas and a low table.
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning to face you, Epona leans in and kisses you hotly on the lips, before pulling back and moaning, [epona.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! Now come fuck me!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EPONA_START_SEX_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I was wondering if I could get those stamps traded in,)] you say, smiling at Epona.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Yes! I thought you'd never ask!)] the horse-girl eagerly replies, before stepping to one side and lifting up the counter-top. [epona.speech(Come around here, we can do this in the back room. Oh, and are you wanting to ride me, or shall I take charge?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(If it's ok with you, could you take charge?)] you ask, stepping around behind the counter before moving up next to Epona.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Of course! Don't you worry, I'll take you for a real good ride! Right this way!)] the horse-girl says, placing a 'Be back soon' sign on the counter, before quickly leading you towards a door marked 'Staff Room'. Hurriedly opening it and stepping inside, Epona dominantly pulls you after her, and you suddenly find yourself standing in a rather plain-looking staff room, furnished with a couple of leather sofas and a low table.
	</p>
	<p>
		Turning to face you, Epona leans in and kisses you hotly on the lips, before pulling back and moaning, [epona.speech(~Mmm!~ Yes! I hope you're ready for a good, hard fucking!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EPONA_POST_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Fuck... That was great...)] Epona sighs, stepping back from you and starting to clean herself up as she gets ready to return to work.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yeah, that was great,)] you reply, following Epona's lead as you start to get your things in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Well, back to work for me. Remember, if you get another six stamps, we can do this again,)] Epona says, winking at you as she holds the door open.
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping through the open doorway, you quickly move back out into the gambling hall proper, before turning around to face Epona behind the counter. The horse-girl throws you a knowing smile, before leaning forwards and sighing, [epona.speech(If you've still got some energy left, just let me know if you want to do a game of pregnancy roulette.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="EPONA_POST_SEX_NO_ORGASM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Aww... You didn't even satisfy me...)] Epona sighs, stepping back from you and starting to clean herself up as she gets ready to return to work.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Maybe next time,)] you reply, following Epona's lead as you start to get your things in order.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Well, back to work for me. Remember, if you get another six stamps, we can do this again,)] Epona says, winking at you as she holds the door open.
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping through the open doorway, you quickly move back out into the gambling hall proper, before turning around to face Epona behind the counter. The horse-girl throws you a knowing smile, before leaning forwards and sighing, [epona.speech(If you've still got some energy left, just let me know if you want to do a game of pregnancy roulette.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_RULES"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting some clarification on how pregnancy roulette works, you ask, [pc.speech(What are the rules for this game of yours?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Well, it's pretty simple, really!)] Epona happily responds. [epona.speech(If you're looking to be one of the breeders, you first need to place a buy-in of ten thousand flames. After that, you join five others in trying to knock a volunteer up. I roll a dice to see in what order the breeders go, and then once you've all pumped the lucky girl full of cum, I run a pregnancy tester over her belly, and whoever's the father wins twenty thousand flames!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I see,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(If, however, you're looking to be the one being bred, then, just like the breeders, you first need to give me ten thousand flames. After that, you have to guess which of the six studs is going to knock you up! Once they've all pumped your pussy full of cum, I use a pregnancy tester to see who's the father of your kids, and if you correctly guessed who it'd be, you win fifty thousand flames!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ok, that seems simple enough,)] you say. [pc.speech(What if the volunteer doesn't get pregnant?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Well, in that case, everyone loses their bets,)] Epona replies. [epona.speech(I give the volunteer a [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getName(false)] before we start though, so that shouldn't happen!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Alright, thanks for explaining it to me.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(You're welcome! Let me know if you want to play,)] Epona says, leaning down on the counter in front of her.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_MOTHER_PRE_SELECTION_FUTA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Epona?)] you ask, getting the horse-girl's attention before continuing, [pc.speech(I'd like to play a game of pregnancy roulette, as the one being bred.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You place the ten thousand flames on the counter before you, and, after Epona has counted it all out, she looks up at you and grins. [epona.speech(This is gonna be so much fun! Now, we like to split up the breeders into groups of males and futas, so who do you want to be making you a Mommy?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(The futas,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Great!)] Epona happily exclaims, stamping your loyalty card before rushing out from behind her counter. [epona.speech(Right this way!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Trailing in Epona's footsteps, you're quickly led over to the futa breeding room. The interior of this room is concealed from public view by means of a dark pink canvas privacy screen, which bears a stylised white silhouette of a horse-girl futa sporting a massive erection. As Epona leads you around this screen, she comments, [epona.speech(I bet you can't wait to be #IF(pc.hasLegs())spreading your legs for#ELSEgetting fucked by#ENDIF a bunch of horny futas!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the excited horse-girl around the side of the canvas screen, you find yourself stepping into a small, wooden-floored room. The only furnishings in this area are a couple of elegant wooden tables and padded sofas, which have been pushed up against the left and right-hand walls. Set into the far side of the room, you see a large mirror and solitary door, and a few [unit.lSizes] to the left of those, at about waist-height, there's a round opening in the wall.
	</p>
	<p>
		Epona leads you over to this door, and upon opening it, ushers you inside. Within the small corridor beyond, you discover that the mirror you just passed is one-way, allowing you to look back out into the main room. Up ahead, placed in front of the round opening that links this area to the futa breeding room, is a long, padded bench. It's quite obvious that you're going to be expected to lie on this, allowing your bottom half to be exposed to the breeding room.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Right! So, you just wait here, and I'll go fetch the futas. We like to keep the breeders separated from the volunteer, you see, as we've had issues in the past where the breeders would get a little over-excited and try to force the volunteer to pick them as their guess,)] Epona explains. [epona.speech(I'll be right back!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Epona quickly rushes off, leaving you to wait in the partitioned corridor...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_MOTHER_SELECTION_FUTA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After only a few minutes, you look through the one-way mirror to see Epona entering the room once more. Trailing in her wake, you see six futas, all of them already stripped naked. Trotting alongside each one of these breeders is a rather excited-looking horse-girl. As this large group finishes entering the room, the horse-girls dutifully drop to their knees beside their partner, and, with a combination of licks and strokes, quickly get their chosen breeder's cock to full hardness.
	</p>
	<p>
		While these horse-girls are getting the breeders warmed up, Epona opens the door beside you and steps forwards into the small room. [epona.speech(Heya! Look at all those cocks lined up just for you! So, which one do you think's gonna be the one to knock you up? Remember, after you've chosen, I'll roll dice to see in what order they get to use your pussy. Oh, and I almost forgot! You need to take a [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getName(false)]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Epona hands you a little purple pill, which you quickly swallow. You then turn to look over the six futas before you, and after Epona's pointed out each one and told you her name, you decide upon the futa that you think will be the father of your kids...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_MOTHER_PRE_SELECTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Epona?)] you ask, getting the horse-girl's attention before continuing, [pc.speech(I'd like to play a game of pregnancy roulette, as the one being bred.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You place the ten thousand flames on the counter before you, and, after Epona has counted it all out, she looks up at you and grins. [epona.speech(This is gonna be so much fun! Now, we like to split up the breeders into groups of males and futas, so who do you want to be making you a Mommy?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(The males,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Great!)] Epona happily exclaims, stamping your loyalty card before rushing out from behind her counter. [epona.speech(Right this way!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Trailing in Epona's footsteps, you're quickly led over to the male breeding room. The interior of this room is concealed from public view by means of a dark blue canvas privacy screen, which bears a stylised black silhouette of a horse-boy sporting a massive erection. As Epona leads you around this screen, she comments, [epona.speech(I bet you can't wait to be #IF(pc.hasLegs())spreading your legs for#ELSEgetting fucked by#ENDIF a bunch of horny guys!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the excited horse-girl around the side of the canvas screen, you find yourself stepping into a small, wooden-floored room. The only furnishings in this area are a couple of basic wooden tables and benches, which have been pushed up against the left and right-hand walls. Set into the far side of the room, you see a large mirror and solitary door, and a few [unit.lSizes] to the left of those, at about waist-height, there's a round opening in the wall.
	</p>
	<p>
		Epona leads you over to this door, and upon opening it, ushers you inside. Within the small corridor beyond, you discover that the mirror you just passed is one-way, allowing you to look back out into the main room. Up ahead, placed in front of the round opening that links this area to the male breeding room, is a long, padded bench. It's quite obvious that you're going to be expected to lie on this, allowing your bottom half to be exposed to the breeding room.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Right! So, you just wait here, and I'll go fetch the guys. We like to keep the breeders separated from the volunteer, you see, as we've had issues in the past where the breeders would get a little over-excited and try to force the volunteer to pick them as their guess,)] Epona explains. [epona.speech(I'll be right back!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Epona quickly rushes off, leaving you to wait in the partitioned corridor...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_MOTHER_SELECTION"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		After only a few minutes, you look through the one-way mirror to see Epona entering the room once more. Trailing in her wake, you see six guys, all of them already stripped naked. Trotting alongside each one of these breeders is a rather excited-looking horse-girl. As this large group finishes entering the room, the horse-girls dutifully drop to their knees beside their partner, and, with a combination of licks and strokes, quickly get their chosen breeder's cock to full hardness.
	</p>
	<p>
		While these horse-girls are getting the breeders warmed up, Epona opens the door beside you and steps forwards into the small room. [epona.speech(Heya! Look at all those cocks lined up just for you! So, which one do you think's gonna be the one to knock you up? Remember, after you've chosen, I'll roll dice to see in what order they get to use your pussy. Oh, and I almost forgot! You need to take a [#ITEM_innoxia_pills_fertility.getName(false)]!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Epona hands you a little purple pill, which you quickly swallow. You then turn to look over the six guys before you, and after Epona's pointed out each one and told you his name, you decide upon the guy that you think will be the father of your kids...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_MOTHER_START"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I think [npc.name]'s going to get me pregnant,)] you say, pointing to the [npc.race] which you think has the most impressive-looking cock.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Great! I'll just note that down,)] Epona replies, producing a notepad and pen, before jotting taking down your selection. [epona.speech(Now, let's get you into position.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Epona leads you over to the padded bench, before turning around. [epona.speech(Right, so you just slide your [pc.legs] through there, and wait for me to go give the signal to start! It's up to you whether you want to be on your front or back.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Stepping towards the bench, you prepare to slide your lower half out into the breeder's room, but first, you need to decide whether to lie on your stomach or back...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ROULETTE_STARTING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] steps up behind you, before hungrily grabbing your [pc.ass+]. [npc.speech(I'm gonna pump you full of kids!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ROULETTE_STARTING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] rubs [npc.her] fingers up and down over your [pc.pussy+], before [npc.moaning], [npc.speech(You're gonna be stuffed full of my cum in a moment, [pc.girl]!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ROULETTE_STARTING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] steps forwards, sliding a finger up into your [pc.pussy+] as [npc.she] [npc.moansVerb], [npc.speech(Mmm, yeah, this is a nice cunt you've got!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ROULETTE_STARTING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] steps up behind you, before lining [npc.her] [npc.cock+] up to your [pc.pussy+]. [npc.speech(You're gonna love carrying my kids.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="ROULETTE_STARTING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] steps up behind you, before delivering a sharp slap to your [pc.ass+]. [npc.speech(I'm gonna fill you up real good!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_ROULETTE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As [npc.name] steps back, [npc.she] lets out a low [npc.moan], [npc.speech(Your pussy's lookin' real good, stuffed full of my cum like that!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_ROULETTE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[npc.Name] steps back, letting out a low whistle as [npc.she] admires the creampie [npc.she]'s just given you.
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_ROULETTE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As [npc.name] steps back, laughing as [npc.she] looks down at your creampied pussy, [npc.speech(There's no way that's not gonna get you pregnant!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_ROULETTE_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As [npc.name] steps back, [npc.she] gives your [pc.ass+] a squeeze. [npc.speech(You're gonna love being a Mommy!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_MOTHER_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As the last of the breeders steps away from your well-used pussy, Epona opens the door and steps forwards into the partitioned area. [epona.speech(Great job, [pc.name]! You're sure to be a Mommy now!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With the horse-girl's help, you wriggle back out of the opening, feeling the still-hot cum sliding out of your well-used pussy as you stand up on quivering [pc.legs]. Epona helpfully produces a tissue, and before you can say anything, leans down to help wipe the excess cum off your [pc.legs]. As she does this, she explains, [epona.speech(Right, so now I'll just run a pregnancy tester over your belly, and we can see which of the breeder's the father! Now, in the past, some of the breeders have lost their temper when they found out they didn't win, so, for your safety, we'll keep you back here until they're all gone.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Ok,)] you respond, waiting for Epona to get on with the testing.
	</p>
	<p>
		You don't have to wait more than a moment, as Epona quickly finishes helping to get you cleaned up, before swiping a pregnancy tester over your stomach. The little device makes a beeping noise as it travels over your lower abdomen, and, with this confirmation that it's taken a reading, Epona holds the tester up so that you can read the results:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_MOTHER_WINNER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Congratulations! You guessed correctly!)] Epona happily exclaims, before leaning forwards and giving you a big hug.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thanks, Epona,)] you reply, smiling happily to yourself as you realise that you've just won a lot of money.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, the horse-girl releases you and steps back, before telling you what's going to happen next. [epona.speech(Right, I need to go let the breeders know who won. You stay here for a moment, and after they've gone, we'll go back to the main counter to get your winnings.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You do as Epona asks, and wait in the little room until the horse-girl has shown all the breeders to the exit. After that, she comes to collect you, and the two of you head back over to the main counter. Unlocking a safe, Epona retrieves fifty thousand flames, before handing them over to you with a big grin on her face. [epona.speech(Congratulations once again, [pc.name]!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking your winnings, you thank Epona once again, before stepping back and wondering what to do next. As you move off to continue on your travels, you wonder if you'll ever have to tell your kids how they were conceived...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_MOTHER_LOSER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Aww, I'm sorry! You didn't get it right this time,)] Epona says, before leaning forwards and giving you a big hug.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'm ok, Epona,)] you reply, enduring the horse-girl's consolatory hug.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, the horse-girl releases you and steps back, before telling you what's going to happen next. [epona.speech(Right, I need to go let the breeders know who won. You stay here for a moment, and after they've gone, we'll go back to the main counter.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You do as Epona asks, and wait in the little room until the horse-girl has shown all the breeders to the exit. After that, she comes to collect you, and the two of you head back over to the main counter. [epona.speech(I'm sorry again, [pc.name]. Please do come back and have another go some other time!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		You say goodbye to Epona, before stepping back and wondering what to do next. As you move off to continue on your travels, you wonder if you'll ever have to tell your kids how they were conceived...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_MOTHER_LOSER_NO_PREGNANCY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Aww, I'm sorry! It looks like you're not having kids this time,)] Epona says, before leaning forwards and giving you a big hug.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(I'm ok, Epona,)] you reply, enduring the horse-girl's consolatory hug.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, the horse-girl releases you and steps back, before telling you what's going to happen next. [epona.speech(Right, I need to go let the breeders know that they all lost. You stay here for a moment, and after they've gone, we'll go back to the main counter.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You do as Epona asks, and wait in the little room until the horse-girl has shown all the breeders to the exit. After that, she comes to collect you, and the two of you head back over to the main counter. [epona.speech(I'm sorry again, [pc.name]. Please do come back and have another go some other time!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		You say goodbye to Epona, before stepping back and wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_BREEDER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Epona?)] you ask, getting the horse-girl's attention before continuing, [pc.speech(I'd like to play a game of pregnancy roulette, as one of the breeders.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You place the ten thousand flames on the counter before you, and, after Epona has counted it all out, she looks up at you and grins. [epona.speech(This is gonna be so much fun! Now, we like to split up the breeders into groups based on femininity, so you're going to be joining five guys, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sure,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Great!)] Epona happily exclaims, stamping your loyalty card before rushing out from behind her counter. [epona.speech(Right this way! We've already got a volunteer and five other breeders ready, so there's no need to wait around.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Trailing in Epona's footsteps, you're quickly led over to the male's breeding room. The interior of this room is concealed from public view by means of a dark blue canvas privacy screen, which bears a stylised black silhouette of a horse-boy sporting a massive erection. As Epona leads you around this screen, she comments, [epona.speech(I bet you can't wait to be pumping this slut full of cum!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the excited horse-girl around the side of the canvas screen, you find yourself stepping into a small, wooden-floored room. The only furnishings in this area are a couple of basic wooden tables and benches, which have been pushed up against the left and right-hand walls. Set into the far side of the room, you see a large mirror and solitary door, and a few [unit.lSizes] to the left of those, at about waist-height, there's a round opening in the wall.
	</p>
	<p>
		The other five breeders are already present, and beside each of them, a horse-girl is down on her knees, stroking and licking her partner's cock in order to keep them hard and ready to penetrate the volunteer at a moment's notice. As you step into the room, an idling horse-girl walks up beside you, before dropping to her knees and quickly taking hold of your cock. As she leans in to give it a slow, wet lick, Epona happily turns around to address the room, [epona.speech(Right! I'll go and ask the volunteer who she thinks will be getting her pregnant. You all stay here for a moment.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You do as Epona says, and wait patiently with the other breeders as the horse-girl opens the solitary door and steps through into the room beyond. After just a moment, you see movement through the round opening in the wall, before suddenly #IF(npc.hasLegs())a pair of [npc.legs]#ELSEa [npc.legs+]#ENDIF and the lower abdomen of [npc.a_fullRace(true)] slide out into the room. The other breeders start to grow restless as they gaze upon the volunteer's [npc.pussy+], but before any of them can do anything to ruin the game, Epona steps back into the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(You all look like you're ready!)] the horse-girl exclaims. [epona.speech(Now, I'll roll a dice to see in what order you get to fuck [npc.name] here! [pc.Name], I'll start with you!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_BREEDER_FUTA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Epona?)] you ask, getting the horse-girl's attention before continuing, [pc.speech(I'd like to play a game of pregnancy roulette, as one of the breeders.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You place the ten thousand flames on the counter before you, and, after Epona has counted it all out, she looks up at you and grins. [epona.speech(This is gonna be so much fun! Now, we like to split up the breeders into groups based on femininity, so you're going to be joining five futas, ok?)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Sure,)] you reply.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Great!)] Epona happily exclaims, stamping your loyalty card before rushing out from behind her counter. [epona.speech(Right this way! We've already got a volunteer and five other breeders ready, so there's no need to wait around.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Trailing in Epona's footsteps, you're quickly led over to the futa breeding room. The interior of this room is concealed from public view by means of a dark pink canvas privacy screen, which bears a stylised white silhouette of a horse-girl futa sporting a massive erection. As Epona leads you around this screen, she comments, [epona.speech(I bet you can't wait to be pumping this slut full of cum!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Following the excited horse-girl around the side of the canvas screen, you find yourself stepping into a small, wooden-floored room. The only furnishings in this area are a couple of elegant wooden tables and padded sofas, which have been pushed up against the left and right-hand walls. Set into the far side of the room, you see a large mirror and solitary door, and a few [unit.lSizes] to the left of those, at about waist-height, there's a round opening in the wall.
	</p>
	<p>
		The other five breeders are already present, and beside each of them, a horse-girl is down on her knees, stroking and licking her partner's cock in order to keep them hard and ready to penetrate the volunteer at a moment's notice. As you step into the room, an idling horse-girl walks up beside you, before dropping to her knees and quickly taking hold of your cock. As she leans in to give it a slow, wet lick, Epona happily turns around to address the room, [epona.speech(Right! I'll go and ask the volunteer who she thinks will be getting her pregnant. You all stay here for a moment.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You do as Epona says, and wait patiently with the other breeders as the horse-girl opens the solitary door and steps through into the room beyond. After just a moment, you see movement through the round opening in the wall, before suddenly #IF(npc.hasLegs())a pair of [npc.legs]#ELSEa [npc.legs+]#ENDIF and the lower abdomen of [npc.a_fullRace(true)] slide out into the room. The other breeders start to grow restless as they gaze upon the volunteer's [npc.pussy+], but before any of them can do anything to ruin the game, Epona steps back into the room.
	</p>
	<p>
		[epona.speech(You all look like you're ready!)] the horse-girl exclaims. [epona.speech(Now, I'll roll a dice to see in what order you get to fuck [npc.name] here! [pc.Name], I'll start with you!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_BREEDER_FIRST"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you rolled a one, you're the first to step up to [npc.name]'s exposed body. Reaching down to take a hold of her [npc.hips], you line your [pc.cock+] up to her [npc.pussy+] and prepare to penetrate her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_BREEDER_MIDDLE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As you aren't the first to fuck [npc.name], you find yourself looking down at a fresh creampie dripping out of her exposed pussy as you step up to her. Reaching down to take a hold of her [npc.hips], you line your [pc.cock+] up to her well-used cunt and prepare to penetrate her...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_BREEDER_POST_SEX"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		As all of you breeders have now finished, Epona steps forwards turns to address the room, [epona.speech(Great job everyone! Now I'll go and find out which of you is the father to this slut's kids! Please be patient, I'll be back in a moment.)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_BREEDER_FINISHED"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		You and the rest of the breeders watch as the volunteer's #IF(npc.hasLegs())[npc.legs] slide#ELSE[npc.leg] slides#ENDIF back into the other room. You hear Epona talking with her for a moment, before the solitary door opens once more. The horse-girl steps back out into the room that you're in, holding up a pregnancy tester for you all to see:
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_BREEDER_WINNER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Congratulations! You got this slut knocked up!)] Epona happily says to you, before leaning forwards and giving you a big hug.
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Thanks, Epona,)] you reply, smiling happily to yourself as you realise that you've just won a lot of money.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, the horse-girl releases you and steps back, before addressing the room, [epona.speech(Right, sorry everyone else. Better luck next time! Now, [pc.name], follow me to the counter so I can give you your winnings.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		You do as Epona asks, and the two of you head back over to the main counter. Unlocking a safe, Epona retrieves twenty thousand flames, before handing them over to you with a big grin on her face. [epona.speech(Congratulations once again, [pc.name]!)] 
	</p>
	<p>
		Taking your winnings, you thank Epona once again, before stepping back and wondering what to do next. As you move off to continue on your travels, you wonder if you'll ever have to tell your kids how they were conceived...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_BREEDER_LOSER"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Congratulations! You got this slut knocked up!)] Epona happily says to the winner, before leaning forwards and giving them a big hug.
	</p>
	<p>
		You, along with all the other breeders, let out a defeated sigh as you realise that you've lost your ten thousand flame bet.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, the horse-girl releases the winner and steps back, before addressing the room, [epona.speech(Right, sorry everyone else. Better luck next time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having lost your bet, you find yourself wandering out into the gambling hall proper. You soon find yourself drifting back towards the pregnancy roulette counter, and, turning around to look back down the length of the gambling hall's atrium, you wonder where to go next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="PREGNANCY_ROULETTE_BREEDER_LOSER_NO_PREGNANCY"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[epona.speech(Aww, I'm sorry! It looks like none of you are having kids this time,)] Epona says, placing her hands on her hips.
	</p>
	<p>
		You, along with all the other breeders, let out a defeated sigh as you realise that you've lost your ten thousand flame bet.
	</p>
	<p>
		After a moment, the horse-girl addresses the room, [epona.speech(Right, sorry everyone. Better luck next time!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having lost your bet, you find yourself wandering out into the gambling hall proper. You soon find yourself drifting back towards the pregnancy roulette counter, and, turning around to look back down the length of the gambling hall's atrium, you wonder where to go next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MURK -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_REPEAT"><![CDATA[
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkMaster))
		<p>
			Knowing that your Master will want to see you again, you ask Epona if she'll let you into the back room to see Murk. Unaware of the sort of relationship you and the rat-boy have, she smiles and asks, [epona.speech(Still trying to reform him, huh? Well, I think that you're wasting your time, but you're more than welcome to try...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Moving over to one side, the horse-girl lifts up the counter-top and beckons you forwards. [pc.Stepping] around to the other side, you follow Epona as she once again leads you past the door to her office and over to the storage room in which your Master is being kept.
			#IF(pc.hasVagina())
				 Already getting wet
			#ELSEIF(pc.hasPenis())
				 Already getting hard
			#ELSE
				 Already getting excited
			#ENDIF
			 at the thought of servicing your Master's fat cock, you quickly thank Epona and watch as she returns to stand behind the counter. Turning to face the door to the storage room, you prepare to enter and submit to your Master once again...
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Wanting to pay [murk.name] another visit, you ask Epona if she'll let you into the back room to see the [murk.race]. Letting out a short sigh, the horse-girl smiles and asks, [epona.speech(Still trying to reform [murk.herHim], huh? Well, I think that you're wasting your time, but you're more than welcome to try...)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Moving over to one side, Epona lifts up the counter-top and beckons you forwards. [pc.Stepping] around to the other side, you follow the horse-girl as she once again leads you past the door to her office and over to the storage room in which Murk is being kept. After thanking Epona for letting you back here again, you watch as she returns to stand behind the counter, before turning to face the door to the storage room and preparing to enter once again...
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Knowing that Epona has been given the task of looking after Murk, you ask her where she's keeping him. Raising her eyebrows in surprise at your interest in the rat-boy, Epona places her hands on her hips and sighs, [epona.speech(I've got him locked up in the storage room behind me. I'm not particularly fond of slavery, but when I heard that he'd kidnapped some humans and turned them into his sex slaves... Slavery's too good for scum like him.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Having confirmed that the rat-boy is close by, you ask Epona if she'd let you see him. Frowning at you, she asks, [epona.speech(You actually want to see that piece of trash?! Well, seeing as you're the one to thank for putting an end to his abuse of those poor girls, I suppose I can trust you...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Moving over to one side, the horse-girl lifts up the counter-top and beckons you forwards. [pc.Stepping] around to the other side, you follow Epona as she leads you past the door to her office and over to a second door marked as 'Staff Only'. Turning towards you, she says, [epona.speech(He's chained up in here, and I only allow him out to help with cleaning the breeding stalls. I assume that you're here to try and scold him for his abhorrent behaviour, but I'm warning you now that he doesn't listen to anyone.)]
	</p>
	<p>
		With that, Epona turns around and starts to walk back over to her counter, but after taking a couple of steps, she suddenly remembers something and turns back to reveal, [epona.speech(There's a feminising potion on the top shelf in there... I had it created a long time ago as part of a trial for pregnancy roulette, but I never used it. I can't bring myself to force something like that on someone else, even someone as despicable as Murk, but if you wanted to use it on him, then feel free. It has some pretty potent mind-altering effects, so it should mellow him out...)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out a deep sigh, the horse-girl flashes you one last smile, before turning around one more and walking off back to her counter. Left alone facing the door to the storage room in which Murk is being kept, you wonder whether you should enter or instead turn around and leave...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MURK_ALONE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_ALONE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Pushing open the door, you [pc.step] into the storage room and quickly scan your surroundings. The dimensions of the room are very small, and it's made even smaller by the fact that there are shelving units pushed back against all three sides of the walls in front of you. A single arcane-powered lightbulb hangs from the drab grey ceiling, which illuminates the form of the chubby [murk.race] who's slouched down on a pile of shabby old cushions in front of you.
	</p>
	#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkMaster) || game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_eponaMurkSubmitted))
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_eponaMurkSeen))
			<p>
				#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
					#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(murk))
						#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(murk.getId()))
							A wicked grin instantly crosses your Master's face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, he looks down at your swollen belly and sneers, [murk.speech(I got ya knocked up, eh, slut? Heh! Shoulda known that all that stinkin' cum I stuffed inta yer womb would get ya pregnant! Anyway, get down an' give me fat cock a
							#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
								 kiss,
							#ELSE
								 stroke,
							#ENDIF
							 bitch!)]
						#ELSE
							A wicked grin instantly crosses your Master's face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, he looks down at your swollen belly and sneers, [murk.speech(Someone's gone an' got ya knocked up, eh, slut? Heh! Anyway, get down an' give me fat cock a
							#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
								 kiss,
							#ELSE
								 stroke,
							#ENDIF
							 bitch!)]
						#ENDIF
					#ELSE
						#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(murk.getId()))
							A wicked grin instantly crosses your Master's face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, he looks down at your still-swollen belly and sneers, [murk.speech(You's still carryin' our kids around? Hurry the fuck up an' get 'em birthed, so I can 'ave a go at breedin' yer ugly cunt again! Anyway, get down an' give me fat cock a
							#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
								 kiss,
							#ELSE
								 stroke,
							#ENDIF
							 bitch!)]
						#ELSE
							A wicked grin instantly crosses your Master's face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, he looks down at your still-swollen belly and sneers, [murk.speech(You's still pregnant? Hurry the fuck up an' get 'em birthed, so I can 'ave a go at breedin' yer ugly cunt! Anyway, get down an' give me fat cock a
							#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
								 kiss,
							#ELSE
								 stroke,
							#ENDIF
							 bitch!)]
						#ENDIF
					#ENDIF
				#ELSE
					A wicked grin instantly crosses your Master's face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, he snaps his fingers and points down at his exposed groin, sneering,
					#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
						 [murk.speech(Get down an' give me fat cock a kiss, slut!)]
					#ELSE
						 [murk.speech(Get down an' give me fat cock a stroke, slut!)]
					#ENDIF
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_eponaMurkSubmitted))
					You can't help but let out a hungry whine as you look down at the rat-boy's fat, sheathed cock, and you wonder whether you should do as he commands, or tell him that things have gone too far...
				#ELSE
					Your previous conditioning to obey your Master instantly takes over, and without thinking, you move forwards to obey...
				#ENDIF
			</p>
		#ELSE
			<p>
				A wicked grin instantly crosses your Master's face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit, and after letting out a loud belch, he spreads his legs and presents you with his exposed groin, sneering, [murk.speech(I's 'appy ta see yer 'ere, slut! Me fat balls ain't been emptied since them Enforcer cunts nabbed me an' 'ad me locked up in 'ere! There ain't no 'ope o' me ever gettin' out o' this place, but at least I's got a faithful slut 'o I can stick me fat cock inside of!)]
			</p>
			<p>
				Your previous conditioning to please your Master instantly takes over, and without thinking, you move forwards and ask, [pc.speech(What can I do for you, Master?)]
			</p>
			<p>
				#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
					[murk.speech(Get down on yer knees an' give me stinkin' cock a nice big kiss!)] your Master commands, before reaching up to scratch his chubby belly and sneer, [murk.speech(I'll 'ave ya make love ta me cock an' then give ya a real 'ard poundin'!)]
				#ELSE
					[murk.speech(Get down on yer knees an' give me stinkin' cock sum attention!)] your Master commands, before reaching up to scratch his chubby belly and sneer, [murk.speech(I'll 'ave ya jerk me off an' spurt me cum all over ya face! Heh!)]
				#ENDIF
			</p>
			#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
				<p>
					#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(murk.getId()))
						Looking down at your swollen belly as though noticing it for the first time, the chubby rat-boy sneers, [murk.speech(I got ya knocked up, eh, slut? Heh! Shoulda known that all that stinkin' cum I stuffed inta yer womb would get ya pregnant! Anyways, 'urry up an get ta servicin' me cock!)]
					#ELSE
						Looking down at your swollen belly as though noticing it for the first time, the chubby rat-boy sneers, [murk.speech(Someone's gone an' got ya knocked up, eh, slut? Heh! Anyways, 'urry up an get ta servicin' me cock!)]
					#ENDIF
				</p>
			#ENDIF
			<p>
				Eager to please your Master, you move forwards to obey...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ELSE
		#IF(!murk.isFeminine())
			#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_eponaMurkSeen))
				<p>
					#IF(pc.isVisiblyPregnant())
						#IF(!pc.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(murk))
							#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(murk.getId()))
								A hungry grin instantly crosses [murk.namePos] face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, he looks down at your swollen belly and sneers, [murk.speech(I got ya knocked up, eh, slut? Heh! Shoulda known that all that stinkin' cum I stuffed inta yer womb would get ya pregnant! Anyway, get down an' give me fat cock a
								#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
									 kiss,
								#ELSE
									 stroke,
								#ENDIF
								 bitch!)]
							#ELSE
								A hungry grin instantly crosses [murk.namePos] face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, he looks down at your swollen belly and sneers, [murk.speech(Someone's gone an' got ya knocked up, eh, slut? Heh! Anyway, get down an' give me fat cock a
								#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
									 kiss,
								#ELSE
									 stroke,
								#ENDIF
								 bitch!)]
							#ENDIF
						#ELSE
							#IF(pc.getPregnantLitter().isFatherId(murk.getId()))
								A hungry grin instantly crosses [murk.namePos] face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, he looks down at your still-swollen belly and sneers, [murk.speech(You's still carryin' our kids around? Hurry the fuck up an' get 'em birthed, so I can 'ave a go at breedin' yer ugly cunt again! Anyway, get down an' give me fat cock a
								#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
									 kiss,
								#ELSE
									 stroke,
								#ENDIF
								 bitch!)]
							#ELSE
								A hungry grin instantly crosses [murk.namePos] face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, he looks down at your still-swollen belly and sneers, [murk.speech(You's still pregnant? Hurry the fuck up an' get 'em birthed, so I can 'ave a go at breedin' yer ugly cunt! Anyway, get down an' give me fat cock a
								#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
									 kiss,
								#ELSE
									 stroke,
								#ENDIF
								 bitch!)]
							#ENDIF
						#ENDIF
					#ELSE
						A hungry grin instantly crosses [murk.namePos] face as he sees that you've come to pay him a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, he snaps his fingers and points down at his exposed groin, sneering,
						#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
							 [murk.speech(Come an' give me fat cock a kiss, slut! I's knowin' ya wantin' it really!)]
						#ELSE
							 [murk.speech(Come an' give me fat cock a stroke, slut! I's knowin' ya wantin' it really!)]
						#ENDIF
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					Frowning down at the crass rat-boy, you wonder what to do about his uncouth behaviour...
				</p>
			#ELSE
				<p>
					#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkCaptiveBlowjob))
						A wicked grin instantly crosses Murk's face as he sees that it's you who's come to pay him a visit, and after letting out a loud belch, he spreads his legs and presents you with his exposed groin, sneering,
						#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
							 [murk.speech(I's 'appy ta see yer 'ere, slut! Me fat balls ain't been emptied since them Enforcer cunts nabbed me an' 'ad me locked up in 'ere! You's may 'ave escaped from yer milkin' stall, but yer 'ungry fer anotha taste o' me stinkin' cock, ain't ya?! Come on, get down an' give it a kiss, slut!)]
						#ELSE
							 [murk.speech(I's 'appy ta see yer 'ere, slut! Me fat balls ain't been emptied since them Enforcer cunts nabbed me an' 'ad me locked up in 'ere! You's may 'ave escaped from yer milkin' stall, but yer 'ungry fer anotha taste o' me stinkin' cum, ain't ya?! Come on, get down an' give it a stroke, slut!)]
						#ENDIF
					#ELSE
						A look of surprise crosses Murk's face as he sees that someone other than Epona has come to pay him a visit, but after letting out a loud belch, he flashes you an arrogant smirk and spreads his legs to present you with his exposed groin. Looking down, you see that although Murk's cock is currently sheathed, it's quite clearly absolutely massive, and you can't help but imagine how disproportionately huge it must look to his relatively short stature when fully erect. Seeing what it is you're glancing at, the rat-boy spits on the floor and sneers,
						#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
							 [murk.speech(I's can tell that ya wantin' a taste o' it! Come on, get down an' give me fat cock a kiss, slut!)]
						#ELSE
							 [murk.speech(I's can tell that ya wantin' a feel o' it! Come on, get down an' give me fat cock a stroke, slut!)]
						#ENDIF
					#ENDIF
				</p>
				<p>
					Frowning down at the crass rat-boy, you wonder what to do about his uncouth behaviour...
				</p>
			#ENDIF
		#ELSE
			#IF(murk.isVisiblyPregnant())
				#IF(!murk.isCharacterReactedToPregnancy(pc))
					<p>
						A devious grin instantly crosses [murk.namePos] face as she sees that you've come to pay her a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, she rubs her chubby hands over her [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)] and sneers, [murk.speech(Look at wot you's done an gone ta me! You's got me knocked up! Heh-heh-heh!)]
					<p>
					<p>
						Slipping her chubby fingers down towards her groin, the chubby rat-girl spreads her legs and starts touching herself, sneering, [murk.speech(Me cunt's still 'ungry ta be filled with cock, so come on, do me already! I's all wet an' eager ta get ya inside o' me!)]
					</p>
				#ELSE
					<p>
						A devious grin instantly crosses [murk.namePos] face as she sees that you've come to pay her a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, she rubs her chubby hands over her [style.colourSex(pregnant belly)] and sneers, [murk.speech(I's still all nice an' swollen with our kids! Heh-heh-heh!)]
					<p>
					<p>
						Slipping her chubby fingers down towards her groin, the chubby rat-girl spreads her legs and starts touching herself, sneering, [murk.speech(Me cunt's still 'ungry ta be filled with cock, so come on, do me already! I's all wet an' eager ta get ya inside o' me!)]
					</p>
				#ENDIF
			#ELSE
				<p>
					A hungry grin instantly crosses [murk.namePos] face as she sees that you've come to pay her a visit again, and after letting out a loud belch, she spreads her legs and starts rubbing her chubby fingers over her exposed pussy, sneering, [murk.speech(You's 'ere ta give me cunt a good fuckin' ain't ya?! Come on, I's all wet an' eager ta get ya inside o' me! Heh!)]
				<p>
			#ENDIF
			<p>
				Looking down at the horny rat-girl, you wonder whether you should do as she asks and fuck her, or do something else instead...
			</p>
		#ENDIF
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_SEX_DOM"><![CDATA[
	#IF(murk.isFeminine())
		<p>
			[pc.Stepping] forwards, you dominantly push [murk.name] down onto the cushions she's been using as a makeshift chair, before moving up between her legs and preparing to fuck her. Clearly getting excited at the prospect of having her hungry pussy used, [murk.name] squeals, [murk.speech(Oh yeah! ~Mmm!~ Come on, fuck me juicy cunt!)]
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Not having any time for Murk's attempts at asserting his dominance, you simply [pc.step] forwards and forcefully push him down onto the cushions he's been using as a makeshift chair. Quickly moving up between his legs and preparing to fuck him, you can't help but smirk as he grunts, [murk.speech(Hey! W-What ya doin'?! I should be da one in charge!)]
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_SEX_SUB_VAGINA"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself madly turned on at the thought of being dominated by this chubby rat-boy, you let out a horny whine and tell him that you want him to fuck you. Letting out a rumbling chuckle as he hears what it is you're saying, Murk teases,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkCaptiveBlowjob))
			 [murk.speech(Wot? Ya can't stop thinkin' about 'ow good it were when I was fuckin' yer face an' trainin' ya ta be one o' me milkers? Heh-heh-heh! Go on then, slut, get down on yer knees and give me fat cock a big, lovin' kiss, an' I'll consider fuckin' ya!)]
		#ELSE
			 [murk.speech(Wot? Ya can't stop thinkin' about 'ow good it'd feel ta 'ave me fat cock stuffed deep inta yer cunt? Heh-heh-heh! Go on then, slut, get down on yer knees and give me fat dick a big, lovin' kiss, an' I'll consider fuckin' ya!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you drop down onto the floor in front of Murk, before leaning in and planting a big, wet kiss on his sheathed cock. Quickly pushing out and rising to full erection in response to your oral attention, Murk's huge, fat cock starts leaking a steady stream of musky precum, and you can't help but lick it up as he grunts, [murk.speech(That's it, slut! Now call me yer Masta an' give me cock one last kiss, then I'll shove it in yer cunt an' give ya a real good ruttin'!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, Master,)] you submissively reply, before planting one last big, wet kiss on the head of your Master's cock.
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an amused grunt, the chubby rat-boy stands up, before waddling around behind you and unceremoniously clambering up onto your back. Without any further foreplay, he suddenly thrusts forwards and slams his massive cock into your pussy, before starting to ruthlessly pound you on the floor of the storage room...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_SEX_SUB_ANUS"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself madly turned on at the thought of being dominated by this chubby rat-boy, you let out a horny whine and tell him that you want him to fuck you. Letting out a rumbling chuckle as he hears what it is you're saying, Murk teases,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkCaptiveBlowjob))
			 [murk.speech(Wot? Ya can't stop thinkin' about 'ow good it were when I was fuckin' yer face an' trainin' ya ta be one o' me milkers? Heh-heh-heh! Go on then, slut, get down on yer knees and give me fat cock a big, lovin' kiss, an' I'll consider fuckin' ya!)]
		#ELSE
			 [murk.speech(Wot? Ya can't stop thinkin' about 'ow good it'd feel ta 'ave me fat cock stuffed deep inta yer ass? Heh-heh-heh! Go on then, slut, get down on yer knees and give me fat dick a big, lovin' kiss, an' I'll consider fuckin' ya!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you drop down onto the floor in front of Murk, before leaning in and planting a big, wet kiss on his sheathed cock. Quickly pushing out and rising to full erection in response to your oral attention, Murk's huge, fat cock starts leaking a steady stream of musky precum, and you can't help but lick it up as he grunts, [murk.speech(That's it, slut! Now call me yer Masta an' give me cock one last kiss, then I'll shove it in yer ass an' give ya a real good ruttin'!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, Master,)] you submissively reply, before planting one last big, wet kiss on the head of your Master's cock.
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an amused grunt, the chubby rat-boy stands up, before waddling around behind you and unceremoniously clambering up onto your back. Without any further foreplay, he suddenly thrusts forwards and slams his massive cock into your [pc.asshole+], before starting to ruthlessly pound you on the floor of the storage room...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_SEX_SUB_ORAL"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself madly turned on at the thought of being dominated by this chubby rat-boy, you let out a horny whine and tell him that you want him to fuck you. Letting out a rumbling chuckle as he hears what it is you're saying, Murk teases,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkCaptiveBlowjob))
			 [murk.speech(Wot? Ya can't stop thinkin' about 'ow good it were when I was fuckin' yer face an' trainin' ya ta be one o' me milkers? Heh-heh-heh! Go on then, slut, get down on yer knees and give me fat cock a big, lovin' kiss, an' I'll consider fuckin' yer face!)]
		#ELSE
			 [murk.speech(Wot? Ya can't stop thinkin' about 'ow good it'd feel ta 'ave me fat cock stuffed deep down yer throat? Heh-heh-heh! Go on then, slut, get down on yer knees and give me fat dick a big, lovin' kiss, an' I'll consider fuckin' yer face!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you drop down onto the floor in front of Murk, before leaning in and planting a big, wet kiss on his sheathed cock. Quickly pushing out and rising to full erection in response to your oral attention, Murk's huge, fat cock starts leaking a steady stream of musky precum, and you can't help but lick it up as he grunts, [murk.speech(That's it, slut! Now call me yer Masta an' give me cock one last kiss, then I'll shove it down yer throat an' give yer face a real good ruttin'!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		[pc.speech(Yes, Master,)] you submissively reply, before planting one last big, wet kiss on the head of your Master's cock.
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out an amused grunt, the chubby rat-boy grabs the back of your head, before slamming your face down into his groin. Not caring at all about the gargled splutters which you start to make as you suddenly find your throat filled with rat-cock, your Master sets about roughly fucking your face...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_SEX_SUB_HANDJOB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Finding yourself madly turned on at the thought of being dominated by this chubby rat-boy, you let out a horny whine and tell him that you want him to fuck you. Letting out a rumbling chuckle as he hears what it is you're saying, Murk teases,
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkCaptiveBlowjob))
			 [murk.speech(Wot? Ya can't stop thinkin' about 'ow good it were when I was fuckin' yer face an' trainin' ya ta be one o' me milkers? Heh-heh-heh! Well, slut, seein' as yer 'oles ain't available fer me ta fuck, you's gonna 'ave ta settle fer jerkin' me off! Get down an' start strokin' me cock!)]
		#ELSE
			 [murk.speech(Wot? Ya can't stop thinkin' about 'ow good me fat cock would feel stuffed deep inta one o' yer 'oles? Heh-heh-heh! Well, seein' as yer 'oles ain't available fer me ta fuck, you's gonna 'ave ta settle fer jerkin' me off! Get down an' start strokin' me cock!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you drop down onto the floor in front of Murk, before leaning in and starting to stroke his sheathed cock. Quickly pushing out and rising to full erection in response to your attention, Murk's huge, fat cock starts leaking a steady stream of musky precum, and you can't help but use it as extra lubrication as he grunts, [murk.speech(That's it, slut! Keep on goin'!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Doing as you're told, you continue stroking Murk's cock, eager to bring him to an orgasm and drain the cum from his huge balls...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_ALONE_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding that you don't want anything more to do with [murk.name] for the time being, you turn around and swiftly exit the room. Shutting the door behind you, you make your way back over to Epona, and after telling her that everything went ok, you [pc.step] back around to the other side of her counter and head off into the Gambling Den, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MURK_LECTURING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_LECTURING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting [murk.name] to fully understand why what [murk.she] did was wrong, you spend a good amount of time lecturing [murk.herHim] on the harm [murk.she] caused to innocent people during [murk.her] time as one of Vengar's gang members.
		#IF(murk.isFeminine())
			 Having become far more submissive since being feminised, she gives you her full attention, and after you've asked her several times about whether she regrets what she's done, you're left with the impression that she's legitimately sorry for her past behaviour.
		#ELSE
			 Scowling and grunting at you, Murk shows no sign of being sorry for what he's done, and although you ask him several times to apologise, he outright refuses to do as you say.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After half an hour of lecturing [murk.herHim], you eventually feel as though you've had enough, and after telling the [murk.race] one last time to think about what [murk.sheHas] done, you [pc.step] back and wonder what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MURK_SPANKING -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_SPANKING"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Wanting to teach [murk.name] a lesson for all of the bad things [murk.sheHas] done in the past, you grab hold of [murk.her] by the arm and forcefully push [murk.herHim] down over the pile of cushions [murk.sheHas] been using as a chair. Caught off-guard, the [murk.race] 
		#IF(murk.isFeminine())
			 lets out a surprisingly erotic moan and squeals, [murk.speech(~Ooh!~ You's gonna punish me?! Come on then, gimme a good spankin'!)]
		#ELSE
			 lets out a startled grunt and shouts, [murk.speech(Get yer filthy 'ands off o' me! You's can't treat me like dis!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(murk.isFeminine())
			Ignoring [murk.namePos] horny response, you bend her over the cushions and start delivering a series of sharp slaps to her exposed ass. Lifting her tail and squealing in a mixture of pain and pleasure, the [murk.race] quite clearly loves this sort of humiliation, and you can't help but notice how her [murk.pussy+] is soon dripping wet from excitement.
		#ELSE
			Ignoring [murk.namePos] insolent response, you bend him over the cushions and start delivering a series of sharp slaps to his exposed ass. Squirming and struggling against you, the [murk.race] lets out an angry cry each time you slap his butt, but despite his resistance, you're easily able to hold him in place and finish administering his punishment.
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Only once her ass has been thoroughly spanked do you [pc.step] back and bring an end to [murk.namePos] beating, which causes
		#IF(murk.isFeminine())
			 her to look back at you and breathlessly pant, [murk.speech(Yeah... I's been a bad girl... Now gimme a good, 'ard fuckin'!)]
		#ELSE
			 him to look back at you and furiously scowl, [murk.speech(Ya fuckin' bitch! Don't ya ever do that ta me again!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Looking down at the [murk.race], you wonder what to do with [murk.herHim] next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- AFTER_MURK_SEX -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_MURK_SEX_AS_DOM"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had your fun with [murk.name], you [pc.step] back and allow [murk.herHim] to collapse to the floor in front of you. As [murk.she] sinks down onto the tatty old cushions which serve as [murk.her] chair, the [murk.race] pants,
		#IF(murk.isFeminine())
			 [murk.speech(That were real good... Come back an' fuck me again soon...)]
		#ELSE
			 [murk.speech(Ya bitch... I's supposed ta... be da one in charge...)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		After quickly getting your things back in order, you look down to see that [murk.name] is still heavily panting and completely worn-out from the sex. Realising that you're not going to be able to get anything out of [murk.herHim] until later, you decide to leave and come back at another time...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_MURK_SEX_AS_SUB"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Having had his fun with you, your Master steps back and lets out a triumphant grunt, [murk.speech(You's ain't nothin' but me cock-sleeve! Tell me that ya love me stinkin' cock, ya dumb bitch!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Sinking down onto the floor and panting form exertion, you do as the chubby [murk.race] says and sigh, [pc.speech(Yes, Master... I love your big, fat cock...)]
	</p>
	#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
		<p>
			Chuckling in delight at your display of submission, your Master steps up in front of you and pushes his musky cock into your face. Grabbing the back of your head and pulling your mouth down into his groin, he grunts, [murk.speech(That's me good slut! Now give me fat cock a big kiss, then fuck off an' leave me alone; I's wantin' ta get some rest before that horse bitch makes me do some work.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly doing as you're told, you plant a big, wet kiss on the head of your Master's fat cock. Letting out an amused grunt, the [murk.name] then collapses down onto his pile of tatty old cushions, before pointing at the door and telling you to leave... 
		</p>
	#ELSE
		<p>
			Chuckling in delight at your display of submission, your Master waddles around behind you and delivers a stingingly-sharp slap to your ass. Taking a moment to grope you and rub his chubby fingers over your groin, he grunts, [murk.speech(That's me good slut! Now thank me fer lettin' ya 'ave sum fun with me cock, then fuck off an' leave me alone; I's wantin' ta get some rest before that horse bitch makes me do some work.)]
		</p>
		<p>
			Eagerly doing as you're told, you submissively thank your Master for letting you pleasure his fat cock. Letting out an amused grunt, the [murk.name] then collapses down onto his pile of tatty old cushions, before pointing at the door and telling you to leave... 
		</p>
	#ENDIF
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_MURK_SEX_DOM_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Turning around and leaving the exhausted [murk.race] panting on the floor, you swiftly exit the room. Shutting the door behind you, you make your way back over to Epona, and after telling her that everything went ok, you [pc.step] back around to the other side of her counter and head off into the Gambling Den, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="AFTER_MURK_SEX_SUB_LEAVE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to annoy your Master by loitering around, you do as he commands and swiftly exit the room. Shutting the door behind you, you make your way back over to Epona, and after telling her that everything went ok, you [pc.step] back around to the other side of her counter and head off into the Gambling Den, wondering what to do next...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MURK_FEMINISE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_FEMINISE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Deciding to make use of the feminising potion which Epona told you about, you start to look over the top shelves which line the room. Ignoring Murk's rude questioning about what you're doing, you soon find a dusty old bottle of bright pink liquid hidden behind a stack of papers. Retrieving this potion, you advance towards the crass rat-boy with the intent of forcing him to drink it.
	</p>
	<p>
		[murk.speech('Ey! Wot's that fuckin' bottle ya got! Get it away from me, ya fuckin' bitch! Fuck off!)] he curses, kicking out at you with his short, chubby legs as you bend down and take the stopper out of the bottle. Wrestling with him for a moment, you easily overpower the chubby rat-boy, and before you have a chance to think twice about your chosen course of action, you're forcing the bottle's neck into Murk's mouth and forcing him to drink down the transformative potion. Despite his efforts to spit out the bright pink liquid, he ends up swallowing a good amount of it, and once the bottle's been completely emptied, you step back and look down at Murk as he starts to transform...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_FEMINISE_END"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		[murk.speech(I's feelin' funny... 'An horny...)] the newly-transformed Murk pants as she lies back on her cushions. While still just as short and chubby as she was a few minutes ago, the rat-girl before you is now unmistakably feminine, and in place of a huge cock, she has a wet pussy. Reaching up to grope her [murk.breastSize] breasts, she looks up at you and submissively whines, [murk.speech(I ain't feelin' like I used to... Please, I... I's wantin' ya ta fuck me! Come on, please!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		The potion has quite clearly altered Murk's mind, and as you grin down at her, you wonder whether you should give her what she wants...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MURK_SUBMIT_ACCEPT -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_SUBMIT_ACCEPT"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		#IF(game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_murkMaster) || game.getDialogueFlags().hasFlag(FLAG_eponaMurkSubmitted))
			Unable to resist your Master's demand, you obediently drop down onto your knees before him and shuffle forwards towards his groin. Letting out a deep grunt as he sees that you're obeying him, the chubby rat-boy sneers,
		#ELSE
			Unable to resist Murk's demand, you obediently drop down onto your knees before him and shuffle forwards towards his groin. Letting out a surprised grunt as he sees that you're actually doing what he says, the chubby rat-boy sneers,
		#ENDIF
		#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
			 [murk.speech(Come on, slut, give me fat cock a nice big kiss! Heh-heh-heh!)]
		#ELSE
			 [murk.speech(Come on, slut, give me fat cock sum attention! Heh-heh-heh!)]
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		#IF(pc.isAbleToAccessCoverableArea(CA_MOUTH, true))
			Doing as you're told, you lean forwards and plant a big, wet kiss on Murk's sheathed cock. The musky smell of his groin overwhelms your senses as his fat shaft quickly rises into a full erection, and you can't help but let out a hungry whine as you eagerly lap up the salty precum which starts to ooze from the tip.
		#ELSE
			Doing as you're told, you lean forwards and start to lovingly stroke Murk's sheathed cock. The musky smell of his groin overwhelms your senses as his fat shaft quickly rises into a full erection, and you can't help but let out a hungry whine as you eagerly smear his salty precum over your [pc.fingers+].
		#ENDIF
	</p>
	<p>
		Letting out yet another deep grunt, Murk scratches his chubby belly and sneers, [murk.speech(That's it, slut! You's me good submissive bitch, ain't ya? Now ta use ya ta 'elp me empty me balls! Heh-heh-heh!)]
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
	
	<!-- MURK_SUBMIT_REFUSE -->
	
	<htmlContent tag="MURK_SUBMIT_REFUSE"><![CDATA[
	<p>
		Not wanting to make a habit of submitting to this foul rat-boy, you refuse to do as Murk commands and tell him that he'd better watch his tone of voice. Grunting in annoyance as he sees that you're no longer willing to submit to him, the chubby rat-boy sneers, [murk.speech(You's an insolent bitch, ain't ya?! Fuck off if ya ain't 'ere ta service me cock!)]
	</p>
	<p>
		Glaring down at him, you wonder what to do with Murk now...
	</p>
	]]>
	</htmlContent>
	
</dialogue>
